<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="4B2C05D6">Gilded Decadence Tile</Text>
  <Text Key="737623AB">This awning comes with whimsical string lights and a handy retractable arm. It's your ticket to creating unforgettable, starlit nights out, regardless of the weather or the cosmos!</Text>
  <Text Key="9E6C92AA">Cozy Evenings Awning</Text>
  <Text Key="10F557CE">Step into the allure of the past with the Trattoria Bistro Bar. This seasoned sentinel of stories, forged from antique wood and graced with a zinc top, whispers tales of hushed conversations over deep-red nectars and clandestine rendezvous around rich, robust coffee. With every crack and crevice, it harbors the secrets of the ages, a silent spectator to a symphony of soirees. The Trattoria Bistro Bar - where timeless design meets the intoxicating intrigue of film noir. Nectar, coffee, mystery - it's all on the house.</Text>
  <Text Key="E88D5DF1">Trattoria Bistro Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="A032CD07">No Bistro is complete without one of these! Experience the fusion of retro charm and modern functionality with the Buongiorno Drip Coffee Maker. Adorned with chrome trim, this vintage-style coffee maker promises a luxurious brew, transforming any coffee ritual into an unforgettable experience. </Text>
  <Text Key="B9C742BE">Buongiorno Drip Coffee Maker</Text>
  <Text Key="A9992279">Unveil the magic of sophisticated style with these Tableside Lace Curtains. Featuring a perfect blend of privacy and panache, they are sure to transform any humble space into a timeless and inviting destination.</Text>
  <Text Key="18125C7C">Tableside Lace Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="299061E2">Crafted with a blend of mystery and sophistication. It's a dramatic pause before the plot unfolds, a tantalizing teaser of the comfort that lies within. This detailed bistro front door opens to a story worth telling. With the Verandah Entry Door, life isn't just in black and white - it's beautifully detailed.</Text>
  <Text Key="3A8AA75D">Verandah Entry Door</Text>
  <Text Key="A9BD893C">This pair of accordion doors erases the boundary between inside and out, transforming your bistro into an airy, seamless sanctuary. Enjoy the charm of the open-air without leaving the comfort of your establishment. Say hello to limitless possibilities and goodbye to walls!</Text>
  <Text Key="EFEA7793">Verandah Open Doorway</Text>
  <Text Key="2422B9D2">A glass of Plumberry Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="C1D2D8ED">Plumberry Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="5C976E8C">A glass of White Llama Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="50D3AB43">White Llama Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="75FFDD56">Elevate your bistro with the "Atlas Shrugged" Pendant. This brass light fixture offers a timeless, vintage charm, casting a warm and inviting glow over your bar. Experience world-class style and coziness without the weight of the world on your shoulders.</Text>
  <Text Key="C9CD9209">"Atlas Shrugged" Pendant</Text>
  <Text Key="75E91ABE">Small in size, big on ambiance. This brass dining lamp brings a touch of bistro-style romance to your meal times. Perfect for those who value both taste and atmosphere.</Text>
  <Text Key="EDEE8541">Quaint &amp; Cozy Dining Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="1CEC895E">Handcrafted from rich brass, this unique sconce design brings a cosmopolitan flair to any bistro or home. Its soft, inviting light is perfect for dining, relaxing, or intimate conversation.</Text>
  <Text Key="482B8661">"Around the Globe" Sconce</Text>
  <Text Key="F9FD4BFC">Get ready to be surprised by your reflection as you enjoy a glass of nectar, similar to the surprise of unintentionally opening your front phone camera. This mirror contains the magic and unique wear of a charming Bistro. Is the reflection clear? No, but it's pretty close to a Simstagram filter.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B30E353">Foodie’s Focus Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="B257BDD7">An exquisite collection of antique advertisement prints that pay homage to the timeless allure of coffee and nectar. These prints serve as a unique testament to advertising aesthetics of a bygone era, making "Vintage Vignettes" an essential addition for connoisseurs of vintage art and lovers of fine coffee and nectar alike.</Text>
  <Text Key="318C2DAE">Vintage Vignettes</Text>
  <Text Key="1D1D2838">Elegance, sophistication, and grandeur - all hanging just above your bar. This suspended nectar rack transforms your finest collection into a floating masterpiece. Adorn your ceiling with this statement piece and let the finest nectars bask in the spotlight they deserve. </Text>
  <Text Key="3C49C837">Notable Nectar Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="1919D60F">Perfect for hushed whispers and clandestine meetings, this divider adds an air of mystery to your meet-ups out on the town. Get cozy behind the Intimate Divider, where privacy meets style! </Text>
  <Text Key="BC43B3D6">Intimate Divider</Text>
  <Text Key="CB459173">Set the stage for an enchanting evening filled with good food, fine nectar, and unforgettable memories. This expertly curated menu and sophisticated nectar glasses are ready and waiting for the next "table of two" who's evening is just getting started.</Text>
  <Text Key="6CC6FAA2">"Table for Two" Menu</Text>
  <Text Key="454BD39D">This isn't your ordinary nectar; this is a bottle you've held on to for so long for that special occasion. And after all that waiting around, it evaporated away. Now, you display it on a shelf for sentimental reasons and aesthetics. It may be empty, but it still looks classy!</Text>
  <Text Key="163B7588">Sentimental Bottle of Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="328BB664">This vintage gem boasts elegant gold lettering brought to life by exquisite calligraphy that hints at the elegance and warmth inside. It's a nod to the past and an invitation to indulge in an atmosphere of timeless allure. </Text>
  <Text Key="61C206AB">Verandah Menu Panel</Text>
  <Text Key="91475C56">This sign is a bistro's introduction, personality, and invitation, all wrapped into one stylish and eye-catching display. </Text>
  <Text Key="23BDDF09">Bistro Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="1287CC31">The Trattoria Barback - Small is your personal touch of vintage charm. This compact wonder offers ample storage space, making it the ultimate mixologist's companion. It's a conversation starter that keeps your spirits high and your bottles higher!</Text>
  <Text Key="51110104">Trattoria Barback - Small</Text>
  <Text Key="B6A09094">Crafted from elegant wood, this spacious barback doesn't just store objects but showcases your captivating curios or anything else you fancy. With this must-have piece, the only thing that'll run dry is your guests' glasses, never your style!</Text>
  <Text Key="6D3B527B">Trattoria Barback - Large</Text>
  <Text Key="9B636B3E">The Debonair Display Shelf is designed to flaunt your best wares in a sophisticated manner, adding a touch of unique charm to any setting.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8D38EC1">Debonair Display Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="4A03902E">This barstool is a silent witness to hushed confessions and candle-lit nights. Its blend of comfort and style could make even a hard-boiled detective soften. The Trattoria Barstool - because every plot twist needs the right setting.</Text>
  <Text Key="A4239AD1">Trattoria Barstool</Text>
  <Text Key="D2BADE58">This dining booth is the perfect blend of old-world luxury and contemporary elegance. A comfortable, inviting space where you can enjoy any drink, snack, or meal. In fact, it's not just a dining booth; it's a memory maker. Every drink becomes a special occasion, every conversation a cherished memory. Sip, snack, and delight as you create unforgettable moments in style.</Text>
  <Text Key="8685E4D7">"Vintage Velvets" Dining Booth</Text>
  <Text Key="DF16994C">Take a seat in this Quintessential Bistro Chair, where every moment becomes a memory. Imagine a bustling street corner, laughter echoing, coffee brewing. It's more than just a chair; it's a time machine to simpler, cozier times. Sit back, relax, and let the stories unfold.</Text>
  <Text Key="6AB5AF03">Quintessential Bistro Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="D0791674">Imagine a table where memories are made, stories are shared, and laughter never ends - that's the À La Carte Table for you. It's not just about the drink and snacks, but the moments spent together. </Text>
  <Text Key="E45F15DB">À La Carte Table</Text>
  <Text Key="69C260CE">This window offers more than just a view - it's a statement of style that seamlessly blends the past with the present.</Text>
  <Text Key="E02428F1">Verandah Window</Text>
  <Text Key="DEF204E3">Grab Quick Drinks</Text>
  <Text Key="409B0676">Your Neighborhood Bistro</Text>
  <Text Key="B21DA7C3">Grab Quick Snacks</Text>
  <Text Key="542B76C2">Grab a Cup of Coffee</Text>
  <Text Key="5EF087FF">Black Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="4A020D00">Grab a Cup of Black Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="047FEA3B">Plumberry Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="6C68E6B4">Pour Plumberry Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="738F1F55">White Llama Nectar </Text>
  <Text Key="EEB507A6">Pour White Llama Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="5E579661">Bistro Bliss Wallpaper</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>