<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="48F141FC">This floor level is Dusty! It feels lived-in and homey, and Sims will build relationships faster and enjoy cleaning more. If Sims make no effort to clean up a little though, this floor will become Dirty...</Text>
  <Text Key="BF09AE20">The floor level is Filthy! Sims will be very uncomfortable, especially with Filth Fiends invading their space! The good news is, there's nowhere to go but up, but only if you clean up.</Text>
  <Text Key="5FAFB9F0">This floor level is Clean! The sparkling surroundings fill Sims with focus, inspiration, and energy. Keep up the good work, or else your home will become Dusty.</Text>
  <Text Key="6FCB8D09">This floor level is Dirty! Sims may start having some social troubles, and some interactions may take longer to do while your Sims are distracted by the mess. If no measures are taken, the floor will become Filthy!</Text>
  <Text Key="50230A18">(From happily cleaning in a dusty floor)</Text>
  <Text Key="F37DBC85">(From cleaning or vacuuming on a floor already clean)</Text>
  <Text Key="F753DEF6">(From continuing to clean while on a clean floor level)</Text>
  <Text Key="990D4931">(From deep cleaning on a Filthy floor level)</Text>
  <Text Key="97F14A4A">(From continuing to clean while already in a rage)</Text>
  <Text Key="C48A2D51">{0.SimFirstName} befriended a Dust Bunny! Since {M0.he}{F0.she} made {M0.his}{F0.her} fluffy companion feel so welcomed and cared for in {M0.his}{F0.her} house, this dust bunny will behave a bit differently. It can now survive in even the cleanest environments and will no longer be destroyed by cleaning around the house - it's here to stay. \n\nBefriended Dust Bunnies will also show their appreciation by finding rarer items and occasionally even digging up substantial piles of Simoleons. </Text>
  <Text Key="0AC96F81">(From befriending a Dust Bunny)</Text>
  <Text Key="5B1AE25D">(From feeding a Dust Bunny)</Text>
  <Text Key="064EB532">(From petting a Dust Bunny)</Text>
  <Text Key="42FE16DB">(From destroying a cute, helpless dust bunny)</Text>
  <Text Key="99E064A4">(From trying to pet a Filth Fiend)</Text>
  <Text Key="D51F2132">(From trying to Step On a Filth Fiend and chickening out)</Text>
  <Text Key="36DAF92E">(From slaying a Filth Fiend)</Text>
  <Text Key="17B8A80F">(From having visitors over while the house is dirty or filthy)</Text>
  <Text Key="94E1CC49">(From attempting romance in Filthy surroundings)</Text>
  <Text Key="6A73F641">(From attempting romance in Dirty surroundings)</Text>
  <Text Key="6D5E1409">(From being in a Clean area)</Text>
  <Text Key="4F95337A">(From being in a Dirty area)</Text>
  <Text Key="1FF5A2BB">(From being in a Dusty area)</Text>
  <Text Key="FA694C72">(From being in a Filthy area)</Text>
  <Text Key="CAF0BEB7">(From vacuuming thoroughly)</Text>
  <Text Key="3322FE51">(From Power Cleaning as a Fast &amp; Fastidious Sim)</Text>
  <Text Key="509E40C1">(From vacuuming a toddler)</Text>
  <Text Key="637F0022">What a great find! {0.SimFirstName} was gifted a cool collectible by {M0.his}{F0.her} resourceful dust friend!</Text>
  <Text Key="77577C59">{1.ObjectName} burrowed around in the dust and returned with an insect. Check your inventory to collect this crawling critter!</Text>
  <Text Key="C21BFCD4">This Dust Bunny was so happy with {0.SimFirstName} that it managed to find lost Simoleons all over the house! {1.Money} has been added to household.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDB68228">{0.SimFirstName}'s dust friend did not feel particularly motivated or happy, but did manage to half-heartedly rustle up a few Simoleons. {1.Money} has been added to household. Perhaps a little bribery in the form of dust snacks might encourage {M0.his}{F0.her} dusty friend to search a bit more industriously...</Text>
  <Text Key="132E5AE8">{0.SimFirstName} just received a handy upgrade part from {M0.his}{F0.her} burrowing dust bunny. You've got one useful bundle of fluff and dust on your hands!</Text>
  <Text Key="0C7052EA">{0.SimFirstName} may have asked for valuables, but sometimes a Dust Bunny's definition of treasure is indeed literal trash. Clearly there's some kind of failure to communicate here. Try speaking in a language your dust friend might understand better - feeding your bunny a dust snack might be a good start.</Text>
  <Text Key="53B4D5A4">{1.ObjectName} managed to find quite a rare collectible! This bunny must really love {0.SimFirstName}! </Text>
  <Text Key="48025F6C">{1.ObjectName} could certainly have looked a bit harder for something more enticing. Try keeping this Dust Bunny a bit happier and maybe it will feel motivated to scrounge up some fresher grub next time. </Text>
  <Text Key="6E233FA3">{1.ObjectName} found a dust-covered toy hidden in the household clutter! Who knows how long that toy had been lost!</Text>
  <Text Key="E4970A07">{1.ObjectName} scrounged up a particularly tasty looking tidbit for {0.SimFirstName}. Nevermind where it came from, this offering means your dust friend must really care about you!</Text>
  <Text Key="5D7EBBEE">This Dust Bunny didn't exactly hit the jackpot, but it did manage to scrounge up a few Simoleons that had been covered up by a layer of clutter and dust. {1.Money} have been added to household.</Text>
  <Text Key="1D399F8B">{1.ObjectName} dug through heaps of dust to find a mysteriously pristine fruit or vegetable - and even managed to refrain from chomping into it!</Text>
  <Text Key="3C33DA6A">{0.SimFirstName}'s dust bunny quickly returned empty-pawed, clearly having put minimal effort into actually finding anything. Perhaps a dusty snack or a caring cuddle might encourage {1.ObjectName} to try a bit harder. </Text>
  <Text Key="72E74AE6">{1.ObjectName} was feeling cranky and searched far and wide for something that would suitably express its grumpiness - a rotting bit of fruit or vegetable matter covered in dust. Bun Appétit!</Text>
  <Text Key="38C251BA">{1.ObjectName} found some rusty upgrade parts hidden around the house. While it's not exactly treasure, the fact that {0.SimFirstName} has managed to harness the destructive energy of a filth fiend for something productive is a testament to {M0.his}{F0.her} mischief-managing skills! </Text>
  <Text Key="3A1CD823">Jackpot! Who knew Filth Fiends could be so resourceful? They may not seem friendly, but with enough care and love, {0.SimFirstName} found a way to bond with {M0.his}{F0.her} filth-dwelling friend. {1.Money} were found around the house and have been added to your household funds. </Text>
  <Text Key="9CE7DB4A">There's no telling how long this meal has been rotting away, but it's clear that {1.ObjectName} was proud to excavate it from the filthy floors and present it to {0.SimFirstName}. This putrid meal can be found in {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory if {M0.he}{F0.she} is feeling particularly brave. </Text>
  <Text Key="578DAC68">{1.ObjectName} set off somewhat grumpily to rustle up clutter and returned with a piece of garbage. Knowing how much filth fiends love their trash and clutter, this could be interpreted as a sign that your fiend was trying to please you. </Text>
  <Text Key="973EA41B">{1.ObjectName} may be filled with dastardly intent most of the time, but {0.SimFirstName} saw through this fiend's filthy exterior and found a friend. And when a fiend uses its craftiness to find cool things instead of creating chaos, it turns out they can find some pretty rare and valuable stuff. Check your inventory to see the rare collectible that {1.ObjectName} dug up!</Text>
  <Text Key="7D2A4ECD">{0.SimFirstName} has clearly done a good job pacifying {M0.his}{F0.her} filth fiends, because {1.ObjectName} just rummaged up a nifty collectible! {1.ObjectName} might be a noxious ball of grime and discontent most of the time, but with the right combination of bribery, begging, and luck, a fiend can be an asset to a household. </Text>
  <Text Key="D97FEC98">Procrastinator</Text>
  <Text Key="16277823">Chore Dodger</Text>
  <Text Key="AFCC231A">Low Standards</Text>
  <Text Key="C4E47725">Filth Friend</Text>
  <Text Key="0C22CF2D">Basic Home Training</Text>
  <Text Key="193B5A9E">Proactive Cleaning</Text>
  <Text Key="3FD94E37">Vacuum Virtuoso</Text>
  <Text Key="56F4A940">Chief Cleaning Officer</Text>
  <Text Key="64C3F93B">{0.SimFirstName} has become one with the filth and finds solace in the familiar presence of dirt and grime. As {0.SimFirstName} learned to let messes pile up and live it up, {M0.he}{F0.she} found enlightment. Why bother cleaning when things will just get dirty again? Why hold yourself to some impossible standard of cleanliness? Once {0.SimFirstName} embraced and accepted her filthy ways, {M0.he}{F0.she} realized {M0.he}{F0.she} was free - and on this day, a Filth Dweller was born. </Text>
  <Text Key="CC71E453">This Sim revels in filthy, messy homes and avoids cleaning at all costs. Procrastinate, dodge chores, lower your standards, and find creative ways to thrive in the filthiest environments!</Text>
  <Text Key="136D7D4F">Fabulously Filthy</Text>
  <Text Key="F8DB2892">{0.SimFirstName} has scrubbed tirelessly, vacuumed voraciously, and mastered the art of maintaining a clean, perfect home. Keeping a pristine property has taught {M0.him}{F0.her} to form good daily habits, but more importantly, to truly enjoy the satisfying feeling that comes from each shined floor and scrubbed surface. {0.SimFirstName}'s reward isn't just {M0.his}{F0.her} deep knowledge of cleaning techniques or exquisite vacuum handling skills -- {M0.his}{F0.her} reward is the attitude {M0.he}{F0.she} developed along the way. </Text>
  <Text Key="64AB5AC6">This Sim likes their home to be presentable and clean all the time. Taking pride in their pristine homes, these Sims shoot for perfection and thrive when they have a spotless house to show off to guests. </Text>
  <Text Key="C013BD8A">Perfectly Pristine</Text>
  <Text Key="9B45E548">{0.SimFirstName} is feeling as fresh and clean as the room {M0.he}{F0.she}'s in. Romance sounds a lot better when everyone can enjoy a dust-free ambiance. </Text>
  <Text Key="108673E7">Fresh N' Frisky</Text>
  <Text Key="5DF78485">Obviously, the best way to keep a clean house is to clean before it gets dirty. As {0.SimFirstName} keeps cleaning, {F0.her}{M0.his} desire for a perfectly clean house will get stronger...</Text>
  <Text Key="9400EE80">Perfectionist Zeal</Text>
  <Text Key="3BF9F6AA">{0.SimFirstName}'s focus intensifies. Messes will be terminated, floors will be shined, and dust won't stand a chance!</Text>
  <Text Key="111FC787">{0.SimFirstName} has laser-like focus and every speck of dust will soon get its comeuppance! The more {M0.he}{F0.she} cleans, the more satisfying it feels. Looking around at this sparkling ode to cleanliness, {0.SimFirstName} feels unstoppable - but why stop now?</Text>
  <Text Key="669C8ECC">{0.SimFirstName} is no longer just a Sim. {F0.She}{M0.He} has become a cleaning machine! {F0.Her}{M0.His} surroundings were clean a long time ago, but now, everything has been double shined, triple polished, and cleaned to perfection! </Text>
  <Text Key="33A49D6E">It's not you, {0.SimFirstName}, it's just hard to feel the vibes when there's dust sticking to my feet and a vaguely musty scent emanating from everywhere around me. </Text>
  <Text Key="38813C11">Messiness Kills the Mood</Text>
  <Text Key="7BF8A320">Filth Kills the Fun</Text>
  <Text Key="204046A4">{0.SimFirstName} has visitors and the place is a mess! {M0.He}{F0.She} explained that they just happened to come "in between cleanings" and the guests nodded politely, but somehow {0.SimFirstName} still feels judged. </Text>
  <Text Key="18B2F5EB">It's Not Usually Like This!</Text>
  <Text Key="00901959">Cleaning when there's a light covering of dust on furniture and floors is surprisingly enjoyable. Before the mess builds up, busting the dust feels like more of a fun pastime than a chore. </Text>
  <Text Key="9FB04EDC">Chore Galore!</Text>
  <Text Key="7D80D633">Do Not Disturb: Rage Cleaning</Text>
  <Text Key="7081F591">When things are this messy, the only thing to do is to channel that anger and not stop cleaning until the job is done. {0.SimFirstName} has procrastinated long enough, and now, the day of reckoning has come. Fueled by the herculean task ahead, {0.SimFirstName} will resist distractions and have no need of rest - the rage clean is building. </Text>
  <Text Key="06B65B56">{0.SimFirstName}'s cleaning rage intensifies. It started with the floors. But what's the point of clean floors if the baseboards are dirty? And if {M0.he}{F0.she} cleans the floors, and leaves the counters dirty, won't the scraps of counter-debris soon wind up on the floor anyway, ruining all of {M0.his}{F0.her} work? With each cleaned room, {0.SimFirstName}'s temper gets a little hotter, {M0.his}{F0.her} voice gets a little more exasperated, and {M0.his}{F0.her} grip on the cleaning weapon of choice becomes tighter. No rest until the job's done!</Text>
  <Text Key="C108CF93">Approach with caution and definitely avoid making a mess in the area {0.SimFirstName} just cleaned - {M0.he}{F0.she} has worked {M0.himself}{F0.herself} into a rage beyond rage, a cleaning fury beyond compare. The finish line is in sight and {0.SimFirstName} has slayed fiends, busted dust, and scrubbed until the walls and floors trembled in fear of {M0.his}{F0.her} superhuman cleaning power. \n\nNow who made that fingerprint mark on the wall? Whose sock is that on the floor! Is that an ant?!?! </Text>
  <Text Key="5AD25BCD">{0.SimFirstName} was ordered to clean rather rudely, as though {M0.he}{F0.she} doesn't pull {M0.his}{F0.her} weight around the house. {M0.He}{F0.She} totally does her share of cleaning chores... just yesterday {M0.he}{F0.she} cleaned the... Nevermind! Fine! </Text>
  <Text Key="9D9F2818">Chore Shamed!</Text>
  <Text Key="D7179C8C">Do I look like your maid? How about a "please" and "thank you" around here? {0.SimFirstName} may have been willing to help with cleaning if {M0.he}{F0.she} was asked nicely, but now we'll never know. </Text>
  <Text Key="AA60D543">I'm Not Your Housekeeper!</Text>
  <Text Key="C4120D2F">{0.SimFirstName} feels invigorated and inspired by {M0.his}{F0.her} sparkling clean surroundings! Being in a well-cared for environment will help {0.SimFirstName} be more productive and creative in many different pursuits. As long as {M0.he}{F0.she} keeps things clean, {M0.he}{F0.she} will be more successful at working from home and learning new skills. </Text>
  <Text Key="E4349C76">Sparkling Clean Surroundings</Text>
  <Text Key="92A19580">{0.SimFirstName} can't touch anything around {M0.him}{F0.her} without encountering a layer of dust. It's getting harder to ignore the build up - things are getting dusty, crusty, and musty. Even the air feels heavier with undesirable particles. It will be harder to cook or be productive in these surroundings - but non-fussy Sims who prefer not to clean could certainly learn to get comfortable. After all, it could certainly be worse...</Text>
  <Text Key="1D7D534F">Everything Feels a Bit Dirty</Text>
  <Text Key="98032501">A light sheen of dust enhances the cosy, lived-in feel of {0.SimFirstName}'s home. It's not too clean or too messy, it's just right. These natural, homey surroundings will help Sims feel comfortable with each other, build relationships, have fun together, and feel socially nourished. </Text>
  <Text Key="4CECC434">Someone Lives Here</Text>
  <Text Key="A202DD04">{0.SimFirstName}'s surroundings have become filthy! The floors are caked in dust and grime, and even the air feels noxious. Heaps of filth are stacking up, notorious filth fiends are running rampant, and {0.SimFirstName} is feeling overwhelmed by the mounting messes. Starting to clean in these conditions will be a tiresome task - and the thought of cooking or creating anything in such a filthy environment feels pretty unappetizing. </Text>
  <Text Key="41CBA3CB">Unbelievably Filthy!</Text>
  <Text Key="BD63C6C6">Where others saw clumps of pesky dust, {0.SimFirstName} saw a friend in need of attention and nurturing. Dusty floors may come and go, but {0.SimFirstName} and {M0.his}{F0.her} dust bunny are officially BFFs! </Text>
  <Text Key="BA049359">Bunny Friends Forever!</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE9D52D">By feeding and petting a Dust Bunny, {0.SimFirstName} is keeping {M0.his}{F0.her} household dust friends as happy as possible. They might still be balls of dust, lint, hair, and debris held together by static electricity and magic, but they can also be contributing members of {0.SimFirstName}'s cozy home. </Text>
  <Text Key="34CCA2F8">Dust Bunny Caretaker</Text>
  <Text Key="37EE4A08">{0.SimFirstName} lost a friend today. As {M0.he}{F0.she} mourns {M0.his}{F0.her} dearly departed dust friend, hopefully the marginally cleaner floors will provide some small solace. </Text>
  <Text Key="907666A7">From Dust Friends to Dust</Text>
  <Text Key="2A208D50">{0.SimFirstName} considered approaching the Filth Fiend, but {M0.he}{F0.she} reconsidered after getting closer and receiving a menacing glare. Some creatures are best observed from afar. </Text>
  <Text Key="BB99947F">I'll Just Keep My Distance</Text>
  <Text Key="6BA4FB02">Filth and anarchy ruled the {0.SimLastName} household until {0.SimFirstName} fearlessly destroyed a Filth Fiend. {M0.he}{F0.she} feels a burst of renewed hope and energy, as the mischievous, mess-making fiends seem less menacing today. The carpets and floors may still be covered in grime and leftover fiend dust, but it's nothing that a cleaning champion like {0.SimFirstName} can't handle.</Text>
  <Text Key="351610FD">Slayer of Filth Fiends</Text>
  <Text Key="89862461">Fast &amp; Fastidious Sims don't play around when it comes to cleaning. They aren't here to tidy up, they aren't interested in "dusting" - they are here to blast any manner of filth off of the face of the planet. </Text>
  <Text Key="8692E714">All Messes Terminated</Text>
  <Text Key="952E2A41">{0.SimFirstName} is going on a vacuuming kick and has no plans of ceasing {M0.his}{F0.her} relentless assault on the dust occupying {M0.his}{F0.her} home. Spurred on by a fresh burst of energy and focus, {0.SimFirstName} could do this all day - the floors will rue the day they tested {0.SimFirstName}'s resolve. </Text>
  <Text Key="EA3C8574">No Dust Left Behind!</Text>
  <Text Key="114281BE">{0.SimFirstName} can't help but congratulate {M0.himself}{F0.herself} on finding a new way to clean {M0.his}{F0.her} toddler. Toddlers may throw a tantrum when it's bath time, but they find the whirring sounds and pull of the vacuum cleaner to be rather entertaining. </Text>
  <Text Key="70200A41">What Can't Be Vacuumed?</Text>
  <Text Key="CD14D9A9">So friendly! So cute! But also... so dusty! They may help find a few Simoleons under the couch, but at the cost of your clean home.</Text>
  <Text Key="C070318C">Dust Bunny</Text>
  <Text Key="67DA448F">Uh oh. You know you haven't done chores in a while when these critters appear. They're lean, they're mean, and unclean!</Text>
  <Text Key="6144B756">Filth Fiend</Text>
  <Text Key="A5FCA86F">Small dust pile walks warily down the Lot\nWith its dusty self hanging low on the floor\nAin't no sound but the sound of its feet\nVacuum's ready to go</Text>
  <Text Key="9135BDB6">Small Pile Of Dust</Text>
  <Text Key="9D536996">Are you ready hey are you ready for this?\nAre you hanging on the edge of your seat?\nOut of the doorway the Vacuums roll in\nTo the sound of the simlish beat ya!\nAnother dust to bust\nAnother dust to bust</Text>
  <Text Key="8762F349">A Medium Pile Of Dust</Text>
  <Text Key="82CE6DA1">And another one gone and another one gone\nAnother dust to bust\nHey all Sims are gonna get you too\nAnother dust to bust</Text>
  <Text Key="D8FACC54">A Giant Pile Of Dust</Text>
  <Text Key="9CDCC4B2">This wonderous innovation in dust-removal technology removes dust from your home and transports it through a portal. We aren't authorized to say where the portal leads, but rest assured that you won't have to deal with it. That's the Gruntled Company promise.</Text>
  <Text Key="6E72214D">The Debonair Dust Portal by Gruntled Inc. </Text>
  <Text Key="4684CCAA">Corral the dust bunnies in your home! Restore your home to its sparkling, spotless state with the Dust Dandy. This convenient lightweight vacuum can do the dirty work for you, letting you be dust bunny free for as long as possible. The Dust Dandy: It's not just great, it's just dandy!</Text>
  <Text Key="A5E9DC35">Dust Dandy Cordless Vacuum by SuckUp Industries</Text>
  <Text Key="A1BB25AF">Whisper quiet with a flexible design and our patented bag-less technology. This vacuum is the highest end way to give your home the deep-clean it deserves. If you ever split from your spouse, make sure you get this vacuum.</Text>
  <Text Key="515B7DF6">G7 Swivel Swank by Gruntled Inc.</Text>
  <Text Key="C2908421">The party's over, dust! This budget-friendly vacuum sucks, traps, and escorts dirt and debris safely away all without the high price tag. Patented hurricane-style technology ensures that only half the dust particles are violently blown back into the air, which is a fine track record for a previously owned refurbished model.</Text>
  <Text Key="B28047D4">The Dusty Chaperone Upright Vacuum by SuckUp Industries</Text>
  <Text Key="841D73D9">One of our largest and most intimidating models yet, the Dirt Herder 5000 is sure to trample any dust bunny, pile of errant crumbs, or any unwelcome pile in your home. Our innovative bag-less style of vacuum locks away dust and dirt in a special chamber which can be detached and easily released over any trash can. The future is here, and it sucks!</Text>
  <Text Key="E16C565C">Dirt Herder 5000 Upright Vacuum by SuckUp Industries</Text>
  <Text Key="37229754">Empty Vacuum</Text>
  <Text Key="7E441FD4">Stop Spawning Dust Piles (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="2D9B3743">Ask for Help Cleaning</Text>
  <Text Key="2A94E2EF">{1.ObjectName} has already searched this area. Try again later.</Text>
  <Text Key="0583FAA4">Ask {1.ObjectName} to Search for Valuables</Text>
  <Text Key="94D5390E">Befriended Dust Bunnies will no longer disappear when a house becomes clean or filthy.</Text>
  <Text Key="56AC8D3B">This Dust Bunny is not happy enough for you to befriend. Try feeding it dust and petting it!</Text>
  <Text Key="959A3382">Befriend</Text>
  <Text Key="CCB4CA02">{1.ObjectName} has already been fed a hearty meal of dust sprinklings. </Text>
  <Text Key="FA961205">Feed Dust</Text>
  <Text Key="BBB5EB62">Try to pet {1.ObjectName} in a little bit - right now this Dust Bunny prefers to frolick around your home and attract dust. </Text>
  <Text Key="D9F16CE7">This Dust Bunny is not happy enough to be pet. Try feeding it some dust to cheer it up! </Text>
  <Text Key="35425C56">Pet</Text>
  <Text Key="62702AC0">Step On</Text>
  <Text Key="93A59C33">{0.SimFirstName} got a bit spooked the last time {M0.he}{F0.she} went near a Filth Fiend. For now it might be best to keep a safe distance...</Text>
  <Text Key="8D6E5DAC">{1.ObjectName} has already been bribed with it's favorite snack - a sprinkling of filth. Try again later.</Text>
  <Text Key="D5AE6294">Appease</Text>
  <Text Key="07AF3BB6">Ask {1.ObjectName} to Rummage for Clutter</Text>
  <Text Key="462F02F4">{0.SimFirstName} did the seemingly impossible and befriended a Filth Fiend! Since {M0.he}{F0.she} made {M0.his}{F0.her} grimy companion feel so welcomed and cared for in {M0.his}{F0.her} house, this fiend will behave a bit differently. It can now survive in even the cleanest environments and will no longer be destroyed by cleaning around the house - it's here to stay. \n\nBefriended Filth Fiends have developed a peculiar sense of loyalty to their filth-ridden households. While they are still fussy, filth-kicking, havoc-wreaking balls of chaos, they will try their best to care for the Sims they have bonded with by occasionally rummaging up rare items, piles of simoleons, and questionable bits of food. </Text>
  <Text Key="80FEB99C">Only Sims who have completed the Fabulously Filthy Aspiration can befriend Filth Fiends</Text>
  <Text Key="BA188DFF">This Filth Fiend is too mischievious to befriend. </Text>
  <Text Key="7A57A8D0">This Filth Fiend has already been befriended!</Text>
  <Text Key="DC9AC14C">Befriend</Text>
  <Text Key="D2F755E4">{1.ObjectName} has already been begged and pleaded with. Further negotiations at this time had better involve a filth snack...</Text>
  <Text Key="8AC00236">Beg For Mercy</Text>
  <Text Key="88D980D4">{1.ObjectName} was too devious and intimidating to be stepped on, and is really agitated right now. Maybe it's best to try again later...</Text>
  <Text Key="060E1D47">{1.ObjectName} was too intimidating to be pet and prefers to snarl, kick up dust, and be filthy . Maybe it's best to try again later...</Text>
  <Text Key="BF3FF824">Try to Pet</Text>
  <Text Key="B70419E9">Check Dust Level</Text>
  <Text Key="ACF42A0B">Ask For Help Cleaning</Text>
  <Text Key="CAAF74AA">Argue About Filthy Surroundings</Text>
  <Text Key="B3145D33">Argue About Dirty Surroundings</Text>
  <Text Key="16506253">(From being ordered to clean)</Text>
  <Text Key="8C960A6D">Order {1.SimFirstName} to Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="5B2BC1AC">Vacuum</Text>
  <Text Key="7E5B18CD">Vacuum Around</Text>
  <Text Key="FE987F85">Clean Toddler with Vacuum</Text>
  <Text Key="51AE32D1">Requires a Handheld Vacuum in Inventory</Text>
  <Text Key="8344425E">Clean Toddler with Vacuum</Text>
  <Text Key="D86412F5">Check Dust Level </Text>
  <Text Key="3A8A98AC">Vacuum Here</Text>
  <Text Key="D1262F47">Remove as Favorite Handheld Vacuum Cleaner</Text>
  <Text Key="8BD95D69">Choose Favorite Handheld Vacuum Cleaner</Text>
  <Text Key="F372A5DE">Remove as Favorite Vacuum Cleaner</Text>
  <Text Key="C11CBF38">Choose Favorite Vacuum Cleaner</Text>
  <Text Key="9E65622A">Install Bottomless Pit</Text>
  <Text Key="CF6A48C1">Ensures that your vacuum is never full and will no longer overflow. </Text>
  <Text Key="F796624E">Resume Installing Bottomless Pit</Text>
  <Text Key="95F3DDEA">Bottomless Pit (Completed)</Text>
  <Text Key="09CBE883">Self-Charging Power Cell (Completed)</Text>
  <Text Key="B2E62380">Titanium Rotors (Completed)</Text>
  <Text Key="B0CCD2DE">Vaporizing Pulse (Completed)</Text>
  <Text Key="8B04DBC3">Install Self-Charging Power Cell</Text>
  <Text Key="AFDF5F2E">Using a self-charging battery, this Vacuum no longer costs power to run and will function Off-the-Grid. </Text>
  <Text Key="28E65195">Resume Installing Self-Charging Power Cell</Text>
  <Text Key="1B14C3C0">Install Titanium Rotors</Text>
  <Text Key="D1740933">Titanium Rotors ensure that your vacuum will never break, no matter how much dust it devours. </Text>
  <Text Key="04EDEBA4">Resume Installing Titanium Rotors</Text>
  <Text Key="2CC36F1E">Install Vaporizing Pulse </Text>
  <Text Key="39C63FDD">This upgrade causes your vacuum cleaner to emit a powerful electro-magnetic pulse which vaporizes nearby messes.</Text>
  <Text Key="E5464D52">Resume Installing Vaporizing Pulse</Text>
  <Text Key="A1860C38">Vacuum</Text>
  <Text Key="2B85FCE8">Power Vacuum</Text>
  <Text Key="ADB08FF4">This vacuum is broken and needs to be repaired first</Text>
  <Text Key="0D11B888">Vacuum Lightly</Text>
  <Text Key="EBD14EDD">Deep Vacuum</Text>
  <Text Key="14807800">Vacuum to Perfection</Text>
  <Text Key="09B63A87">Cashmere</Text>
  <Text Key="72CE6C34">Chonk</Text>
  <Text Key="D5FAAA05">Buttons</Text>
  <Text Key="43CD516E">Clover</Text>
  <Text Key="47F0A890">Bunsy</Text>
  <Text Key="2454780C">Chai</Text>
  <Text Key="C0E238C3">Duchess</Text>
  <Text Key="8222E230">Sniffles</Text>
  <Text Key="97951AE4">Mochi</Text>
  <Text Key="7AE2A368">Cinnabun</Text>
  <Text Key="20574469">Latte</Text>
  <Text Key="0F86AA35">Bao</Text>
  <Text Key="300365B6">Freckles</Text>
  <Text Key="22E5DF9E">Napoleon Bunnyparte</Text>
  <Text Key="315956C3">Truffles</Text>
  <Text Key="48D63603">Pudding</Text>
  <Text Key="9DCF11D5">Nibbles</Text>
  <Text Key="AEDF8526">Befriended</Text>
  <Text Key="8373AC72">Happiness Level: Neutral</Text>
  <Text Key="3B6E2BAA">Happiness Level: Very Low</Text>
  <Text Key="D68D9D96">Happiness Level: Low</Text>
  <Text Key="3D56AFAD">Happiness Level: High</Text>
  <Text Key="84068D34">Happiness Level: Very High</Text>
  <Text Key="935E91CD">Coal</Text>
  <Text Key="3A6E8316">Nyx</Text>
  <Text Key="45CBD737">Cinders</Text>
  <Text Key="EB9CEE74">Ash</Text>
  <Text Key="886840B6">Morgana</Text>
  <Text Key="C8FD6C6B">Attila the Bun</Text>
  <Text Key="6CC9D818">Luna</Text>
  <Text Key="0C906F21">Mocha</Text>
  <Text Key="ED342466">Pepper</Text>
  <Text Key="1007009E">Fang</Text>
  <Text Key="13EE3C3E">Maximillian</Text>
  <Text Key="F58590B6">Rex</Text>
  <Text Key="B4EC623C">Muck</Text>
  <Text Key="C2A9BDF8">Bandit</Text>
  <Text Key="D47F5A08">Pudge</Text>
  <Text Key="65189C91">Betelgeuse</Text>
  <Text Key="14DC3383">Midnight</Text>
  <Text Key="127534DB">Mischief Level: Low</Text>
  <Text Key="81EA268F">Mischief Level: Neutral</Text>
  <Text Key="D4C7CDF2">Mischief Level: Very Low</Text>
  <Text Key="CA406C54">Mischief Level: Very High</Text>
  <Text Key="B43F0510">Mischief Level: High</Text>
  <Text Key="F8D79702">Befriended</Text>
  <Text Key="5FE6EE10">{0.ObjectDescription}</Text>
  <Text Key="FA75393F">{0.ObjectName}</Text>
  <Text Key="3C65D4D8">Vaporizing Pulse</Text>
  <Text Key="FA489EA6">Titanium Rotors</Text>
  <Text Key="4F8CBDA3">Bottomless Pit</Text>
  <Text Key="13641595">Self-Charging Power Cell</Text>
  <Text Key="F9618BA0">Vacuum Fullness: High</Text>
  <Text Key="B4E3CB3E">Vacuum Fullness: Empty</Text>
  <Text Key="5639FBA5">Vacuum Fullness: Full</Text>
  <Text Key="7C08B056">Vacuum Fullness: Low </Text>
  <Text Key="4ED1FB14">Leave Out Food to Spoil</Text>
  <Text Key="A2C1CC51">Leave out 3 plates or bowls of food until they get spoiled. Because that's how you get ants!</Text>
  <Text Key="E9DC7CAB">Let 3 Kitchen or Bathroom Objects Get Dirty</Text>
  <Text Key="F3BAA28C">Neglect your kitchens and bathrooms. You'll clean them "tomorrow".</Text>
  <Text Key="AC34EA3A">Let At Least One Floor Level of your Home Become Dirty</Text>
  <Text Key="064DEEA3">Make messes, procrastinate on cleaning, and let the dust keep building. </Text>
  <Text Key="4530E629">Max Out {0.SimFirstName}'s Fun Motive While on a Dusty, Dirty, or Filthy Floor</Text>
  <Text Key="D438EA6E">True masters of procrastination don't just avoid the task that should be done -- they replace those tasks with fun, and lots of it. Play video games, party, do anything other than deal with the mounting mess you call home. </Text>
  <Text Key="A3B3125F">Successfully Ask 3 Sims to Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="4ED28F40">Why do work when someone else will do it for you? Ask nicely or demand that they clean, that's up to you -- the important thing is that the job gets done (by someone else). </Text>
  <Text Key="4E603858">Befriend a Dust Bunny</Text>
  <Text Key="673636F5">When your house is dusty or dirty, find a Dust Bunny and feed, pet, and befriend it.</Text>
  <Text Key="7DAB3691">Cook 3 Meals in a Dirty or Filthy Kitchen</Text>
  <Text Key="56CF6336">Cook a meal on a dirty or filthy floor and learn to enjoy the special flavor the grossness adds to your food.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AFE5582">Pay for a Cleaning Service</Text>
  <Text Key="E91415AB">Sometimes you need things to be a bit cleaner, but you're still determined to dodge chores at all costs. Stick to your values and pay another Sim to clean your house from your phone or computer.</Text>
  <Text Key="01B586E6">Let a floor level get filthy</Text>
  <Text Key="0507E09F">Let a floor level get dusty, dirty, and finally filthy. If your Sim feels uncomfortable or tense around the escalating levels of filth and grime, remember that nearly every problem in life can be solved by lowering your standards. </Text>
  <Text Key="DAE5C319">Eat 3 Meals that are Spoiled</Text>
  <Text Key="FD57727E">Real filth connoisseurs have no qualms about a little mold. Leave out plates or bowls of food to spoil and eat them anyway.</Text>
  <Text Key="14016B60">Bathe or Shower 3 Times in a Dirty Shower or Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="714A267D">Let your shower or tub get really grimey and nasty from use - and use it anyway. Cleaning yourself is already more cleaning than any filth lover wants to do.</Text>
  <Text Key="7950B25B">Don't Wash Your Hands After Using the Toilet</Text>
  <Text Key="D83A205C">Why waste time washing your hands? Go straight from the toilet to shaking hands and cooking dinner. Nobody has to know. </Text>
  <Text Key="A431A56A">Invite a Guest Over while House is Dirty or Filthy.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC7052F3">Using your phone or relationship panel, invite a friend to hang out. You may feel embarrassed, but push through that and learn to be proud of your filthy abode. </Text>
  <Text Key="6B0A5529">Knock Over 3 Trash Cans</Text>
  <Text Key="C471CF6E">Fill up an outdoor trash can and in a fit of rage, knock it over to assert your dominance. </Text>
  <Text Key="D59D8976">Throw a Party Social Event in a Filthy House</Text>
  <Text Key="78C9E00F">Let a household floor level get filthy and use your phone to throw a scheduled party event.</Text>
  <Text Key="C433B6D7">Appease a Filth Fiend with a Filth Tribute</Text>
  <Text Key="3C11FE18">Let your house get filthy enough for Filth Fiends to spawn and try to appease them with a filth tribute. Make them feel welcome in your filthy home!</Text>
  <Text Key="74AB6A14">WooHoo in a Filthy House</Text>
  <Text Key="92FAB151">Filth Dwellers have no shame and find love in the grimiest of places. Most Sims won't be in the mood for romance when they see the state of your home, but don't let that get you down. If they can't love you at your filthiest....</Text>
  <Text Key="8146650D">Become Very Happy (+3 or higher) on a Filthy Floor</Text>
  <Text Key="9403D3C2">Be one with your surroundings and find happiness amongst the deluge of dust and filth. By finding true happiness in the filth, you have learned what it means to be fabulously filthy. </Text>
  <Text Key="3A13AC05">Clean 3 Kitchen or Bathroom Objects</Text>
  <Text Key="15AFAE1A">Clean 3 kitchen or bathroom objects like sinks, stoves, bathtubs, or toilets. </Text>
  <Text Key="3E2FDAD2">Vacuum for 3 hours</Text>
  <Text Key="7D68081B">Choose either a handheld or upright vacuum and enjoy harnessing the power of machines to eliminate dust from your carpets and floors. </Text>
  <Text Key="47559083">Wash 3 Dishes</Text>
  <Text Key="52D88324">Using the sink or dishwasher, wash or clean the dishes after a meal. </Text>
  <Text Key="BC3A48A8">Empty the Trash</Text>
  <Text Key="FC33AA65">Perfectly Pristine Sims can't have sparkly clean floors with a stinking, heap of garbage in their kitchen trashcan. After the indoor trashcan fills up, take it out promptly. </Text>
  <Text Key="19DF3CA6">Clean Up 5 Messes </Text>
  <Text Key="86975E5F">Clean up 5 dust piles, puddles, pet poops, fur balls, toddler messes, or other undesirable household entities. </Text>
  <Text Key="33DFCFD9">Wash Hands After Toilet Use</Text>
  <Text Key="55ADA33E">Don't be a savage. After using the bathroom, ensure your Sim makes a timely and thorough visit to the nearest sink. After a few hand-washings, your Sim will hopefully learn to always wash their hands. </Text>
  <Text Key="0EC05F20">Show Off Your Clean House to Guests</Text>
  <Text Key="C8DA743D">Invite a guest over from your relationship panel or phone and show them a clean floor level. </Text>
  <Text Key="DB02E01B">Earn the Moodlet "Perfectionist Zeal +4"</Text>
  <Text Key="4FD40A1C">Being a proactive cleaner means continuing to clean even when things look clean. Keep cleaning and cleaning until your Sim's Perfectionist Zeal intensifies into its most potent, energized state. </Text>
  <Text Key="8EC6CC1F">Purchase a Handheld and Upright Vacuum</Text>
  <Text Key="002F6200">Vacuum Virtuosos need the finest in suctioning technology to slay dust. Purchase a handheld and upright vacuum from Build/Buy Mode .</Text>
  <Text Key="2FB42B18">Destroy 3 Dust Bunnies or Filth Fiends with Vacuum Cleaner</Text>
  <Text Key="1255B1B5">Let your house get dusty, dirty, or filthy. When Dust Bunnies or Filth Fiends emerge, ignore their cute charms and vacuum them up with heartless precision. On the road to pristine perfection, all manner of dust must be considered foes. </Text>
  <Text Key="0C2FDC51">Destroy 5 Messy or Dust Pile Objects with Vacuum Cleaner</Text>
  <Text Key="27EFD7F6">As dust piles and other messes emerge on the floor, destroy them with your trusty Vacuum Cleaner.</Text>
  <Text Key="B05D6B42">Perform 2 Upgrades on a Vacuum Cleaner</Text>
  <Text Key="550DE46B">Gather parts and increase your handiness until you can successfully upgrade your vacuum cleaner. Modding your vacuum with a Bottomless Pit or a Vaporizing Pulse is the best way to flex on those other vacuum noobs that just use the stock models.</Text>
  <Text Key="C9790373">Choose a Favorite Vacuum Cleaner</Text>
  <Text Key="6B2E56F4">Designate a specific vacuum cleaner as your favorite. This vacuum cleaner will now be what your Sim prefers to use. This begins the deepest of bonds, the bond between a Sim and their prized vacuum cleaner. </Text>
  <Text Key="83A582B8">Throw a Party Social Event in a Clean House</Text>
  <Text Key="A4156615">Keep your house clean and host a scheduled social event from your phone or calendar. A Birthday party, house party, dinner party, or similar party will do. If a house is clean, and no one else sees it, can it truly be considered clean?</Text>
  <Text Key="1887783F">Clean for 5 hours in a Happy, Confident, Inspired, or Focused Mood</Text>
  <Text Key="610341E0">Mastery of cleaning requires no longer seeing cleaning as a chore. Keep your Sim in a Happy, Confident, Inspired, or Focused mood and keep on cleaning or vacuuming. </Text>
  <Text Key="0EC7177E">Successfully Ask or Demand that Other Sims Clean 3 times</Text>
  <Text Key="80366A77">To be a Chief Cleaning Officer, you must know how to delegate. Your time is too valuable to be the only person in the household scrubbing toilets, mopping puddles, and vacuuming floors. Boss up your cleaning game and ask (or demand) that other household Sims get to cleaning!</Text>
  <Text Key="E86B0A55">Hire a Housekeeping Service 2 times</Text>
  <Text Key="DB818A0A">Graduate from doing the cleaning yourself. By hiring a service from your phone or computer, you'll spend more time enjoying your clean house and less time actually cleaning. </Text>
  <Text Key="0A845CBC">Install 3 Self-Cleaning and Unbreakable Upgrades</Text>
  <Text Key="D92AF7B9">Prevent messes before they happen. By upgrading stoves, ovens, or bathroom objects to be Self-Cleaning, you're saving yourself countless hours of future scrubbing. And when plumbing objects become unbreakable, they will no longer produce pesky puddles. The best way to clean is to not make a mess in the first place!</Text>
  <Text Key="DBACC187">Filth Dweller</Text>
  <Text Key="7C768CB8">Fast &amp; Fastidious</Text>
  <Text Key="681E8087">{0.SimFirstName} already has too many Dust Friends on this floor!</Text>
  <Text Key="03C6C0F0">Fast &amp; Fastidious</Text>
  <Text Key="1E89F7D8">Fast &amp; Fastidious</Text>
  <Text Key="312D133F">Sims don't get negative moodlets or lose fun while cleaning. Sim will clean at a more rapid pace and is more likely to become focused when cleaning, and for maximal cleaning efficiency, Fast &amp; Fastidious Sims can use the "Power Clean" and "Power Vacuum" interactions.</Text>
  <Text Key="B2B10F92">(From completing the Perfectly Pristine Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="E7854C05">Filth Dweller</Text>
  <Text Key="84B3C78B">Filth Dweller</Text>
  <Text Key="C94B9484">This Sim no longer receives negative moodlets from living in dusty or messy environments. They loathe cleaning and love filth, and will receive Happy moodlets while in Dirty or Filthy houses. Additionally, they gain the ability to bond with and befriend Filth Fiends!</Text>
  <Text Key="4BC30D0F">(From completing the Fabulously Filthy Aspiration)</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>