<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="4E84A0DF">More emerald than ivy, greener than envy, these tendrily curtains will make your walls and windows luscious and green year-round. So lovely you'll want to keep your guests from trying to nibble it, otherwise it might be curtains for them. Just kidding. This version is not poisonous.</Text>
  <Text Key="A5E23186">Fine Vine Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="FFB7D529">Most String-of-Pearls plants are fake, but this one is totally real! A perennial creeper, (but not a creep) this sassy succulent enjoys bright light, making it the perfect companion plant for this hanging lamp.</Text>
  <Text Key="18894C0C">String-of-Pearls Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="3C3926FE">Plants like light, right? But do we know if lights like plants? Artificial plants don’t care for light, so let’s go with artificial lights and real plants: Lamps and plants together, that is! Confused? So is this lamp-plant/plant-lamp, but it's a great freak of nature.</Text>
  <Text Key="C7518B81">Green Light Plant Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="1A67D5EE">Asymmetric, yet geometric. The warmth of the wooden structure enhances the natural quality of the plants, making you wonder how you ever lived without this shelf configuration. Seriously. Don't let your life slip through your fingers without owning this contemporary organization solution. Don't wake up in a cold sweat in the middle of the night screaming "Geometric plant shelving!" only to awaken to an empty, plant-less wall and a dry, barren existence. Go geometric!</Text>
  <Text Key="2B9C7D91">Go Geo Plant Shelving</Text>
  <Text Key="F6D1E9DE">It's a jungle in here! If you're looking for a gargantuan plant that says "I'm a proud plant parent" or "I want to live in a rainforest," you've found your match. This giant pothos plant is here to bring life to your space, and can act as a conversation starter for those quieter, awkward moments. When you don't know what to say, now there's always "Hey, check out my huge plant."</Text>
  <Text Key="C344BFE1">Green Goddess Pothos</Text>
  <Text Key="64A643D7">Jade plants are often said to attract good fortune, so make sure to place one in your home if you are low on funds. Though the plant will not generate Simoleons for you, or win you any lotteries, its green, coin-like leaves and outstretched branches seem to beckon to the universe "hey, can I have some money?"</Text>
  <Text Key="D804DFAE">Fortune Favors the Jade Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="945CD78B">Take a deep breath. Imagine your-Sim-self sat on a sofa (or a chair, the floor, wherever… we’re not picky), contemplating the green of the plant, relaxing, letting your eyes wander and your mind travel through depth of space and time. Through the soft moss on the spiral pot into part of your mind that might not have been used in a long time (hello, algebra class and world history factoids). Now imagine yourself watering your brand new ficus tree...</Text>
  <Text Key="EEA9590A">Therapeutic Ficus</Text>
  <Text Key="86814968">Don't wait for life to give you lemons, go get some yourself! This visually a-peeling citrus bush will have you pleased as punch. Not to go off on a tangelo tangent but this cute little plant will be your main squeeze in no time. Orange you glad you got it?</Text>
  <Text Key="96336E87">Sunny Days Citrus Tree</Text>
  <Text Key="2B773D47">This adorable desert rose bonsai is here to complete your life and make existence a better place! From its pink blossoms to its Cthulhu-like roots, this succulent is a head-turner and will make anyone say "ya leel ya leel!"</Text>
  <Text Key="0C539EFE">Desert Rose</Text>
  <Text Key="38FF47F3">If you looked up "plant" in the dictionary, there would probably be a picture of this one. And let's face it, looking up "plant" would be a lot easier than trying to pronounce its proper botanical name. Anyway, just look at it! The classic elegant pot, the perky but not overly perky leaves... it's almost like it's always been in this room... hasn't it? Plant perfection in a pot.</Text>
  <Text Key="A1615622">Dieffenbachia</Text>
  <Text Key="7DC0704E">This light-loving plant often reaches up to the sky to grab whatever sunlight it can get its leaves on. Just don't confuse this plant with its sister, the Calathea plant. Imagine if someone confused you with your sister all the time - so rude!</Text>
  <Text Key="357A3F71">Triostar Stromanthe</Text>
  <Text Key="11C235AD">Also known as the Zanzibar gem, eternity plant, or the Zuzu plant, this tropical perennial is tough to kill. Before you break out the flame thrower and give it a go, you should know that ZZ plants are great air purifiers, have been used in traditional medicine, and can also be great listeners too. Just don't talk to it too much or you might make it zzzzzz...</Text>
  <Text Key="324EDC78">Faustus the ZZ Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="A6E98800">Into tea? Into plants? These old tea cannisters would have wound up in the trash, but here at Simergy Tea Sensations we believe in second chances. It's why we let Bob come back to work even though he microwaved a cod. (Really, Bob?) Anyway, these upcycled tea cannisters now house gorgeous snowdrop plants and are ready to up the twee factor in any home. Here's to second chances, tea, and snowdrops!</Text>
  <Text Key="DEB5A2CF">Twee Tea Planters by Simergy Tea Sensations</Text>
  <Text Key="96EF86F4">This ferntastic fern frequently wins Best-In-Show in the "heavily misted" category during plant expos. You might say the judges are quite &lt;i&gt;frond&lt;/i&gt; of it! Don't confuse it with large bowls of salad you might have hanging around your house.</Text>
  <Text Key="933E7F5B">Ferntastic Mr. Fern</Text>
  <Text Key="73B30388">This wall of verdant vases is perfect for plant lovers, plant admirers, plant daddys, plant queens, or anyone looking to fill an empty void in their life with plants. Who needs pictures of loved ones when you can put your loved ones directly on the wall?</Text>
  <Text Key="C62C5B27">Wall of Verdant Vases</Text>
  <Text Key="F867B9A9">Cute, cheerful pots for cute, cheerful plants! Perky lily pad-like leaves and bright blooms make this plant a superstar of any plant family. Housed within an adorable animal-inspired pot, these floral friends will be sure to put a smile on your face even on your grumpiest of days.</Text>
  <Text Key="E232D18C">Superb Nasturtiums</Text>
  <Text Key="65DE52B9">For the love of all that is good and green! Section your space into a sanctuary of biophilic tranquility with this tangled treasure of a room divider. Holey monstera deliciosa!</Text>
  <Text Key="2D6119BC">Biophilic Room Divider</Text>
  <Text Key="03158E5D">If you've got some rage, you might want a plant in a cage. That's right! Plants have proven to have rage-reducing properties. Even just looking at the color green is said to reduce your heart rate. This beautiful statement piece has nine plants just waiting to lessen your stress with their air-purifying natural goodness. Lock it in!</Text>
  <Text Key="19D2E548">All the Rage Plant Cage</Text>
  <Text Key="265AA0DD">This adorable propagation station is a must-have for any plant parent! Two small plant vials let you see your seedlings progress from root to tendril. What's cuter than a plant? Baby plants!</Text>
  <Text Key="B73894C8">Propagation Station</Text>
  <Text Key="C537A0FC">Three plants are better than one! Triple your plant-real-estate with this tri-level plant stand. One for all and all for botanical love. Mesmerize your friends and family with a mystical number that recalls arcane secrets and reaches for the synthesis that is more than the sum of its parts. Or just arrange your plants in a fancy and elegant way. After all, three is like black: it goes with everything.</Text>
  <Text Key="63B5D253">Cryptic Triptych Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="39C20D16">From our greenhouse to your green-home! This open-front greenhouse-style shelving unit has enough built in windows to keep any high-maintenance plants looking and feeling their best. If only there was a greenhouse like this for high-maintenance Sims...</Text>
  <Text Key="B03E85C9">Greenhome Greenhouse-Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="BCAD2FB0">For the houseplant hobbyist who wants to get a little dirty! Park this shelf in a sunny spot and cram it with whatever you feel like, but we recommend houseplants, naturally. Comes complete with entryway clutter, gardening supplies, and you guessed it... even more houseplants!</Text>
  <Text Key="A33BC25F">Houseplant Hobbyist Shelving</Text>
  <Text Key="EE6003AB">shelfWall2x1_SP29FLORAgeometric placeholder description</Text>
  <Text Key="9D4432AA">shelfWall2x1_SP29FLORAgeometric placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="8A4F1C69">Lush reflections intermingle and intertwine with the organic refraction. A poetic game of light, life, and clarity flowing into each other to give shape to… a great place to put stuff! Bring home this end table today and have a whole new place to hunt for your keys.</Text>
  <Text Key="7188F34C">Lush Reflections End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="9ED0645B">The elegance of structural support complete with the gorgeousness of the greenery makes for the perfect glossy-glassy composition. A must-have for any green-thumbed Sim. What reflections! What refraction! What chlorophyll!</Text>
  <Text Key="E21F363A">Of Glass and Greenery</Text>
  <Text Key="C2E6CBBB">Plant Lover's Patio</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>