<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="5A7D37AB">Cardio Couture</Text>
  <Text Key="9D331C59">Street Smart</Text>
  <Text Key="2BAFA376">Refined Rogue</Text>
  <Text Key="8002D4CD">Sophisticated Snooze</Text>
  <Text Key="558DBF13">Envision an evening with friends where your modern bar becomes the centerpiece. Showcasing your finest spirits and glassware, it turns your home into the ultimate setting for stylish gatherings and impressive displays.</Text>
  <Text Key="900F31C2">The Zenith Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="D220C584">Introducing the ChillTech Pro Mini Fridge - the ultimate beverage cooling solution. It is compact yet powerful and features advanced cooling technology to keep your drinks chilled perfectly. Ideal for any space, its sleek design and quiet operation make it a must-have. </Text>
  <Text Key="1397F54B">ChillTech Pro Mini Fridge</Text>
  <Text Key="DCB9B310">Discover the future of entertainment today and experience unparalleled visual clarity with the TitanScreen 5000. Boasting an ultra-jumbo screen, vibrant colors, and seamless connectivity, this TV transforms your living space into an upscale theater experience.</Text>
  <Text Key="201C243F">TitanScreen 5000</Text>
  <Text Key="9F818B1A">Each piece in this collection is meticulously crafted to bring vibrant visuals and contemporary flair to your living spaces. Perfect for those looking to elevate their home decor with unique and stylish artwork.</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE7A245">Designer Wall Prints by Valor Visuals</Text>
  <Text Key="A9ADF1AD">Discover the latest trends and style with a stack of SIM-Q Magazine. Dive into vibrant pages filled with fashion and style tips and inspiring lifestyle articles. Perfect for fashion enthusiasts and trendsetters looking to stay ahead of the curve!</Text>
  <Text Key="518D5078">SIM-Q Magazine</Text>
  <Text Key="F40C6EFE">Each frame captures your most Simstagram-worthy moments: unforgettable vacations, breathtaking sunsets, and candid laughter. Guests can’t help but admire and comment on these stunning photos, turning your living space into a gallery of your life's best moments!</Text>
  <Text Key="3658E381">Tabletop Memories</Text>
  <Text Key="61AA854A">Elevate your memorabilia collection with this custom framed jersey display. Crafted to showcase your autographed jersey, this display boasts premium materials, UV-protected glass, and a professional finish, ensuring your keepsake remains preserved and beautifully showcased for years to come.</Text>
  <Text Key="0927C555">The Ultimate Jersey Frame</Text>
  <Text Key="CBF54D84">Elevate your media room with the Zenith Wall Unit: a sleek, built-in wall cabinet. It offers ample storage and a modern design, perfect for keeping your entertainment space tidy and showing off your hard-earned possessions. </Text>
  <Text Key="8A5F0D4B">The Zenith Wall Unit</Text>
  <Text Key="13A60C2E">This sofa will elevate any get-together like no other. Its refined design and sumptuous comfort invite you to lose yourself as you watch the big game with friends or spend a quiet evening embracing a loved one in style.</Text>
  <Text Key="D94A4ED1">Streamlined Leather Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="045E761F">This luxurious cabinet cradles your turntable in style and flaunts your prized vinyl collection with unmatched sophistication. Elevate your space and let your exquisite music collection shine in unparalleled elegance. </Text>
  <Text Key="7F89E2C6">TurntableTrove Media Cabinet </Text>
  <Text Key="73926D19">Turn your media room into the ultimate hangout spot with this sleek coffee table—a true hub of activity! With its spacious glass and marble surface, it’s the perfect size for laying out snacks, drinks, and more. Trust us, your popcorn has never looked so stylish! </Text>
  <Text Key="FB1ACC9C">The Zenith Glass Coffee Table</Text>
  <Text Key="B8DD9F18">Imagine the thrill of a high-stakes card game: the tension rises as players gather around, eyes locked, with the stakes higher than ever. With every turn of the card, the room buzzes with excitement, the table witnessing both triumphs and defeats.</Text>
  <Text Key="DC8EA097">High Stakes Card Table</Text>
  <Text Key="0C51F893">The Casanova Cave</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>