<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="9F60B62B">Puzzled Stone Floor</Text>
  <Text Key="07F04B44">This well-loved open-style cabinet's got nothing to hide! Bring a bright, airy look to your space that says "Here I am, world, and I've got baskets!"</Text>
  <Text Key="82DCD90B">Country Charm Cabinet</Text>
  <Text Key="B286B759">Bring your kitchen back to basics in the best way! Whether you're baking a pie, several pies, a pie baked inside of a cake or several pies baked inside a tower of cakes, this kitchen island is here for you. It is also suitable for non-pie endeavors if you're into that kind of thing.</Text>
  <Text Key="3BF5C8DC">Country Charm Kitchen Island</Text>
  <Text Key="78B237AC">This vintage wooden counter has lots of tall tales to tell, gossip to gab about and several secret recipes whispered to it over the years, but unfortunately it's just a kitchen counter that was never given the gift of speech. While it can't talk, it can serve as a great, flat surface to rest stuff on and prep delicious foods.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F623FE3">Country Charm Counter</Text>
  <Text Key="9B6AD223">Not your grandparent's fridge - but close! They really don't make 'em like they used to, so why not go retro? With double French doors and a delicate design, this fridge will be the heart of your country kitchen or a welcome twist on a modern space. Just look at those little feet!</Text>
  <Text Key="A0E837F2">Country Charm Fridge</Text>
  <Text Key="E7176EF4">This repurposed toolbox reminds us that some problems can't be fixed by tools, but can be helped by fresh flowers. Except if you have allergies...in which case, a bouquet of wrenches might be better.</Text>
  <Text Key="E3E1B75B">Handy-Dandy Flower Caddy</Text>
  <Text Key="19CE4CF5">If you find yourself in a jam, or in a crumby situation where everything's gone a-rye, take it with a grain of salt and reach for your bread-box. The love of a good loaf is the best thing since sliced bread.</Text>
  <Text Key="8F125290">Heritage Bread Box</Text>
  <Text Key="7CE0C079">Who needs fine china with a casserole dish this cute? Passed down through generations of foodies, this twee floral-print dish will feel at home on any kitchen counter top. But a dish is only as good as what's inside it, so make sure you put your kitchen to good use! And let us know what time supper is...</Text>
  <Text Key="057AD67C">Granny's Cozy Casserole Dish</Text>
  <Text Key="896DB8F6">Whether you're milling your own flour or stocking up on store-bought, this sweet little tin might be the most romantic flour arrangement out there.</Text>
  <Text Key="89735829">Heritage Flour Tin</Text>
  <Text Key="B2B89A49">Farm-fresh foods the old-fashioned way: in a bucket! Forget the fancy pantry. Four out of five kitchen stylists agree that if you really want to go for a charming, rustic look, put it in a bucket. Apples? In a bucket. Potatoes? Bucket. Lemons? Bucket. Pumpkins? Bucket. A bunch of smaller buckets? Hmm. You might be better off storing those in a shed.</Text>
  <Text Key="E96C52AC">Bountiful Bucket</Text>
  <Text Key="46DF6F16">Suitable for storing anything and everything! But that wasn't always the case.\nGenerations ago, this was a storage jar for buttons and only buttons. One day, a young lady named Nicki Knack tried to put a knitting needle into the jar and was met with much disdain from her parents who lectured her about proper storage etiquette.\n When Nicki asked why the jar was solely designated for buttons, her parents were shocked. "That's the way it has always been!" they both were quite taken aback, but after a few months of introspection, the Knack family realized their daughter had a point. Why couldn't the jar be used for anything?\n Even though it was quite unheard of to change organization techniques, Nicki started a revolution. Today, the jar can be used for anything and everything.</Text>
  <Text Key="3CF50BC9">Nicki Knack's Anything 'n Everything Jar</Text>
  <Text Key="82876F15">No country kitchen would be complete without a floral motif wooden shelf. This particular shelf was featured in "The Sim-ple Life" Magazine where it enjoyed a two page spread as part of the annual "Shelf Esteem" edition.</Text>
  <Text Key="F1E2FC30">Country Charm Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="E3F11940">Great stoves often get a lot of credit for making a good kitchen feel homey, but we think it's really the kitchen sink that should get a medal of recognition. Don't let its prim appearance fool you. This sink has tackled the toughest of dirty dish disasters over the years with only minor wear-and-tear. Battle scars!</Text>
  <Text Key="AA124D0F">Country Charm Sink</Text>
  <Text Key="EF06F2EA">So the story goes, a land dispute over a hundred years ago caused quite the kerfuffle when the Tinker family and Landgraab family could not come to an agreement on whose land parcel was whose. When an ancestor of the Tinker family planted a crabapple tree on the border, things got quite rowdy.\nThe Landgraabs sent strongly worded letters which eventually resulted in the Tinkers challenging the Landgraabs to a duel by way of pancakes. The two families met at dawn on the 21st of December, 1917, and cooked up a storm on this very stove!\nAfter rigorous judging, it was determined that the Landgraab family recipe was the winner, and so the disputed land was turned over to them. Years later rumors began circulating that the Landgraabs stole their pancake recipe from the Jacquet family, but nothing has been proven.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D325475">Pancakes at Dawn Stove</Text>
  <Text Key="A6D90BCB">Country Comforts</Text>
  <Text Key="FFF562E7">Stones In Stacks</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>