<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="317D5F84">Riviera Floor Tile</Text>
  <Text Key="8D1B12A2">This Bronze Firepit literally elevates fire to a new level. Modeled on classical designs from antiquity, these were once used to heat the homes of merchants and nobility alike. Perfect for roasting marshmallows.</Text>
  <Text Key="7423251D">Bronze Firepit</Text>
  <Text Key="ED6BC90A">Designed to grace your poolside patio or cabana, these curtains add an air of refreshing and captivating elegance. As they billow gently in the breeze, they create a dynamic ambiance - a dance of shadow and light that is as enchanting as it is relaxing. Pairs nicely with the Rustic Riviera Arch.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA71EC15">Windswept Cabana Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="EB2DF7F6">Step into a world of old-world charm with the Rustic Riviera Arch. This stunning archway immediately transports you to sunny Mediterranean shores with its weathered riviera stone facade, elegantly curved top, and artfully distressed finish.</Text>
  <Text Key="37F1E529">Rustic Riviera Arch</Text>
  <Text Key="EE90BACA">A glass of Mint Citrus Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="24516DD5">Mint Citrus Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE4DF06">Pop, fizz, and clink with this sophisticated symphony of bubbles. The silver platter? That's just our way of serving you a touch of sophistication and allure. It's the perfect way to celebrate; no occasion is necessary!</Text>
  <Text Key="B5D83E99">"On a Silver Platter" Drink Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="63C550AB">This natural stone waterfall isn't just a fountain; it's a transformation. Crafted with the finesse of Mother Nature, it's the perfect blend of elegance and tranquility, turning your pool into the perfect retreat. It's small in size but huge in impact! (Pairs well with the Grotto Gravel Pool Trim and Grotto Accent Rocks).</Text>
  <Text Key="A3E889AA">Grotto Cascade - Small</Text>
  <Text Key="AA7CC7F5">Have you ever seen yourself and not recognized your face? Did you ever doubt your dreams would ever come true? Hold up and listen to your own heart, do your own thing, and you'll end up on top. Bet on it. (Pairs well with the Grotto Gravel Pool Trim and Grotto Accent Rocks).</Text>
  <Text Key="354ED390">Grotto Cascade - Large</Text>
  <Text Key="438A76D0">Introducing the Aqueduct Fountain - the ultimate statement piece for your outdoor oasis! This stunning stone fountain is a masterpiece that will transform your poolside spaces, patios, or elegant gardens into a tranquil haven.</Text>
  <Text Key="0DD818FF">Aqueduct Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="5CB297D0">This pool light is a radiant touch of brass elegance for your aquatic retreat. Experience the glamour of a starlit swim, right in your own backyard.</Text>
  <Text Key="E8E4ABFF">Embellished Pool Light</Text>
  <Text Key="7D3181DB">Travel back in time with these Timeless Tapers. This brass wall sconce, adorned with taper candles, illuminates your space with a rustic allure that leaves echoes of times long forgotten. </Text>
  <Text Key="DB7516BA">Timeless Tapers</Text>
  <Text Key="C90C9132">This planter is a harmonious fusion of nature's elegance and allure. Nestled within is a flourishing bergamot plant, its invigorating style is poised to infuse your surroundings with a touch of sophistication. Experience the earthy charm of this exquisite greenery, the epitome of luxurious simplicity.</Text>
  <Text Key="A346DECD">"Essence of Bergamot" Planter</Text>
  <Text Key="CEB6A67E">Navigate the waters of your Riviera Retreat with the Mariner's Pool Ladder. Designed with the lavish elegance of a Riviera yacht in mind, this ladder brings the luxury of the high seas to your poolside. </Text>
  <Text Key="442AF201">Mariner's Pool Ladder</Text>
  <Text Key="CA25D0E3">Why just step when you can stride with style? Step into nature's charm with our Serene Stepping Stones. Handcrafted and designed to seamlessly accent your outdoor space, these stones are more than a pathway – they're an invitation to explore.</Text>
  <Text Key="8EDD4EB2">Serene Stepping Stones</Text>
  <Text Key="2A93D713">Perfect for sun-soaked siestas or starlit serenades, it's your passport to an eternal summer. May your love blossom like the precious ivy seen climbing upon this arbor. Maybe one day it can offer protection from the elements! Wait, which one will protect us? Love or the ivy?</Text>
  <Text Key="AB95F9C2">Romeo &amp; Juliet Arbor</Text>
  <Text Key="C88B2B2B">With the ultimate 'rock' star of outdoor accents, you can now transform your outdoor space into an aesthetic wonderland. Perfectly sized for poolside grottos or garden corners, it brings a hint of wild nature right to your doorstep. (Pairs well with a set of Grotto Cascade waterfalls, and the Grotto Gravel Pool Trim).</Text>
  <Text Key="FAE6112A">Grotto Accent Rock - Small</Text>
  <Text Key="C9AE0773">For those who appreciate the understated beauty of nature's artistry, experience the rugged allure of the Large Grotto Accent Rock. Its robust and natural charm is the perfect addition to pool grottos and garden landscapes, providing a majestic touch to your outdoor oasis. (Pairs well with a set of Grotto Cascade waterfalls, and the Grotto Gravel Pool Trim).</Text>
  <Text Key="438A7CA2">Grotto Accent Rock - Large</Text>
  <Text Key="5745451B">Stay sun-kissed, not soaked! The Poolside Towel Station - your personal, poolside butler keeping your towel dry, handy, and off the ground. Dive into convenience!</Text>
  <Text Key="AC787FFA">Poolside Towel Station</Text>
  <Text Key="EA35BA16">Designed for those who appreciate the finer things in life, this chair transforms every poolside meal into a sophisticated alfresco dining experience.</Text>
  <Text Key="1BFFFCC9">Patio Prestige Dining Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="42A13BA3">Perfect for poolside posturing, sun-soaking, or just a casual catnap. Dive into a book, or dive into the pool - the choice is yours. With the Poolside Lounger, every day can feel like a vacation!</Text>
  <Text Key="81E43C72">Poolside Lounger</Text>
  <Text Key="14A20548">Experience the epitome of poolside pampering with the Luxury Lounger. Crafted from premium linen, this pool float guarantees a lavish float session like no other. And we didn't stop there - we've paired it with a cozy throw pillow, ensuring your relaxation is nothing short of bliss. </Text>
  <Text Key="0FA0D3E7">The Luxury Lounger</Text>
  <Text Key="5DB31968">Seamlessly blending style and functionality, this outdoor marvel is your perfect companion for poolside dining. With a built-in canvas umbrella, you'll be able to savor your meals without a side of sunburn. </Text>
  <Text Key="027FDE87">Patio Prestige Dining Table</Text>
  <Text Key="F74C5242">Built to weather, water, and warmth, it's the coolest companion for your lounge chair or patio.</Text>
  <Text Key="1992B93D">Sunbath Soiree Table</Text>
  <Text Key="858D5653">Can't restock when tray is full.</Text>
  <Text Key="9BF5E8C5">Restock Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="E495D260">Aww... No more tasty beverages left... </Text>
  <Text Key="91C0B907">Grab Drink</Text>
  <Text Key="34190AD7">Backyard Riviera Retreat</Text>
  <Text Key="DAB6469A">This exquisite blend of stone and natural rock turns ordinary pools into lavish lagoons. It's a stylish upgrade that blends seamlessly into any landscape, turning your pool into a natural oasis. (Pairs nicely with Grotto Cascade waterfalls and accompanying Grotto Accent Rocks).</Text>
  <Text Key="9489FCC5">Grotto Gravel Pool Trim</Text>
  <Text Key="221305FC">Crafted from superior stone and glazed tiles, it's not just a trim; it's a trip to paradise with every swim! (Pairs nicely with the Riviera Tile - Wall and Floor).</Text>
  <Text Key="5230F153">Riviera Tile Pool Trim</Text>
  <Text Key="862E0CFD">Mint Citrus Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="0BA0E64E">Make Juice</Text>
  <Text Key="9B7C3B91">It's as delicious as it looks!</Text>
  <Text Key="0811E044">Riviera Cobblestone</Text>
  <Text Key="310190C7">Riviera Wall Tile</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>