<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="0BB250A7">(From Feeding a Rodent)</Text>
  <Text Key="0A5FB911">(From Observing a Rodent)</Text>
  <Text Key="41405372">(From Playing with a Rodent)</Text>
  <Text Key="A599ABA8">(From Acquiring a New Rodent)</Text>
  <Text Key="9D351994">(From Releasing a Rodent)</Text>
  <Text Key="EAB07E89">(From Rodent Bite)</Text>
  <Text Key="8C40A94B">
  </Text>
  <Text Key="5D5790EE">(From Being Near a Sim With Rabid Rodent Fever)</Text>
  <Text Key="9C789582">{0.SimFirstName} has become dangerously contagious! Nearby Sims are in danger of having Rabid Rodent Fever spread to them. {0.SimFirstName} should urgently seek help by researching the disease on a computer, or by consulting with {M0.his}{F0.her} local veterinarian. Untreated cases of Rabid Rodent Fever are known to result in death.</Text>
  <Text Key="8CAD809C">CONTAGIOUS</Text>
  <Text Key="4C44C880">{0.SimFirstName}'s head is starting to ache, and there's a tickle in the back of {M0.his}{F0.her} throat. It seems {M0.he}{F0.she} may have contracted a serious sickness.</Text>
  <Text Key="BFF89FFB">(From Owning a Rodent Cage)</Text>
  <Text Key="115165A3">Yum yum gimme some! Rodents are super cute when they get excited for mealtime!</Text>
  <Text Key="C7C89A72">Nibbles 'n Bits</Text>
  <Text Key="7C4CCF11">Hide &amp; Squeak</Text>
  <Text Key="B3147D66">It looks like a new rodent has joined the household... Now to "Ooh" and "Aah" over how cute it is!</Text>
  <Text Key="8F0E8279">New Pet Rodent</Text>
  <Text Key="94736C23">Silly little critter; I see you hiding in the tunnel!</Text>
  <Text Key="BA1D08E4">You spin my tail right round, right round, when you go round when you go round round.</Text>
  <Text Key="B5D8762B">Pipe Size Exercise</Text>
  <Text Key="7B20A78E">Being well rested helps improve focus... Rodents are so wise!</Text>
  <Text Key="BFB1BC47">{0.SimFirstName} is overcome with an overwhelming case of cuteness after watching {M0.his}{F0.her} happy little critter scamper around its habitat.</Text>
  <Text Key="88ACEBFE">Content Rodent</Text>
  <Text Key="42315ED6">For a tiny rodent, a little playtime goes a long way!</Text>
  <Text Key="5A1F5E89">Rodent Playtime</Text>
  <Text Key="F542DB9E">Rested Rodent</Text>
  <Text Key="2AFBDB2E">Ouch! That was a just little nibble, but it's a lot of pain!</Text>
  <Text Key="26748BD1">Bite-Sized Bite</Text>
  <Text Key="1DFDB2D4">{0.SimFirstName} doesn't feel so good... {M0.His}{F0.Her} head is pounding and {M0.he}{F0.she} can't shake this cough.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA17C9BB">Feeling Fuzzy</Text>
  <Text Key="5488E8BB">{0.SimFirstName}'s cough has turned into a full blown fever. Those dizzy spells can't be a good sign, and {M0.he}{F0.she}'s losing control of {M0.his}{F0.her} bladder.\n\n{M0.He}{F0.She} should research {M0.his}{F0.her} fever on a computer to find a cure.</Text>
  <Text Key="DBA8B71A">Fuzzy Fever</Text>
  <Text Key="8108FC7E">It's a full blown outbreak of Rabid Rodent Fever! {0.SimFirstName} looks delirious, and {M0.he}{F0.she}'s dangerously contagious. {M0.His}{F0.Her} condition is rapidly deteriorating; {M0.he}{F0.she} should use a computer to research {M0.his}{F0.her} illness or consult with a veterinarian immediately.\n\nFailure to seek help could result in grave consequences...</Text>
  <Text Key="74C61401">Rabid Rodent Fever</Text>
  <Text Key="C9D0ED5D">Death in {0.Timespan}</Text>
  <Text Key="8E5B0C80">Every rodent dies; not every rodent really lives. Run free little one; I believe in you!</Text>
  <Text Key="F7B2084F">Freeeeeeedom!</Text>
  <Text Key="D50582E3">Snuggly Twinsie</Text>
  <Text Key="76823870">Best Pet Pal</Text>
  <Text Key="FA0626DE">One With The Pet</Text>
  <Text Key="8CAE86BC">Crayons and a healthy imagination for four-legged friends is all it takes for a child to enjoy the Cranimals Activity Table, even if they produce a drawing that only a parent could love.</Text>
  <Text Key="E829F813">Cranimals Activity Table</Text>
  <Text Key="114D7566">What is best in life? To crush your enemies, see them driven before you, and to sleep on top of them.</Text>
  <Text Key="BFF7EA79">The Barbarian's Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="0C8C5A4A">There's nothing like waking up to a nice hot meal after a restful night's sleep. Pamper your pet with a heaping helping of green eggs and ham - it's all part of a complete breakfast!</Text>
  <Text Key="990B3455">Rise 'n Shine Sleepy Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="03D74643">Is your child lugging home book after book from endless book fairs? Sounds like you need the Book Fair Bear! With three generous shelves of storage, it's "beary" capable of handling all the books you need to stow away.</Text>
  <Text Key="ABA31592">Book Fair Bear</Text>
  <Text Key="2644B243">Get in muh belly, it's comfy in here! This cat condo has just enough space for a cat to curl up with their big carpeted kitty friend.</Text>
  <Text Key="86579992">Muh Belly Cat Condo</Text>
  <Text Key="9353DE32">Inspire your cat to have happy dreams of nomming on fishies with the Om Nom Nom Cat Condo. Perfect for play, passing out, or lazing on the backs of plush kitties floating through the sky; your curious kitty will love every spot in this comfy perch.</Text>
  <Text Key="6EF135CD">Om Nom Nom Cat Condo</Text>
  <Text Key="34BD5E0F">Dodging cats at Whiskerman's Wharf. Send help!</Text>
  <Text Key="0147CBD6">Whiskerman's Wharf: Postcard</Text>
  <Text Key="BC302D36">Negotiating climate agreements in Champ Les Sims!</Text>
  <Text Key="9592EF69">Champ Les Sims: Postcard</Text>
  <Text Key="7D4838C1">Dodging mummies in Al Simhara, be glad you're not here!</Text>
  <Text Key="2AD868F4">Al Simhara: Postcard</Text>
  <Text Key="E2143DC0">Greetings from Deadgrass Isle... where the grass is dead, but the fishing is great!</Text>
  <Text Key="2731928F">Brindleton Bay: Postcard</Text>
  <Text Key="88036C6B">Come to Windenburg, dance in Windenburg, laugh in Windenburg, prance in Windenburg! Get together in Windenburg!</Text>
  <Text Key="7155576A">Windenburg: Postcard</Text>
  <Text Key="E0D2A0E2">Sttub ruoy ot no dloh; Maxis ot emoclew!</Text>
  <Text Key="8DEF345D">Sixam: Postcard</Text>
  <Text Key="419BE18D">Namaste... Enjoying peace and tranquility in the secluded Sylvan Glade.</Text>
  <Text Key="42751BD8">Sylvan Glade: Postcard</Text>
  <Text Key="CB67D104">Tired of strangers mean mugging you as they walk by your home? Throw shade back at them, and block their negativity from your life.\n\n*This shade is suitable for windows that are one tile wide.</Text>
  <Text Key="DB403FCB">Throw Shade - Small</Text>
  <Text Key="2B17C5F9">Tired of strangers mean mugging you as they walk by your home? Throw shade back at them, and block their negativity from your life.\n\n*This shade is suitable for windows that are two tiles wide.</Text>
  <Text Key="C31DEEFC">Throw Shade - Medium</Text>
  <Text Key="B1631B1A">Tired of strangers mean mugging you as they walk by your home? Throw shade back at them, and block their negativity from your life.\n\n*This shade is suitable for windows that are three tiles wide.</Text>
  <Text Key="C8B75245">Throw Shade - Large</Text>
  <Text Key="46F389A8">Abyssinians, and Toygers, and Bears! Oh, my! Chart the growth of your own young cub with this handy wall decal.</Text>
  <Text Key="52A462C7">Cubs 'n Kittens Height Chart</Text>
  <Text Key="202FF45A">Devote yourself to simple, decent, and affordable hamster housing. Sold at cost, all you have to do is snap this decorative piping together to create a fun faux hamster habitat that spans your home's walls! \n\n*Look for complimentary vertical and connector piping pieces in the catalog to complete your full habitat.</Text>
  <Text Key="E351F485">Habitat for Hamsters - Horizontal</Text>
  <Text Key="02DB8F39">Devote yourself to simple, decent, and affordable hamster housing. Sold at cost, all you have to do is snap this decorative piping together to create a fun faux hamster habitat that spans your home's walls! \n\n*Look for complimentary vertical and horizontal piping pieces in the catalog to complete your full habitat.</Text>
  <Text Key="9343273C">Habitat for Hamsters - Connectors</Text>
  <Text Key="FEB63820">Devote yourself to simple, decent, and affordable hamster housing. Sold at cost, all you have to do is snap this decorative piping together to create a fun faux hamster habitat that spans your home's walls! \n\n*Look for complimentary horizontal and connector piping pieces in the catalog to complete your full habitat.</Text>
  <Text Key="579FDB6F">Habitat for Hamsters - Vertical</Text>
  <Text Key="A9464516">Pencils down, paws up! This little desk comes with a bit of privacy; perfect for taking tests, doing homework, or just a little isolation when you're trying to study.</Text>
  <Text Key="C0A5ADC9">Pawsome Desk</Text>
  <Text Key="2CEB0B99">Shouldn't your dog's door match your McModern Mansion? Now it can! The skinny windows will both compliment your home's aesthetic, and help prevent any dustups at the doorway.</Text>
  <Text Key="DB0D601C">Modern Doggo Door</Text>
  <Text Key="A86B558D">Shouldn't your pup's door match your McModern Mansion? Now it can! The skinny windows will both compliment your home's aesthetic, and help prevent any dustups at the doorway.\n\nThis little door is ideal for small dogs and cats.</Text>
  <Text Key="8B2137D8">Modern Pupper Door</Text>
  <Text Key="664F2FC4">Immediately cures any stage of Rabid Rodent Fever.</Text>
  <Text Key="E0635E8B">Rabid Rodent Serum</Text>
  <Text Key="F42C3B56">Permanently protects Sims from contracting Rabid Rodent Fever.</Text>
  <Text Key="F5484C09">Rabies Inoculation Serum</Text>
  <Text Key="9CA4C2F2">Even pets aren't immune from our charged political climate. Regularly fill their bowl, or prepare yourself to be routinely subjected to your pet's stump speech for treats.</Text>
  <Text Key="DF038A8D">Stump for Treats Bowl</Text>
  <Text Key="59E86B04">Fruit, veggies, proteins, and grains... all compressed into delicious pellet form. Keeps a rodent full and happy! </Text>
  <Text Key="F9CAEDCB">Rodent Pellets</Text>
  <Text Key="6A95D475">This big kitty lamp is mega cute, desu! It's soft silicon shell emits a lovely glow... perhaps creating the perfect mood lighting, desu?</Text>
  <Text Key="731B5110">Dekai Kawaii Neko Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="5DC0FCA2">Every child needs a Leaping Lamp in their bedroom to stir the imagination of cats and dogs jumping over the moon while they drift off to sleep. Cow and fiddle sold separately.</Text>
  <Text Key="7E7CC31D">Leaping Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="171CD7D1">The gaping feline maw on the Chow Down Litter Box triggers an instinctual fear response from dogs, warding off any who may be sniffing around for a snack.</Text>
  <Text Key="1D5CF524">Chow Down Litter Box</Text>
  <Text Key="A989DD29">The majestic sky cat lives amongst the clouds, content to gaze down upon the mortal realm it oversees. Do you dare gaze back?</Text>
  <Text Key="DBD0E40C">Sky Cat Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="9280A861">Cats or dogs... the eternal struggle to declare which pet is best continues to rage across the interwebs. You look reasonable though; hang this collage of cats and dogs on your walls and celebrate the best of both!</Text>
  <Text Key="1CB33314">The Pet Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="77C117F1">Fresh Aspen shavings offer natural bedding for your tiny friend.</Text>
  <Text Key="344C44C4">Restful Rodent Bedding</Text>
  <Text Key="B586D7F4">♪ Stomp your feet and clap your hands,\nc'mon, everybody, it's the hams... ♪\n\n*record scratch*\n\n"...shhh; they must never find out about the dance! Back to plotting our escape!"</Text>
  <Text Key="0411A25B">Hammy</Text>
  <Text Key="987A4396">Perhaps you have a prickly personality... if so, the Pygmy Hedgehog may be the right pet for you. Before hedgehogs came into existence, they lived in the ocean as the creature we call sea urchins. While there's still disagreement over what caused this critter to grow legs and walk onto land, acknowledging that they make fantastic pets is settled science!</Text>
  <Text Key="728C6149">Thimble</Text>
  <Text Key="8D078750">San Myshuno! It's a wonderful town, well... except for its infamous rat infestation. Running through the sewers, crawling through apartment building walls; they're everywhere! What's a mayor to do? Thankfully, there's nothing a little political spin can't fix... Can I interest you in a pet rat? How about two? Seriously, take three, they make wonderful companions!</Text>
  <Text Key="9BC9627F">Whiskers</Text>
  <Text Key="DD03068A">The frothing demand for the Voidcritters television show has created entire lines of unexpected products. After a talking plush of Bubalus became the best-selling toy of 2016, pet breeders saw an opportunity they were uniquely qualified to seize upon. Using genetic engineering, they've taken the body of a Hippopotamus, the color and spiral shape of a Violet Sea Snail, and the fur, size, and disposition of a Hamster, to create a new species of animal dubbed the Dwarf Bubalus. Now you can have one of these once fictional creatures to call your very own!</Text>
  <Text Key="8F502C95">Bubalus</Text>
  <Text Key="4D2F1AEA">A collection of synthetic skins and furs from the animal kingdom are brought together in harmony on this patterned print rug.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B624C75">Rugs-N-Camaraderie</Text>
  <Text Key="DFC8850B">All right meow, it's time to take a seat and get your homework done.</Text>
  <Text Key="B8F9E98A">Nya Desk Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="D2E6501F">Everyone knows the hamster's tummy is where the softest fur is... Now you can lounge on the lap of snuggly 'ole Hampton the hamster.</Text>
  <Text Key="150650C6">Hampton's Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="882357C8">The open ended design of the Puppy Loveseat makes it an inviting place to stretch out for a cat nap.</Text>
  <Text Key="84874367">Puppy Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="1DA9C64F">This loveseat snuggles into a bay window recess the same way a cute cat snuggles into your lap... juuuuust right.</Text>
  <Text Key="3937B316">Snuggle Seat</Text>
  <Text Key="D8EE13B7">Go ahead and set items down on the surface of this aquarium. The fish won't mind a little tapping; in fact they've been specially trained to ignore it.</Text>
  <Text Key="8B55E90E">Tap Tap Table</Text>
  <Text Key="89A2B509">From the makers of the Tap Tap Table comes an end table concept piece, available first to those who back it via their online fundraising campaign! Once they figure out how to create a self-sustaining fish habitat within this smaller size, they'll happily sell you an upgrade kit to convert it into a full blown aquarium.</Text>
  <Text Key="283A386C">Tap Tap Table Mini Backer Kit</Text>
  <Text Key="B6CC3A35">The Woof Box proudly presents the preeminent playthings for your pup to work out their perpetual pep. The Mrow Box contains a curated compilation of cute curios that's certain to charm the most cantankerous of cats. No matter which you choose, your pets will surely love it!</Text>
  <Text Key="508947D0">Woof Box / Mrow Box</Text>
  <Text Key="80A54407">Oi! There's a fun little fuzzy Fozzy hamster to play with over here!</Text>
  <Text Key="82D6F7BE">Fozzy Ozzie Ozzie Toy</Text>
  <Text Key="53E2C368">This treat will permanently halt the aging process in rodents.</Text>
  <Text Key="FFCABC87">Anti-Aging (Rodents)</Text>
  <Text Key="7230A254">This numbing agent will return a rodent's mental capacity to that of a normal pet.</Text>
  <Text Key="3636803B">IQ Limiter (Rodents)</Text>
  <Text Key="116261D8">Rabid Rodent Fever is a dangerous disease. Left untreated, it results in death. As the conditions of the patient worsen, the disease mutates into an airborne contagion which spreads to other Sims in close proximity!\n\nThankfully, help is available. Use a Computer to order a Rodent Remedy. You can choose to order a cure, or to inoculate yourself against future outbreaks.</Text>
  <Text Key="EBFEA73C">Research Rabid Rodent Fever</Text>
  <Text Key="D8EFFFDD">{0.SimName} is foaming at the mouth, as {M0.he}{F0.she} succumbs to end-stage Rabid Rodent Fever. </Text>
  <Text Key="A6511252">Death by Rabid Rodent Fever</Text>
  <Text Key="24F03918">You're showing symptoms of Rabid Rodent Fever? That disease is very dangerous! In time, you'll become contagious and spread the disease to nearby Sims. If left untreated, it's known to result in death!\n\nYou should use a computer to order the Rabid Rodent Serum... one sip and you'll be cured. You can also order an inoculation to help prevent future outbreaks.</Text>
  <Text Key="E7324A8F">Ask About Rabid Rodent Fever</Text>
  <Text Key="39EB8128">{1.ObjectName} is busy; come back later.</Text>
  <Text Key="25455E39">Increases {1.ObjectName}'s Relationship.</Text>
  <Text Key="6FAFD930">The habitat is not dirty.</Text>
  <Text Key="C14F969B">Clean Habitat</Text>
  <Text Key="FAA83653">Feed Treat</Text>
  <Text Key="A7B05B74">Feed IQ Limiter Treat</Text>
  <Text Key="FEE113C2">Increases {1.ObjectName}'s Hunger, Attention, and Relationship.</Text>
  <Text Key="8C9A75CE">Feed Anti-Aging Treat</Text>
  <Text Key="846DEE5A">Increases {1.ObjectName}'s Hunger and Relationship.</Text>
  <Text Key="71FD310B">The habitat already has food.</Text>
  <Text Key="39BEFB86">Fill Food</Text>
  <Text Key="E25C7DF2">{0.ObjectName} is showing signs of growing old... \n\nIf you're interested, vet clinics sell an anti-aging treat that permanently halts the aging process.</Text>
  <Text Key="22780F4C">Use Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="E5C7743D">Use Sand Bath</Text>
  <Text Key="9BDD0206">Use Tunnel</Text>
  <Text Key="AA210007">Use Wheel</Text>
  <Text Key="809F30C7">{0.ObjectName} is very hungry! Without food, this rodent may not make it much longer! Fill its food bowl, or feed it a treat.</Text>
  <Text Key="95FAAACD">{0.ObjectName} passed away due to starvation... Perhaps you're not ready for the responsibility of caring for a little life.</Text>
  <Text Key="0A25EF54">Purchase Rodent</Text>
  <Text Key="9FFC79E9">Spread Rodent Fear</Text>
  <Text Key="923D9D84">Increases {1.ObjectName}'s Attention.</Text>
  <Text Key="E222B4B4">Observe</Text>
  <Text Key="76EC163B">Increases {1.ObjectName}'s Attention, Activity, and Relationship.</Text>
  <Text Key="0FE95CC1">Play With</Text>
  <Text Key="A484D96E">Set your rodent free to live in the wild.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF12D1F3">Release</Text>
  <Text Key="D86F61DE">Study Rodent</Text>
  <Text Key="3498F016">Talk To</Text>
  <Text Key="E858CD4F">Ask About Day</Text>
  <Text Key="F453B27C">Ask About Rodents</Text>
  <Text Key="89A895CE">Call Names</Text>
  <Text Key="CBCA5FB3">Tell Secret to {1.ObjectName}</Text>
  <Text Key="B321BEDD">Yell At</Text>
  <Text Key="E9B7AE11">Thanks for ordering! The Rabid Rodent Fever cure that {0.SimFirstName} purchased can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="7415EEF7">Purchase Rodent Remedies</Text>
  <Text Key="D2380795">Thanks for ordering! The rodent treats that {0.SimFirstName} purchased can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B13AE33">Purchase Rodent Treats</Text>
  <Text Key="052BB573">Give this rodent a new name...</Text>
  <Text Key="1FC78801">Name Your Critter</Text>
  <Text Key="81417EA0">Rename</Text>
  <Text Key="E9254DE0">Run in Fear</Text>
  <Text Key="F0F54AC7">Sleeptime Pals</Text>
  <Text Key="4FAEBF8B">Hamster's Playground</Text>
  <Text Key="72576032">Casually Catty</Text>
  <Text Key="E9B5DEAD">Hammy</Text>
  <Text Key="F7514226">After a good long life filled with treats and scritches, {0.ObjectName} has succumbed to old age and passed away.</Text>
  <Text Key="5B858D94">{0.ObjectName}'s miniature rocket launches have resulted in a lucrative asteroid mining operation. It's graciously placed some of the space minerals it returned with inside the household's inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="74869412">Tiny Space Delivery</Text>
  <Text Key="AA5357C7">The doctors at the Sacred Spleen Memorial Hospital wish to express their gratitude to {0.ObjectName}. 2018 will be remembered in medical history as the year that a fully functioning ear was grown on {0.ObjectName}'s back, which was then transferred to a Sim suffering from anotia. Here's to you, {0.ObjectName}!</Text>
  <Text Key="8ADB22F2">...was that music coming from {0.ObjectName}'s habitat? That rodent is showing how far critters have come since the hamster dances of the aughties!</Text>
  <Text Key="2D4420CC">Rodent Rave</Text>
  <Text Key="16EE0FD6">Ghostwritten under the pseudonym Stephen Rat King, "Redundant Rodent Realities: The Life &amp; Times of {0.ObjectName}" continues to chart on the San Myshuno Times best sellers list. The books publisher, Printed Arts, is thrilled to deliver this royalty payment and express their eager anticipation for "Stephen's" upcoming novel.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF1DD1F0">Book Royalties Received</Text>
  <Text Key="75A0F05F">At FutureSim Labs, we thought we needed to conduct tests on guinea pigs in the name of scientific advancement, but it was a different kind of rodent that showed us the way. Our deepest gratitude to {0.ObjectName} for assisting in our breakthrough discovery!</Text>
  <Text Key="BABFD7FD">Thank You, {0.ObjectName}</Text>
  <Text Key="AE125A0B">{0.ObjectName} brought you a postcard from its grand adventure. This little rodent traveled an awfully long way!</Text>
  <Text Key="CF79817F">{0.ObjectName} was thinking about you during its travels, and brought a postcard back to share!</Text>
  <Text Key="727A229B">Tiny Rodent; Big Adventure</Text>
  <Text Key="34FA82B5">Anyone seen a rodent around here? Goes by the name {0.ObjectName}? Let 'em know that Don Landgraab is looking for a payment, if they want to continue to feel "protected".</Text>
  <Text Key="D0F1F137">Times Up, {0.ObjectName}</Text>
  <Text Key="9E14027E">Trace signatures of radiation seem to be lingering by {0.ObjectName}'s habitat. Thankfully readings are low enough to pose no danger to Sims. Just what kind of trouble is that rodent getting into?</Text>
  <Text Key="755B6F58">Nuclear Blast Detected</Text>
  <Text Key="8084433D">Fascinating... {0.ObjectName} appears to be conducting experiments on reaching escape velocity from its habitat.</Text>
  <Text Key="5E7DF07F">3... 2... 1... Blastoff</Text>
  <Text Key="E7B0A8FE">Attention: &lt;font color='#3AAF69'&gt;Content&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="EC334EA5">Attention: &lt;font color='#EC262E'&gt;Low&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="7493D8A3">Hunger: &lt;font color='#3AAF69'&gt;Full&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="5232ACDE">Hunger: Okay</Text>
  <Text Key="32181CA8">Hunger: &lt;font color='#EC262E'&gt;Starving&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="6BFD7EAE">Activity: &lt;font color='#EC262E'&gt;Low&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="7C2074D9">Activity: &lt;font color='#3AAF69'&gt;Content&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="A605C17B">Thimble</Text>
  <Text Key="2E00110D">Whiskers</Text>
  <Text Key="7A454927">Bubalus</Text>
  <Text Key="251E88B7">{0.ObjectCatalogDescription}</Text>
  <Text Key="BA619D2E">Cheat Rodent Activity</Text>
  <Text Key="8CE34212">Clean a Rodent Cage</Text>
  <Text Key="A90423EA">Select a dirty Rodent Cage and Clean Habitat.</Text>
  <Text Key="A25F98CF">Feed a Rodent</Text>
  <Text Key="A34BB9C1">Select a Rodent Cage and Fill Food or Feed Treat.</Text>
  <Text Key="8569917B">Play With a Rodent</Text>
  <Text Key="ADE1FC95">Select a Rodent Cage and then Play With.</Text>
  <Text Key="0246736E">(Transmissible Rodent Disease)</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>