<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="163AF9F4">Reminiscent of centuries past, nothing compares to this spandrel's authentic and intricate carvings. Use it anywhere to add a touch of noble charm to your grand estate.</Text>
  <Text Key="A650685B">Gothic Spandrel</Text>
  <Text Key="AF68954C">Many consider columns a mere architectural element, but this impressive column begs to differ. Use it as an ornate accent, or place it on corners for added flair.</Text>
  <Text Key="6DD2E303">Compound Column</Text>
  <Text Key="DEAE6D69">The perfect pairing with the "Battlement Frieze," a castle wouldn't be complete without this brilliant set! In days long past, these battlements were used for defensive purposes, and insults would often be cast down for smelling of "elderberries." Nowadays, it's used just for decoration, and it's become a staple of castle architecture.</Text>
  <Text Key="8934164C">Battlement Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="537B107E">"Wherefore art thou?" In your castle, of course! Honor your castle halls and balconies with this elegant handrail. Its ornate curves and carved details are fit for the finest castles.</Text>
  <Text Key="7B981001">Heirloom Handrail</Text>
  <Text Key="5603B3DE">Weathered Stone Pavers</Text>
  <Text Key="F67CE670">This embellished stone trim is used as a final touch for an authentic castle look. </Text>
  <Text Key="C0A2091F">Embellished Castle Trim</Text>
  <Text Key="E2E7DC7A">Your castle will stand tall and proud when you use the Cornerstone Castle Foundation! This stone block foundation creates a solid base for your castle, guaranteed to stand the test of time. With this foundation, your charming structure will stay beautiful for generations to come.</Text>
  <Text Key="C48BFA25">Cornerstone Castle Foundation</Text>
  <Text Key="56358C10">The perfect pairing with the "Battlement Fence," a castle wouldn't be complete without this brilliant set! Line your sturdy castle walls with stone corbels for added sophistication. This storied architectural element adds depth, interest, and tradition to any castle.</Text>
  <Text Key="3DE65F3F">Battlement Frieze</Text>
  <Text Key="BEF88E99">Many centuries ago, the Earls of Yore commissioned this dramatic and imposing oak door with the intention of creating a grand entrance for any room. The result is an impressive set of oak doors paired with intricate stone carvings. These doors will make any visitor aspire to be a castle owner!</Text>
  <Text Key="ABA8791C">The Earls' Double Door</Text>
  <Text Key="70A89E52">The Noble's Entrance was designed for the owner of a castle. It marked the home and the entire estate with a sense of dignity and grandeur. Today's homeowner will find pride in this door, knowing it has served as a grand entryway for generations.</Text>
  <Text Key="731E5E6D">The Noble's Entrance</Text>
  <Text Key="31D581C5">Crafted in the style of traditional castle architecture, "The Arch of Ages" brings a dash of charm to your home's interior halls or grand outer courtyard. With historic stone detailing and a weathered finish, this arch evokes the grandeur of a bygone era.</Text>
  <Text Key="71016AC0">The Arch of Ages</Text>
  <Text Key="C6B39E86">Usher in the feeling of a revered castle estate with this exquisite Portcullis Entryway. This impressive archway originally served as the well-guarded entrance to a castle's grounds. Now, it only serves as a decorative reminder of days past.</Text>
  <Text Key="33616519">Portcullis Entryway</Text>
  <Text Key="968D8FB0">The Earls' Door is an homage to those who once lived in great castles. Crafted from the finest oak, shaped by hand, and finished with intricate carvings and dark veneer, this door speaks to the past and the future, reminding us that we must honor our roots while striving for the next great generation.</Text>
  <Text Key="A82EE25F">The Earls' Door</Text>
  <Text Key="C39E74A8">A finely carved stone plaque from the notable "Yore" period. The artistry of this historic piece is unparalleled, and the crest bears unique symbols that represent an ideal of virtue of the castle's family. Display it proudly as a reminder of your family's honor and glory!</Text>
  <Text Key="064B33C7">Heraldic Crest of Yore</Text>
  <Text Key="6F5BBFD3">If you're well acquainted with keeping secrets from prying eyes, this wall sculpture is for you. Otherwise, take heed; this historic sculpture of an eavesdropping llama is known to listen in on your deepest, darkest secrets. Historians agree that "mystery still surrounds this piece."</Text>
  <Text Key="BFBE3A82">The Eavesdropping Llama </Text>
  <Text Key="F9571B24">"OMG, it's my lady. Oh wow, it's my crush!
If only she knew how amazing she is, I - aaahhhh!
Oh no, Ah! Ouch! I fell into a thorny bush!
I hope she finds it funny and doesn't think I'm a klutz,
But hey, at least I'll have a hilarious story to tell her later, so now hush!"</Text>
  <Text Key="13FE4B6B">"Catch a Glimpse" Window</Text>
  <Text Key="17CA621A">This small casement window features a lovely leaded glass design with an accentuated stone trim. The elegance of this historic window will bring a charming touch to any home.\n\n&lt;i&gt;Hint: Toggle to quarter-tile placement mode with "F5" for extra precision when placing windows together.&lt;/i&gt;
</Text>
  <Text Key="38EC7745">Earls' Casement Window</Text>
  <Text Key="FDBA8365">This tall casement window features a lovely leaded glass design with an accentuated stone trim. The elegance of this historic window will bring a charming touch to any home.\n\n&lt;i&gt;Hint: Toggle to quarter-tile placement mode with "F5" for extra precision when placing windows together.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="3CDD79E0">Earls' Casement Window - Tall</Text>
  <Text Key="A560F665">Beautiful windows like these are all but gone from the 21st century. This charming window features a classic arched design, ornate leaded glass pattern, and exquisite stone details. Elevate your home and transport yourself to days long past.\n\n&lt;i&gt;Hint: Toggle to quarter-tile placement mode with "F5" for extra precision when placing windows together.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="141062E0">Earls' Arched Window</Text>
  <Text Key="A3E48314">Beautiful windows like these are all but gone from the 21st century. This charming window features a classic arched design, ornate leaded glass pattern, and exquisite stone details. Elevate your home and transport yourself to days long past.\n\n&lt;i&gt;Hint: Toggle to quarter-tile placement mode with "F5" for extra precision when placing windows together.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="30A7A1FB">Earls' Arched Window - Tall</Text>
  <Text Key="F87F600D">The Earls' Grand Window is a testament to the artistry and skills of craftsmen who lived centuries ago. This opulent window is made of glass encased in lead, and fixed to a stone frame. The result is a stunning window that can only be produced by the most experienced hands in the land.\n\n&lt;i&gt;Hint: Toggle to quarter-tile placement mode with "F5" for extra precision when placing windows together.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="35524F58">Earls' Grand Window</Text>
  <Text Key="50216D42">The Earls' Grand Window is a testament to the artistry and skills of craftsmen who lived centuries ago. This opulent window is made of glass encased in lead, and fixed to a stone frame. The result is a stunning window that can only be produced by the most experienced hands in the land.\n\n&lt;i&gt;Hint: Toggle to quarter-tile placement mode with "F5" for extra precision when placing windows together.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="24411A3D">Earls' Grand Window - Tall</Text>
  <Text Key="E8321388">Grand Sitting Room</Text>
  <Text Key="8A563130">This historic banister has survived many generations, which makes one wonder…what did people wear? How did they talk? How was their life different from ours today? We may never know; all you can do is look at banisters like this with awe and wonder.</Text>
  <Text Key="E75C0EDF">Heirloom Banister</Text>
  <Text Key="93E53576">Add a touch of history to your space with the Heirloom Stairs. Hand-carved from solid stone, these stairs are rumored to have survived centuries of use by nobility, so they will surely last you for many more generations to come!</Text>
  <Text Key="7E3025A9">Heirloom Stairs</Text>
  <Text Key="63972217">Historic Stone Bricks</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>