<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="0D83B63A">Each artist is merely one member of an ever-evolving legacy of artists that have come before them, and this variety of sketches and studies showcases this never-ending legacy.</Text>
  <Text Key="18B25EE5">Sketches and Studies of Studies</Text>
  <Text Key="18771FE6">The CreativePro Tablet puts all the dynamic tools and mediums of a professional artist in the palm of your hand! It features a sleek travel case and tons of battery life, so who knows where your art will take you (or where you will take it!).</Text>
  <Text Key="3A37E1F9">The CreativePro Tablet</Text>
  <Text Key="954448B6">This light is perfect for when you need that perfect angle of light for your next still life or portrait painting. Your next masterpiece is only a set of brush strokes away!</Text>
  <Text Key="4DF569E9">Industrial Spotlight</Text>
  <Text Key="BDCDC1B8">With The Rolling Easel, you have the flexibility and storage space for all your artistic needs. With a built-in drawer and storage shelf, you're fully equipped to zone out and paint endlessly for hours... or days.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB3D5CB7">The Rolling Easel by Independent Expressions Inc. </Text>
  <Text Key="23C6FD54">When creating art and perfecting your craft, sometimes the unexpected objects are the most interesting. Use this thrown-together display to make your own still-life creations! Will you paint an arrangement of stunning plants, bowls of fruits, or perhaps some gemstones? The possibilities are endless! </Text>
  <Text Key="50E4A13B">Improvised Studio Pedestal</Text>
  <Text Key="6BF08B23">When the artist is at work, no surface is safe from haphazardly placed brushes, palettes, and that scrupulous cup of dirty paint water. DO NOT mistake the dirty water for your cup of tea... </Text>
  <Text Key="57EA12F2">"Anything's a Surface" Pedestal</Text>
  <Text Key="8F4EB73B">These splatters may have been unplanned, but what do you see? A face, a shape? Is it accidental or a message from the universe? </Text>
  <Text Key="68FBDA9A">Accidental Paint Splatters</Text>
  <Text Key="221497ED">Drapery is an iconic part of classical and fine art. Use this backdrop for a still life, or pose your family in front of it to paint the perfect family portrait!</Text>
  <Text Key="063D2FB8">Studio Drape Backdrop</Text>
  <Text Key="73BCCDD4">Why are they discounted, you may ask? Well, you went to the hardware store and stumbled upon an impressive set of unwanted paints at an exceptional price. Naturally, you took advantage of the deal. Then, you came home, only to realize the unending buckets of paint already in your studio. Still, you saved some money! So, the cycle continues as you tell yourself you'll make use of them someday...</Text>
  <Text Key="73642ABB">Discounted Paint Cans</Text>
  <Text Key="CC6629BD">The artist who created this masterpiece went to great lengths. They learned the fundamental steps to creating a masterpiece: first, the artist visualized their concept before embracing the marble, washing the marble, and then becoming the marble!  </Text>
  <Text Key="34765B28">Torso in Repose</Text>
  <Text Key="1237FB84">When you have this many brushes, you'll use anything for storage. Is it an excuse to hold on to that sentimental mug that you couldn't let go of? Maybe! But at least it's a sustainable and warm reminder of precious memories.</Text>
  <Text Key="BEABB74B">Odds and Ends Brush Storage</Text>
  <Text Key="8C6C43E2">A pile of sketchbooks like this encapsulates an artist's complete body of work. To some, this stack is more than its weight in gold!</Text>
  <Text Key="E734AD5D">Collection of Sketchbooks</Text>
  <Text Key="DA196B19">An excerpt from Classical Images in Art:\n&lt;i&gt;"The forlorn pitcher, accompanied by a bounty of fruits, turns away and opposes its very existence. Why is it forlorn, and why does this image continue to haunt artists? We're unsure, but that pitcher's bombastic side eye captivated the world."&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="CD63669C">The Forlorn Pitcher</Text>
  <Text Key="B3888F4C">Ah, the lily—a potent and symbolic image in many cultures. How will you choose to represent it in your work? Will it be fresh, fragrant, and lush to comment on the beauty of nature, or will you pursue its dried and withering counterpart to reflect on the essence of life itself? </Text>
  <Text Key="CA5DB103">Lilium Mortem</Text>
  <Text Key="1454108E">Is it weird to think these little paint tubes cost exorbitantly more than the palettes themselves?</Text>
  <Text Key="065212B1">Painter's Palettes</Text>
  <Text Key="4F2ED13A">Stow away your possessions and favorite hoodie to keep them free of paint splatters and accidental spills because art is inevitably messy. Did you really have to hang a paint can from the ceiling and let it drip everywhere? Of course you did!</Text>
  <Text Key="BA02BFE5">Pollock's Storage Locker</Text>
  <Text Key="F432CF77">For all your creativity needs, look no further than the "Ready, Set, Gogh!" Cart! This rolling cart is built with industrial steel and metal casters for durability and sturdiness. With enough storage space for bins, paints, brushes, and more, you'll have all you need to create a work of art without ever stepping away from your easel. </Text>
  <Text Key="2C3582CE">"Ready, Set, Gogh!" Cart</Text>
  <Text Key="D0B5A1D4">Nothing says "you're a professional artist" more than this cabinet! It has everything you need to store your treasured supplies, including rows of paper and canvas storage, small drawers for paint tubes, and a stylish glass panel.</Text>
  <Text Key="A18E66BB">The Companion Cabinet by .ECT</Text>
  <Text Key="A7669A68">Do you need more space in your art studio? Why not use a step ladder up? Those steps may have been meant for something other than your sketchbooks and art supplies, but they do the job. After all, isn't creative solutions what art is all about? </Text>
  <Text Key="40909187">The Step-Ladder Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="1AF4DED5">Like a trusted companion, this storage cabinet will dry your precious works of art and supply new canvases for your next great masterpiece. It even holds everything else in between! It's genuinely a "catch-all", yet you'll soon find it essential. </Text>
  <Text Key="A3A6B2F0">The Rolling Drying Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="F2643C49">Who doesn't love storage? This cabinet is no exception! It is filled to the brim with paints, brushes, and even a well-loved artist's smock. </Text>
  <Text Key="5FF998AC">Storage Savy Smock Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="8A1FC737">First encountered in the school art room, this sink continues to be a staple for the duration of an artist's life. No matter the place or time, one will always find a set of unwashed brushes, a trash can overflowing with scrapped drawings, and an inevitably clogged sink. This sink is notorious and ever-present... perhaps it should be placed on a pedestal in an art gallery now?</Text>
  <Text Key="25EDAB8E">The Notorious Slop Sink</Text>
  <Text Key="1213A935">From the brand that brought you the original, KraftMatic Woodworking Table 2.0 delivers an exceptional workspace for all your woodworking needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="859664D0">KraftMatic Woodworking Table 2.0</Text>
  <Text Key="4E05E5D3">The Artist's Studio</Text>
  <Text Key="D161D3A3">"Down to the Studs" Wall</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>