<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="67C0F73A">(Getting a Photo on a Magazine Cover)</Text>
  <Text Key="77FE1B51">(From Posting a Photo to Fashion Simstagram)</Text>
  <Text Key="91C6B75F">(Getting a Selfie with a Style Influencer)</Text>
  <Text Key="776BD434">(From Chatting with a Style Influencer on a PC)</Text>
  <Text Key="CE74EB38">The lighting, the angle, the contrast, they're all perfect! This is a great photo for a magazine cover. The client will review your submission and return the photo via snail mail, so be sure to check your mailbox.</Text>
  <Text Key="732DCC03">(From Editing Photos)</Text>
  <Text Key="9BFBC87A">(Posing for a Photo)</Text>
  <Text Key="C744B27C">(From Presenting Photos to a Style Influencer)</Text>
  <Text Key="3D55D9D5">Rejection is never easy. The client doesn't feel this photo is the right fit. Can you submit a different photograph?</Text>
  <Text Key="7432E4C0">The client has approved your photo! What a fantastic shot. Approved photos arrive in the mail in the next one or two days, so check your mailbox then post the photo online to Fashion Simstagram.</Text>
  <Text Key="D1672433">(From Submitting Photos for Client's Approval)</Text>
  <Text Key="310FF44A">{0.SimFirstName} has submitted a photo for Approval.</Text>
  <Text Key="713A7277">(From Taking a Photo with a Camera Tripod)</Text>
  <Text Key="F920C791">You're in the big leagues now!</Text>
  <Text Key="870781E4">Cover Photo!</Text>
  <Text Key="3D9486DA">Recognition from the digital world of fashion.</Text>
  <Text Key="EDFE2405">Fashion Simstagram</Text>
  <Text Key="BFA8F894">Pleasing a client fills me with professional pride.</Text>
  <Text Key="F9980A7B">Freelance Photos</Text>
  <Text Key="1FE402DF">Working with the best of the best to bring fashion to the world.</Text>
  <Text Key="67BEB786">Influenced Fashion Photos</Text>
  <Text Key="3A651888">Approval makes you glow with pride.</Text>
  <Text Key="D40C8A27">The Influenced Photos</Text>
  <Text Key="978663FA">Speaking with famous influencers is motivating and inspiring.</Text>
  <Text Key="0E69F8A5">Influencer Style</Text>
  <Text Key="99DE2101">Quick touchup for a perfect mood enabling photo</Text>
  <Text Key="EC54F834">Photo Editor</Text>
  <Text Key="6D691765">Sometimes things don't go as planned...</Text>
  <Text Key="05BCF5E0">Fashion Simstagram</Text>
  <Text Key="9DADBF25">Tripods really help to keep the camera steady and eyes focused.</Text>
  <Text Key="C96646A0">Steady Eye</Text>
  <Text Key="0558BC6E">So excited to see how the photo turns out!</Text>
  <Text Key="C2D56911">Can't Wait to See!</Text>
  <Text Key="1862D323">This is not my good side...</Text>
  <Text Key="F49E6AF2">Not My Good Side</Text>
  <Text Key="8BEC605A">Why is it taking so long?</Text>
  <Text Key="6AC37885">Take the Picture!</Text>
  <Text Key="C7E57070">Fashion Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="E929B5DE">{0.SimFirstName} has been recognized for great performance and client satisfaction. Dealing with the fickle clients and finger cramps were worth it in the end. In addition to raising {F0.her}{M0.his} rate, {0.SimFirstName} also received rewards!\n\n{7.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="CF251449">Over Guard creates a superior product that supports the needs of top tier athletes. Unfortunately, they mostly sell to Sims whose longest hike is from the couch to the fridge. Help them adjust their image with photos of average Sims in Athletic Wear.</Text>
  <Text Key="55AFC94A">Athletic Wear for the Couch Potato</Text>
  <Text Key="78A4E122">{0.SimName} really captured what the brand is all about in a terrific photo. The brand will keep {0.SimName} in mind for future social media campaigns.</Text>
  <Text Key="4BABFEA5">The client is pleased with {0.SimName}'s photos, or so they say. They promise {0.SimName} more work, but {0.SimName} never hears from them again.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C09E256">After looking at the comments online the client wonders if {0.SimName} was really paying attention to what the brand was all about. Displeased, they have canceled {0.SimName}'s contract.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB8B5E12">Titanium Teens Athletic Apparel needs a photo of Sims in Athletic Wear, illustrating how sports build friendships...and rivalries.</Text>
  <Text Key="1695C91B">Titanium Teens Athletic Apparel</Text>
  <Text Key="608C6D25">{0.SimName}'s photo pleased the client so they sent over a thank you card featuring the company's motto, "Success is sweet, and sweat is success." Athletic apparel sure is weird. </Text>
  <Text Key="980F328A">The client finds {0.SimName}'s work acceptable, but ultimately they are underwhelmed. Don't expect any future gigs from them. </Text>
  <Text Key="D7B090E8">Demonstrate your skills as a photographer of high fashion by matching the perfect outfit with the perfect background using the Fashion Studio Backdrop.</Text>
  <Text Key="A89A6C4D">Set the Stage</Text>
  <Text Key="F08A8F39">Photography Level 3</Text>
  <Text Key="62EAE2FA">The client sends a terse e-mail declaring {0.SimName}'s work an absolute disaster. They say that {0.SimName} has damaged their brand image, and they threaten to sue, oh no!</Text>
  <Text Key="0D16C82B">The brand's sales have doubled over night thanks to the viral success of {0.SimName}'s photo. The client is very pleased and promises to send a muffin basket as thanks. Sadly, the basket arrives, but someone has eaten all the muffins...</Text>
  <Text Key="479C3634">A famous model, Adrianna Tapir, admires {0.SimName}'s photo and friends {0.SimName} on Simstagram! Thanks to Adrianna the photo is a viral success and the client is quite pleased.</Text>
  <Text Key="CCE457BB">The esteemed Estella Landgraab demands a flawless photo of Sims in a Fashion Pose. Don't let her down.</Text>
  <Text Key="733AF5B0">Estella Landgraab Fashions</Text>
  <Text Key="FC226719">The photo went viral...for all the wrong reasons. The client's brand has been damaged, and {0.SimName}'s imagery has been immortalized as a meme used by forum trolls. </Text>
  <Text Key="14D55C54">A famous movie star loves {0.SimName}'s photo and shared it on her Simstagram, rocketing the client's brand to new heights of fame!</Text>
  <Text Key="6200B043">{0.SimName}'s photo gets a moderate amount of likes and shares, and the client is pleased. They send {M0.him}{F0.her} an e-mail praising {M0.his}{F0.her} work accompanied by a smiley face.</Text>
  <Text Key="362A9686">Stylish Sims need to be stylish when going out on the town, or when taking out the trash. Put together some shots of a great Everyday outfit with Sims in a Thoughtful Pose.</Text>
  <Text Key="C07EF6C7">Casual and Stylish</Text>
  <Text Key="BB94D124">What a disaster! {0.SimName}'s photo was not well received and the client is insulting {0.SimName} on a public forum. </Text>
  <Text Key="640D27C1">{0.SimName}'s photo receives such a positive response that the client decides to use it for their international marketing campaign. There is no extra pay, but it is great exposure for {0.SimName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA50BD56">{0.SimName}'s photo is nominally successful online, but is quickly forgotten as the masses move on to the next big thing. The client is pleased with {0.SimName}'s work.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CA7C256">Looking to upscale their brand a fashion website has asked for photographs of up and coming styles that will appeal to the socialites in San Myshuno. Think bold and bright with upscale prices. Take a photo of Sims in Formal Wear and deliver it ASAP.</Text>
  <Text Key="5A24DB77">Mostly Fashionable Formals</Text>
  <Text Key="3BF88C5B">Photography Level 2</Text>
  <Text Key="46C455B4">{0.SimName} receives an angry phone call from the client. The client hates {0.SimName}'s photo and refuses to work with {0.SimName} again.</Text>
  <Text Key="DCB94371">A fashion blogger comes across {0.SimName}'s photo and shares it with her millions of Simstagram followers rocketing the brand to success. The client is very pleased and praises {0.SimName}'s skill with the camera.</Text>
  <Text Key="24C54D46">The client is pleased with {0.SimName}'s photo, and they promise to send {0.SimName} a fruit basket as a thank you. Unfortunately, the fruit basket never arrives.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C1A5161">Lights! Camera! Action! A blockbuster in the making, Secrets and Simoleons is looking for photos of Young Adult Sims in Formal Wear to use in the background on set.</Text>
  <Text Key="AD6205F2">Secrets and Simoleons</Text>
  <Text Key="9315B563">{0.SimName}'s photo is mocked online causing irreparable damage to the client's brand, forcing them to lay off thirty percent of their staff world wide. {0.SimName} feels bad for the newly unemployed workers and cries about it in the bath.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A010E3A">{0.SimName}'s photo is a huge success! The client loves it and the company president calls {0.SimName} to express her gratitude.</Text>
  <Text Key="E0F18B1D">The client is pleased with {0.SimName}'s work and tells {0.SimName} so via a colorful email filled with cat pictures. It is not very professional, but it makes {0.SimName} happy.</Text>
  <Text Key="9C5B6D7C">Little Darlings Formal Attire is seeking to build positive brand awareness after an unfortunate social media snafu involving a squirrel and a tangerine. Snap some stylish photos of Children in Formal Wear that will put the brand back on top.</Text>
  <Text Key="C28F5779">Little Darlings Formal Attire</Text>
  <Text Key="C99A61E6">What a disaster! A vocal vlogger with questionable taste tells the whole world why he finds {0.SimName}'s photo offensive, and an online petition calling for the company to remove the photo from their social media has 10,236 signatures by the end of the day.</Text>
  <Text Key="7A21C407">Couture culture blogger Cindi Von Simmerman raves about {0.SimName}'s photo on her weekly vlog, shooting the client's brand to instant stardom! The client is happy, and {0.SimName} is pleased that Cindi understood the overall vision of the composition.</Text>
  <Text Key="9568C840">The client is pleased with {0.SimName}'s work and thanks {0.SimName} for a job well done.</Text>
  <Text Key="26DDEEAC">Utilize Fashion Studio Lights to make your subjects glow from head to toe. All fashion and poses are acceptable, this is a play of light and shadow.</Text>
  <Text Key="9C302789">Playing With Light</Text>
  <Text Key="473BB8A0">The internet has a long memory, and so does {0.SimName}'s client...{0.SimName}'s photo is universally mocked and the client vows to ruin {0.SimName} in retaliation.</Text>
  <Text Key="2BEB625D">In 24 hours {0.SimName}'s photo has gathered nearly 1 million likes! The client is pleased and {0.SimName} feels great pride.</Text>
  <Text Key="17785E22">The photo is well received garnering over 200,000 likes in 24 hours. The client is pleased and {0.SimName} feels the joy of a job well done.</Text>
  <Text Key="65EF1B05">Photography Level 4</Text>
  <Text Key="0EB8DB47">An art dealer has asked you to utilize Fashion Studio Lights to capture a perfectly lit photo of a Sim in a Fashion Pose. If the client likes it it will be displayed in their gallery.</Text>
  <Text Key="BCC13964">Lights! Camera! Fashion!</Text>
  <Text Key="F91F53E9">A prominent fashionista insults {0.SimName}'s photo within minutes of it being posted online. Her followers rise to the occasion and down vote the photo. The client is devastated and {0.SimName} is mortified.</Text>
  <Text Key="208D7984">A fashion model from San Myshuno praises {0.SimName}'s photo and all her followers rush out to buy the client's clothing. Success!</Text>
  <Text Key="D54C63F3">Followers of the brand embrace {0.SimName}'s photo as an innovative representation of the fashion industry. The client is pleased, and {0.SimName} celebrates with a second dessert.</Text>
  <Text Key="C45E21E5">Everyday most Sims get up and put on clothes. But most Sims could stand to be a bit more...stylish. The client asks for photos of Sims in Everyday Attire to showcase that everyone can be fashionable everyday.</Text>
  <Text Key="7B60B26E">Everyday Activities Fashion Shoot</Text>
  <Text Key="A7189BEC">Photography Level 1</Text>
  <Text Key="B17A66DF">Failure has a name. It is {0.SimName}. The client is horrified by {0.SimName}'s low quality work and {0.SimName} feels deep shame.</Text>
  <Text Key="0CFE9EE6">The internet loves {0.SimName}'s photo and client rejoices at the positive reaction. Great job {0.SimName}!</Text>
  <Text Key="180F0629">The reaction to {0.SimName}'s photo is mixed, but overall it is positive. The client is pleased and promises to refer {0.SimName} to other brands.</Text>
  <Text Key="E46A3956">Genius Professor Outdoor Wear claims to be the number one brand of attire for collegiate Professors. In reality, they are a distant third. Help them boost their image and achieve excellent marks by showcasing Sims in Everyday Wear.</Text>
  <Text Key="98249077">Genius Professor Outdoor Wear Study</Text>
  <Text Key="E04E44B4">{0.SimName}'s photo is universally mocked. It starts off as just a few negative memes, but quickly enough the internet is ablaze and the brand is irreparably damaged. {0.SimName} feels shame, despair, and agony. What a world.</Text>
  <Text Key="76433271">The client is awed and delighted when {0.SimName}'s photo is nominated for a Simsational Fashion Simstagram award for best photo composition. Free publicity for your brand is the best kind of publicity.</Text>
  <Text Key="BE4F3C46">{0.SimName}'s photo doesn't get a lot of shares, but it does garner a good amount of likes. The client is pleased and promises to keep {0.SimName} in mind for future opportunities.</Text>
  <Text Key="1DE61E71">Our client needs fun and flirty shots for their upcoming Love Day magazine spread. Show off your skills by selecting appropriate attire and direct your models to use only Flirty Poses.</Text>
  <Text Key="E89342E2">Fun and Flirty</Text>
  <Text Key="B2EF56D3">{0.SimName} has made a lot of poor choices in life, but nothing compares to posting this awful photo online. What was {0.SimName} thinking?! The client is displeased and {0.SimName} is embarrassed.</Text>
  <Text Key="1DFF934A">Everything {0.SimName} has ever experienced pales in comparison to the pride and joy {0.SimName} feels when the photo goes viral. The client is impressed with {0.SimName}'s work, and the brand's sales triple over the course of the week.</Text>
  <Text Key="2BD027AD">Success! The internet likes {0.SimName}'s photo and the client is pleased. Good job.</Text>
  <Text Key="6143FCAA">Every Day Excitement promotes excitement through relaxation. Because what is more exciting than an opportunity to relax! The client requests a photo of a Sim in fashionable Everyday Wear in a Relaxed Pose. </Text>
  <Text Key="AA40D4C3">Every Day Excitement</Text>
  <Text Key="805657DE">Failure...{0.SimName} will do better next time. If there is a next time. The client is horrified by {0.SimName}'s shoddy work and posts a scathing rant online denouncing {0.SimName}'s skills, looks, and mother.</Text>
  <Text Key="13490B2F">The fashion, the lighting, the model - every aspect of {0.SimName}'s photo is perfect and the online masses take notice! The client is enjoying a rise in popularity and praises {0.SimName}'s work.</Text>
  <Text Key="75B2D588">{0.SimName}'s photo is okay. Not great, but okay. The client is happy enough, but the internet largely ignores it. {0.SimName} will do better next time.</Text>
  <Text Key="4A82B82F">A shadowy fashionista says you'll get more likes if you post a photo to your Fashion Simstagram of a Sim in a Goofy Pose wearing a Party Outfit.</Text>
  <Text Key="33DC34FC">Goofy Party Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="768715F1">The client hates {0.SimName}'s photo and denounces {0.SimName} as a fraud without an ounce of photography talent. Ouch.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF495C9C">The client loves {0.SimName}'s photos and so does the Simstagram community. {0.SimName} gains recognition online as a top tier fashion photographer.</Text>
  <Text Key="5AEC756B">It won't win any awards, but {0.SimName}'s photo is a solidly average entry in the field of online fashion photography.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F2E9302">Jazzed for Jammies has an image problem. Their name brings the impression of too much energy! They need photos of Sims in Sleep Wear to convey relaxation and comfort for their spring catalog.</Text>
  <Text Key="8EC655AB">Jazzed for Jammies Spring Catalog</Text>
  <Text Key="9D3B68E8">Did {0.SimName} really post that?! The client is angry and {0.SimName} is embarrassed. What was {0.SimName} thinking?</Text>
  <Text Key="8BBAC735">Never in the history of online fashion photography has a photo received so many likes! Well, in recent memory anyways. {0.SimName} did a fabulous job and the client is very pleased.</Text>
  <Text Key="EB93B75A">It could have been better, but it could have been worse. At the end of the day {0.SimName}'s photo has more likes than dislikes, so the client is pleased and thanks {0.SimName} for the hard work.</Text>
  <Text Key="90F95AA5">The latest episode of Growing Up Crumplebottom sparked unexpected interest in a line of pajamas by CozyThreads. They need a quick photoshoot of models in cozy Sleep Wear.</Text>
  <Text Key="CD84BE2E">Silver Screen Sleep Wear</Text>
  <Text Key="36CA171F">Worst. Photo. Ever. The client is not happy, the internet is mocking the brand, and overall it is a disaster. Better luck next time {0.SimName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="A8A34FA6">Likes and shares for {0.SimName}'s photo increase daily and show no sign of slowing down. The client is thrilled and salutes {0.SimName} as a worthy partner for their brand.</Text>
  <Text Key="C65D1FE9">{0.SimName}'s photo is well received, though not widely circulated. The client is pleased with {0.SimName}'s work and promises to send over some free clothes. Sadly, they never arrive. Oh well.</Text>
  <Text Key="81CD12D2">Work with a Style Influencer to create the perfect photo capturing fresh and fun fashions from next season's lines. You have creative freedom to choose your own clothing and photo subjects.</Text>
  <Text Key="66C102DB">Finding the Style</Text>
  <Text Key="DC374106">Working with a Style Influencer should have made this an easy assignment to complete...what happened?</Text>
  <Text Key="F4761F27">Working with such a talented Style Influencer and fashion photographer has made this one of the most successful social media postings of all time! Fantastic work!</Text>
  <Text Key="9C86C2E0">Seems the Style Influencer's suggestions clashed with some of the client's ideas, but the Simstagram community seems to like the photo, so all is well.</Text>
  <Text Key="0FB3CB5F">Photography Level 5</Text>
  <Text Key="C10E68D9">You've been asked to put together a glamour shot of Sims in Swim Wear. The client requests that it features Sims who look good lounging by the pool.</Text>
  <Text Key="4CA0567A">Wet or Dry Swimwear</Text>
  <Text Key="D51B696B">Samantha Seaside, the swimwear guru, says she would rather fight a seagull than wear the fashions highlighted in {0.SimName}'s photo, ouch! {0.SimName}'s reputation took a hit, and the client is facing bankruptcy...</Text>
  <Text Key="5194C6D2">The swimwear fashionista Seaside Samantha saw {0.SimName}'s photo and has praised {0.SimName}'s fashion choices on her blog, vlog, and Simstagram, wow!</Text>
  <Text Key="7E9EBDD5">Seaside Samantha, the self proclaimed Queen of Summer, gave {0.SimName}'s photo 4/5 starfish and 1 sad coconut. Not bad!</Text>
  <Text Key="19D34222">The local pool has had trouble attracting swimmers ever since that incident with the octopus got out of hand. They want to boost their image with photos of Sims having fun in Swim Wear.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6BD294B">Ad Campaign for Local Pool Venue</Text>
  <Text Key="C3C97508">Seaside Samantha, Queen of Summer and first of her name, gave {0.SimName}'s photo 0/5 starfish and 2 upside down krakens, ouch! The client is mortified and {0.SimName} has developed an irrational fear of the water.</Text>
  <Text Key="DB350755">Seaside Samantha, swimwear expert, gushes about {0.SimName}'s photo in her article, "12 Funky Bathing Suits You Must Buy Now." The masses flock to the client's Simstagram and they more than double their followers over night!</Text>
  <Text Key="FF51207A">Seaside Samantha, swimwear goddess, promotes {0.SimName}'s photo on her blog...after the client paid her to do so. The client is happy, Samantha is richer, and {0.SimName} has the satisfaction of a job well done.</Text>
  <Text Key="62E6874F">Freelance Fashion Photographer</Text>
  <Text Key="854DE168">Eye for fashion and style? Build a studio, or venture outside, and take photos of the hottest fashion trends.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF2A8842">Freelance Fashion Photographers take on different gigs to take photos for client’s fashion, advertising, and research needs. Develop photography skills and a good reputation to be selected to work with Style Influencers who represent all the best brands.</Text>
  <Text Key="334B7B3D">Freelance Fashion Photographer</Text>
  <Text Key="2D248C03">Freelance Fashion Photographer</Text>
  <Text Key="B0381E81">Post-Party Heatwave</Text>
  <Text Key="E357C7A2">Clear The Runway</Text>
  <Text Key="304F99B8">The Casualibero</Text>
  <Text Key="B17C7C7A">Mos' Fashionable</Text>
  <Text Key="7EDCB390">By: Portrait George \n\nFrom the rule of fourths to the golden trapezoid, you are ready to master all the best composition techniques. This guide will take your skills from point and shoot to full manual mode.</Text>
  <Text Key="063C3DBF">Photography Vol.2: Mastering Composition</Text>
  <Text Key="57A3A724">By: Portrait George\n\nTake time and compose your first shot. Fill the frame with the subject and keep it in focus. The most expensive camera in the world can't make up for a poorly composed photo.</Text>
  <Text Key="97E62F6B">Photography Vol.1: Your First Exposure</Text>
  <Text Key="25D90B5A">Because sometimes a bookcase isn’t a bookcase, it is an art piece.</Text>
  <Text Key="7B038985">The Tastefully Empty Bookcase</Text>
  <Text Key="03191202">Multiple books, stacked.</Text>
  <Text Key="B238A5FD">Stack of Advanced Photography Books</Text>
  <Text Key="F035D896">Multiple books, stacked.</Text>
  <Text Key="4A511049">Stack of Beginner Photography Books</Text>
  <Text Key="81402BE0">Loft living starts the moment you step through the door. This door.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0FC4A2F">Luxury Loft Sliding Door</Text>
  <Text Key="54FB74F7">Who doesn’t love free clothes? The fashionable attire and accessories are perks of the trade, but you still have to pay for the rack.</Text>
  <Text Key="9B9B7B4E">Designer Samples</Text>
  <Text Key="6C6F083C">Bright lights are the key to happiness. Assuming your happiness is dependent upon seeing stuff.</Text>
  <Text Key="EFF8C493">Fluorescent Focus Ceiling Light</Text>
  <Text Key="ED10B8EE">Because you can’t have perfect photos without perfect lighting.</Text>
  <Text Key="726BB691">Fashion Studio Lights: Perfect Photo Floor Light</Text>
  <Text Key="0D9513A0">Lighting makes or breaks a photograph, so make sure your studio has the BEST lighting in the whole wide world. Seriously, we’re the BEST. In the world. For real.</Text>
  <Text Key="0DE695EF">Fashion Studio Lights: BEST Photo Shoot Light</Text>
  <Text Key="51A31555">Sing with me: Shine shine shine your light, your neon light! Shine shine shine it bright, oh it is so bright! Shine shine shine tonight, it shines every night! Oooooo…SHINE!</Text>
  <Text Key="5FF68E70">Shine Your Neon Light</Text>
  <Text Key="BB31AEA6">When you want to visualize yourself in the thoughts of another, this mirror will do the trick.</Text>
  <Text Key="9F6ADDB9">My Own Best Thoughts Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="BDB6260C">A great conversation starter, this classy quartet looks like something you’d find at an art gallery, but really you bought it online at a discount.</Text>
  <Text Key="A6DB39C3">My First Framed Art Set</Text>
  <Text Key="C181EDEE">Hip, modern, and oh so shiny, this pedestal is the perfect perch for all your artistic acquisitions.</Text>
  <Text Key="391F4591">I’m So Shiny!</Text>
  <Text Key="9A4A83ED">Featuring a variety of fun and festive scenes and styles this backdrop is an essential for photographers who want to add some fashionable pizzazz to their photos.</Text>
  <Text Key="0EE333B8">Fashion Studio Backdrop Curved</Text>
  <Text Key="5D6391F9">These fun and festive backdrops are sure to liven up any photo shoot, and will help give your pic a visual boost that is sure to rocket you to Fashion Simstagram stardom!</Text>
  <Text Key="C85F92FC">Fashion Studio Backdrop Straight</Text>
  <Text Key="BD080729">This camera boasts the latest in camera technology and will save some weight in your gear bag. You will have to rebuy all your favorite DSLR lenses because they won't fit on this body. Those lenses were not expensive were they?</Text>
  <Text Key="9ABF420C">ClickShot P10 Mirrorless Camera</Text>
  <Text Key="7DC489F4">Unlock by maxing out the performance meter in the Freelancer career as a Freelance Photographer for the first time.</Text>
  <Text Key="57633917">Unlock by maxing out the performance meter in the Freelancer career as a Freelance Photographer for the first time.</Text>
  <Text Key="EAF4DADD">Collect and display your photos all in one frame.</Text>
  <Text Key="2B9E22C8">Collage Photo Frame</Text>
  <Text Key="53A4F557">The new way to display all of your photos while conserving wall space.</Text>
  <Text Key="7BD73C2E">MixPix Portrait Digital Photo Frame</Text>
  <Text Key="56586692">The new way to display all of your photos while conserving wall space.</Text>
  <Text Key="B389C0AD">MixPix Landscape Digital Photo Frame</Text>
  <Text Key="1CADADAA">Attach your camera and never take a blurry photo again. If that is bokeh with you.</Text>
  <Text Key="E29CAF35">Fashion Studio Photography Tripod</Text>
  <Text Key="598FB1BB">Sometimes inspiration comes from the most unlikely of places…like the rug beneath your feet.</Text>
  <Text Key="3B40C21A">Modern Muse Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="BAB4720C">Professional photos require professional tools, and every serious photographer needs a photo drape to help frame their shots. A sturdy metal frame paired with durable canvas means that this is an investment piece that will stand the test of time.</Text>
  <Text Key="70AC5DC3">Photo Drape</Text>
  <Text Key="8B2B98C8">Metal and frosted glass combine to form the pinnacle of room divider innovation.</Text>
  <Text Key="00FA3667">Frosted Glass Room Divider</Text>
  <Text Key="71DB02DC">The LiBEARian keeps your books neatly organized on any shelf.</Text>
  <Text Key="43E3C4B3">Libearian</Text>
  <Text Key="0012E9A0">Fashion trends, style tips, health advice, and semi-serious journalism detailing the horrors of modern life. Simsational Style Magazine has it all!</Text>
  <Text Key="482C37EF">Simsational Style Stack</Text>
  <Text Key="F287B7C5">This modern art piece has been known to cause breakdowns in photographers who view it. They lose the ability to compose full sentences and just mutter 'dust' 'lens caps' and 'the Glass!' to themselves.</Text>
  <Text Key="F4F62CC0">The Photographer's Irritation</Text>
  <Text Key="A3AEE91F">A wrenching expression of this artists soul. Said to be inspired by their everlong yearning for a hero.</Text>
  <Text Key="799ACBC6">The Shape and The Colour</Text>
  <Text Key="20976F52">Most photographers throw all their equipment into a bag in the corner. Not you.  You show off your accessories and keep them in pristine condition.</Text>
  <Text Key="8160016D">No Clutter Photo Accessory Organizer</Text>
  <Text Key="E3BB71B7">Most chairs have two arms, but this chair is so wonderful that maximum comfort is achieved with only one.</Text>
  <Text Key="C8E3A30E">The One-Armed Wonder</Text>
  <Text Key="75C63B53">The Sit On Me Now sofa offers two comfortable seats and one less comfortable seat. Keep your friends close, and your enemies uncomfortable.</Text>
  <Text Key="1195D502">Sit On Me Now</Text>
  <Text Key="41329F3A">Help direct your photo subjects to the right location so you can craft that perfect composition. These magic marks will not be visible in your photos.</Text>
  <Text Key="BD88C9E5">Fashion Studio Subject Mark</Text>
  <Text Key="E99326F7">Apparently this fell off the back of a roadie's truck. Their loss is your gain. This repurposed gear makes the perfect addition to your styled apartment.\n\nWhile this stack of Amps doesn't actually function, it has been known to make you feel better when playing air guitar.</Text>
  <Text Key="CA0FF14E">Amp Stack</Text>
  <Text Key="8FF6CBBC">This used to carry around the most valuable tech to all your shows. Now it is a great place to display last weeks magazines.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A95B713">Repurposed Gear Chest</Text>
  <Text Key="741FB307">Layers of laminate dominate the design of this split level coffee table.</Text>
  <Text Key="940D14BE">Laminate Layers</Text>
  <Text Key="55EBAB2D">It may look like wood and metal and glass, but this end table is made of laminate and plastic. Makes it easy to wipe clean.</Text>
  <Text Key="CD5E44F8">The Artificial End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="8AB1547D">Sometimes you need to keep the windows shut in order to keep those pesky birds and bugs and bears out.</Text>
  <Text Key="1330D8E8">Closed Loft Window</Text>
  <Text Key="9A557322">Enjoy a cool or warm or hot (yuck) breeze any time you desire with this loft window.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F2B5E9D">Breezy Loft Window</Text>
  <Text Key="BE1519ED">Whether you need a little air flow, or you just want to hear the sounds of birds and traffic, you’ll be happy to know that this loft window actually opens! Good luck getting it closed.</Text>
  <Text Key="FDF315B8">Breezy, But Tall Loft Window</Text>
  <Text Key="64E4BEC0">Stylish, and symmetrical when placed side by side, this arched window adds a modern vibe without sacrificing sunlight.</Text>
  <Text Key="9C09458F">Lofty Arched Window</Text>
  <Text Key="F8C6B144">I can't wait to see photos of today's trending styles!</Text>
  <Text Key="1E011127">Photo edited successfully!</Text>
  <Text Key="C38604EA">Oops! The edit did not quite come out as expected. Better to scrap this and start over.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF5A8433">{0.SimFirstName}'s Photo already has {1.Number} {S1.like}{P1.likes}. Wow!</Text>
  <Text Key="72935C38">{0.SimFirstName}'s Photo has {1.Number} {S1.like}{P1.likes}.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2948598">Post Photo to Fashion Simstagram</Text>
  <Text Key="CA824C56">Chat with Style Influencer {2.SimName}</Text>
  <Text Key="7838DFC3">Chat With Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="0912EAB5">12 Hours</Text>
  <Text Key="F34E5D27">24 Hours</Text>
  <Text Key="2A27C0E1">Current Setting</Text>
  <Text Key="FCB7B533">1 Hour</Text>
  <Text Key="E20F5895">3 Hours</Text>
  <Text Key="6F9FC686">6 Hours</Text>
  <Text Key="0B79971B">Requires at least one photo in the photo inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="3B9F6CC4">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished installing the digital frame upgrade.</Text>
  <Text Key="DFC3BDFC">Requires {0.SimName} to have at least one photo in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="850ADE62">You can do better than this! These photos look a little out of focus, and they could use a tad more lighting. Get back in the studio and try again.</Text>
  <Text Key="320B3705">These Photos are looking great! You have a incredible Eye for Style.</Text>
  <Text Key="0770A572">Show Off Photos</Text>
  <Text Key="5AD91573">Cameras must be in the Sim's inventory to be added to the tripod</Text>
  <Text Key="C3ECB84A">Add Camera</Text>
  <Text Key="FDCB4A4C">Sim must be standing on Subject Mark.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF0C8147">Remove Camera</Text>
  <Text Key="00E8C772">Must Add a Camera to the Tripod to take a Photo.</Text>
  <Text Key="8A0DE3BA">Take Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="2E47A5E7">Get Photo Taken</Text>
  <Text Key="696DF5B2">Set Timer</Text>
  <Text Key="603548FB">Cubical Wall</Text>
  <Text Key="F0448B5B">Red Carpet</Text>
  <Text Key="36048952">Vertical Lights</Text>
  <Text Key="88F84870">Seeing Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="C6962531">Cityscape</Text>
  <Text Key="FD0BE58E">Bigger On The Inside</Text>
  <Text Key="307B7E67">Sunlit Forest</Text>
  <Text Key="4FBBBB9C">Cotton Candy</Text>
  <Text Key="3AF0265D">Overcast</Text>
  <Text Key="FD6306EA">Forest Skyline</Text>
  <Text Key="16D88D73">Rainbow</Text>
  <Text Key="FE41F05D">Wait for Photographer</Text>
  <Text Key="F0177FA5">I am ready for my close up!</Text>
  <Text Key="E4BFA800">Approved Photos need to be in the Sim's inventory to be available for posting.</Text>
  <Text Key="489DB611">Angry</Text>
  <Text Key="A2EF4E2E">Confident</Text>
  <Text Key="E4A318C6">Flirty</Text>
  <Text Key="19316AB5">Focused</Text>
  <Text Key="B58B922A">Playful</Text>
  <Text Key="EDE0BF7E">Sad</Text>
  <Text Key="1CB90FA1">Only one magazine cover can be reviewed at a time. {0.SimFirstName} must wait until the current submission has been reviewed before submitting a new magazine cover for approval.</Text>
  <Text Key="CCA75680">Submit For Magazine Cover</Text>
  <Text Key="71E45EC8">Submit Photo For Client's Approval</Text>
  <Text Key="E8501028">Hire Fashion Subject</Text>
  <Text Key="33EFD9E9">There is already the max number of Fashion Subjects on lot.</Text>
  <Text Key="F9BD18FA">Meet with Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="41A9EEAF">Ask to Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="6F1A4710">Take Picture Of Sim With Pet</Text>
  <Text Key="861F579F">Take Picture Carrying</Text>
  <Text Key="8ABF99FB">Take Picture Of</Text>
  <Text Key="A920BF89">Take Picture Of Sim on Subject Mark</Text>
  <Text Key="F739D448">Take Picture With</Text>
  <Text Key="89C6DB9B">Plan Outfits for Fashion Subject</Text>
  <Text Key="6D8B0F1E">Discuss Fashion Blogging</Text>
  <Text Key="8D41A3D7">Discuss Fashion Trends</Text>
  <Text Key="FE9640DC">Ask to Change Outfit</Text>
  <Text Key="CD0FE12D">Take selfie with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="AD6B1EEA">Lofty Aspirations</Text>
  <Text Key="5B7FCBAD">Photo Finish Studio</Text>
  <Text Key="DD611D97">Take a Photo of a Group of Three Sims </Text>
  <Text Key="BE97A1D8">Take a Photo of a Group of Three Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="B985BAEB">Take a Photo of Sims in Athletic Wear</Text>
  <Text Key="8DCE6465">Take a Photo of a Sim posing in front of a Fashion Studio Backdrop</Text>
  <Text Key="914A163A">Take a Photo of a Sim posing in front of a Fashion Studio Backdrop</Text>
  <Text Key="7093951B">Take a Photo of Sims in an Excited Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="978A311C">Take a Photo of Sims in an Excited Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="11AF1A52">Take a Photo of a Sim posing in front of a Fashion Studio Backdrop</Text>
  <Text Key="6F07529B">Take a Photo of a Sim in a Fashion Pose in front of a Fashion Studio Backdrop</Text>
  <Text Key="A522C47D">Take a Photo of a Sim in a Fashion Pose with Fashion Studio Lights</Text>
  <Text Key="7C445752">Take a Photo of a Sim in a Fashion Pose with Fashion Studio Lights</Text>
  <Text Key="4730B84F">Take a Photo of Sims in a Flirty Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="25895590">Take a Photo of Sims in a Flirty Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="71BB89E7">Take a Photo of Sims in a Goofy Pose wearing a Party Outfit</Text>
  <Text Key="288BEEE6">Take a Picture of a Sim in a Goofy Pose wearing a Party Outfit</Text>
  <Text Key="A9531432">Take a Photo of Sims illuminated by Fashion Studio Lights</Text>
  <Text Key="866CD1BB">Take a Photo of Sims illuminated by Fashion Studio Lights</Text>
  <Text Key="41059D27">Take a Photo of Two Sims in Athletic Wear</Text>
  <Text Key="22B3A708">Ask your subjects to change into an appropriate outfit. \nThen, use the camera and tripod to photograph those Sims.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D850C94">Take a Photo of Sims in a Relaxed Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="5D14D0E5">Take a Photo of a Sim in a Sad Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="4B9FAFBA">Ask your subject to change into an appropriate outfit. \nThen, use the tripod with a camera to photograph that Sim striking a Sad Pose.</Text>
  <Text Key="89394BD5">Take a Photo of Sims in a Thoughtful Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="9567AA8A">Ask your subject to change into an appropriate outfit. \nThen, use the camera and tripod to photograph that Sim striking a Thoughtful Pose.</Text>
  <Text Key="42DC8D00">Change a Sim's Outfit</Text>
  <Text Key="5615295D">Select a Sim and Ask to Change Outfit to select new clothes</Text>
  <Text Key="30D17F4E">Chat with Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="F44D60A7">Click on a Computer and select the Chat with Style Influencer Interaction under the Freelance Pie Menu</Text>
  <Text Key="EA412C73">Click on a photo and select the Submit Photo for Client's Approval interaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="08598C23">Get Photo Approved</Text>
  <Text Key="BFFAEECA">Use a Fashion Studio Tripod with a camera to take pictures of Sim in the requested Outfit Type</Text>
  <Text Key="85514500">Meet with Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="5C3A115D">From the relationship panel select a Style Influencer Sim, then select Meet with Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="5A9FF15E">Post Photo to Fashion Simstagram</Text>
  <Text Key="146E6B17">Place an Approved photo in to the Sim's inventory, then use a computer to use the Freelancer option to Post to Fashion Simstagram.</Text>
  <Text Key="724BE032">Submit Photo for Client's Approval</Text>
  <Text Key="6F5015BB">Click on a Photo and select Submit Photo for Client's Approval</Text>
  <Text Key="6C04EF74">Take a Photo of Sims in Formal Wear</Text>
  <Text Key="B5FFA5CF">Take a Photo of Sims in an Everyday Outfit</Text>
  <Text Key="5A8D5A10">Ask your subject to change into an appropriate outfit. \nThen, use the camera and tripod to photograph that Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="E17D2870">Take a Photo of Sims in Sleep Wear</Text>
  <Text Key="A3F246C3">Take a Photo of Sims in Swim Wear</Text>
  <Text Key="DB35F919">Set Backdrop</Text>
  <Text Key="483D904D">Photo Editor</Text>
  <Text Key="894649D3">Met With Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="C57FC9DC">Ability to use a computer to Edit a Photo's Mood Enhancement</Text>
  <Text Key="AA20342C">Authorized to Submit Photos for possible selection to become a Magazine Cover</Text>
  <Text Key="4AB96028">Meet With Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="DA842909">Discuss Fashion Blogging</Text>
  <Text Key="A2C49402">Discuss Fashion Trends</Text>
  <Text Key="FC4E7EA0">Take Photo of Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="0950CDCC">Take Selfie with Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="49E82F78">Present Style Photographs to Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="FFB315AC">I can't wait to see your photos on Simstagram!</Text>
  <Text Key="160482CA">Fashion Subject</Text>
  <Text Key="9512DD76">Style Influencer</Text>
  <Text Key="66EB87FF">Likes</Text>
  <Text Key="C0B284FD">Tomorrow's Style</Text>
  <Text Key="043D01C3">Fashion Photographer</Text>
  <Text Key="DC1DE32C">&lt;b&gt;Trade: Freelance Fashion Photographer&lt;/b&gt;\n\nTomorrow's Style represents and gets you the fashion shoots you need. Sure, you might get stuck with a department store catalog, but work hard and you just might shoot the next high fashion collection worn by celebrities at the Starlight Accolades. \n\nHire photo subjects, select the clothes, set the subjects in the appropriate poses, and capture the magic. Build a home photo studio, or take your camera and tripod on location to get the best shots. Don't forget to self-promote by uploading your photos to Fashion Simstagram.</Text>
  <Text Key="69F87197">Fashion Photographer</Text>
  <Text Key="766D9B4E">Fashionable Wall Attire</Text>
  <Text Key="D2929D36">High Fashion Triangles</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>