<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="2B7CC066">Running out of places to add design accents that express your effervescent personality? Turn your attention upwards with this spectacular carved sandstone ceiling rail! You may think it's unwise to put large chunks of stone above your head, but sometimes gravity can be defied in the name of good design.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A3DDB79">Sandstone Halo Ceiling Rail</Text>
  <Text Key="6C6537A9">We could tell you many tall tales about this fancy carved ceiling rail, but we've decided to leave its origins as a mystery. Was it stolen from a palace? Was it formed naturally in a cave? Is it just a really pretty ceiling rail? The world may never know...</Text>
  <Text Key="7E16EB8C">Celestial Sandstone Ceiling Rail</Text>
  <Text Key="9FEC118F">This column looks nearly identical to the column stolen from the Museum of Antique Structural Support last month, but we can assure you it's not the same column. It's a very different column that happens to have the same brilliant carvings and rich patterns. This column will look absolutely stunning in any home, so don't hesitate to buy today! No personal checks accepted. Please ask for Snake Eyes Tony or Jailbird Jenny when calling and say the code word "Magilicutty" to be routed to our columns department.</Text>
  <Text Key="BF468E56">Lawfully Obtained Antique Column</Text>
  <Text Key="A13A7554">Inspired by the desert sky at night, this carved wooden fence was modelled from the constellation Spheros Inetway Major (Large Ball of Twine.)  Now that's one celestially divine fence!</Text>
  <Text Key="8D75893B">Saharan Stars Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="A2930076">Desert Diamonds</Text>
  <Text Key="91EB7B63">What's an ancient sculptor's favorite game? Frieze tag! That joke does really well at architecture conventions, but thankfully you don't have to sit through one of those to get your hands on this decorative frieze carving.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0314632">Old World Frieze Wall Carving</Text>
  <Text Key="3636F6D8">This doorway was originally built to accommodate the very large hats that were in style at the time. Doorways such as this one were since deemed impractical for many households but recently became in fashion again thanks to a spread in &lt;i&gt;Oasis Weekly&lt;/i&gt; magazine. Hopefully the extra large hats will come back into fashion too!</Text>
  <Text Key="E6B5C657">Accommodating Archway</Text>
  <Text Key="22ADD1B0">The double version of our Maximalism to the Max Doorway, for when you need even more doorway! There are doorways and then there are doorways - and this is one beautiful specimen of a doorway! For the ultimate in maximalist design, a few of these will really take your space from shabby to snazzy.</Text>
  <Text Key="A2B8085F">Maximalism to the Max Double Doorway</Text>
  <Text Key="27B9CD1F">This double doorway was painstakingly nibbled by trained termites. Oh, sorry... trained termite artisans. They worked on this magnificent door morning, noon and night to get the patterns just right. Now that's dedication!</Text>
  <Text Key="D13E37C6">Dedicated to Detail Double Door</Text>
  <Text Key="0D080EF1">Intricately carved lattice work and filigree details will make this door an instant focal point in your home. The perfect decoy to draw attention away from any mess or décor disasters that may be plaguing your residence. (We won't judge.) Nothing is perfect all the time, but this door can be! Let it do the hard work of being beautiful for you.</Text>
  <Text Key="C2B179C4">Fabulous Filigree Door</Text>
  <Text Key="D602A07B">There are doorways and then there are doorways - and this is one beautiful specimen of a doorway! For the ultimate in maximalist design, a few of these will really take your space from shabby to snazzy.</Text>
  <Text Key="FAAC48DA">Maximalism to the Max Doorway</Text>
  <Text Key="F8114778">There are many legends surrounding this fountain, and many are contradictory. Some say the fountain is all that remains of a great city that disappeared beneath the sand dunes, and others say it looks pretty similar to a fountain you can buy at Fountains 'n Things over on Fourth street. Whatever its origin story, you've got to admit it's super pretty and even has rose petals in it. Rose petals!</Text>
  <Text Key="1BFDED77">Star of Paradise Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="5E48F646">If you're languishing from dim LEDs and fed up with fluorescent bulbs, this old-world style lantern may be just what you need to transform your home-oasis into a setting for sunset romance. Some say love blooms in good company, but come on, it's all about the lighting.</Text>
  <Text Key="4D2609D9">Sunset Glow Lantern</Text>
  <Text Key="A3974D79">Long ago and far away a poor young ne'er-do-well ventured into a desert cave looking for riches. Amongst all the treasure was a brass lamp. Remembering tales of magical beings living inside such lamps, the thief grabbed it and was indeed able to summon a genie. Unfortunately, this particular genie was quite stubborn and refused to grant any wishes or even put on pants. Disappointed, the young lad sold the lamp to a local pawn shop where they converted it into a lovely hanging wall lantern.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0CEED7C">The Stubborn Genie's Wall Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="4CBAE6F1">Give your home a bunch of tropical vibes with this luscious banana tree! Each banana tree comes in its own earthenware pot and is gauranteed to evoke many questions and comments from guests including "&lt;i&gt;what kind of plant is that&lt;/i&gt;," "&lt;i&gt;is that a banana plant?!&lt;/i&gt;," "&lt;i&gt;where did you get a banana plant?&lt;/i&gt;," "&lt;i&gt;I like bananas!&lt;/i&gt;," "&lt;i&gt;bananas are overrated&lt;/i&gt;," and "&lt;i&gt;squee!&lt;/i&gt;"</Text>
  <Text Key="412281C4">Banana Tree</Text>
  <Text Key="037CF5DE">A symbol of both victory and peace, palm trees add a feeling of rejuvenation and calmness to any private oasis. You might say we're big fans!</Text>
  <Text Key="CF0023E1">Fan Palm Tree</Text>
  <Text Key="8D0D14A8">Crafted lovingly from hand-made clay tile, this opulent octogram mosaic is a stunning addition to any home. Use it as a base for a water feature, or show it off as is. The perfect addition to your slice of paradise!</Text>
  <Text Key="9C1513C7">Piece of Paradise Mosaic</Text>
  <Text Key="E86DAAEC">You could have the most well-decorated courtyard filled with the finest things, but it still wouldn't be complete without a big 'ole vase.</Text>
  <Text Key="16FF6F23">Big 'Ole Vase</Text>
  <Text Key="B43727B8">If you're not already having tea-time with your friends and loved ones, make it your new tradition! Catching up with the crew over hot tea and hot goss is sure to be the new highlight of your day, and what better way to make you smile than a blingy tea-set fit for royalty. Time to spill the tea!</Text>
  <Text Key="5350AEB7">Relaxing Rituals Tea Set by The Piping Pot</Text>
  <Text Key="6D0FA372">Lots of folktales often reference "royal advisors" who either make or break the story with their questionable counsel, but no one ever really explores the chairs behind the advisors behinds. This lovely teak chair is said to have belonged to one such advisor who once told a princess not to bother marrying and instead to focus on her career. At the time, this caused a great scandal, but the princess trusted the advisor and took heed. She focused on her career and ended up being the most successful ruler in the kingdom's history. She was promoted to Junior Queen, then Queen, then Super Queen. True story. Thanks, royal advisor, and of course, the royal advisor's chair!</Text>
  <Text Key="23B5440D">The Royal Advisor's Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="FC75D120">Folktales will reference the Kings and Queens of old and, of course, their court. But no one thinks about the furniture that lived it all. This lovely loveseat was witness to many royal affairs and a lot of gossip. But like, a LOT of gossip. This loveseat is made to be comfortable to sustain many hours of talking, and its plush cushions provide optimal support for those sessions that you are made to attend, but don't really want to, so you look upright... and not asleep.</Text>
  <Text Key="F369566F">The Royal Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="9BB3A311">Here at the Gilded Furniture Factory we believe that anything worth having is worth covering in precious metals. That's why we've brought you this delightfully shiny table. It's the perfect statement piece for those who coddle their coffee or treasure their tea. Sure, some people may call you tacky, but those people don't have the expensive taste you do. Shine on, you crazy metallic-table-buying-diamond. Shine on.</Text>
  <Text Key="822A3C64">Treasured Tea &amp; Coffee Table by Gilded Furniture Factory</Text>
  <Text Key="D28AD533">If you're going to place a coffee table smack dab in the middle of your living area, why not make it a feast for the eyes? Complex patterns adorn this octagonal table, making it a visual treat, and a bold statement piece to add a layer of pizzazz to any room. Octagons - they're not just for stop signs and UFOs anymore! </Text>
  <Text Key="EF692862">Coffee in the Courtyard Table</Text>
  <Text Key="FE15B5E6">Greet the dawn with this stunning latticed window! Sunburst details and colorful inlay tiles will make anyone into a morning person, or at least temporarily quell those murderous tendencies non-morning people have when they first wake up and struggle to form words.</Text>
  <Text Key="5E83C3F9">Greet the Dawn Window</Text>
  <Text Key="2ACE1E09">The original version of this large window was completely open, but after an increase of window related accidents, a screen was installed. Great at keeping big bugs away, but sand is another story...</Text>
  <Text Key="8BDE236C">Riad Window</Text>
  <Text Key="7DEB3FA1">Piece of Paradise</Text>
  <Text Key="458606AB">Why walk on the ground like some sort of peasant when you can have an elevated walking experience? Here at Lofty Life Goals we make it our mission to provide top-notch platforms so you can live in style and away from the dirty dirt. Rise up!</Text>
  <Text Key="28C0CBAA">Elevated Elegance Platform by Lofty Life Goals Inc.</Text>
  <Text Key="AEF67BBE">The desert at night is a magical place and is one of the best places to stargaze. This carved wooden stair-rail is inspired by the desert stars and all the constellations within it. The next time you visit the desert, bring a telescope so you can spot the &lt;i&gt;Sul Sul&lt;/i&gt; constellation, &lt;i&gt;Llama Major&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Llama Minor&lt;/i&gt;, and of course &lt;i&gt;Bob Pancakes' Belt&lt;/i&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="7D26D841">Saharan Stars Railing</Text>
  <Text Key="E4ADC72D">The desert does strange things to travelers, and many who have ventured into the dunes have returned with peculiar stories and tall tales. One in particular involved a staircase that appeared out of nowhere and led to a floating oasis city. One traveler claimed to have lived an entire life in this city, but when he climbed back down the stairs, it was as if no time had passed. These stairs are modelled after that very story, but they don’t have any magical powers, so don’t plan on climbing them to escape paying your bills.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA91D8F8">Traveler's Mirage Staircase</Text>
  <Text Key="5553C182">Saffron Blossom</Text>
  <Text Key="E39869AB">Boldly Brushed</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>