<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="A127CC85">The tea envelops the Sim in an aura of mystique, enhancing their charisma and energy, allowing them to socialize effortlessly while staying invigorated longer.</Text>
  <Text Key="1C8F4680">Radiant Mystique</Text>
  <Text Key="DC1B3FDD">Activewear Allure</Text>
  <Text Key="B758B4B7">Milan Muse</Text>
  <Text Key="050C0E0E">Evening Elegance</Text>
  <Text Key="0520EA3F">Silk Slumber</Text>
  <Text Key="9D04888A">Introducing the Double Bookcase by CrypticCo – a timeless masterpiece. Perfect for showcasing your literary treasures and curiosities, this bookcase transforms any room into a realm of classic elegance and charm.</Text>
  <Text Key="01391295">Secret Sanctuary Bookcase by CrypticCo</Text>
  <Text Key="54A31D98">Add an air of mystery to your home with the Secret Sanctuary Door by CrypticCo! This unique piece combines the charm of a classic bookcase with the thrill of a hidden passage.</Text>
  <Text Key="4471D417">Secret Sanctuary Door by CrypticCo</Text>
  <Text Key="8C357618">Craft an elevated tea time with a touch of arcane sophistication. This beautiful tray features a sleek metal finish and delicate details, with complementing teacups. It is ideal for sharing a tranquil yet enchanting moment.</Text>
  <Text Key="2C907597">Arcane Aroma Tea Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="5C2B0B0D">A cup of Shadowberry Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="A89F6058">Shadowberry Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="16F3559C">Transform your home with the renowned beauty of the Châteaux Charm Fireplace. Crafted with intricate filigree details, it casts a warm, enchanting glow, perfect for creating a captivating ambiance in any living space.</Text>
  <Text Key="29AC8473">Châteaux Charm Fireplace</Text>
  <Text Key="66C6CC1D">Discover the Gilded Looking Glass, an elegant piece that whispers secrets beyond our understanding. Its timeless design holds an air of mystery, inviting you to explore the unknown.</Text>
  <Text Key="3871F708">Gilded Looking Glass</Text>
  <Text Key="8EFC4F0A">Immerse your space in an aura of elegance with our Whispering Walls Gallery Frames. Each frame exudes a hauntingly beautiful charm, perfect for showcasing your most treasured memories and heirloom photographs.</Text>
  <Text Key="57109E15">Whispering Walls Gallery Frames</Text>
  <Text Key="3420A40B">This heirloom jewelry box will guard and display your treasured jewels with effortless allure. </Text>
  <Text Key="41FA168A">Vintage Allure Jewelry Box</Text>
  <Text Key="F9029CAB">Create an atmosphere of enigmatic elegance with the Classical Revival Vanity Chair. Its deep, plush cushioning invites you into a realm of indulgence, while the sleek design melds seamlessly with its accompanying vanity table.</Text>
  <Text Key="F446ADAA">Classical Revival Vanity Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="58531130">Perfect for adding a touch of vintage charm to any sanctuary, it's the ideal spot for unwinding in luxurious comfort amidst the elegance of a bygone era.</Text>
  <Text Key="3CFCAEDF">Twilight Repose Chaise Lounge</Text>
  <Text Key="D1BFB4C4">Step into an era of elegance with the Echoes of Elegance Gramophone and lose yourself in the moody melodies of your favorite music.</Text>
  <Text Key="E653DD8B">Echoes of Elegance Gramophone</Text>
  <Text Key="35FA99CC">This vanity is the perfect blend of classical charm and modern sensibilities. It features antique design elements newly reimagined with contemporary finishes to create a unique focal point for any dressing room.</Text>
  <Text Key="2148C883">Classical Revival Vanity</Text>
  <Text Key="9D75AF6E">Upgrade your space with this blend of antique luxury and modern innovation. Featuring a luxurious gilded gold frame that enhances any living space, this stunning Frame TV doubles as a piece of art whenever you're done watching your favorite TV show.
</Text>
  <Text Key="9CA3D211">Gilded Gaze Frame TV</Text>
  <Text Key="BC87A341">Stock with Shadowberry Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="C086058F">The Secret Sanctuary</Text>
  <Text Key="4F1CCAC6">Shadowberry Tea</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>