<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="373C6A5E">(From Sharing a Photo on Simstagram)</Text>
  <Text Key="8DF2989D">(From Sharing a Photo on Simstagram)</Text>
  <Text Key="4C033C2E">(From Discussing Flavor Profiles)</Text>
  <Text Key="2C33837C">(From Discussing Flavor Profiles)</Text>
  <Text Key="4D6F9908">(From Low-Quality Experimental Food)</Text>
  <Text Key="0418A4CA">(From Experimental Food)</Text>
  <Text Key="A0923531">(From Restaurant Food)</Text>
  <Text Key="E69D19EB">Oh no! It looks like {0.SimFirstName} has food poisoning! Something must have been wrong with that restaurant food. {0.SimFirstName} should get on the phone and let them know!</Text>
  <Text Key="41FB3821">(From Recovering from Food Poisoning)</Text>
  <Text Key="DDEB8B18">We're taking {0.SimFirstName}'s claim of food poisoning very seriously! Please accept {1.Money} as compensation for our mistake...\n\nTry drinking lots of water! Again, we're so sorry! Please don't tell anyone!</Text>
  <Text Key="E51404D4">(From Coloring Placemat)</Text>
  <Text Key="28DDDF4D">Owning a restaurant is hard work. Approximately 59.5% of new restaurants fail within the first year. However, with proper management, skilled employees, a delicious menu, and a little plasma, sweat and tears your restaurant just might succeed.\n\nFor more details, please check out the restaurant Ownership Lesson!</Text>
  <Text Key="4E20BC0F">So you bought a restaurant. Now what?</Text>
  <Text Key="2A6EA790">Go To Lessons</Text>
  <Text Key="0E0F7816">Let me make up for any inconvenience you may have encountered and take care of your bill.</Text>
  <Text Key="DCD1FCD0">Your Simoleons are no good here. Enjoy the complimentary food.</Text>
  <Text Key="4182EED5">You are such a valued customer. Let me take care of the bill for you.</Text>
  <Text Key="4FEC9CA4">Your meal is on the house. Please make sure to dine with us again.</Text>
  <Text Key="7CEDE604">Please enjoy a free meal compliments of the management.</Text>
  <Text Key="62F118BE">Let me have the waiter bring you a complimentary dessert.
</Text>
  <Text Key="BDEFB2FD">I can't let you leave without a smile on your face. Treat yourself to any dessert and I'll pick up the bill.</Text>
  <Text Key="BAD536F8">Thank you for choosing to dine with us today. Choose any one our fine desserts compliments of the restaurant.</Text>
  <Text Key="B321CCDC">Please try one of our delicious desserts. Free of charge!</Text>
  <Text Key="E9D0AC1F">Let me satisfy your sweet tooth and your wallet. Choose any one of our desserts for free.
</Text>
  <Text Key="B6AC97CD">I'm treating this table to a round of free drinks. May I recommend the water?</Text>
  <Text Key="353B1952">Let me have the kitchen bring out a free round of drinks so we can toast to your good meal.
</Text>
  <Text Key="A868C7BB">Let me get a free round of drinks for this table.</Text>
  <Text Key="369398FC">Please enjoy a complimentary drink on us.
</Text>
  <Text Key="841FE5D0">A good drink will improve your mood. A free drink will make it even better. Let me get you round of free drinks.
</Text>
  <Text Key="CA1D2573">Your food will be out before you can say 'Gastronomy'.
</Text>
  <Text Key="1F798ACA">I'm going to make sure your meal is top priority. It will be out shortly.</Text>
  <Text Key="3E344F22">You are too important to wait. I'm going to make sure your food comes out pronto.
</Text>
  <Text Key="3FF805A5">I'll go speed up your order in the kitchen. Your food will be out shortly.
</Text>
  <Text Key="FC74ADB6">I'm going to make sure the Chef turns up the heat to get your food out fast.</Text>
  <Text Key="3D1A2E35">I could have grown and cooked my own food by this point. This is unacceptable. I'm leaving!</Text>
  <Text Key="DD642488">This is horrible! I didn't wait this long for my new phone on opening day. I'm out of here.</Text>
  <Text Key="8641934A">1 Star Review</Text>
  <Text Key="E22A0937">4 Star Review</Text>
  <Text Key="15384EF8">Genius is not a term I throw around lightly. This chef is a genius. Supported by an excellent staff. This restaurant presented me with dishes I'd never imagined and flavors I wish I had. I'll be making my next reservation as soon as I get home.\n\nDine here to take your taste buds to the next level.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F50F0E6">5 Star Review</Text>
  <Text Key="05F6672A">2 Star Review</Text>
  <Text Key="371B060F">3 Star Review</Text>
  <Text Key="4373C371">The food was digestible but not the bill. It was clear I wasn't paying for great service either.\n\nDine here if you have Simoleons weighing you down.</Text>
  <Text Key="6261CC35">I was unimpressed. The food likely had some nutritional value, but that is where the value ended.\n\nDine here if you just need sustenance.</Text>
  <Text Key="A08FA176">Dining here was one of the most remarkable experiences of my life. It has opened my mind to what perfection could really be. The flavors of my meal will linger with me for years to come.\n\nDine here. It's not a suggestion, it's a mandate.</Text>
  <Text Key="38707931">This restaurant is like a waking nightmare for my taste buds. The chef must've got ingredients that fell off the back of a truck into the mud and then were run over by 3 more trucks.\n\nDine here when you know the date will end early.</Text>
  <Text Key="519FA09F">My stomach isn't empty and neither is my wallet. This is a so-so establishment that fulfilled the basic qualifications to be called a restaurant.\n\nDine here if you have a heart condition and must avoid excitement.</Text>
  <Text Key="55D14F51">The cheerful staff went the extra mile to make my meal perfect. I recommend putting your trust in the Chef and ordering the Chef's Choice.\n\nDine here to experience what quality service should be.</Text>
  <Text Key="18CB629F">The service and the décor are just the first insults to your senses. When the food hits your tongue it will grow legs and run for the door. Any price is too high for the meal you will get here.\n\nDine here if you like paying for the privilege of licking dirt.</Text>
  <Text Key="32A4AA17">It's hard to say if this restaurant is a glass half full or half empty. I guess it quenched my thirst.\n\nDine here if your favorite color is beige.</Text>
  <Text Key="5DC04B62">I was pleasantly surprised at the quality of meal I received for such a reasonable price. This is sure to become a local favorite.\n\nDine here to experience food done right.</Text>
  <Text Key="E1EBC424">{0.SimFirstName} has tasted the wonders of Experimental Food and now, understanding the complex flavors involved, can cook this dish at home using their personal chef station.</Text>
  <Text Key="CC1DC87F">If only {0.SimFirstName} had level 5 Cooking skill {M0.he}{F0.she} could have learned to cook this experimental dish at home!</Text>
  <Text Key="47C47C43">Restaurant Date</Text>
  <Text Key="08010BC4">(From Restaurant)</Text>
  <Text Key="685585B6">Additional Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="A8011009">Additional Chef \n\nUnlocks the ability to hire one additional chef with the Manage Employees window. Don't forget to place a second chef station.</Text>
  <Text Key="E537C050">Additional Waiter #1</Text>
  <Text Key="ED27599F">Additional Waiter #1 \n\nUnlocks the ability to hire one additional waiter within the Manage Employees window.</Text>
  <Text Key="F3A3E05B">Additional Waiter #2</Text>
  <Text Key="4FE3DD7C">Additional Waiter #2 \n\nUnlocks the ability to hire one additional waiter within the Manage Employees window.\n\nThis Perk is unlocked by the Additional Waiter #1 Perk.</Text>
  <Text Key="5C9BF55D">Ingredient Discount (small)</Text>
  <Text Key="0C0BAF6A">Ingredient Discount (small) \n\nPermanently lowers the cost of ingredients by a small amount.</Text>
  <Text Key="1EB7B48E">Ingredient Discount (large)</Text>
  <Text Key="590C4461">Ingredient Discount (large)\n\nPermanently lowers the cost of ingredients by a large amount. Requires the Ingredient Discount (small) to be unlocked.</Text>
  <Text Key="375375DB">The Chef's Hat</Text>
  <Text Key="B6574AFC">The Chef's Hat \n\nUnlocks an additional Chef Hat for your Sims.</Text>
  <Text Key="7C6C15A8">Fast Eaters</Text>
  <Text Key="CD52F617">Fast Eaters \n\nCustomers will eat their meals faster.
</Text>
  <Text Key="6B2F6D21">Well Funded Foodies</Text>
  <Text Key="513038C6">Well Funded Foodies \n\nCustomers will more often choose the more expensive menu items.</Text>
  <Text Key="70F09E6B">The cost of ingredients is reduced for 24 hours.</Text>
  <Text Key="96654A2E">Surplus Harvest</Text>
  <Text Key="0D3BBE81">Surplus Harvest (Temporary)\n\nTake advantage of a surplus harvest. The cost of ingredients is discounted for 24 hours.</Text>
  <Text Key="466AA96F">Ingredient Quality Options</Text>
  <Text Key="7C4EA788">Ingredient Quality Options \n\nUnlocks the ability to choose the quality of meal ingredients.</Text>
  <Text Key="694CCE55">Inspirational Speech</Text>
  <Text Key="88295A22">Inspirational Speech \n\nUnlocks the "Inspirational Speech" social interaction, which can be used to inspire your employees.</Text>
  <Text Key="3332761E">Patient Patrons</Text>
  <Text Key="A124F551">Patient Patrons\n\nMake customers easier to impress with quick service and willing to wait longer before they get upset at slow service.</Text>
  <Text Key="09311ABE">Well Managed</Text>
  <Text Key="80A67271">Well Managed\n\nLowers the chance of bad events happening on the restaurant while your Sim is away.</Text>
  <Text Key="52CC8F6F">Lower Employee Training Costs</Text>
  <Text Key="EE68ED88">Lower Employee Training Costs \n\nLowers the cost of training for employees.</Text>
  <Text Key="98CE90BC">The Meal Rush perk is currently active.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF99DE5F">Meal Rush</Text>
  <Text Key="5281E958">Meal Rush (Temporary)\n\nFor 24 hours, more customers will stop in to eat at your restaurant.</Text>
  <Text Key="78936365">Curiouser Customers</Text>
  <Text Key="8A625292">Curiouser Customers\n\nIncreases how often customers request dish recommendations.\n\nThis Perk unlocked by the Curious Customers Perk.</Text>
  <Text Key="2373166E">Curious Customers</Text>
  <Text Key="481A4FC1">Curious Customers\n\nMakes customers occasionally wish for a recommendation on what to order from management and unlocks the ability to give recommendations through the "Recommend Dish" social.</Text>
  <Text Key="FCD5BCBB">The key to earning prestige is patience. Wait a while before attempting to manipulate your restaurant's repute.</Text>
  <Text Key="F07FC5DE">Tidy Tippers</Text>
  <Text Key="52F78C11">Tidy Tippers\n\nCustomers will tip a bit extra on top of every meal. Can be purchased multiple times for ever larger tips!</Text>
  <Text Key="864FB400">Discussing the flavor profile of a recent food dish generates a series of ideas and thoughts to punch up {0.SimFirstName}'s own recipes.</Text>
  <Text Key="A97866CF">Flavor Inspiration</Text>
  <Text Key="51CF878F">This is some bold food. It's like a statement about life's inevitable end dipped in sauce and sprinkled with spices.</Text>
  <Text Key="D18B1056">Superb Grub</Text>
  <Text Key="04779EB4">Wow! That was a gastronomically delectable dish. The emotions filled {0.SimFirstName}'s plate. It was magical and delicious!</Text>
  <Text Key="7FA9371B">Amazing Flavors</Text>
  <Text Key="9815C765">A disaster of a dish with a side of terrible. {0.SimFirstName} is very displeased.</Text>
  <Text Key="C3C405E0">Discordant Flavors</Text>
  <Text Key="748A4567">While the plate is a bit of a mess, it has something special about it that {0.SimFirstName} can't quite figure out.</Text>
  <Text Key="F32A799E">Intriguing Flavors</Text>
  <Text Key="B51D5B0A">Eating this food was like music to {0.SimFirstName}'s taste buds. The flavor was like a symphony of taste.</Text>
  <Text Key="694E0215">Harmonious Flavors</Text>
  <Text Key="D1312B51">{0.SimFirstName} was so impressed with that dish! It was nearly perfect!</Text>
  <Text Key="49DA97A4">Superior Cuisine</Text>
  <Text Key="A5062A2C">This food must have fallen from the heavens above. That is the only explanation that makes sense. Simply sublime!</Text>
  <Text Key="A2FE8F63">Divine Dish</Text>
  <Text Key="1324BE5A">It kind of tastes like plastic and makes strange sounds, but it's also a work of art! ART, I TELL YOU!</Text>
  <Text Key="0BA23285">Interesting Taste</Text>
  <Text Key="08418D14">This experimental food is like art! Like wonderful, edible, great-tasting art!</Text>
  <Text Key="343C9FFB">Mind-Expanding Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="E454F057">This experimental food stuff looks weird and {0.SimFirstName} doesn't like it one bit. Not one bite.</Text>
  <Text Key="97603D2E">Confusing Aftertaste</Text>
  <Text Key="28CB0927">The gurgling of the stomach is a deafening roar. {0.SimFirstName} must call the restaurant immediately to report this. But whatever happens, {M0.he}{F0.she} should not wander too far from a bathroom!</Text>
  <Text Key="5A63ED5E">Food Poisoned</Text>
  <Text Key="CC20C510">Surviving the storm was difficult, but now the stomach is stronger than ever before!</Text>
  <Text Key="D520BA3F">Survived Food Poisoning</Text>
  <Text Key="9B98FF52">It makes a Sim feel really hip to have a bunch of cool photos on Simstagram.</Text>
  <Text Key="5C8FB16D">Photo Hipster</Text>
  <Text Key="F88337DF">{0.SimFirstName} has felt nothing as self satisfying as viewing a collection of photos curated by {M0.himself}{F0.herself}.</Text>
  <Text Key="079C4686">Well Curated Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="538BA7A6">You've done your best, and this is truly a work of art.</Text>
  <Text Key="513578B9">Coloring Completed</Text>
  <Text Key="83C18B91">Because taking {0.SimFirstName}'s favorite Sim out to breakfast is THE thing to do!</Text>
  <Text Key="18C68DE4">Hot Breakfast Date</Text>
  <Text Key="FB4AECF8">Dinner? Check! {0.SimFirstName}'s favorite Sim ever? Check! Everything is wonderful!</Text>
  <Text Key="55E6E5F7">Hot Dinner Date</Text>
  <Text Key="E8523C4A">Taking {0.SimFirstName}'s favorite Sim out to lunch makes {M0.him}{F0.her} very happy!</Text>
  <Text Key="A8533A55">Hot Lunch Date</Text>
  <Text Key="2812BBD9">{0.SimFirstName} believes that breakfast is the most important meal of the day! So why does {M0.he}{F0.she} have to cook it {M0.himself}{F0.herself}? As if!</Text>
  <Text Key="B739AE5C">Out to Breakfast </Text>
  <Text Key="F0FA5430">Mmmmm... delicious. There's nothing like going out to dinner for a big meal. Those chefs can really cook!</Text>
  <Text Key="B6B907DF">Out to Dinner</Text>
  <Text Key="7E6C98D2">Who wants lunch in a sack? That just sounds wrong! Going out to lunch is the only way to live!</Text>
  <Text Key="A27C45ED">Out to Lunch</Text>
  <Text Key="76348F05">Things seem to be going well for {0.SimFirstName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="9C5D0600">Flirty Restaurant Date</Text>
  <Text Key="303C3AFE">{0.SimFirstName} wishes someone would have told {M0.him}{F0.her} what the dress-code was for this place.</Text>
  <Text Key="AC068781">Underdressed</Text>
  <Text Key="F09114EB">Silver Package (§120 / day)</Text>
  <Text Key="E7402B1B">None</Text>
  <Text Key="18FE4560">Gold Package (§240 / day)</Text>
  <Text Key="E7969B63">Diamond Package (§1200 / day)</Text>
  <Text Key="6FCA87B2">Platinum Package (§480 / day)</Text>
  <Text Key="E7B01D65">Meal Quality</Text>
  <Text Key="B877704A">Personal Touch</Text>
  <Text Key="021ACAF3">Wait Time</Text>
  <Text Key="F960EE2C">Service</Text>
  <Text Key="4C860A6F">Meal Value</Text>
  <Text Key="750EE6F2">Ambiance</Text>
  <Text Key="951512DE">250%</Text>
  <Text Key="B681342F">125%</Text>
  <Text Key="D53E2F3B">175%</Text>
  <Text Key="71A9CE11">150%</Text>
  <Text Key="1A34406F">200%</Text>
  <Text Key="A95F7A98">100%</Text>
  <Text Key="2B21E341">300%</Text>
  <Text Key="411E63C9">To have a functional restaurant, make sure a host, waiter, and chef have been hired. Also make sure a menu has been set for patrons to enjoy.</Text>
  <Text Key="373154BB">Restaurant Not Functional.</Text>
  <Text Key="05EE1185">The restaurant is now open and customers are ready to arrive and eat delicious food!</Text>
  <Text Key="F5B6A687">Open For Business</Text>
  <Text Key="40D15E05">Upon confirmation, your restaurant funds and the lot value will be deposited into your household's funds. If your restaurant funds are in the negative, it will be deducted from the value of the lot to clear your debts. The household will earn {0.Money} from this sale.</Text>
  <Text Key="08660707">Sell The Restaurant?</Text>
  <Text Key="14706E6A">This meal definitely doesn't look too great...</Text>
  <Text Key="EF2281AA">Wow! Take a look at this! This meal is amazing!</Text>
  <Text Key="2F09FC9F">I wasn't too happy with the owner...</Text>
  <Text Key="055AA94B">All this attention from the owner is making me feel really special!</Text>
  <Text Key="B0274990">I'm not very happy about the wait times here...</Text>
  <Text Key="712ABCB8">Wow! My meal got here in no time!</Text>
  <Text Key="2D6B0261">I wish this place had more friendly service...</Text>
  <Text Key="2C1BF8ED">The service at this place is fantastic!</Text>
  <Text Key="30DC4654">Hmm...little on the pricey side</Text>
  <Text Key="8868019C">This place has great prices!</Text>
  <Text Key="6503AEE3">The decor here could do with some improvements...</Text>
  <Text Key="8768B85F">Wow! This place has some nice decor.</Text>
  <Text Key="C5418835">Current Restaurant</Text>
  <Text Key="7BDBFD71">Cost of Ingredients:</Text>
  <Text Key="8D3D4BCB">{0.Money}</Text>
  <Text Key="CF62B6C6">Meal Profits:</Text>
  <Text Key="0653ED2C">{0.Money}</Text>
  <Text Key="6196B6FA">Sales:</Text>
  <Text Key="8EF10300">{0.Money}</Text>
  <Text Key="7E38EC5D">Advertising Cost:</Text>
  <Text Key="8275CCD7">{0.Number}</Text>
  <Text Key="DFF984F3">Net Profit:</Text>
  <Text Key="808E0779">{0.Money}</Text>
  <Text Key="BA90C8B4">{0.Money}</Text>
  <Text Key="B85DE9FA">On Demand Cheffing</Text>
  <Text Key="85034FAA">Food and Nectar Magazine</Text>
  <Text Key="0FBE1253">Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="AA77D2CA">Chef Level 1</Text>
  <Text Key="DB9124F7">Chef Level 2</Text>
  <Text Key="F48336DC">Chef Level 3</Text>
  <Text Key="EF427779">Chef Level 4</Text>
  <Text Key="B4F609BE">Chef Level 5</Text>
  <Text Key="0990B29C">Host Level 1</Text>
  <Text Key="668881B5">Host Level 2</Text>
  <Text Key="1B370A8A">Host Level 3</Text>
  <Text Key="F21EDC0B">Host Level 4</Text>
  <Text Key="9A0E83A0">Host Level 5</Text>
  <Text Key="E34EC824">Waiter Level 1</Text>
  <Text Key="4106249D">Waiter Level 2</Text>
  <Text Key="3CE00252">Waiter Level 3</Text>
  <Text Key="23CA4833">Waiter Level 4</Text>
  <Text Key="A4EA6C68">Waiter Level 5</Text>
  <Text Key="E0B8A9BC">Restaurant Critic</Text>
  <Text Key="8C74DD99">Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="B665A757">Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="AA59ED51">Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="E6DB2E4F">Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="13C5E5D3">Host</Text>
  <Text Key="F8D87B09">Host</Text>
  <Text Key="BE27FE73">Waiter</Text>
  <Text Key="E454EF29">Waiter</Text>
  <Text Key="5610DC2E">Restaurant Critic</Text>
  <Text Key="06D30CB6">Restaurant Critic</Text>
  <Text Key="2E2C7769">Safety is my priority. You can count on me to hold anything up and light the way. I will not let you down.</Text>
  <Text Key="725C144C">Structurally Sound</Text>
  <Text Key="E3CD91D7">Yum!!! That looks so tasty.</Text>
  <Text Key="48B8D6E8">Yummmmm!</Text>
  <Text Key="DDF1AAA4">That looks completely like edible art. Those chefs have some serious skill!</Text>
  <Text Key="3B7BB621">That looks so ridiculously delicious! It makes me want to eat my screen!</Text>
  <Text Key="D1917C18">I saw that photo you posted. That food looks amazing!</Text>
  <Text Key="128D6498">Breakfast at Restaurant</Text>
  <Text Key="620EAEAA">Lunch at Restaurant</Text>
  <Text Key="918D6F13">Dinner at Restaurant</Text>
  <Text Key="F114AAFD">You and I haven't always gotten along, but maybe we can become friends. What do you say to dinner at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="4D8A696C">You and I haven't always gotten along, but maybe we can become friends. What do you say to breakfast at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="8DF2DFDD">You and I haven't always gotten along, but maybe we can become friends. What do you say to lunch at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="E6B727D5">I'm really sorry to hear about your loss. Let's go get dinner at {3.String} so we can talk about it.</Text>
  <Text Key="B1267184">I'm really sorry to hear about your loss. Let's get breakfast at {3.String} so we can talk about it.</Text>
  <Text Key="F1781A45">I'm really sorry to hear about your loss. Let's go out grab lunch at {3.String} so we can talk about it.</Text>
  <Text Key="6528F45F">Heard you got a promotion, congrats! I think dinner at {3.String} would be the perfect way to celebrate. You in?</Text>
  <Text Key="D912292E">Heard you got a promotion, congrats! I think breakfast at {3.String} would be the perfect way to celebrate. You in?</Text>
  <Text Key="4C39A0D7">Heard you got a promotion, congrats! I think lunch at {3.String} would be the perfect way to celebrate. You in?</Text>
  <Text Key="C61D80CC">I've been thinking maybe opposites attract. This might be crazy, but let's go have dinner at {3.String} and see if things get spicy.</Text>
  <Text Key="70D47285">I've been thinking maybe opposites attract. This might be crazy, but let's go have breakfast at {3.String} and see if things get spicy.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AB7A814">I've been thinking maybe opposites attract. This might be crazy, but let's go have lunch at {3.String} and see if things get spicy.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF47EDD7">Hey, I need to get out of the house. Want to join me for dinner at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="FB8B210A">I'm starving! Wanna go grab lunch with me at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="91DE8C19">I'm starving! Wanna go grab breakfast with me at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="EF28452C">I'm starving! Wanna go grab dinner with me at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="ADA932C6">Hey, I need to get out of the house. Want to join me for breakfast at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="12A33ADF">Hey, I need to get out of the house. Want to join me for lunch at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="570888F3">I can't get you out of my mind lately. Wanna go on a date and get some dinner at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="956D7E52">I can't get you out of my mind lately. Wanna go on a date and get some breakfast at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="ADAFC16B">I can't get you out of my mind lately. Wanna go on a date and get some lunch at {3.String}?</Text>
  <Text Key="8D390B99">Pretty in Polka-dots</Text>
  <Text Key="351AC9EF">A Well Dressed Lad</Text>
  <Text Key="B381A83C">The Lunch Date</Text>
  <Text Key="2B915154">Bringing Fab to the Table</Text>
  <Text Key="2CCD6D07">Chef's Choice</Text>
  <Text Key="3BCD7785">Pass the Fancy Mustard</Text>
  <Text Key="57C1F862">Dinner with Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="36B94FE1">Waiting with Pizzazz</Text>
  <Text Key="3E9113C4">A-Muse Bouche</Text>
  <Text Key="4CC57896">Fancy Orders Only</Text>
  <Text Key="CF8E44E0">Restaurant\nIn-Vest-ments</Text>
  <Text Key="FA59740F">Slatted Wall Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="02142DD6">Slatted Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="4E3DBA6B">Glass Wall Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="56B6E16A">Glass Wall Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="0A842D4A">Fiber Grain Carpeting</Text>
  <Text Key="1848A481">Floral Fancy Carpeting</Text>
  <Text Key="3C2E4E67">Rectangle Dream Carpeting</Text>
  <Text Key="FD0565AA">Polished Marble Tile</Text>
  <Text Key="7BEFF4FF">Collectible Slate Tile</Text>
  <Text Key="BBF4A8BA">Move your fish into the Sea Plus Aquarium and see them thrive and grow. More swimming space and bubbles makes these fish the happiest water-dwelling creatures in captivity!</Text>
  <Text Key="0E15AE65">Sea Plus Aquarium</Text>
  <Text Key="E8A208E7">Your restaurant will never be complete until people know what it’s called. What better way than a fitting awning sign. It's Simply Advertising!</Text>
  <Text Key="5A776C1E">Simply Advertising</Text>
  <Text Key="E7351DF7">"Order's Up!" will be screamed out in delight at blistering speeds never before seen in a professional kitchen. This free standing chef station unit is a one stop shop that creates an efficient workspace for chefs of all shapes and sizes. </Text>
  <Text Key="DC96264E">"I Dream of Sous" Chef Station</Text>
  <Text Key="ED151831">When the chef wants to hide behind a wall and only hand food through a small hole like pushing a tray into a prison cell, well then look no further than this beauty. Delivers all the grace and functionality of the most professional kitchen unit while still being able to hide even the most hideous chef in a back room.</Text>
  <Text Key="D05F2504">Full Disclosure Chef Station</Text>
  <Text Key="3050FB9F">Vanilla Sea Shells and Chocolate Caviar Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="44C72831">A perfect mix of the classic flavors. #TeamVanilla or #TeamChocolate</Text>
  <Text Key="E62722D9">A bit beyond al dente but it works for this vegetarian dish. #JustBeetIt</Text>
  <Text Key="1EAC335C">Semi-Firm Beet Noodles Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="B1E5AA76">A delightful departure from the flavor of raw bamboo. It was probably taken too far for the panda at heart. #Bamboozled</Text>
  <Text Key="11ED74A9">Glazed Heirloom Bamboo Roll Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="236C2FF8">Its tempting to build walls and structures with these little cubes. Don't forget to experience the taste. #PlayingWithMyFood</Text>
  <Text Key="90F13EF7">Crystallized Coco Blocks Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="A2BA96F8">The chef's homage to the amazingly streamlined shape of the wild tuna. #OpporTunatySiezed</Text>
  <Text Key="22F1C3F7">Cubed Ahi with Veggie Wasabi Matrix Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="9D780079">Sizzling until the last bite. #TastyBiteOfLuck</Text>
  <Text Key="191C967C">Sizzled Brisket over Sour Clover Salad Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="DE0CB0FB">Served without unnecessary humidity and bugs. #CulinarySafari</Text>
  <Text Key="74B4925A">Jungle Moss Egg with Lavender Wisps Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="781A0728">A fresh sampling of the most skilled fish in the sea. #JustForTheHalibut</Text>
  <Text Key="2C8C6347">Artisan Fish Trio Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="BBCFCA2B">The flavor of these tasty shrimp leaps out and attacks the tongue. #CrouchingTigerHiddenFlavor</Text>
  <Text Key="3C03BE2A">Tiger Shrimp in Smoked Dewdrop Broth Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="3546B6EE">The gels are concentrated fruit flavor balanced well with a neutral foam palette cleanser. #NestedFlavor</Text>
  <Text Key="8C915091">Spherized Fruit Gel in Foam Nest Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="B27A73D7">Delicate cups of veggie goodness, each celebrating its own flavor from the garden. #HiveFive</Text>
  <Text Key="9FEA6FAE">Honeycomb Garden Vegetable Cups Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="F207382C">Caution, can cause ice cream headaches without the ice cream. #IcebergAhead</Text>
  <Text Key="70785963">Glacier Infused Iceberg Lettuce Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="6BD8EA44">A single bite will take your mouth on a country holiday. #ReadyToPate</Text>
  <Text Key="2CA6860B">Rustic Pâté Drizzled in Aged Jus Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="DC508C68">Flavor sealed in by the solar curing process really pops when bitten into. #EcoFriendly</Text>
  <Text Key="EEE7C787">Cured Meat Crisps on Reclaimed Forest Wood Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="4873211A">This dish will make you fall in love with bacon all over again. #SixDegreesOfCandiedBacon</Text>
  <Text Key="F6BC8445">Savory Bacon Love Petals Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="38F2E683">Dreamt up by an astronaut that had enough of freeze dried food. #Eggstraterestrial</Text>
  <Text Key="69CE5ED2">Space Taco with Pearled Egg Core Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="926F8939">The suction cups contain bursts of tangy flavor. #EatOrBeEaten</Text>
  <Text Key="0FE9F53C">Free Range Sixam Pit Beast Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="E6ECFEA8">Fruit and honey are the best pairing to bring out the flavors of the finely sliced meat. #RazorThinMeats</Text>
  <Text Key="A8FCB1C7">Honeyed World Fruit Charcuterie Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="E38DC0CA">Layer after layer of berry flavor. #BerriedUnderLayers</Text>
  <Text Key="3E8D9FD5">Vertical Berry Cake Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="EE6F0CA7">Melted cheese at just the right temperature to not burn your mouth. #UnbeLAVAble</Text>
  <Text Key="3C219FDE">Volcano Pasta Simstagram Print</Text>
  <Text Key="4A0BDB1F">The Short Curtain Classic will provide such minimalist shade that you may need more. Even if you don't, you will want to add more.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBDB01C6">Short Curtain Classic</Text>
  <Text Key="592272CA">The Medium Curtain Classic will provide the perfect amount of shade that you will be content with just one.</Text>
  <Text Key="556915D5">Medium Curtain Classic</Text>
  <Text Key="B19D0395">The Tall Curtain Classic will provide so much shade that you might not realize it is day time.</Text>
  <Text Key="2D6E91B0">Tall Curtain Classic</Text>
  <Text Key="0A7FD0C5">It turned out much better than the Chef's signature dish, never mind that.</Text>
  <Text Key="010127C0">Chef's Signature Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="14022858">Nothing says "This is a place to eat!" like a sign which conveys that message. Showcasing your basic set of utensils, proper in any respectable establishment, this sign will tell your guests that no matter what they order, they can surely eat there.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C45A2D7">Utensil Heaven</Text>
  <Text Key="24E229E7">Attract the type of customers who can appreciate and become passionate about a good meal. No holding back with this sign!</Text>
  <Text Key="834BFF1E">House of the Rising Bun</Text>
  <Text Key="2C65B7CE">The story goes that this coat of arms was rejected by the Earl of Sandwich. His loss is your gain.</Text>
  <Text Key="DD307DF1">Coat of Utensils Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="DDE55379">This sign can warm you up on a cold day. Without words it can communicate the tastiest dishes to your customers. There is no room for misinterpretation here.</Text>
  <Text Key="382E1F7C">Only In Your Eyes</Text>
  <Text Key="3FE5F958">A masterpiece created by renowned artist Madame Quick. This piece was inspired by a long list of negative people in her life (we think they were ex-party animals). The strokes represent the tired mornings and the late nights the artist endured.</Text>
  <Text Key="D25645D7">Negative Spaces Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="590189C3">This sign adds that extra fancy flourish and class to your storefront. </Text>
  <Text Key="8C9F8812">Fancy Flourish Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="D70C54FA">Guaranteed to not change colors and stand the test of time. Seriously...it will!</Text>
  <Text Key="8386FBA5">5 Leaves Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="3663A1C5">Steel load bearing beams were recycled to make this sign. We just hope that whatever building that had those beams doesn't need them...that would be bad.</Text>
  <Text Key="6711CAC0">Industrial Strength Lettering Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="C49F61B4">This sign was constructed with only the most correct angles in mind.</Text>
  <Text Key="FEFF101B">The Right Angle Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="D19D5039">This highly specialized dishwasher will make your dishes so clean you will be able to see your reflection in them. Use what the pros use and rejoice on your reflection!</Text>
  <Text Key="2AAA9A3C">Washer Pro Free-Standing Dishwasher</Text>
  <Text Key="B0205003">What lies beyond these doors, we cannot really say. Will it be the place that your heart desires? The place which your stomach will grumble in anticipation? Or will it be the place you despise?\n\nIt is up to you and only you!</Text>
  <Text Key="FAFF6352">Beyond These Doors</Text>
  <Text Key="E30C5D32">It opens. It closes. It opens again! Stainless Steel doors for the masses or, why not, your own personal wonderland dream kitchen.</Text>
  <Text Key="A96482CD">All Steely And Chromed</Text>
  <Text Key="E36AD297">Soft Shadow Avornalino</Text>
  <Text Key="617FA199">Riverblossom Cranerlet Nuala</Text>
  <Text Key="BE13D728">Granite Falls Grappo Blanco</Text>
  <Text Key="C4BC87A7">Von Haunt Estate Meloire</Text>
  <Text Key="93ACC9F4">Large Stemmed Nectar Glass</Text>
  <Text Key="B15CD85B">Red Nectar Blend</Text>
  <Text Key="31AA0FB7">Monte Vista Reserve Renoit</Text>
  <Text Key="11BA0B26">Large Stemmed White Nectar Glass</Text>
  <Text Key="1FC44B39">White Nectar Blend</Text>
  <Text Key="6C7FDA2F">Butternut Squash Soup</Text>
  <Text Key="BFBD5DEE">Caesar Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="4E5BE54B">Clam Chowder</Text>
  <Text Key="F4F97587">Fruit Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="C13DF47C">Minestrone</Text>
  <Text Key="C7A86A6A">{S.Butternut Squash Soup}{P.Bowls of Butternut Squash Soup}</Text>
  <Text Key="346F980F">{S.Caesar Salad}{P.Caesar Salads}</Text>
  <Text Key="026AFB42">{S.Clam Chowder}{P.Bowls of Clam Chowder}</Text>
  <Text Key="64DFAC40">{S.Fruit Salad}{P.Bowls of Fruit Salad}</Text>
  <Text Key="B68A1CBF">{S.Minestrone}{P.Bowls of Minestrone}</Text>
  <Text Key="3F627425">Eggs Benedict</Text>
  <Text Key="AF97A670">Italian Meatballs</Text>
  <Text Key="D465A653">Tiramisu</Text>
  <Text Key="214447EC">{S.Experimental Dish}{P.Experimental Dishes}</Text>
  <Text Key="9630BBD8">{S.Eggs Benedict}{P.Plates of Eggs Benedict}</Text>
  <Text Key="3817F313">{S.Italian Meatballs}{P.Plates of Italian Meatballs}</Text>
  <Text Key="76FD2F8A">{S.Tiramisu}{P.Plates of Tiramisu}</Text>
  <Text Key="EB6ACAFA">Wood Plate</Text>
  <Text Key="15C80C67">Food Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="C9020355">Keep your dish a mystery.</Text>
  <Text Key="7863F870">Food Platter Lid</Text>
  <Text Key="45575B91">For preventing spills and splatter.</Text>
  <Text Key="AEFEFDE4">Frying Pan Lid</Text>
  <Text Key="ACBB3AF1">The ways of the warming lamp were supposedly lost during the first age of Sims and the stories have been generally regarded as a fable ever since. Until the glorious day arrived from whence suddenly the Warming Lamp made a triumphant return! Heat thyselves in comfort!</Text>
  <Text Key="52CB3DC4">Mythic Patio Warming Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="D6565C63">You deserve the most out of your host. Not a little. Not some. The MOST! So check out this beauty and maximize your host's potential. Do it for the sake of the customers. Do it for the children. Do it for the world!</Text>
  <Text Key="400A1932">"Host with the Most" Host Station</Text>
  <Text Key="B7570F13">Classy, smooth, polished. All words to describe the ideal host also apply to this host station. Never settle for second best.</Text>
  <Text Key="C18A21C2">"Wood You Like to Sit" Host Station</Text>
  <Text Key="927A8269">Love that chandelier look, but don’t want to invest in a huge lighting piece that weighs a ton and can’t really take everywhere? A piece that you can have only one of? Say no more! The Just Like a Chandelier Light has all the wonderful visual components similar to a chandelier but in a smaller size so you can have more of them if you wish!\n\nIts reflective particles will make your space the happening place!\n\nNote: Blinding may occur. You have been warned.</Text>
  <Text Key="BF42454C">Just Like A Chandelier</Text>
  <Text Key="0C2A5E8C">An eclectic and elegant light piece that invokes wonder…and maybe hunger? It can look like a strawberry or is it more like a cheese ball?\n\nSee? It is also making you hungry! It is doing its job!</Text>
  <Text Key="30397B43">Meshed Up Pendant Light</Text>
  <Text Key="FC98D0C0">Light will go round and round with this rounded contraption, and it will also serve you as a decorative piece if needed. Modern, elegant, and functional!</Text>
  <Text Key="4E64DB8F">Rounded Luminosity</Text>
  <Text Key="820291E5">It’s a light in a box!\n\nFor your celling...\n\nIt's a light in a box!</Text>
  <Text Key="9EA35D60">Boxed In</Text>
  <Text Key="4BB5BF43">Seen originally in restaurants to create a romantic and cozy feel. This updated version will evoke those same feelings of romance and you will get points for giving it a modern touch.</Text>
  <Text Key="B3D33092">Light In A Bottle</Text>
  <Text Key="AC0D3D8F">It will keep the light safe, it will keep the light true.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D4A5256">Little Light</Text>
  <Text Key="EB64C44A">You don't need to be a nature enthusiast to enjoy this cute little accent piece that will brighten up your Lot instantly. Be green chic with this delicate and luxurious bamboo inspired decorative piece and amaze your guests!\n\nNote: Bamboos may vary, pandas not included.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA745255">Bambuluxious</Text>
  <Text Key="F82CF38E">Coming in a gorgeous brushed metal or bronze finish, this light will impress all. Make no mistake - this is no first draft lamp. This is a polished, quality item that girl lights want and boy lights want to be!</Text>
  <Text Key="59B14BB1">Polished Metal Wall Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="B5E29225">Anyone can just grab a boring old bulb to light up a room. But for those with a more discerning taste look no further than the Modern Wall Mounted Light Bar. It will illuminate your life as well as your kitchen.\n\nDisclaimer: Results vary. Product may not illuminate your life.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE364FA0">Modern Wall Mounted Light Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="BEA9400D">This beautiful wall sconce emits light through a delicate filigree to perfectly create that soft lighting tone. It took 4 versions to perfect this design; previous iterations were known to catch fire, explode, have electrical issues, even cause death. But it's totally safe now. Really.</Text>
  <Text Key="B1E9EF58">Decorated Wall Sconce (Version 4)</Text>
  <Text Key="0C8D3A03">Where all the tasty dishes are listed.</Text>
  <Text Key="7FFE0152">Menu</Text>
  <Text Key="6B9CA422">The Catch of the Day Chalkboard is a great way to let Sims know special ingredients are cooking in the kitchen. Whether the catch is fresh fish, fresh vegetables, or meaty cows/pigs/chickens, these boards will cover it all. Just don't erase the pictures. It took a really long time to draw them.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF48219D">Catch of the Day Chalkboards</Text>
  <Text Key="C9CE603D">The falling leaves perfectly represent change and movement in the world we live in. Symbolically speaking, time continues and the millions of leaves (Sims) flutter and fall with barely a sign from the universe that they even existed at all. Gosh, that's a bit sad really. But the colors are pretty.</Text>
  <Text Key="33D436A8">The Leaf Pile Prints</Text>
  <Text Key="B10ABCD6">Having trouble getting hungry? Well hang this on your wall and let the tummy grumbling commence! Just be advised: it is NOT recommended to actually eat this item. It is just a picture and should not be confused with real food. (The lawyers made us say this. One Sim chokes on a mouthful of canvas and suddenly WE'RE the ones to blame. Seriously, who eats a painting anyway?)</Text>
  <Text Key="2E111889">Sunny Side Up Prints</Text>
  <Text Key="A43CBFB3">A series of images that focus on natural landscapes, old buildings, some familiar faces, and most importantly...stillness. Just glancing at the collection evokes a sense of calm gentleness. It's the perfect decoration to bring the serenity of the outdoors inside any room!</Text>
  <Text Key="C64DDFE2">The Calm Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="D0A8725E">Ah, that first swirl of juice in the glass. The sound of it splashing to the bottom, the sweet aroma wafting purposefully up to the nose, the taste as it washes over taste buds… well you get none of that! It's just a picture after all. But it sure looks pretty.</Text>
  <Text Key="6598F161">A Perfect Swirl</Text>
  <Text Key="F1145BE7">An exercise in abstraction, this piece focuses on the harmonious aura generated by a perfectly set table as interpolated through subconscious aural resonance. (It's actually just a collection of multi-colored circles, but that description won't sell some units.)</Text>
  <Text Key="D887F51E">A Set Table</Text>
  <Text Key="A4F60626">Gilfred von Bonhomme was pondering his latest treatise regarding oil on canvas when he walked thoroughly into a protruding branch. Though his first reaction was one of rage, von Bonhomme soon saw that his transgressor was a beautiful, ancient blossoming tree. He immediately set forth painting it. Now, to celebrate the 100 year anniversary, we re-release The Branching Bloom print.</Text>
  <Text Key="65314C39">The Branching Bloom</Text>
  <Text Key="90C658B8">Contains all the pepper you will need.</Text>
  <Text Key="62C571B7">Pepper Shaker</Text>
  <Text Key="540DABFA">Let your imagination and inspiration shine through color!</Text>
  <Text Key="454D50A5">Coloring Placemat</Text>
  <Text Key="190239F6">The plight of the distiller is one of flavorful production, then waste. Ancient oak barrels can only hold fine youthful liquors for so long before they peter out and are sent to the yards to decay and grow mold. Portles, the head distiller at Landgraab’s Stouts, shook his fist at the metaphorical waste and began planting lovely plants in his old barrels. “Waste not, want not, and grow hearty, my green pretties,” he is reported to have said.</Text>
  <Text Key="41570B29">Stouter Stuff Potter</Text>
  <Text Key="5DAEFA8C">These gorgeous, radiant, and rainbow defying fronds are the latest product of the best efforts of Chloro-physicists. They combine the finest and most vibrant colors in an unassuming package that delights children and terrifies certain birds.</Text>
  <Text Key="1D2C8F43">The Exotic Fronds</Text>
  <Text Key="F62976C3">Every Sim should have the agricultural capabilities to build their own tire plant. Now with the House Rubber Starter Kit, your household can experience the feeling of rubber without concerns of the actual rubber yield or difficult task of manufacturing tires. However, be warned! When burned, the House Rubber Starter Kit does reek of a low quality tire fire.</Text>
  <Text Key="8BC9BF12">House Rubber Starter Kit</Text>
  <Text Key="2F6C0A35">After years of daintily clipping locks and trimming whiskers, Cornelius Shear of Windenburg threw in his well-haired towel and dedicated his few remaining days to art and sculpture. While his first unsuccessful pieces focused on the affliction of male pattern baldness, his final, and most successful piece, took the famous stripe from barber shops, narrowed the top, and stuck a plant in it. Magnificent!</Text>
  <Text Key="69BFB7D0">The Barber’s Vase</Text>
  <Text Key="8D2768AB">A dapper lass by the name of Winsome Jass spied a tree set to die with not a bird or a fly. She ambled to the tree, batted away a bee, and plucked its last berried branch. Into her satchel it was tucked! The tree died, ‘cus from the clouds water was not supplied, but the berry lived then, as it lives now, in The Berry End.</Text>
  <Text Key="95C351AA">The Berry End</Text>
  <Text Key="D970B144">Although the original version of the Perfect Bloomin’ Poof was an artisan creation made by Sim hands, it was imperfect. Such is the way of the artisan. However, Perfect is in the name, and perfection is required. Therefore, enormous and terrifying robots were brought in to meticulously and perfectly shear the Poof until it appeared in a subdued, spherical pose.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2852B0B">Perfect Bloomin’ Poof</Text>
  <Text Key="1EEF45FF">Deep beneath the surface, numerous scientists reside without access to sunlight, air that hasn’t been filtered fourteen times, or good, modern television. Tasked with proving that life can exist in the outer reaches of space, these scientists have largely failed. However, one enterprising, lab coat adorned scientist invented the Scientific Sprout. Surprisingly, plant life can exist in any environment, as long as it’s in a beaker.</Text>
  <Text Key="82A89B26">Scientific Sprout</Text>
  <Text Key="2B7D29AC">A great alternative during drought years when Water Lilies are hard to find.</Text>
  <Text Key="BF8C75E3">Table Lilies</Text>
  <Text Key="8ACF4B5D">A lively and chic alternative to decorate your walls and add a bit of life to your Lot. We are not sure of the species, but we think it is delightful.</Text>
  <Text Key="A1698C48">Planted Life</Text>
  <Text Key="410A9867">Invented for the scientists working in liquid soap factories. Every rug now comes lemon scented.</Text>
  <Text Key="C405029E">No Slip - No Mess Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="E2248642">The only vase that will do when you need to display a bouquet of 2 dozen sunflowers.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA7D153D">Potted into a Corner</Text>
  <Text Key="66756B55">Where else would you store your 5 gallon tubs of mayonnaise?\n\nWhat? Mayonnaise not your thing? Oookey...</Text>
  <Text Key="3011B070">Industrial Pantry Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="B6C94867">The room divider you can still pass notes through.</Text>
  <Text Key="F2A2129E">Slat Wall Room Divider</Text>
  <Text Key="46C54657">Bring the forest inside without all that pesky foliage.</Text>
  <Text Key="01F55F2E">Birch Tree Room Divider</Text>
  <Text Key="BB70C5FD">A weight saving technique turned into a trendy new design.</Text>
  <Text Key="0AE97568">Windowed Slat Wall Room Divider</Text>
  <Text Key="89018B2F">Often replaced by dancing teenagers spinning handheld signs, this sign draws in customers with its more traditional approach.</Text>
  <Text Key="5C4EB676">Restaurant Menu Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="2E6DA2A6">Years of R&amp;D, millions of Simoleons spent, and numerous interns were lost to bring you this technological achievement. It perfectly simulates a hole in the ground.</Text>
  <Text Key="70B479B9">The Executive Cave Nectar Cooler</Text>
  <Text Key="223C86A6">Do not underestimate this little menu. In a sea of queues, sticky menus and hard to read chalkboards, this little guy saves the day telling you exactly what you need to know. The information held by this small table menu can potentially save your life...I mean your day!</Text>
  <Text Key="C463E5B9">Your Handy Table Menu</Text>
  <Text Key="D3D52FB4">The perfect wooden platter to serve your guests or customers. Includes stainless steel pitcher and hand-woven cloth napkins to show them that you’re a proper host.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F7B1A1B">Proper Pitcher Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="24B590B7">Ultimate olive fans will love this jar of salty fruit. That’s right, olives are fruit. The more you know…</Text>
  <Text Key="D229D00E">Olive Olives Jar</Text>
  <Text Key="D5154B11">The Spicebox Duo is the latest in spice-storage technology. Secure latches keep your spices fresh as the day they were harvested.</Text>
  <Text Key="61CEB464">Spicebox Duo</Text>
  <Text Key="E12A2903">Kitchenwurx is the top provider of quality cookware. These pots are great for boiling, steaming, stirring, or simply being shiny.</Text>
  <Text Key="EE139E52">Kitchenwurx Pot Set</Text>
  <Text Key="00CE5365">This swanky cardholder is a great accent to your professional décor. People will think you’re important since even your cards need their own clothes.</Text>
  <Text Key="432FE9E0">Leaning Diagonals</Text>
  <Text Key="CB67331A">A little salt, pepper, and proper napkins go a long way.</Text>
  <Text Key="06D81A45">S.P.N.</Text>
  <Text Key="C81C1634">Guess how many peppers are in the jar.\n\nIf you guess correctly, you win!\n\nNote: We are not sure what yet, but something!</Text>
  <Text Key="B6D6059B">Pot o’ Peppers</Text>
  <Text Key="99768EB0">This classy wall decoration is the perfect fit for any establishment looking to bring in fresh clientele.</Text>
  <Text Key="5C4BAF5F">School of Class</Text>
  <Text Key="8D15ED0D">Representing the oh so current design of the building this is placed on.</Text>
  <Text Key="F4466658">Sign of the Times</Text>
  <Text Key="2D8E4940">Unreadable to Sims under a certain age.</Text>
  <Text Key="D902DD0F">Casually Cursive Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="D37D77EB">This sign is perfect for the place that prides itself in being niche and/or unique. Set your place apart from the rest by confusing your guests and have them asking "Excuse me, where are the forks?" as they peruse your menu realizing that most dishes will be a challenge to eat.</Text>
  <Text Key="2326A1EA">No Forks Allowed!</Text>
  <Text Key="07AA38B6">Stand out from the standard signs above the more common shops in the neighborhood.</Text>
  <Text Key="476439E9">Bold and Beautiful Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="06ED9AE2">Soothing bubbles are a great way to let your friends know that you’ve got cash and class. After all, you’ve got to be rich to afford that many bubbles.</Text>
  <Text Key="297B025D">Great Wall of Bubbles</Text>
  <Text Key="F1491F1F">A hint of color and shape to add pizzazz to the room. Perfect for those small spaces that you want to spruce up without making it look cramped.</Text>
  <Text Key="BFC78DC6">Sliver of Color Short Wall Accent</Text>
  <Text Key="005FB6CA">Need more than a hint of color? Add this unique shape graphic to your wall to add pizzazz to the room.</Text>
  <Text Key="4955A1D5">Sliver of Color Medium Wall Accent</Text>
  <Text Key="58DA4795">Really want to make a statement? Add a color and shape to add some (or a lot of) pizzazz to the room.</Text>
  <Text Key="215B1DB0">Sliver of Color Tall Wall Accent</Text>
  <Text Key="426EB923">When a plain wall just doesn't cut it, add some depth and flair with this.\n\nTake a long hard look and tell the world what you see in the depths of this adornment. Is it a flower? A torch? Let us know!</Text>
  <Text Key="69113CF2">Dry Leaf Lattice</Text>
  <Text Key="A2FA7FC1">The ship's log records coming across a harbor master trying to sink the S.S. Medicine to make an artificial reef. He needed weight to help the ship sink that would leave no trace. The captain donated the stores of sugar to this task. It was recorded that the Schooner full of sugar helped the S.S. Medicine go down.</Text>
  <Text Key="90FE8DF4">The Travers</Text>
  <Text Key="B8F97A0C">It is said that the lower shelf was only built so that there could be a top shelf.</Text>
  <Text Key="10DCF5C3">Within Reach Nectar Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="8B5A2CB4">The fancy all natural version of a wall socket air freshener.  </Text>
  <Text Key="8A0F811B">Lily of the Wall</Text>
  <Text Key="CDB15428">Don't leaf the light on.</Text>
  <Text Key="1926BA47">Twiggy's LED Accent</Text>
  <Text Key="EBDDD5CD">Add to a rare steak and serve to dragons. What? No dragons? That is fine, you can still add to a steak or anything you fancy and feed your guests.</Text>
  <Text Key="CE147618">Extra Virgin Olive Oil Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="73768124">Just the right size to break up the hard angles in your standard room.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D539D6B">Fluid Forms Short Lighted Wall</Text>
  <Text Key="ED46805D">Staring at it for too long may result in a queasy feeling.</Text>
  <Text Key="874F1B48">Fluid Forms Lighted Wall</Text>
  <Text Key="C3EDBD32">It almost feels like it will come crashing down on you.</Text>
  <Text Key="618AA2CD">Fluid Forms Tall Lighted Wall
</Text>
  <Text Key="6F9588E5">If the salt tips and spills into the soup you only have your shelf to blame.</Text>
  <Text Key="EC2C9260">Master Chef Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="30489EC2">It can hold ten thousand types of spoons, but maybe all you need is a knife. Isn't it beautiful though? Don't you think?</Text>
  <Text Key="2A24F6BD">Master Chef Shelf &amp; Utensil Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="24EB9FD6">Too heavy for the mischievous to run off with, this sign is here to stay. Look, but don't touch!</Text>
  <Text Key="A3085189">Signature Steel</Text>
  <Text Key="B7A64F45">This blank sign is the perfect blank canvas to create a sign that truly expresses the essence of your establishment. Mix and match different colors, wall decals, and sculptures to create the sign of your dreams.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D375B40">Unfulfilled Floor Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="C6477570">Ever wondered where those pesky menu handouts are? Never fear! This sign will not only display the specials, but itemizes the menu so well that you will never ask for a menu handout again.</Text>
  <Text Key="DF8E861F">What's On The Menu?</Text>
  <Text Key="1126FB0E">Created by a Master Calligrapher who used the finest llama hair brush. It is said that when viewing this sign, the spirit of the llamas engulfs your senses, making you wonder what is happening in the Lot the sign is displayed on.\n\nNote: No llamas were harmed when making the brushes.</Text>
  <Text Key="82C9CA31">Four Treasures of the Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="9A607368">An accent of color helps distract customers from your prices.</Text>
  <Text Key="F674CC87">Bite of Light Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="3EE09612">Created from a repurposed fast food burger grill, this sign gives a new life to your walls with 100% less grease.</Text>
  <Text Key="3624372D">Granite Grill Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="A5786BCF">Made to display the most valuable menu items to passing pedestrians while securing them behind 2 inch thick shatterproof glass. This menu will survive any natural disaster.</Text>
  <Text Key="42CFAB96">The Menu Archive</Text>
  <Text Key="B2C867FD">This blank sign is the perfect blank canvas to create a sign that truly expresses the essence of your establishment. Mix and match different colors, wall decals, and sculptures to create the sign of your dreams.</Text>
  <Text Key="80BABB68">Unfulfilled Wall Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="4241E4A6">The angles on this sign are pretty cute. That’s right.</Text>
  <Text Key="4C199FB9">Acute Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="1826B722">This blank sign is the perfect blank canvas to create a sign that truly expresses the essence of your establishment. Mix and match different colors, wall decals, and sculptures to create the sign of your dreams.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA93EA9D">Unfulfilled Hanging Wall Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="A20F6F66">A modern classic for when your washing needs go beyond the consumer level.</Text>
  <Text Key="7CC8B879">Industro-sink</Text>
  <Text Key="E3DC6CE6">So retro. It will make you see in black and white.\n\nSavalani's has done it again with this magnificent piece that just screams "blast from the past" even though it looks super trendy and modern. Savalani's vision for this stool was something that would make people wonder where it belonged.\n\nLegend says that the idea was taken from the mind of Savalani himself as he perused his wardrobe on what to wear one morning.</Text>
  <Text Key="62DC38F9">Retro Dinette Bar Stool</Text>
  <Text Key="8B9E0C91">A relic of an age long past, this particular style of booth is a frozen capsule of timeless elegance. One can almost picture the several generations of Sims sliding up close to their date to make a move!</Text>
  <Text Key="B70240E4">Retro Dinette Stretch Booth</Text>
  <Text Key="AEF4BF24">The perfect booth for couples! This model offers the latest privacy technology letting you get up close and snuggly with that special Sim-one without all those pesky stares.</Text>
  <Text Key="825DF76B">Straight Arrow High Back Plush Booth</Text>
  <Text Key="3088059D">Sometimes it's not prudent to sit directly next to someone at a straight booth. What would everyone say? The scandal! So yeah, it's probably best to sit right over there, bub! Across the table where I can see you.</Text>
  <Text Key="A6756B88">Retro Dinette Corner Booth</Text>
  <Text Key="1B389CC0">Not just a booth, but a tale of woe and morality. With but a mere 90 degree turn, what began as a tale of a booth with a straight path to success becomes one in which a booth becomes twisted and crooked. There aren't many ups and downs in the storyline to be sure, but there are a few lefts and rights.</Text>
  <Text Key="00627F8F">Angled High Back Plush Booth</Text>
  <Text Key="A60E2CBC">Another masterpiece by Savalani's, the famous furniture emporium. Its founder wanted to create a visionary chair that it is impossible to not sit up straight in...maybe? We guess. It looks deceptively simple, but it will be the best chair for great posture.</Text>
  <Text Key="0ECC0A13">Straight Back Plush Dining Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="FE3D52F9">Made from the finest pleather by the famous furniture emporium Savalani's. Even though they call themselves a furniture company, Savalani's can only make chairs, ok maybe tables, no...chairs, only chairs for sure. It is said that this particular model came inspired by the founder's journey in finding the perfect chair to ponder about life or have a meal pondering about life. We can't really say, but it is a pretty nice chair suitable for all your fancy table placement needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="8A8F05FC">Retro Dinette Dining Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="FDC06325">This wall-mounted stereo is intended for use at community venues. Playing more jazz subgenres than you knew existed.</Text>
  <Text Key="D314F2A0">Venue Wall Speaker: Jazz</Text>
  <Text Key="C6D067FE">Neatly pressed and placed for your everyday dining needs. This chic table can be used for holding your most important possessions or impressing your guests as if you were giving a 5 star dining experience. Just be careful and don't remove the cloth...just don't.</Text>
  <Text Key="D7417E81">Dressed Squared Table</Text>
  <Text Key="2585402A">Do not be fooled by its appearance! This table can give your Lot the necessary ambiance to provide an excellent dining experience. Just don't try to wash the cloth...</Text>
  <Text Key="DF31DEB5">Dressed All Around Table</Text>
  <Text Key="2902C0C1">If you fancy that industrial chic look, this is the table for you! The fusion of metal and wood gives extra support for those tasty meals. Also useful to display garden gnome collections, if you dare!</Text>
  <Text Key="267180F4">Industrial Wood Square Table</Text>
  <Text Key="B47E34CD">Having an event? Looking to spice your home with that formal dining room flair? This table is perfect for any occasion when you desire a little bit of something extra.\n\nNote: Cloth is not removable.</Text>
  <Text Key="04F96318">Dressed Up Dining</Text>
  <Text Key="5EEB6AF0">Be the envy of friends and strangers as they gaze into your dining room with this trendy and sophisticated table. Inspired by restaurants' communal tables, this table features a rustic design that can fit any style.</Text>
  <Text Key="A2056E9F">Not A Communal Table</Text>
  <Text Key="DE2C4E93">Metal and wood combine to make the illusion of a communal table on any Lot. Have an event or dine by yourself. All that matters is that this table would make your dining experience something to talk about. May it be what you were looking for.</Text>
  <Text Key="085EC842">May Be Communal Table</Text>
  <Text Key="738C69DC">The fusion of metal and wood comes together with precise angles to support the tastiest meals. Also useful to display garden gnome collections.</Text>
  <Text Key="F99D49B3">Bar Height Industrial Wood Square Table</Text>
  <Text Key="4CB5AF9D">The extra height works with bar stools so you can make sure all friends and neighbors can see this table. The point of a trendy sophisticated table is to draw the envy of friends and strangers.</Text>
  <Text Key="995A4988">Not A Communal Bar Height Table</Text>
  <Text Key="2412CF12">Metal and wood combine to make the illusion of a communal table on any Lot - Now in Bar height! This table will serve many needs, but more importantly it will serve what you'll have for dinner.</Text>
  <Text Key="9A83922D">May Be Bar Height Communal Table</Text>
  <Text Key="5B43DE3E">Quite the statement piece if you are looking to wow and amaze your guests as they stroll down the hallways of your Lot - or if you are looking to make your abode look expensive without much effort. Beautifully crafted, its function is still questioned, but who cares? It is gorgeous!</Text>
  <Text Key="4F9477C1">Marvel The Marvelous Marbled</Text>
  <Text Key="6F20F6BD">Have your hallways help you exchange greetings in style. This hallway piece has a unique and intricate design that will have your guests wonder if someone can actually fit inside if opened the moment they walk in 'til the moment they walk out.</Text>
  <Text Key="50233228">Aplenty Slats</Text>
  <Text Key="BDE36112">Just a regular table knife.</Text>
  <Text Key="678CA82D">Table Knife</Text>
  <Text Key="6990AE3B">Need to place an order? Need more water? Need a menu? Need some plates cleared? Whatever your restaurant needs, this waiter station comes packed with all the modern technology to make the wait staff shine!</Text>
  <Text Key="2F620F9A">"Always Waiting" Waiter Station</Text>
  <Text Key="1FE1AFF3">Jazz</Text>
  <Text Key="56C0C2A4">Add to a Half Wall for a polished look.</Text>
  <Text Key="A213A9EB">Slatted Wall Trim</Text>
  <Text Key="19E90A1E">Add to a Half Wall for a polished look.</Text>
  <Text Key="E1650D21">Glass Wall Trim</Text>
  <Text Key="17F3325E">{0.SimFirstName} cannot sit at a table that is not {M0.his}{F0.hers}.</Text>
  <Text Key="8FA47978">Sit</Text>
  <Text Key="D1B9C44C">The Chef is currently working on an order.</Text>
  <Text Key="CCD9E8BC">Place Order</Text>
  <Text Key="3532EB99">Send Chef Home</Text>
  <Text Key="B90F9DBD">Compliment Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="B1A51B74">Insult Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="5FCE4205">Add Order</Text>
  <Text Key="B7B84159">Add Order (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="AA258343">Begin (test)</Text>
  <Text Key="FD85B676">Compliment Cooking</Text>
  <Text Key="91320C7A">Debug: Route to Chef Station</Text>
  <Text Key="D14D4F3A">Send Chef Home</Text>
  <Text Key="1E9EB22B">Hire {2.SimName} as a Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="4ABC5063">There is already a Chef hired on this lot.</Text>
  <Text Key="C41BE61A">Hire Specific Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="DC174573">Insult Cooking</Text>
  <Text Key="2B600314">Talk To Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="3AB36971">Chef Station Pan (test)</Text>
  <Text Key="27D1A47F">Cook at Pan (test)</Text>
  <Text Key="B072EF9F">Currently banned from the restaurant.</Text>
  <Text Key="52E3212E">The Chef is currently working on an order.</Text>
  <Text Key="C2752808">Place Order</Text>
  <Text Key="A6E96DDC">place order NPC (debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="EF1D4DB9">Chef Station Pot (test)</Text>
  <Text Key="5871A065">Cook at Pot (test)</Text>
  <Text Key="FC2440BB">Chef Station Prep (test)</Text>
  <Text Key="C241C590">All right, I'll get out of your way. Just let me finish up and collect my things.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D83368D">Send Chef Home</Text>
  <Text Key="27C0A111">Serve (test)</Text>
  <Text Key="DB34FE48">The Chef is not available to talk right now! Come back later!</Text>
  <Text Key="B31397E4">Oh, well thank you! You are a good customer.</Text>
  <Text Key="24F37F3B">Wow, how often do I get complimented! NEVER. Come back soon!</Text>
  <Text Key="2F463354">{0.SimFirstName}, you are the only one that understands my cooking! Thank you!</Text>
  <Text Key="CF1B5339">Compliment the Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="19296E6A">Customers are loving your cooking Chef! Keep up the good work!</Text>
  <Text Key="5B3B4BEC">The Chef is not available to talk right now. Come back later!</Text>
  <Text Key="8DBE7384">You want more bread!? It will be extra! You're pushing your luck, little Sim!</Text>
  <Text Key="7C946E4F">What did you say to me?! How dare you!</Text>
  <Text Key="3EE6D1E5">If you don't like it, then get out of my kitchen! The nerve!!</Text>
  <Text Key="729A5448">Insult the Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="13BC4196">The customers are furious! What are you doing back there!? Pull yourself together and cook better food!</Text>
  <Text Key="B20450F9">Wait for Order</Text>
  <Text Key="E247A08E">Buy a Restaurant</Text>
  <Text Key="CD6AA119">Your Sim needs to be sitting in front of a placemat to draw on it.</Text>
  <Text Key="844003C6">Remove Food Poisoning</Text>
  <Text Key="71BE5A4C">Add Food Poisoning</Text>
  <Text Key="FAEEDE74">Cook Experimental Food</Text>
  <Text Key="1C967D60">Debug: Route to Host Station</Text>
  <Text Key="0CCA8E5A">Here's your table. Enjoy your meal.</Text>
  <Text Key="BAB498DB">Be Seated</Text>
  <Text Key="8493E689">Take Reservation</Text>
  <Text Key="A9ECE64C">Browse Reservations</Text>
  <Text Key="89C62CE9">{0.SimFirstName} has already claimed a table. {M0.He}{F0.She} must Give Up Table before claiming a new one.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6DC02F9">Request Table</Text>
  <Text Key="C0647104">Reserve Table</Text>
  <Text Key="F8129E98">Right This Way</Text>
  <Text Key="0EE36741">Buy a Restaurant</Text>
  <Text Key="CAA923C5">You liked the food, yes? Wonderful! I will let the Chef know how happy you were when I have a chance!</Text>
  <Text Key="1BB8092E">Ask to Deliver Compliment</Text>
  <Text Key="C5ED16CC">I'm sorry to hear that you didn't like the food. I will inform the Chef as soon as possible! Sorry about that!</Text>
  <Text Key="869A77F3">Ask To Deliver Insult</Text>
  <Text Key="0F562362">Brag about Surviving Food Poisoning</Text>
  <Text Key="B8F0060A">Hear about {1.SimFirstName}'s Food Poisoning</Text>
  <Text Key="20653371">Complain about Food Poisoning</Text>
  <Text Key="1B6B91CA">Be Fed a Bite by {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="D472CF6B">Complain about Dish Preparation</Text>
  <Text Key="36806A8A">Complain about Dish</Text>
  <Text Key="424B2512">Listen to {1.SimFirstName}'s Complaint</Text>
  <Text Key="6C27FA78">Express Gastronomical Confusion</Text>
  <Text Key="6C27FA7B">Enthuse about Taste and Texture</Text>
  <Text Key="6C27FA7A">Scowl at Plate Layout</Text>
  <Text Key="6C27FA7D">Lament On Meal's Carbon Emissions</Text>
  <Text Key="0EED52A9">Bemoan Lack of Banana for Scale</Text>
  <Text Key="45B1CF6E">Debate Flavor Profiles</Text>
  <Text Key="45B1CF6C">Brainstorm Methods of Chef-napping</Text>
  <Text Key="45B1CF6B">Question Meal's Social Consciousness</Text>
  <Text Key="45B1CF6A">Meditate upon Sublime Flavors</Text>
  <Text Key="4CA5AA27">Savor the Flavors</Text>
  <Text Key="28B560E4">Discuss Flavor Profile</Text>
  <Text Key="4DFDE817">Discuss Food Flavors</Text>
  <Text Key="B7F2B055">Discuss Food Flavors with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="82A92893">Rave about the Dish Complexity</Text>
  <Text Key="82A92890">Comment on Bold Flavors</Text>
  <Text Key="82A92891">Relish Cuisine's Delicious Nature</Text>
  <Text Key="82A92896">Beam Blissful Feelings of Food Transcendence</Text>
  <Text Key="82A92897">Debate possibility of Food Coma</Text>
  <Text Key="C6C0E9E5">Enthuse about Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="0143BEDA">Be Checked Up on by Waiter</Text>
  <Text Key="D9D5C652">There is already a Chef hired on this lot.</Text>
  <Text Key="E7EDF54F">Hire Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="B9E7F677">Hire Personal Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="91223291">This is the current cooking style.</Text>
  <Text Key="4AEED2CD">Request to Cook Carefully</Text>
  <Text Key="957AA9AD">The chef will cook more slowly but produce higher quality meals.</Text>
  <Text Key="6CEBB167">Carefully</Text>
  <Text Key="44C0F94C">Request to Cook Normally</Text>
  <Text Key="B761FFBC">A balance between cooking speed and meal quality.</Text>
  <Text Key="43980DEC">Normally</Text>
  <Text Key="97209EEA">Request to Cook Quickly</Text>
  <Text Key="2803664A">The chef will cook more quickly at the expense of meal quality.</Text>
  <Text Key="B9AA3036">Quickly</Text>
  <Text Key="F04325D6">{0.SimFirstName} has hired a new chef. {1.SimName} will arrive for {M1.his}{F1.her} first shift as soon as possible.\n\nBe sure to track {1.SimFirstName}'s skills in the Manage Employees window.</Text>
  <Text Key="AAF1B2E0">Hire Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="B38AED54">{0.SimFirstName} has hired a new host. {1.SimName} will arrive for {M1.his}{F1.her} first shift as soon as possible.\n\nBe sure to track {1.SimFirstName}'s skills in the Manage Employees window.</Text>
  <Text Key="0C6B9EA2">Hire Host</Text>
  <Text Key="B76DBE74">{0.SimFirstName} has hired a new {M1.waiter}{F1.waitress}. {1.SimName} will arrive for {M1.his}{F1.her} first shift as soon as possible.\n\nBe sure to track {1.SimFirstName}'s skills in the Manage Employees window.</Text>
  <Text Key="780D0E02">Hire Waiter</Text>
  <Text Key="DB0CE93F">Choose a dish and/or beverage from your menu for your customer to order.</Text>
  <Text Key="48CA6F29">This Sim has recently been checked on.</Text>
  <Text Key="089AC511">Welcome to my restaurant. I trust everything is going well.
</Text>
  <Text Key="50E83E16">I'm stopping by to make sure this restaurant is living up to your expectations so far.</Text>
  <Text Key="D1691E01">Welcome! I hope to hear you are having a great meal. Our Chef has some serious culinary talent. 
</Text>
  <Text Key="74438E0E">I hope you brought your appetite. Let me know if you need a recommendation today.</Text>
  <Text Key="68689CDE">Just checking in to make sure you are getting the service you need. 
</Text>
  <Text Key="9A2AEC74">Check On Table</Text>
  <Text Key="73601593">The Sim must have received their meal to comp their food.</Text>
  <Text Key="C22949A3">This table's food has already been comped.</Text>
  <Text Key="AAFEB195">Comp Food</Text>
  <Text Key="10379872">The restaurant will be charged the cost of the desserts.</Text>
  <Text Key="6485D81A">The table has already been offered a free menu item.</Text>
  <Text Key="98251306">The Sim must have received their meal to offer them free dessert.</Text>
  <Text Key="FB23ECFE">Give Table Free Dessert</Text>
  <Text Key="E0E2493D">The restaurant will be charged the cost of the drinks.</Text>
  <Text Key="DD3BC01D">The Sim must have received their meal to offer them free drinks.</Text>
  <Text Key="BD11BDB7">Give Table Free Drinks</Text>
  <Text Key="2C8415FD">Prioritizing a table's food will help it come out more quickly.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B118DAF">This table's order has already been prioritized.</Text>
  <Text Key="A85EF6F7">Prioritize Food</Text>
  <Text Key="F54EA67E">This Sim has already been recommended a dish.</Text>
  <Text Key="96D39315">Dishes can only be recommend to customers wanting a recommendation. These customers will have a question mark over their heads.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB5B5523">This Sim has already decided what to order.</Text>
  <Text Key="F1737D27">This dish was made with a fresh shipment of the best ingredients. You are really missing out. Maybe come back and try it next time.</Text>
  <Text Key="577FA270">May I recommend the Chef's Choice. The Chef has crafted a treat for your tastebuds.\n\nNo. I hope the Chef doesn't take it too personally.</Text>
  <Text Key="4DBE551D">Try this dish. It's a recipe that has been handed down in my family for generations. I'll make sure the Chef cooks it to meet my Grandmother's standards.</Text>
  <Text Key="B2D6CD2F">You won't try this dish. It's a recipe that has been handed down in my family for generations. I guess it is something you have to grow up eating.</Text>
  <Text Key="1842AE5D">Our staff is loving the flavors brought out in this dish. We all highly recommend it! I see you would rather not trust public opinion though. Next time maybe.</Text>
  <Text Key="1529AF08">Here is my recommendation. The fresh ingredients will provide a fantastic flavor, but I see you want something with a more aged taste.</Text>
  <Text Key="34FEB41B">This dish was made with a fresh shipment of the best ingredients. You won't be disappointed with this selection.</Text>
  <Text Key="83ED68CE">Our staff is loving the flavors brought out in this dish. We all highly recommend it! May I say you have excellent taste by accepting this recommendation.</Text>
  <Text Key="38C56546">May I recommend the Chef's Choice? The Chef has crafted a treat for your tastebuds. Quite the symphony of flavors!\n\nYes? Excellent! The Chef will be happy to hear that.</Text>
  <Text Key="982F773B">Here is my recommendation. The ingredients are fresh from the farm this morning. The fresh ingredients will provide a fantastic flavor.</Text>
  <Text Key="936AF877">Recommend Dish</Text>
  <Text Key="0EACA084">This Sim has already been welcomed.</Text>
  <Text Key="66D8B0A1">Welcome</Text>
  <Text Key="41403109">Post Photo on Simstagram</Text>
  <Text Key="97A860D6">Report Food Poisoning</Text>
  <Text Key="921B2129">Post Photo on Simstagram</Text>
  <Text Key="69AD341D">Put in Inventory</Text>
  <Text Key="83397F37">Clean Up</Text>
  <Text Key="31A7047D">Draw on Placemat</Text>
  <Text Key="65032095">There's no room for a drawing placemat on the table.</Text>
  <Text Key="2CF94CE3">This table has been claimed by other diners.</Text>
  <Text Key="5D5DE624">{0.SimFirstName} already has a table. {M0.He}{F0.She} should give up {M0.his}{F0.her} current table to get a new one.</Text>
  <Text Key="62AA5A5B">Wait to be Seated</Text>
  <Text Key="547E09F0">Give Up Table</Text>
  <Text Key="239EFFD3">Claim Table</Text>
  <Text Key="EC958B78">The umbrella is in the way.</Text>
  <Text Key="8ED10C55">SimCity Cheesecake</Text>
  <Text Key="526075FD">Tiered Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="0DC52568">Ask to Deliver Compliment to Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="92070B1D">Ask to Deliver Insult to Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="5F73FACD">{0.SimFirstName} took a photo of an Experimental Dish. It can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="76D6228A">Take Photo of Experimental Food</Text>
  <Text Key="2B52A59D">Dump Dishes</Text>
  <Text Key="EDD51471">Waiter Idle</Text>
  <Text Key="79BDA03C">There isn't enough room to place another item at the table.</Text>
  <Text Key="6DFCE3D7">Blue Confetti Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="F4DB18E1">Chocolate Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="4291ED38">Strawberry Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="EBBA1344">White Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="65EC4DA2">React to Food</Text>
  <Text Key="8E36C9A3">Your Sims must claim a table before placing an order.</Text>
  <Text Key="8BD3D390">End Meal and Pay Bill</Text>
  <Text Key="1C9C9B17">Will make this table available to others. All food will be cleared.</Text>
  <Text Key="31BF8A0A">The restaurant hopes you enjoyed your meal! Simoleons have been automatically deducted from the household funds.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDC4BB0D">{0.SimName} has abandoned {M0.his}{F0.her} current dining table. If {M0.he}{F0.she} wants another table, {M0.he}{F0.she} can request one from the host.</Text>
  <Text Key="11AEB4C7">Give Up Table</Text>
  <Text Key="D17D1613">End Meal and Pay Bill</Text>
  <Text Key="3E92DD9A">React to Spill</Text>
  <Text Key="57CF09A1">Your waiter will be bringing your food soon. Are you sure you want to cancel your order?</Text>
  <Text Key="D7E194C5">Wait for Order to be Delivered</Text>
  <Text Key="A909A752">Your waiter will come to your table soon to take your order. Are you sure you want to cancel?</Text>
  <Text Key="369AB056">Wait to Place Order with Wait Staff</Text>
  <Text Key="084571FF">Thanks for being such a fantastic customer! This one is on the house!</Text>
  <Text Key="3327F231">Serve Food</Text>
  <Text Key="A48E9219">Order for Table</Text>
  <Text Key="3809ACCF">Order for Table</Text>
  <Text Key="AA78B06A">Pick Up Food Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="1812F2BA">Pickup Food Platter (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="A5C7450B">Serve Food</Text>
  <Text Key="173F690B">Serve Food (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="BE5BB819">Thank you, we'll bring your order out as soon as it's ready.</Text>
  <Text Key="B1785421">Take Order</Text>
  <Text Key="9B2D7480">Request Table</Text>
  <Text Key="D4340F08">End Meal and Pay Bill</Text>
  <Text Key="367DDC52">{0.SimFirstName} has already claimed a table. {M0.He}{F0.She} must Give Up Table before claiming a new one.</Text>
  <Text Key="747C9357">Request Table</Text>
  <Text Key="C8470BBA">Listen to Jazz</Text>
  <Text Key="58906FE3">Listen to Jazz</Text>
  <Text Key="8AA9EEDD">Cook an Experimental Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="11619E39">You'll need to taste an experimental dish at a restaurant before you can cook it yourself!</Text>
  <Text Key="D17C41A5">Cook an Experimental Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="1B4E6F3E">Go to Table</Text>
  <Text Key="778DEA1E">Check Up on Table</Text>
  <Text Key="0D94FBDF">Pay Bill</Text>
  <Text Key="9026E1FD">Order for Table</Text>
  <Text Key="9251990A">For Most Family Dinners</Text>
  <Text Key="DD26122D">Trendy Dining</Text>
  <Text Key="003BA9F6">Rustic Diner</Text>
  <Text Key="629FD93D">Botanical Eating</Text>
  <Text Key="5F610024">From Our Kitchen To Yours</Text>
  <Text Key="7714979E">Kitchen Professional</Text>
  <Text Key="D35D43D4">Dining In The Open</Text>
  <Text Key="F6DC6E26">Relax to Jazz</Text>
  <Text Key="D17C1767">Jazz</Text>
  <Text Key="32A1D4A7">Fully Fulfilled Hanging Wall Sign Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="CD12C702">This Booth Collection comes with a table to match! Perfect for the fancy pants restaurateur who doesn't have time to do the matching themselves!</Text>
  <Text Key="FA1DB4FD">Retro Dinette Stretch Booth Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="738DBF86">Retro Dinette Corner Booth Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="AF8CB66B">Straight Arrow High Back Plush Booth Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="F944CED0">Angled High Back Plush Booth Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="C5EF83FB">Fully Fulfilled Floor Sign Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="C7CD6DD4">Why create a sign from scratch when someone else has already done the creating part for you?</Text>
  <Text Key="03740ABB">Fully Fulfilled Wall Sign Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="15C9DA20">Waiter</Text>
  <Text Key="B89EB8E1">Request Cooking Speed</Text>
  <Text Key="96992475">Bring Out Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="D5B83112">Restaurant</Text>
  <Text Key="658200E9">Placemat</Text>
  <Text Key="151BF0CE">Sparkling Water</Text>
  <Text Key="205983A1">Make Sparkling Water</Text>
  <Text Key="C55485E8">Granite Falls Grappo Blanco</Text>
  <Text Key="90D8A6F3">Pour Granite Falls Grappo Blanco</Text>
  <Text Key="A316CBD9">Red Nectar Blend</Text>
  <Text Key="B17D39A2">Pour Red Nectar Blend</Text>
  <Text Key="75838E3B">White Nectar Blend</Text>
  <Text Key="0F282AB4">Pour White Nectar Blend</Text>
  <Text Key="1C99379F">Monte Vista Reserve Renoit</Text>
  <Text Key="72F47CA0">Pour Monte Vista Reserve Renoit</Text>
  <Text Key="A7F6E7B8">Riverblossom Cranerlet Nuala</Text>
  <Text Key="EA475B23">Pour Riverblossom Cranerlet Nuala</Text>
  <Text Key="9D444569">Soft Shadow Avornalino</Text>
  <Text Key="BED11B52">Pour Soft Shadow Avornalino</Text>
  <Text Key="63042592">Von Haunt Estate Meloire</Text>
  <Text Key="4B6D789D">Pour Von Haunt Estate Meloire</Text>
  <Text Key="2B7D36B1">Honeyed World Fruit Charcuterie</Text>
  <Text Key="53CD9576">Spherized Fruit Gel\n in Foam Nest</Text>
  <Text Key="94935069">Serve Spherized Fruit Gel in Foam Nest</Text>
  <Text Key="3079D478">Glacier Infused\n Iceberg Lettuce</Text>
  <Text Key="3B50E4E3">Serve Glacier Infused Iceberg Lettuce</Text>
  <Text Key="34532B8A">Cured Meat Crisps on Reclaimed Forest Wood</Text>
  <Text Key="2732C835">Serve Cured Meat Crisps on Reclaimed Forest Wood</Text>
  <Text Key="9D6DD1A6">Savory Bacon Love Petals</Text>
  <Text Key="9960E339">Serve Savory Bacon Love Petals</Text>
  <Text Key="7B1F1A5F">Serve Honeyed World Fruit Charcuterie</Text>
  <Text Key="FF6A40BF">Vanilla Sea Shells and Chocolate Caviar</Text>
  <Text Key="14CE3AC0">Serve Vanilla Sea Shells and Chocolate Caviar</Text>
  <Text Key="E78934B0">Crystallized Coco Blocks</Text>
  <Text Key="08C85D5B">Serve Crystallized Coco Blocks</Text>
  <Text Key="4F8811EE">Vertical Berry Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="A08730C1">Serve Vertical Berry Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="E889B3C4">Semi-Firm Beet Noodles</Text>
  <Text Key="7FB83B17">Serve Semi-Firm Beet Noodles</Text>
  <Text Key="EE139F29">Glazed Heirloom Bamboo Roll</Text>
  <Text Key="45983C12">Serve Glazed Heirloom Bamboo Roll</Text>
  <Text Key="DB65BC7F">Cubed Ahi with\n Veggie Wasabi Matrix</Text>
  <Text Key="18CCB580">Serve Cubed Ahi with Veggie Wasabi Matrix</Text>
  <Text Key="21EABBDC">Sizzled Brisket over\n Sour Clover Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="A31E8E8F">Serve Sizzled Brisket over Sour Clover Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="66CD777A">Jungle Moss Egg with Lavender Wisps</Text>
  <Text Key="85D7B8C5">Serve Jungle Moss Egg with Lavender Wisps</Text>
  <Text Key="2A90B0E7">Artisan Fish Trio</Text>
  <Text Key="392C8668">Serve Artisan Fish Trio</Text>
  <Text Key="74C1C1DA">Tiger Shrimp in Smoked Dewdrop Broth</Text>
  <Text Key="21448FA5">Serve Tiger Shrimp in Smoked Dewdrop Broth
</Text>
  <Text Key="799BC7DE">Honeycomb Garden\n Vegetable Cups</Text>
  <Text Key="1EFC7D91">Serve Honeycomb Garden Vegetable Cups</Text>
  <Text Key="3C55224B">Rustic Pâté Drizzled\n in Aged Jus</Text>
  <Text Key="9564F8A4">Serve Rustic Pâté Drizzled in Aged Jus</Text>
  <Text Key="F55EF3EA">Space Taco with\n Pearled Egg Core </Text>
  <Text Key="40039E95">Serve Space Taco with Pearled Egg Core </Text>
  <Text Key="B89807A4">Free Range Sixam Pit Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="A3CDA7F7">Serve Free Range Sixam Pit Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="58346B2E">Volcano Pasta</Text>
  <Text Key="42D45801">Serve Volcano Pasta</Text>
  <Text Key="C333ADCA">Butternut Squash Soup</Text>
  <Text Key="80190875">Serve Butternut Squash Soup</Text>
  <Text Key="CD61AB2E">Cook Butternut Squash Soup</Text>
  <Text Key="A4E03383">Caesar Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="3A475A7C">Serve Caesar Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="2CA99CD7">Make Caesar Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="BC760325">Eggs Benedict</Text>
  <Text Key="FF86B756">Serve Eggs Benedict</Text>
  <Text Key="2B40578D">Cook Eggs Benedict</Text>
  <Text Key="ACE7B4A7">Tiramisu</Text>
  <Text Key="9D3A1A28">Serve Tiramisu</Text>
  <Text Key="30651893">Make Tiramisu</Text>
  <Text Key="8594F30D">Clam Chowder</Text>
  <Text Key="D9D040BE">Serve Clam Chowder</Text>
  <Text Key="B4F0E6C5">Cook Clam Chowder</Text>
  <Text Key="78E45017">Fruit Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="8A126238">Serve Fruit Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="3E603563">Make Fruit Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="115051C3">Italian Meatballs</Text>
  <Text Key="16A773BC">Serve Italian Meatballs</Text>
  <Text Key="1464FF97">Cook Italian Meatballs</Text>
  <Text Key="E02916C4">Minestrone</Text>
  <Text Key="B0629617">Serve Minestrone</Text>
  <Text Key="AF7C6E6C">Cook Minestrone</Text>
  <Text Key="2C833A40">Placemat</Text>
  <Text Key="B6F3434B">Color</Text>
  <Text Key="41C94DC6">Prepare Tiramisu</Text>
  <Text Key="D197AB56">Click on the Refrigerator, select Cook a Gourmet Meal, and select a recipe from the list.</Text>
  <Text Key="6BE6C09B">Prepare Butternut Squash Soup</Text>
  <Text Key="6CE968B5">Click on the Refrigerator, select Cook a Gourmet Meal, and select a recipe from the list.</Text>
  <Text Key="0598163C">Prepare Caesar Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="692D96DC">Click on the Refrigerator, select Cook a Gourmet Meal, and select a recipe from the list.</Text>
  <Text Key="495B8B2F">Prepare Clam Chowder</Text>
  <Text Key="BF8C0E1A">Prepare Eggs Benedict</Text>
  <Text Key="68F51242">Click on the Refrigerator, select Cook a Gourmet Meal, and select a recipe from the list.</Text>
  <Text Key="CABE4997">Prepare Fruit Salad</Text>
  <Text Key="741BEBD3">Prepare Italian Meatballs</Text>
  <Text Key="516C66B2">Prepare Minestrone</Text>
  <Text Key="79CFE606">Buy a Chef Station</Text>
  <Text Key="1C069196">Purchase a Chef Station from the Appliances Category!</Text>
  <Text Key="1C20A357">Cook an Experimental Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="E217CA79">Click on the Chef Station, select Cook Experimental Meal, and select a recipe from the list.</Text>
  <Text Key="7EB894D7">Draw on Placemat</Text>
  <Text Key="FB780AF9">{1.SimFirstName} wants to pass the time by bringing a little color to the restaurant's placemat. Once {M1.he}{F1.she} has been assigned a table, click on it and choose Draw on Placemat.</Text>
  <Text Key="F84B5220">Drink a Glass of Nectar</Text>
  <Text Key="E9C19BE8">Click on a Bar to Order a Glass of Nectar, or order a glass from the waiter.</Text>
  <Text Key="DD9BA197">Eat and Learn an Experimental Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="C0B091B9">Find a restaurant that serves experimental food and then taste it! Maybe then you'll figure out what it takes to cook it?!</Text>
  <Text Key="C8DEE404">Take a Photo of Experimental Food</Text>
  <Text Key="5E29D514">Click on Experimental Food and click Take a Photo of Experimental Food.</Text>
  <Text Key="5619BB15">Restaurant Critic</Text>
  <Text Key="D598FD97">Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="FBC4DDA2">Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="41F3DCD9">Host</Text>
  <Text Key="5271CCB8">Host</Text>
  <Text Key="11763871">Waiter</Text>
  <Text Key="781E8740">Waiter</Text>
  <Text Key="D1CA3879">Influences the quality of food. Difficult foods require high skill.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D5F0750">Influences the quality of drinks. Difficult drinks require high skill.</Text>
  <Text Key="C44DAABC">Chef</Text>
  <Text Key="F36F28E8">Influences customer reviews of the service when seated.</Text>
  <Text Key="C7A155EA">Influences customer reviews of the service when seated.</Text>
  <Text Key="BD67D232">Host</Text>
  <Text Key="5453509C">Influences how often a waiter may drop food while serving.</Text>
  <Text Key="5191F4C1">Influences customer reviews of the service when meals are served.</Text>
  <Text Key="20F49762">Waiter</Text>
  <Text Key="C815346B">(From Requesting a Table at a Restaurant)</Text>
  <Text Key="0C243BA4">Ownable Restaurant Customer Quality</Text>
  <Text Key="CE20D4C4">Ownable Restaurant Customer Value</Text>
  <Text Key="EF1BAF6F">Customer Star Rating</Text>
  <Text Key="82996F3B">Your restaurant’s inviting décor makes it the talk of the town.</Text>
  <Text Key="52F6F53B">Try adding some nicer décor to your restaurant’s dining area. Make sure your restaurant is clean too.</Text>
  <Text Key="7C29B654">Your customers are raving about the quality of food at your restaurant.</Text>
  <Text Key="17ED6552">Try training your chefs to level up their cooking skills. Make sure they’re able to properly prepare your menu.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D9DEAC8">Your restaurant is known to offer food at great prices.</Text>
  <Text Key="A58CF962">Try lowering your price markup, and make sure your chef is cooking food at a quality that customers expect.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8DBF628">What a fantastic owner you are! Keep up those personal interactions with your customers.</Text>
  <Text Key="FB59685E">Try interacting with your customers more. They’ll appreciate the owner’s attention.</Text>
  <Text Key="8E64B28E">Your staff are renowned for their impeccable service. They’re always friendly and skilled at what they do.</Text>
  <Text Key="E76C4518">Try training your Hosts and Waiters to level up their skills. Improving their moods will also improve their service.</Text>
  <Text Key="A3196EB7">Your customers love how quickly food comes out.</Text>
  <Text Key="8DEAFC1F">Try hiring more waiters or chefs. If food’s still taking too long to get to tables, rearrange your floor plan.</Text>
  <Text Key="D36F2F12">Your customers will be rating their dining experience from 1 to 5 stars. These rating will determine your restaurant's overall star rating which will go on to determine how many more customers will come to eat there.\n\nThe customers will be paying attention to the ambiance of the dining room, how well they are treated by the host, how long they have to wait for food, and more. Read the "Restaurants - Ratings" lesson for more tips on how to effectively keep your diners happy.</Text>
  <Text Key="5C48D010">When you first arrive at your restaurant you'll be asked to transfer some funds to your business to cover basic operating expenses. To learn more about managing your money, read the "Restaurant - Funds" lesson.</Text>
  <Text Key="D7A78120">You'll need a functioning restaurant before you can open the doors. This means placing and staffing a chef station, a waiter station, and a host station. You will also need to place at least 4 dining spots, a bathroom, and a sink. Next, you will need to customize your menu.</Text>
  <Text Key="D6B487DF">Sims can own and manage restaurants to earn Simoleons. To open a restaurant, use the Phone or Computer and select "Buy Restaurant." You can buy an existing restaurant, or purchase any unoccupied lot and start from scratch.\n\nA household can own and run multiple restaurants at the same time. Go ahead and try to create your culinary empire.
</Text>
  <Text Key="D390DA2A">Check out the Owned Businesses panel in the bottom right hand corner. This is where you open and close your restaurant. You will find useful information and shortcuts that will help you customize and run your restaurant.</Text>
  <Text Key="578C1B7A">If you decide you no longer want to run your restaurant, you may offload it by using the "Sell Venue" interaction on the Restaurant Settings panel. Your restaurant's funds will be added to the value of the lot and get refunded to your household. Once you've sold your restaurant, it will continue to run under new management, and you can visit it in the future as a customer!</Text>
  <Text Key="9F84C66D">Restaurants - Ownership</Text>
  <Text Key="DD2DF3AE">Each customer will display a rating over their head while at the restaurant. When the meal is finished and the customer leaves this rating will be added into the overall restaurant rating. Work hard to raise the customer's satisfaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="291A361B">Food quality, food value, hospitality, speed of food delivery, restaurant ambiance and personal attention from the manager will all impact a customer's rating.\n\nSims will be happy with low quality food if it is cheap. They will also have no problem paying a high markup for high difficulty dishes cooked well.\n\nHosts and waiters with high skills will provide better service and put the customers in a better mood. Make sure you also have enough staff to keep the food coming out of the kitchen quickly.\n\nSpend time making your dining room a nice place to eat. It is hard for Sims to enjoy their meal if they have to close their eyes.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F17261F">You can review details on the restaurant's rating by performing a mouse hover on the star rating or clicking on the View Last Finances/View Shift Summary button. Review the summary of feedback to find out what is going well and what needs improvement.</Text>
  <Text Key="CB57E729">Customers will enter the restaurant while it is open and there are available dining spots. Your restaurants overall rating, the time of day, and your advertising will determine how many customers stop by. You can also purchase perks that increase the number of customers.</Text>
  <Text Key="40C5EF0F">Pay close attention to the icons over the Sim's heads. They will show when the Sims's rating of the restaurant changes and indicate why. If you miss a change, the tool tip on each Sim will show their last bit of feedback.</Text>
  <Text Key="62285250">Restaurants - Ratings</Text>
  <Text Key="9701C081">Since your Sim is the boss, they have to manage their employees. Your Sim can check in on, praise, criticize, send to training, promote or even fire each employee.</Text>
  <Text Key="9DCCF648">Employees have different skills that determine how well they work. Review these on the "Manage Employees" panel. If you can't find the perfect Sim with high skills to hire don't worry. Employees will slowly gain skills over time as they work. The best way to raise their skills quickly is to send them to after work training. Just be prepared to pay for this training.</Text>
  <Text Key="177702F9">An employee's satisfaction is raised by being paid appropriately for their skill level, receiving praise from the boss, and getting promoted. Berating your employees, demoting them, or working them for longer than eight hours per shift are just some ways to lower their satisfaction. If they get too upset, don't be surprised when they quit!</Text>
  <Text Key="174AC78B">Use the "Manage Employees" interaction on the Owned Businesses panel to quickly check the status of your employees. You can view their skills and current pay level, and see how satisfied they are with their employment.\n\nYou can use this panel to give a worthy employee a raise, punish an employee with a demotion, or outright fire a worker who isn't working out.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF8148B8">Running a restaurant is no piece of cake, but fortunately you can hire employees to offload some work. Select "Manage Employees" on your Owned Businesses panel to view a list of Sims to hire. Review their skills and their starting pay to determine if they're a good match for your restaurant. If you don't like the list of applicants, simply try again later.</Text>
  <Text Key="8C197D7C">As your restaurant becomes more successful, you can unlock the perks to hire additional employees using your Perk points. See the "Restaurant - Perks" lesson for more details.</Text>
  <Text Key="19E187F2">Restaurants - Employees</Text>
  <Text Key="831E9BBB">As a restaurant owner, your restaurant's funds are tracked separately from your normal household funds. Each restaurant that you own has its own separate funds that are used to cover the restaurant's expenses. When you visit your restaurant, you can simultaneously view your restaurant's funds in the Owned Businesses panel in the bottom right corner, along with your household's funds in the bottom left corner.</Text>
  <Text Key="C60B86C3">At any time you can use the Venue Funds Transfer button near your household's Simoleons in the bottom left corner to move money between your household and any of the restaurants that you own. Within this panel you can select the account you're transferring from and to, and enter the amount of money you want to transfer. Try transferring funds when you need more money to pay your business' expenses, or to send the profits from your business back to your household.</Text>
  <Text Key="E8F598A1">You can click on the "View Shift Summary/Last Finances" button on the Owned Businesses panel to get a detailed breakdown of your profits and expenses. Use this information to make strategic decisions about your restaurant to help maximize profits.</Text>
  <Text Key="262BD1ED">There's a chance that your restaurant can go into debt if you don't have enough money to pay your employees, or if you purchase advertising while low on funds. If your restaurant doesn't have enough money to pay its debts, you won't be allowed to reopen your restaurant until those debts have been cleared. Transfer money from your household to your restaurant to cover your debts.</Text>
  <Text Key="12003351">Every action taken as an owner while at your restaurant uses money from your business' funds. This includes building on the restaurant lot, placing objects, paying your employees, purchasing advertising, and more. When you enter Build Mode, the money shown in the bottom left corner will switch to display your restaurant funds that you're building with. Finally, any money you can from your restaurant's sales will be deposited into your restaurant funds.</Text>
  <Text Key="D229FC71">Restaurants - Funds</Text>
  <Text Key="7BF6DB87">Restaurant Perks have a direct impact on your restaurant and your household’s Sims that you’re playing. Employees that you hire are not affected by the Perks. Instead employees can be improved separately by building their skills at various tasks. You can learn more about that in the “Restaurant - Employees” lesson.</Text>
  <Text Key="99DA4A76">Earning Perk Points is simple - just have your Sims help out around the restaurant. Interacting with customers and managing employees will all provide some Perk Points. The more customers that come to the restaurant the more points you can earn. Employees will not earn Perk Points for you, so get to work!</Text>
  <Text Key="CC63A7A9">Some Perks provide a temporary bonus, such as the ability to get a discount on ingredients for your meals or a influx of extra customers. You can return to purchase these Perks again in the future once your original purchase runs out.</Text>
  <Text Key="F196BCBE">Perks are the key to building bigger, more efficient restaurants. They will allow you to make your restaurant more profitable and popular. Do not let them go unspent.\n\nThere are a wide variety of Perks to choose from. You can unlock the ability to hire additional employees. Spend Perk points to get a short term or permanent discount on ingredients. Learn how to recommend more expensive dishes to customers. There are even powerful bonuses that influence your customers to tolerate longer wait times or eat their meals faster. Perks that are purchased will be applied to every restaurant your household owns.</Text>
  <Text Key="FC45B999">Owners of restaurants can earn Perk Points from running their restaurant.\n\nPlayers can use those Perk Points to buy Perks, which in turn, make the restaurant more effective. You’ll find the various Perks within the Owned Businesses panel in the bottom right corner of the screen.</Text>
  <Text Key="1D6D8862">Restaurants - Perks</Text>
  <Text Key="ABB99F2A">A restaurant is a great place to grab a bite to eat while socializing with friends. Leave the cooking, and the dishes, to the professionals. Head to your favorite Burger Joint, or go for something a little more Experimental at one of the fine dining restaurants.</Text>
  <Text Key="1752021C">If you want to get the best seat in the house you need to talk to the restaurant host. Find the host station or host and click on them to Request a Table.</Text>
  <Text Key="3E6615FB">After your first course you can order another course or pay your bill and head home.</Text>
  <Text Key="BED3FF63">The food is why your Sim is here. Click on the table to Order for Table and call over the waiter. Make sure to check out the Chef's Choice for a discounted dish. Confirm your food selection for each member of your dinner party.</Text>
  <Text Key="A4D0E26B">Restaurants - Dining Out</Text>
  <Text Key="D184F2EC">Spend time with us! Share a good meal!</Text>
  <Text Key="9AB54C2A">Come taste all the dishes! I hear the Chef is amazing!</Text>
  <Text Key="6ACA1B81">Come indulge your tastebuds! You know you really want to go!</Text>
  <Text Key="C19E8659">Dining Spot</Text>
  <Text Key="AABD58EB">Sink</Text>
  <Text Key="7D7637BB">Host Station</Text>
  <Text Key="A22C5F12">Waiter Station</Text>
  <Text Key="A1B25F88">Chef Station</Text>
  <Text Key="1388BBF8">Toilet</Text>
  <Text Key="6EC550A0">Visit the Restaurant</Text>
  <Text Key="3BF6E521">Visit the Restaurant...</Text>
  <Text Key="6F060E67">Restaurant</Text>
  <Text Key="ADA95FDA">Restaurant - Incomplete</Text>
  <Text Key="201EA712">Chez Llama is the ultimate culinary destination for your Sims. Dress up and try the Chef's latests experimental creations. \nYou can find it and other restaurants in the "My Library" tab in the Gallery.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA1D4827">The Restaurant is a great place to grab a bite to eat!</Text>
  <Text Key="2110F03D">Lofty Brick</Text>
  <Text Key="C4FD72EC">Determined Brick</Text>
  <Text Key="7070E193">Modern Wood Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="BE87F79C">Hey! You left without paying your bill of {0.Money}, but looks like you're a little down on your luck, so don't worry about it. It's a free meal on us!</Text>
  <Text Key="E3A6F074">Hey! You left without paying your bill of {0.Money} so we charged you. Don't forget next time!</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>