<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="45EC0EE3">Show off your favorite selection of books with these elegant bookends. Trust us when we say these beauties were built to make a statement! </Text>
  <Text Key="623FA8B2">Strike-a-Prose Bookends</Text>
  <Text Key="213D12BC">This bookshelf is a godsend for your overflowing library. Display some treasured trinkets or trendy decor alongside all the other treasures you can’t get enough of—books! This winning combo of curios and books is the perfect way to show off and inspire conversation with anyone who enters your reading space.</Text>
  <Text Key="5737DC13">The Genremax Partially Full Bookshelf</Text>
  <Text Key="AFB1B498">Don't allow your reputation to be tarnished in the eyes of your peers. Instead, try jumping into something incredible, like a good book! Become the most well-read person in all the land. Between your newfound hobby, and your natural poise and grace, your erudition will become notorious, shattering the expectations of even your most pretentious neighbors. Rather than foul omens, you'll find treasure ahead in your literary journey! And it &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; starts with this bookshelf!</Text>
  <Text Key="CC5BE917">The Genremax Bookshelf</Text>
  <Text Key="D6136EE9">Keep your books out of sight, out of mind, and safely tucked away. With this unit, you can organize your precious collection and mount it on the wall to elevate your books to a place of honor. Rest assured; this bookcase underwent rigorous testing to ensure it could hold an impressive number of books. Don't worry about falling off the shelf with this one!</Text>
  <Text Key="65C862CC">The Genremax Medium Bookshelf</Text>
  <Text Key="39EC0608">If you’re in the mood for something modest, this small bookshelf is here to be your steadfast companion. It is the perfect cubby for a quaint selection of books, or it could be used as an addition to your overflowing library.</Text>
  <Text Key="4D4ADAA7">The Genremax Small Bookshelf</Text>
  <Text Key="326FD257">The modern solution to the age-old question: "How can you even see that?". Eye strain will be the last thing on your mind under this guiding light, leaving room for total immersion into that sci-fi novella you're reading. Spoiler alert: the heartless killing machine has feelings.</Text>
  <Text Key="5397432E">The Standing Orb</Text>
  <Text Key="166B51CE">Is it aesthetically pleasing? Yes. Will it get a lot of likes if you post it on Simstagram? Absolutely! With all that being said, that candle placement is a bit precarious. </Text>
  <Text Key="BD3A2BF1">The Fire Hazard</Text>
  <Text Key="129B184E">A versatile reading light for all the desk readers and bedroom dwellers out there because the living room is the domain of mindless TV watchers, after all. We all know the book is always better!</Text>
  <Text Key="2C39B771">The Table Orb</Text>
  <Text Key="37D26AE5">Express your love of literature in more ways than one! These prints of best-selling novels and famous literary quotes can be hung in any room to inspire your Sim with their favorite intellectual hobby. You can also use it to show your guests that you decorate your home with things other than books!</Text>
  <Text Key="59299860">Ex Libris Book Print</Text>
  <Text Key="1C0D4463">This is the lowest your "to read" pile has ever been. The only logical course of action is to go to a bookstore and purchase more books; when you do, you know exactly where to put them!</Text>
  <Text Key="0E2A5132">Basically Empty Book Basket</Text>
  <Text Key="82FE7F62">Every reader knows The Pile. The &lt;i&gt;to be read&lt;/i&gt; pile of books that just somehow keeps growing. As long as it doesn't reach the ceiling, go ahead and add to it! </Text>
  <Text Key="AD7787DD">The Pile</Text>
  <Text Key="9A82D3D7">You need a soft rug to stand on while you stare at your bookshelves. Whether you are contemplating whether you should buy another book (hint: the answer is always yes), admiring your collection, or just trying to remember where you left your reading glasses, you should have a comfortable place to stand.</Text>
  <Text Key="A6D58FAE">Rug of Poetic Justice</Text>
  <Text Key="ED980A1D">This basket is the most logical place to store all the books you want to read, but we know this is just the beginning. It always starts like this: you have good intentions to keep your reading bug under control, but like the plant you added to the mix, it will soon take on a life of its own.</Text>
  <Text Key="99055108">To-Be-Read Book Basket</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACD39D2">This minimalistic tray is built to hold your book and hot beverage as you nestle into a comfy couch. Keep your space organized, and never worry about a wet book again with this handy tray. </Text>
  <Text Key="58CA58ED">The Self-Care Book Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="CF80502B">If bookmarks are too mainstream for you, try a Storybook House. This little structure will mark your page for you while using it to shelter your other books from the elements. What elements? Why, the four indoor elements of coffee, food, dust, and tears as you finish that final chapter.</Text>
  <Text Key="2502702A">Storybook House Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="06A816BD">Listen, before you judge me, you need to know how good these cake decorators have gotten these days. They can make hyper-realistic fruits with ultra-detailed textures that are secretly a cake inside. They can... Oh. Oh my. They can make &lt;i&gt;edible paper&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;i&gt;Edible paper&lt;/i&gt;. Do you &lt;i&gt;realize&lt;/i&gt; what that means? These books could be a cake inside, too, for all we know! Nothing is safe! &lt;i&gt;Nothing&lt;/i&gt;!</Text>
  <Text Key="6BCE9228">Alleged Stack of Books</Text>
  <Text Key="DB8AEAB9">This brand-new shelf is a blank slate. It is definitely not another place for you to store more books. Place pictures of your family here. Maybe add a decorative sculpture that speaks to you. Anything would work because it's not like you purchased this shelf to accommodate your spiraling out-of-control book-buying habits!</Text>
  <Text Key="051361BC">The Genremax Display Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="66CA0EC3">When you have all the books you want on display, it's time to make room for more. Use this to display your next haul of books, or perhaps a few of your worldly possessions, which, to be honest, are probably more books. It's ok... we get it.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA180712">The Genremax Storage Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="D455459B">Say goodbye to messy shelves and hello to organization! The Genremax Medium Storage Shelf takes your books from stack to shelf in a simple, sleek design that fits any room. Mount this bookcase flat against the wall and store away everything you want out of sight. We recommend filling the shelves with all of your favorite titles, but don't stop there—why not add some display items as well? If you're feeling particularly bold, you can even place them up top!</Text>
  <Text Key="65CF997A">The Genremax Medium Storage Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="DF53A806">Your cozy corner is not complete without an all-natural boucle armchair! Its pillowy cushions and trendy, soft-to-the-touch material will keep you comfortable for hours on end. Now's the time to settle in and finally immerse yourself in that book you've been meaning to read (or scroll through Social Bunny posts—we don't judge.)</Text>
  <Text Key="9B284999">Cozy Corner Boucle Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="54FA64D4">Even the most meticulous scholar deserves a brief bit of supple relaxation. Stretch out with your earnest loved one or a furry friend after a long hour of sorting and organizing your reads. Knowledge of the Dewey Decimal Library System is not included. </Text>
  <Text Key="08AB3FBB">The Genremax Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="841E17A7">It's your favorite spot inside your home— you return to it daily to unwind and recharge. Its cushions have perfectly molded to you, making it the perfect place to sit after a long day. And as you sit down to pick up your favorite book or to binge that new show all your friends told you about, you get the feeling that everything feels just right—you're home.</Text>
  <Text Key="ED5AD0DE">Snugly Spot Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="180BB3D5">Coffee Table Books exist for the sole purpose of showing off how smart you are. These oversized books are never opened, let alone read, and are usually full of giant maps or vibrant pictures. The fewer words, the better. Books like these need a prominent place to be displayed to all of your house guests, and what better way to do that than on this coffee table?  </Text>
  <Text Key="BA1921F0">Rounded Coffee Table</Text>
  <Text Key="DF0AC485">This unassuming end table can complement any décor! More importantly, it can accommodate any book you want to display. Whether textbooks, cookbooks, or storybooks, they can all take center stage on this end table.</Text>
  <Text Key="A856AE80">Perfectly Round End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="4B6BA085">Serene Reading Room</Text>
  <Text Key="44EF79A7">The Genremax Wall</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>