<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="DF1C30E1">Have you always dreamed about showing your books while hiding your mess? This bookcase lets you do both, and with style.</Text>
  <Text Key="A2466494">Sleek Bookcase</Text>
  <Text Key="399A6B98">Nothing is more satisfying than a complete collection of your favorite author.</Text>
  <Text Key="DF7A5E17">The Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="3978102E">This original book rack can be placed on any surface to make sure you'll have something to read at hand.</Text>
  <Text Key="D7591AD1">Bragging's Bookend</Text>
  <Text Key="67D740A7">Depending on your needs, you can adjust this lamp up and down, left or right. You can even adjust the brightness!</Text>
  <Text Key="43BBFBDE">Up and Down Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="39541F85">This little lamp seems to be the perfect mix between a UFO and a very very soft cloud. Until it decides to get back to its home planet, you can place it on any surface to bring a soft and warm lighting to your space.</Text>
  <Text Key="E8ADCF80">Cloudy Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="AA9EDC00">This painting represents anything you want, all you need is your imagination. You're still not seeing anything? That's ok, you can just pretend this reminds you your childhood house in the countryside, the fresh air in the morning, and the feeling of freedom you had as a child. It's pretty basic, but it will work for sure!</Text>
  <Text Key="B36D5ECF">Precise Strokes for Random Shapes</Text>
  <Text Key="FC5EBF85">This old pedestal is perfect for showing off your fancy decor items.</Text>
  <Text Key="C08BAF80">Pedestal from the Old Times</Text>
  <Text Key="F87EB563">A plant that provides the perfect way to bring life into your home, with a bit of greenery!</Text>
  <Text Key="8731D432">Small Paradise</Text>
  <Text Key="376E0814">This rug is a unique piece, hand-woven by the best weaver of the market. Don't forget to mention it every time a guest compliments it!</Text>
  <Text Key="D19320FB">Contrasted Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="4ECA54D9">Nothing is better than an elegant divider screen to add a little bit of privacy!</Text>
  <Text Key="0C6B295C">Divider Screen of Elegance</Text>
  <Text Key="2C95E5E0">This old abacus is the ancestor of our calculator. It may not be very useful nowadays, but it's a nice piece to have as a decor item.</Text>
  <Text Key="2DBC582F">Off the Grid Calculator</Text>
  <Text Key="81252D42">Thanks to this decorative bowl, you will be able to add a touch of color to your room.</Text>
  <Text Key="8C805A3D">Shelly the Bowl</Text>
  <Text Key="AAA8D226">Testimony of the old time, it's the closest thing to selfies in the classical days. Even if this bust is so damaged that we can't recognize who it was, it's still looking nice in your living room!</Text>
  <Text Key="E9F7F039">Ancient Bust</Text>
  <Text Key="BDAED197">This abstract sculpture doesn't have a specific shape intended. It's made to let you imagine what you want. Apparently some people see a llama in it.</Text>
  <Text Key="9BA0A06E">Perfect Stacking Masterpiece</Text>
  <Text Key="E5B2EC4C">Be careful of this decorative vase. It perfectly survived the last few centuries, it would be a shame to break it now.</Text>
  <Text Key="57243803">Perfectly Preserved Antique Vase</Text>
  <Text Key="D3B109D7">Just like macaroni and cheese, those two pieces are made to be together.</Text>
  <Text Key="F37E51AE">The Duo</Text>
  <Text Key="929D4E7F">Inspired by architectural shapes, this piece of art casts different shadows during the day, giving it a unique look every time you look at it.</Text>
  <Text Key="73EB4CA6">Shadow of the Day</Text>
  <Text Key="3EC5970F">Thanks to its chrome feet and rotative seat, this armchair mixes elegance and comfort. It will be ideal to rest yourself in for a moment.</Text>
  <Text Key="F04926D6">Vintage Leather Armchair</Text>
  <Text Key="9C7A432F">Simplicity and elegance merged together to give you this lovely armchair.</Text>
  <Text Key="956B5E76">One Piece Armchair</Text>
  <Text Key="FBCD70C2">This loveseat isn't only classy, but it's also very comfortable and perfect to rest after a long day of work, spend time with your friend or your lover.</Text>
  <Text Key="4996CCBD">Two Pieces Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="4EFE9D69">Do you remember when you bought the first Two Pieces? Now your family is expanding, and you need the third seat. Fortunately, there's no need to buy a new sofa. Thanks to its discrete attachment system and a few extra Simoleons, you can add as many seats as you want!</Text>
  <Text Key="F7CDA64C">Three Pieces Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="26EAD093">SimStone &amp; Co. offers you this elegant coffee table. It's made of the best rock, directly from Tartosa! You can trust SimStone &amp; Co. when they claim that it's the best material on the market, so much so that this coffee table is guaranteed for life!</Text>
  <Text Key="4DEEAE42">The Laying Rock</Text>
  <Text Key="8028AC73">Luckily, SimStone &amp; Co. have too much rock left over from their coffee table—and they hate wasting material—so they are able to create this matching end table! Perfect to be placed along sofas, this end table is of course guaranteed for life too!</Text>
  <Text Key="123F5BA2">By My Side Table</Text>
  <Text Key="EA1DE6C2">Found in a dusty old attic, this old sideboard has kept the secrets of several generations. Thanks to its generous dimensions and robust hinges, it's ready to carry your secrets for decades too.</Text>
  <Text Key="9B924EBD">Old Carved Sideboard</Text>
  <Text Key="1A5B1EF1">Woody's Wallpaper</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>