<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="9F1D923D">Have a Sim bowl a perfect game of all strikes on the Bowling Lane.</Text>
  <Text Key="D9C8224D">Perfect Llama </Text>
  <Text Key="CA3EBA22">(From Bowling Too Much)</Text>
  <Text Key="791E0235">(From Bowling Too Much)</Text>
  <Text Key="56A1F24F">(From Watching Bowling)</Text>
  <Text Key="1B26C56F">(From Legitimately Losing a Bowling Game)</Text>
  <Text Key="480AA9B5">Wow, ten strikes! {0.SimFirstName} just bowled a perfect game!\n\nIt would take a pretty narcissistic Sim to purchase a bowling trophy just to show off their accomplishment, but we'll look the other way if {0.SimFirstName} wants to poke around in Build Mode...</Text>
  <Text Key="C77349D4">Perfect Llama</Text>
  <Text Key="D71B5BFD">(From Moonlight Bowling)</Text>
  <Text Key="ACDFF61E">(From Winning a Bowling Game)</Text>
  <Text Key="D5B82357">Bowling Skill Boost</Text>
  <Text Key="BF0895D0">This will boost the speed at which your Sim gains Bowling Skill while in a Club Gathering.</Text>
  <Text Key="4D8688D8">All hail the Bowling {M0.King}{F0.Queen}! Long may {M0.he}{F0.she} reign!</Text>
  <Text Key="660BDC57">Bowling {M0.King}{F0.Queen}</Text>
  <Text Key="BF9CD5E2">{0.SimFirstName} looks positively radiant after a bowling match through the cosmos.</Text>
  <Text Key="825DC35D">Bowling by Moonlight</Text>
  <Text Key="6DD88DC4">{0.SimFirstName}'s arms have gone completely numb. {M0.He'll}{F0.She'll} be worse at bowling until {M0.he}{F0.she} recovers.</Text>
  <Text Key="BF65188B">Over Bowled</Text>
  <Text Key="2C504DDD">{0.SimFirstName}'s muscles are starting to feel tight from all this bowling. Consider taking a break.</Text>
  <Text Key="C7E00BC8">Sore Arms</Text>
  <Text Key="3F86A851">Don't you dare ask {0.SimFirstName} how some other Sim cheated {M0.him}{F0.her} at bowling... it should be obvious!</Text>
  <Text Key="B6F87EA4">They Cheated!</Text>
  <Text Key="F18ABBE6">There's something soothing about the rhythmic roll of a bowling ball followed by the crash of ten pins.</Text>
  <Text Key="BAA7F5F9">Bowling Bystander</Text>
  <Text Key="ECF507A8">Go Bowling</Text>
  <Text Key="73518F67">Go Bowling</Text>
  <Text Key="AA79A30B">Don't Go Bowling</Text>
  <Text Key="693D3082">Going for Pro</Text>
  <Text Key="D09131DF">Team Captain</Text>
  <Text Key="A500B64C">Cropped Together</Text>
  <Text Key="267E8340">Bowling Queen</Text>
  <Text Key="25030599">Bowling King</Text>
  <Text Key="29B744EC">Participation At Leisure</Text>
  <Text Key="1D7A7E0B">Bowled Over Linoleum</Text>
  <Text Key="31230249">Bowled Over Linoleum</Text>
  <Text Key="0045BF01">Bowled Over Linoleum</Text>
  <Text Key="3DE7581B">Bowled Over Linoleum</Text>
  <Text Key="5A166E41">Bowled Over Linoleum</Text>
  <Text Key="1BFC6FB5">Bowled Over Linoleum</Text>
  <Text Key="C317DDBE">Bowled Over Linoleum</Text>
  <Text Key="EB937F93">Bowled Over Linoleum</Text>
  <Text Key="CD64F90B">Occasionally stylistic influences from the Far East seeped into mid-century modern design. Such is the case with the Domo Arigato Bar, an homage to the art of origami.</Text>
  <Text Key="527D058A">Domo Arigato Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="87002EA5">A United Sims Bowling Congress approved bowling ball.</Text>
  <Text Key="93CB7D20">Bowling Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="19892644">Strike fear in your (bowling) enemies.</Text>
  <Text Key="810A7A0B">Clear Skull Bowling Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="DFA5965E">Bowling! It's the adrenaline packed game that's sweeping the nation... again!\n\nSims House Bowling Rules:\n· One shot per frame to promote rapid play.\n· Scoring multipliers are in effect based upon each Sim's Bowling skill.\n· Bowl consecutive center hits to activate "On Fire!" mode.\n· Bumpers are automatically enabled for child bowlers.\n\nWhile bowling lanes can be placed anywhere, groups of bowlers will only show up when two or more lanes are added to the following venue types:\n· Bar\n· Nightclub\n· Lounge\nThese venues offer Moonlight Bowling from 7-11pm weeknights, and 11am-2pm weekends.</Text>
  <Text Key="BAFF1D61">Ten Pin Adrenaline</Text>
  <Text Key="CB123B73">A single bowling pin.</Text>
  <Text Key="2A58D8A2">Bowling Pin</Text>
  <Text Key="C82062C6">There's a starclock waiting in the sky\nIt would come and sync us\nBut 4d would blow our minds\nThere's a starclock waiting in the sky\nWeaving spacetime fabric\nWhile Sims go about their lives...</Text>
  <Text Key="9D1FA759">Starclock</Text>
  <Text Key="B86584B7">Illuminated peaks and valleys will adorn your walls via these self-luminous strips. Smart use of flourescent paint ensures a trendy, reliable, and renewable source of style.</Text>
  <Text Key="728F6C0E">Peak Performance</Text>
  <Text Key="2B4225D9">Ever found yourself in a greasy roadside diner at 2am? Your eyes roll towards the heavens as you struggle to stay awake. A waitress named Flo is taking her sweet time getting a cup of black coffee into your hands. Suddenly, you find yourself taken by the gorgeous lights suspended above the counter. Don't worry, we've all been there. Now you can take those very same light fixtures home!\n\nCuppa Light - Short is intended for rooms with low ceilings.</Text>
  <Text Key="B7F7CC5C">Cuppa Light - Short</Text>
  <Text Key="C86C5BB0">Ever found yourself in a greasy roadside diner at 2am? Your eyes roll towards the heavens as you struggle to stay awake. A waitress named Flo is taking her sweet time getting a cup of black coffee into your hands. Suddenly, you find yourself taken by the gorgeous lights suspended above the counter. Don't worry, we've all been there. Now you can take those very same light fixtures home!\n\nCuppa Light - Long is intended for rooms with tall ceilings.</Text>
  <Text Key="61B9865F">Cuppa Light - Long</Text>
  <Text Key="AC192BA4">While it comes in varying degrees of mild to wild, the lampshade on this groovy lamp will always be a focal point of style in any room.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0AE94EB">Bubble Trouble</Text>
  <Text Key="DE21E043">Confused on where to go? The Right-of-Way wall fixture will light the way... just head to the right!</Text>
  <Text Key="6F6BC392">Right-of-Way</Text>
  <Text Key="A0834B5D">Ultramodern barn lighting... it sounds like an oxymoron, but the future is here. Via a retrofitted socket, what's old is new again! Buy now before it goes back out of style.</Text>
  <Text Key="CC458C48">Calla Chameleon Barn Light</Text>
  <Text Key="9BCB1E72">"All that glitters is not gold..."\n\nA wise proverb that applies as much to this art as it does life. These elegant bowling themed lightboxes slowly shift their image between shades of maroon and royal blue.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C88C50D">Pin-up Art</Text>
  <Text Key="3358241C">A standard issue rug to family entertainment centers across the globe. Choose from a number of patterns guaranteed to look garish, while cleverly hiding dirt, stains, and standard wear and tear.</Text>
  <Text Key="1BACA7F3">On Pins &amp; Nebula</Text>
  <Text Key="37945957">"Cheers to you? No... cheers to me!"\n\nThe only thing finer than basking in the glory of your own bowling triumphs is forcing others to mentally prostrate themselves to your splendor each time they pass by.</Text>
  <Text Key="8D00282E">Cheers to Me Trophy Case</Text>
  <Text Key="63429658">When something is turned up or popping...\n\nJohn: "Did you go to the bowling alley last night?"\nDaquan: "Yeah, the dividers in there were lit!"</Text>
  <Text Key="3B9F8CD7">Lit Divider</Text>
  <Text Key="DAE4ED9D">A set of retro modern cubbies equipped with LED lighting serves as a bold room divider in this intriguing piece.</Text>
  <Text Key="15A7A388">Retro Modern Cubbies</Text>
  <Text Key="D9B54C22">Undoubtedly the designer of these sleek retro modern cubbies dreamed of what treasured possessions would be displayed on its luminous shelving. What he got was... bowling shoes.</Text>
  <Text Key="1161999D">Bowling Shoe Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="59184FDB">Some people focus entirely on improving their bowling score. Those people are wrong. Welcome to Fashion Bowling, the fiercest competition you'll find in your local alley. Choose your bowling ball wisely... your color coordination is being judged.</Text>
  <Text Key="A13420BA">Bowling Ball Rack #1</Text>
  <Text Key="F2FD663D">Some people focus entirely on improving their bowling score. Those people are wrong. Welcome to Fashion Bowling, the fiercest competition you'll find in your local alley. Choose your bowling ball wisely... your color coordination is being judged.</Text>
  <Text Key="F00668A8">Bowling Ball Rack #2</Text>
  <Text Key="527EA507">This pin is officially approved for regulation ten-pin bowling by the United Sims Bowling Congress. An inscription on the pin reads, "We Beat This Pin Up At Sim Mateo Bowl".</Text>
  <Text Key="AAB34ABE">USBC Bowling Pin</Text>
  <Text Key="D5657115">Just think of the one-liners you'll spring on other unsuspecting Sims should you be lucky enough to lay claim to a couple of bowling trophies...</Text>
  <Text Key="D4B96230">Peggy's Championship Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="96B36598">Unlock by Bowling a Perfect Llama.\n(all strikes in a single game)</Text>
  <Text Key="97D1E10B">Unlocked by Bowling a Perfect Llama</Text>
  <Text Key="A86EE7C4">"To be the man, you've gotta' beat the man."\n\nDisplay your lane's house champs so everyone knows who they need to knock down a peg or two.</Text>
  <Text Key="46C5068B">House Leaderboard</Text>
  <Text Key="85ADA690">A back bar for bowling bar backs. This set of shelving will be the pride of your bowling alley, with memorabilia and memories on full display.</Text>
  <Text Key="C5E6A6BF">Triple B Back Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="A0FF8D07">Add a touch of authenticity to your bowling alley with this classic Googie sign. The slow death of neon has signaled the end of vintage roadside Americana, but this beautiful restoration will serve as a beacon to eager bowlers.</Text>
  <Text Key="C51182BE">3-2-1 Let's Bowl!</Text>
  <Text Key="7B348445">Project power from the high summit of Seema. A patterned cushion rests nestled between the simple fiberglass shell. But make no mistake, this juxtaposition is globally recognized as an apex of style.</Text>
  <Text Key="ACB1EA40">Seema Barstool</Text>
  <Text Key="CED5A776">Pull up a chair. Not just any chair... make it a Seema Dining chair. When you sit at this table, you'll sit on only the finest.</Text>
  <Text Key="5AD2DBA9">Seema Dining</Text>
  <Text Key="2E5F78FA">Look closely... do you notice something wrong with this chair? Ah-hah, I see the dawning realization slowly spreading across your face. You've been duped! This chair is no Seema, it's a KNOCKOFF! It's an affront to organic design!\n\n...that said, it is a heck of a lot cheaper than a true original.</Text>
  <Text Key="760F27A5">Seema Living</Text>
  <Text Key="337805A0">It takes a true design luminary to cut through the cloying excess of 21st century design. It takes courage to bring us back to the basics, back to the rudimentary elements that furniture design is rooted in. It takes Seema.</Text>
  <Text Key="9BD8CBEF">Seema Ottoman</Text>
  <Text Key="66B9EF74">Add more Seema to your life. What was once contemporary, is now timeless. Don't be fooled by its subtle style - this piece will define any room it's placed within.</Text>
  <Text Key="C36850DB">Seema Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="C1DB8C74">This wall-mounted stereo is intended for use at community venues. Disco is alive and well baby! An added modern twist proves that you just can't keep a good genre down.</Text>
  <Text Key="4EF097DB">Venue Wall Speaker: NuDisco</Text>
  <Text Key="CFC30D6E">Coffee... the drink of choice for millennials. And so shall this masterful example of democratic design be the coffee table of choice for Generation Y.</Text>
  <Text Key="B8B18C11">Mid-millenium Modern Coffee</Text>
  <Text Key="15DEF00F">Ride the timewave as you dine at this table that revels in its simplicity. Meals of future past will come and go, but this table will last forever.</Text>
  <Text Key="B173E1D6">Mid-millennium Modern Dining</Text>
  <Text Key="6768C7CE">Mid-century modern is SO 1950s. Meet Mid-millenia modern - furniture for contemporaries (not to be mistaken for contemporary furniture).</Text>
  <Text Key="6DACADF1">Mid-millenium Modern End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="93A90B08">A credenza for the avid bowling family. The spacious storage compartment is sealed shut with a practical accordion door. Perfect for storing bowling shoes, bowling balls, bowling gloves, and any other bowling paraphernalia you may need at a moment's notice.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B78D9A7">Bowler's Hidey Hole</Text>
  <Text Key="5DCC5917">Always Throw Tricks</Text>
  <Text Key="942F1097">Already Enabled on Sim</Text>
  <Text Key="461AA5B5">Never Fail</Text>
  <Text Key="344838DD">Red Swirl Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="308C7E19">Matte Black Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="D9C4A0E2">Marbled Blue Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="64D747EC">Gold Glitter Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="06D938B8">Sky Blue Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="42339DDF">Raise your Bowling skill to acquire more bowling balls.</Text>
  <Text Key="C6001813">Clear Skull Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="ED04CD28">Disable Moonlight Bowling</Text>
  <Text Key="2D820CEF">Enable Moonlight Bowling</Text>
  <Text Key="6A57B8D7">Join Bowling Game</Text>
  <Text Key="CFF234A7">Bowl</Text>
  <Text Key="AC7D03B1">Watch</Text>
  <Text Key="389BE268">{0.SimFirstName} needs level 5 Handiness skill to add this upgrade.</Text>
  <Text Key="9D02AB16">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished installing the Moonlight Bowling upgrade kit to {M0.his}{F0.her} bowling lane. Bowling and raves... raves and bowling... the world is {M0.his}{F0.her} oyster!</Text>
  <Text Key="FD06C643">Add Moonlight Bowling Upgrade</Text>
  <Text Key="7D8D3D15">Continue Moonlight Bowling Upgrade</Text>
  <Text Key="028BB7CE">Bowl</Text>
  <Text Key="4B1D2932">Invite To Bowl</Text>
  <Text Key="E873E8F1">Listen to NuDisco</Text>
  <Text Key="78086C5E">NuDisco</Text>
  <Text Key="F3295FF7">Alley For One</Text>
  <Text Key="D4ED02FB">Delighting Den</Text>
  <Text Key="969B92F8">Music for the modern disco fan.</Text>
  <Text Key="B72A2D3D">NuDisco</Text>
  <Text Key="4589AA46">Select Bowling Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="D4F805B1">Cheat Bowling</Text>
  <Text Key="E19B3065">Go Bowling</Text>
  <Text Key="C9302FCF">Click on a Bowling Lane and select Bowl.</Text>
  <Text Key="778C23E1">What a game! {1.SimFirstName} ended up beating {2.SimFirstName} {3.Number}-{4.Number}.</Text>
  <Text Key="4CA74455">Feels like {1.String} ganged up on {2.SimFirstName}, and ended up beating {M2.him}{F2.her} {3.Number}-{4.Number}.</Text>
  <Text Key="D21ED9CD">Despite being outnumbered, {1.SimFirstName} beat {2.String} {3.Number}-{4.Number}!</Text>
  <Text Key="83641D6B">Great round! {1.String} beat {2.String} {3.Number}-{4.Number}.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA640F56">{1.SimFirstName} bowled a game of {2.Number}.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C467774">{1.SimName} won the bowling game with a score of {2.Number}.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C9667DF">Bowling! A game of skill for children and adults alike. Reading a book isn't going to help you here, you need to play, play again, and then keep on playing if you want to rise through the ranks.\n\nAs {0.SimFirstName} improves {M0.his}{F0.her} skill, {M0.he'll}{F0.she'll} improve {M0.his}{F0.her} form and score. {M0.He'll}{F0.She'll} also unlock new bowling ball colors as {M0.he}{F0.she} goes, which can be selected from the bowling ball rack.\n\nKeep the dream of a Perfect Llama game of all strikes alive... with high skill and a bit of luck, {0.SimFirstName} is sure to get there!</Text>
  <Text Key="EF60DB7D">Bowling Skill Acquired</Text>
  <Text Key="00ACF400">{0.SimFirstName} can now select the Gold Glitter bowling ball.\n\n{M0.He}{F0.She} will stumble less often when releasing the ball, which is always important when you're looking to impress at the local lanes.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0B0F74E">Reached Bowling Level 3</Text>
  <Text Key="8203841D">{0.SimFirstName} can now select the Red Swirl bowling ball from the ball rack.\n\nOh, and {M0.he}{F0.she} should throw a few less gutterballs... always a nice perk.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF89925F">Reached Bowling Level 2</Text>
  <Text Key="397816A4">{0.SimFirstName} is a true {M0.Kingpin}{F0.Queenpin}, having perfected {M0.his}{F0.her} bowling form and skill! {M0.He}{F0.She} can now choose the Clear Skull bowling ball.\n\nAdults will now wear a bowling glove while playing, and all ages will throw strikes on a more consistent basis. It's time to start thinking about acquiring {0.SimFirstName}'s first Perfect Llama game of ten strikes!</Text>
  <Text Key="64561762">Reached Bowling Level 5</Text>
  <Text Key="BDB0B23A">{0.SimFirstName} can now select the Marbled Blue bowling ball.\n\n{M0.He}{F0.She}'s really finding {M0.his}{F0.her} balance, and will fail less often when throwing the ball. {0.SimFirstName} will start to throw more strikes as well... Can {M0.he}{F0.she} pick up {M0.his}{F0.her} first turkey?</Text>
  <Text Key="ABA57134">Reached Bowling Level 4</Text>
  <Text Key="1A293393">Some would call Bowling a minor skill, but they'd only be technically correct. While it may only have five levels of advancement, Sims who put in the work to skill up will look undeniably cool. They'll acquire additional bowling balls as they go, and you may just bowl a Perfect Llama game of all strikes someday.\n\nBowling Skill is improved via... well... bowling. Get to it!</Text>
  <Text Key="F2B644CB">Bowling</Text>
  <Text Key="57396AEF">(Pre)FAB Stone Slab</Text>
  <Text Key="90C86606">(Pre)FAB Stone Slab</Text>
  <Text Key="0A5D2420">(Pre)FAB Stone Slab</Text>
  <Text Key="E9339F9F">(Pre)FAB Stone Slab</Text>
  <Text Key="850BFB16">(Pre)FAB Stone Slab</Text>
  <Text Key="3BA12501">Wooden Chevron Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="992FFBC4">Wooden Chevron Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="CCCA98CB">Wooden Chevron Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="CD6CF163">Wooden Chevron Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="18C4CA10">Wooden Chevron Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="2C3CE689">Wooden Chevron Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="811D3AA5">Wooden Chevron Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="B24274BC">Wooden Chevron Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="51D4962E">Wooden Chevron Paneling</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>