<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="D8CFCE9D">Earbuds have been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory.\n\nYou can use the earbuds from {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory, or you can click on {M0.him}{F0.her} while {M0.he's}{F0.she's} the active Sim and select the Earbuds menu.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBFF6509">(From Rock Climbing Wall)</Text>
  <Text Key="AA41BD98">{0.SimFirstName} conquered the Rock Climbing Wall endurance challenge!</Text>
  <Text Key="DB6F6E81">(From Rock Climbing Wall)</Text>
  <Text Key="823888FA">(From Rock Climbing Wall)</Text>
  <Text Key="F6C8E47B">(From Rock Climbing Wall)</Text>
  <Text Key="47968625">(From Rock Climbing Wall)</Text>
  <Text Key="51988B87">(From Rock Climbing Wall)</Text>
  <Text Key="997C618C">(From Rock Climbing Wall)</Text>
  <Text Key="D3C074CC">{0.SimFirstName} was unable to complete the endurance challenge climb. Allow {M0.his}{F0.her} muscles to cool down for a few hours before trying again.\n\nHigher Fitness Skill can provide increased stamina if {0.SimFirstName} continues to struggle.</Text>
  <Text Key="55D892F5">(From Rock Climbing Wall)</Text>
  <Text Key="5D34DE86">{0.SimFirstName} survived the first endurance challenge the Rock Climbing Wall has to offer. Not bad... can {M0.he}{F0.she} take the next step?\n\nTake a break to enjoy {M0.his}{F0.her} achievement and let those muscles relax before attempting another challenge.</Text>
  <Text Key="10A12519">Defeated Endurance Challenge #1</Text>
  <Text Key="9AD414C1">{0.SimFirstName} beat the toughest vertical endurance challenge the Rock Climbing Wall has to offer... but there are more challenges yet to be conquered.\n\nTake a break to enjoy {M0.his}{F0.her} achievement and let those muscles relax before attempting another challenge.</Text>
  <Text Key="72BD3CF4">Defeated Endurance Challenge #2</Text>
  <Text Key="F2CB109C">{0.SimFirstName} bested the easier of the Rock Climbing Wall's two overhang endurance challenges! Not bad, not bad... Does {M0.he}{F0.she} have what it takes for the next step up in difficulty?\n\nTake a break to enjoy {M0.his}{F0.her} achievement and let those muscles relax before attempting another challenge.</Text>
  <Text Key="DAA0C573">Defeated Endurance Challenge #3</Text>
  <Text Key="C6993217">{0.SimFirstName} made it past the second overhang endurance challenge - the toughest of its kind on the Rock Climbing Wall. Very impressive!\n\nTake a break to enjoy {M0.his}{F0.her} achievement and let those muscles relax before attempting another challenge.</Text>
  <Text Key="FAB8D9EE">Defeated Endurance Challenge #4</Text>
  <Text Key="09BE6BBA">{0.SimFirstName} survived the fifth and final endurance challenge! This dangerous challenge is attempted by few, and completed by even fewer... but {0.SimFirstName} can proudly declare {M0.himself}{F0.herself} amongst the list of victors, without a single singed hair on {M0.his}{F0.her} body!\n\nTake a break to enjoy {M0.his}{F0.her} achievement and let those muscles relax before attempting another challenge.</Text>
  <Text Key="20B18765">Defeated Endurance Challenge #5</Text>
  <Text Key="816E70D2">Uh huh! That's right! Climbing champion coming through! {0.SimFirstName} has defeated the toughest challenge the Rock Climbing Wall has to offer and lived to tell the tale!</Text>
  <Text Key="1BAA4DED">Challenge Climb Champion</Text>
  <Text Key="5DB0C3DA">{0.SimFirstName} did it! {M0.He}{F0.She} beat the top endurance time set on the Rock Climbing Wall! Now when other Sims want to challenge themselves, it's {0.SimFirstName}'s time they'll be attempting to conquer. Ahhh... life's good at the top!\n\nWhy not run and brag about {M0.his}{F0.her} achievement to the Sim whose time you beat?</Text>
  <Text Key="D4344B05">The Champ Is Here</Text>
  <Text Key="32947FE4">Whew! If this were a rodeo, {0.SimFirstName} would score big points for how well {M0.he}{F0.she} clung to the climbing wall as it bucked to and fro.</Text>
  <Text Key="4DE72B2B">Survived Climbing Wall Malfunction</Text>
  <Text Key="6F654519">Hello! I’m contacting you on behalf of Be Fit as a Fiddle Co. We'd like to send you a free sample of our newest product, Hitz Earbuds. If you'd like to buy more, we accept online orders through the computer. We also make a Treadmill Rock Climbing Wall, and offer fitness videos via your TV. Be well!</Text>
  <Text Key="F80BE71E">I don't want free earbuds.</Text>
  <Text Key="3E3EA9FA">Rebel Sports</Text>
  <Text Key="2DD0E78B">Athleisure Defined</Text>
  <Text Key="416A62C3">Compression Discretion</Text>
  <Text Key="23C28AE9">Comfort In Sweats</Text>
  <Text Key="33AF5E7B">Running The Beat</Text>
  <Text Key="462A15B8">{0.SimFirstName} conquered the Rock Climbing Wall endurance challenge and set {1.Number} seconds as the new time to beat!</Text>
  <Text Key="44ABD57C">From the makers of the "Fountain of Gluteus Maximus" comes Trap's Trapezoid Tub! Every inch of this precision engineered whirlpool tub has been built with trapezius relief in mind. From the trapezoid base to the meticulously arranged jets, you won't find a better remedy for post-workout recovery. Be prepared... lowering yourself into the tub is known to cause your traps to slip into a state of instant bliss. Trap's Trapezoid Tub offers better muscle relief than any stretch or massage, along with the science to prove it!</Text>
  <Text Key="36DB47D3">Trap's Trapezoid Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="76108945">The harmonious balance of this leaning bookshelf helps create the perfect feng shui for an environment conducive to reading, learning, and absorbing the teachings of renowned authors.</Text>
  <Text Key="060CE940">Lean-To Learning</Text>
  <Text Key="38FCA5E7">Anything nature can do, man can do better. Such is the nature of the Fractal Door, with an elegant bow tie pattern etched with mathematical precision to serve as the entryway to a home.</Text>
  <Text Key="1E5AB31E">Fractal Door</Text>
  <Text Key="3F282BF9">Don't be sad, the Tear Drip Drop Lamp is here to brighten your day! You'll save money by not paying for superfluous things like lampshades, and in turn your room will be fully lit. That's a win-win in anyone's book!</Text>
  <Text Key="357640FC">Tear Drip Drop Lamp - Short</Text>
  <Text Key="3E1D5850">Don't be sad, the Tear Drip Drop Lamp is here to brighten your day! You'll save money by not paying for superfluous things like lampshades, and in turn your room will be fully lit. That's a win-win in anyone's book!</Text>
  <Text Key="C6D0057F">Tear Drip Drop Lamp - Medium</Text>
  <Text Key="54863ABB">Don't be sad, the Tear Drip Drop Lamp is here to brighten your day! You'll save money by not paying for superfluous things like lampshades, and in turn your room will be fully lit. That's a win-win in anyone's book!</Text>
  <Text Key="261C0D1A">Tear Drip Drop Lamp - Long</Text>
  <Text Key="64148CD1">This stone's secret only reveals itself in the dark of night! This is no mere rock... it happens to be an exquisitely crafted light fixture. It's interior has been hollowed out with a surface so thin that light passes through to emit a pleasant glow.</Text>
  <Text Key="E1DC0424">Secret Stone</Text>
  <Text Key="0F84128D">This portal only makes itself traversable to ascendant Sims, of which there is only one known to be in existence... the Grim Reaper himself. Some say a tithe of restless, miserable souls would rend the portal open for a mere mortal, but this hearsay has never been shown to have a shred of credibility.</Text>
  <Text Key="84A4DED8">Ascendant Portal</Text>
  <Text Key="0302D09E">Ansim Adams, descendant of the famous nature photographer, tried to launch his career by subverting his grandfather's work through the use of full color photography. Unsurprisingly, art critics labeled this move as shallow and pedantic, and Ansim is a relatively unknown footnote in the history of photography.</Text>
  <Text Key="CF0298A1">Naturewatch</Text>
  <Text Key="3FE17EB3">What's the use of a good shag rug if you can't tell others about it? No need to be a gentleman; brag to all your friends about this sumptuous hand woven piece. Exquisitely crafted on a loom, the yarns and backing are joined together into one harmonious product that's guaranteed to retain its flawlessness for years to come.</Text>
  <Text Key="9C51ECE2">Shag &amp; Tell Runner Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="5922699E">Subdivide the fractal pattern on this rug and it'll be as if you received two rugs in one. Subdivide it again to quadruple your rug count! With this exponential growth, your floor will be fully carpeted in no time... I've run the numbers; the math checks out!</Text>
  <Text Key="45EC13A1">Fractal Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="4CAFCA86">An ancient proverb states that "A rolling stone gathers no moss." Well, don't you worry - this stone won't be rolling anywhere anytime soon. Decorate your home with these lovely moss covered stones to assert that you're no longer part of life's rat race, and are fully content loafing about while reveling in your success.</Text>
  <Text Key="E2062919">Moss Covered Stone</Text>
  <Text Key="BF2BF47A">Hitz Earbuds - music for Sims on the move!\n\nListen to your earbuds when you want to soak in the music, or simply turn them on when you're looking to multitask.</Text>
  <Text Key="DE70CA95">Black Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="1BF7EB42">White Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="ED690247">Red Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="4D3556EC">Green Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="5F85AC61">Blue Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="8064A7CE">Pink Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="8E3FD3D3">Orange Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="BD936668">Teal Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="264F3E6D">Gold Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="E4D11C85">Back in the 20th century, Sims were known to use stationary climbing walls to simulate scaling a rock surface... can you imagine? How quaint! This sculptural piece hearkens back to those yesteryears... just don't try and attach a carabiner to it.</Text>
  <Text Key="8DAA3680">Ode to Antique Climbing Walls</Text>
  <Text Key="BB983E6C">The glossy sheen on this towel rack's vaneer can be attributed to multiple years of bath towels being drug across its surface that were coated with the residue of natural body oils.</Text>
  <Text Key="8A6BD1A3">Shine On Towel Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="521806A7">When is a mirror not a mirror? Perhaps it's when you gaze into the reflective surface and see an optical illusion. This mirror is no ordinary trick of the eye though, it's simply double vision.</Text>
  <Text Key="5EF76DDE">Double Vision</Text>
  <Text Key="DD24AABC">A prefabricated shelf that allows you to bring a bit of nature into your home with ease. Simply pop the hinges open, lock them into place, and mount it on your wall.</Text>
  <Text Key="26AB2413">Pop n' Lock Shelving</Text>
  <Text Key="A8877749">Cleanse yourself of the shackles of the daily grind in the At One With Shower. Be at one with yourself, at one with nature, or at one with luxury. Regardless of your motivation, you'll slip into blissful serenity as your worries are rinsed away.</Text>
  <Text Key="8EF859AC">At One With Shower</Text>
  <Text Key="563773CE">What seems to be a simple sink on its surface, can in fact play tricks with the mind when stared at. If you gaze at the Bilvet Basin from a precise angle, what once appeared to be two legs will suddenly become three.</Text>
  <Text Key="2140F1F1">Blivet Basin</Text>
  <Text Key="5FB6BD83">This exquisite dining chair is made from Black Ironwood - a special wood that's one of the densest and heaviest known to Sims. Due to its high cutting resistance, carpenters actually shape this chair's frame by pounding on the wood with metallic hammers.</Text>
  <Text Key="405433D2">Hammer Forged</Text>
  <Text Key="0CE443CC">Is your body a bit pear shaped? Working to get that svelte form you know is the "true you"? Try the Counterbalance Living Chair - it's off-balanced in just the right way to accommodate you.</Text>
  <Text Key="8FA1A683">Counterbalance</Text>
  <Text Key="B03C3137">The Perfect Balance Chaise Longue offers a 'tough love" solution to those suffering from vertigo. With its squared edges and unforgiving backrest, it's a surface no Sim will desire to spend long on, no matter how dizzy they may feel.</Text>
  <Text Key="51E2C98E">Perfect Balance</Text>
  <Text Key="03EE0D11">The regional government of Shang Simla permitted the removal of the peak of Mount Ai-a-Nie after locals complained that the mountain was blocking a spectacular sunset from the viewing platform atop the Temple of Heaven. The top of the mountain was sliced clean off, and then divided into 60 equal slabs of rock. These pieces were formed into coffee tables and presented as gifts to dignitaries from other countries around the world. As years passed, some of these tables came into the possession of private dealers, and are now available for purchase at this extraordinarily reasonable price. Act now to own a piece of history!</Text>
  <Text Key="FE195A64">Mt. Ai-a-Nie Summit Coffee Table</Text>
  <Text Key="540D2A64">A dining table fit for the 1%! The Signature V dining table incorporates a glass surface so that you can admire your expensive one-of-a-kind shoes while you dine.</Text>
  <Text Key="17E422AB">Signature V</Text>
  <Text Key="F01F7134">Local artist Lansing Feltham crafted this end table based on sonar mappings of the Windenburg shoreline. This environmental study was carried out when the government tried to prove the existence of a long rumored sea-monster which locals affectionately referred to as Emily. While the results of the investigation were inconclusive, the reality TV series it spawned was thoroughly entertaining.</Text>
  <Text Key="9F3B269B">Unfathomable End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="950957C5">There's nothing artificial about this elegant hallway table. Don't mind the termites, that's the price you pay to bring the beauty of nature inside.</Text>
  <Text Key="93890CC0">Au Naturel Slab</Text>
  <Text Key="C6635C46">The Throne World exists as the antithesis of light. It serves as a plane of existence where the contents of a Sim's bowels descend into the dark bowels of the sewage underworld.</Text>
  <Text Key="897C5BD9">Throne World</Text>
  <Text Key="BFF0EA73">Conduct your workouts in a socially and environmentally irresponsible manner, namely... indoors in an air conditioned gym with membership fees and a lengthy application designed to keep out the riffraff.</Text>
  <Text Key="8E07B5A2">Selfish Ethos Treadmill</Text>
  <Text Key="236C32C0">Here at Be Fit as a Fiddle Co. we aim for the top - and so can you!\n\nHave you ever felt like your life goals are just out of reach? Struggling to climb the corporate ladder and falling just short? We've got the solution! Introducing our Top Hitz Rock Climbing Wall, featuring an endless treadmill climb. We think it's a handy metaphor for the pivotal moments in your life; will you succumb to the grind, or will you strive for the top? Work out! Improve yourself! Success CAN be within reach!\n\n*Great for simultaneously losing weight and building muscle.</Text>
  <Text Key="6E5D618F">Top Hitz Rock Climbing Wall</Text>
  <Text Key="370BA993">This innovative window from Mr. Swisher contains a patented, fully automatic washing system to ensure it's always crystal clear. A small motion detector scans the area to ensure no Sims are nearby, at which point the scrubbing brush is engaged and travels the length of the window.</Text>
  <Text Key="B497E942">S. Swisher Auto Washing Window</Text>
  <Text Key="29A2EA07">No matter how many times you duplicate this window, its fractal pattern remains the same. Therein lies the mathematical beauty of this accoutrement to architectural masterpieces.</Text>
  <Text Key="69F309BE">Fractal Window</Text>
  <Text Key="3C4802FF">Before you step up your muscle game, you better put some respect in your workout routine. Follow these common rules to practice good gym etiquette:\n\n1) Wipe down gym equipment after every workout to remove sweat.\n2) Absolutely no calls or texting near the workout equipment.\n3) When the lunk alarm sounds, cease your workout and calmly proceed to the exit.</Text>
  <Text Key="4AEC4226">You Better Respect</Text>
  <Text Key="76DD8915">Brag About Climbing Prowess</Text>
  <Text Key="C4D1D7B4">Brag About Beating Climbing Time</Text>
  <Text Key="247E3179">{0.SimFirstName} already has a pair of earbuds in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB362090">Black Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="A089419B">White Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="90462B92">Red Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="B9C0BC7D">Green Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="6C9FACBC">Blue Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="0A357A87">Pink Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="C3CEADAE">Orange Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="B9EC4929">Teal Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="AD460B48">Gold Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="54F0808D">Thanks for ordering! The Earbuds {0.SimFirstName} purchased can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F466FBB">Purchase Earbuds</Text>
  <Text Key="DF5CE802">Be Upset</Text>
  <Text Key="74A7436E">Celebrate Win</Text>
  <Text Key="769740C6">Climb Gentle Incline</Text>
  <Text Key="C8293551">1) Vertical Challenge - Beginner</Text>
  <Text Key="D6866A03">Reset Record Time</Text>
  <Text Key="FF4214E5">Sabotage!</Text>
  <Text Key="ADB1457C">Climb Gentle Incline (Push the Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="61F77A36">Climb Vertical Incline (Push the Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="0C8DA775">Climb Vertical Incline</Text>
  <Text Key="305C54E2">This is too difficult for {0.SimFirstName}'s current rock climbing abilities. </Text>
  <Text Key="BD11F754">Climb Overhang (Push the Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="17D54D34">Climb Overhang</Text>
  <Text Key="DD0F1E04">Climb Overhang with Fire (Push the Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="F6058CB3">Climb Overhang with Fire</Text>
  <Text Key="04AD81AB">{0.SimFirstName} has already set the current time to beat.</Text>
  <Text Key="4AA1E74A">{0.SimFirstName} should practice climbing before attempting {M0.his}{F0.her} first endurance challenge.</Text>
  <Text Key="2704F53B">1) Vertical Challenge - Beginner (Push the Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="9402E370">Defeat {1.SimFirstName}'s Time of {2.Number} Seconds</Text>
  <Text Key="99E78234">2) Vertical Challenge - Easy</Text>
  <Text Key="9412C704">{0.SimFirstName} must defeat the previous endurance challenge level first.</Text>
  <Text Key="E7A1718F">2) Vertical Challenge - Easy (Push the Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="35F260D2">3) Overhang Challenge - Medium (Push the Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="03AB413E">3) Overhang Challenge - Medium</Text>
  <Text Key="1ABA6905">4) Overhang Challenge - Hard (Push the Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="5AB4F161">4) Overhang Challenge - Hard</Text>
  <Text Key="812CEB46">5) Fire Challenge - Dangerous (Push the Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="CECA8A60">5) Fire Challenge - Dangerous</Text>
  <Text Key="2F947A9E">Defeat {1.SimFirstName}'s Time of {2.Number} Seconds (Push The Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="D1E6446F">Defeat Record Time of {2.Number} Seconds</Text>
  <Text Key="013A3F7A">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished upgrading the Rock Climbing Wall with self-repair functionality. Should the wall experience any malfunctions in the future, nanomachines will be released to restore its operational status in no time at all.</Text>
  <Text Key="E84A913D">Upgrade Self-Repairing</Text>
  <Text Key="5155D624">The Rock Climbing Wall will immediately repair itself after malfunctioning.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="61930077">Continue Upgrade Self-Repairing</Text>
  <Text Key="235C2DE4">Watch Climber</Text>
  <Text Key="392D6DFA">Plumboomba Dance Video (Push The Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="CF372808">Plumboomba Dance Video</Text>
  <Text Key="B3B97FBF">Power Sculpting Video (Push The Limits)</Text>
  <Text Key="776C07C3">Dance Video</Text>
  <Text Key="A3E3F9B4">Power Sculpting Video</Text>
  <Text Key="4F033CAE">Form a group with another Sim before attempting a group workout.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBDC2807">Workout To Dance Video With</Text>
  <Text Key="98FA3ACD">Workout To Power Sculpting Video With</Text>
  <Text Key="654E1180">HomeSpa</Text>
  <Text Key="70F8EA4E">Work-It Circuit</Text>
  <Text Key="8CE07BCC">No Workout Zone</Text>
  <Text Key="1C844962">{0.SimFirstName} already has a pair of Earbuds in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE9075CA">Watch Dance Video</Text>
  <Text Key="D18530E3">Dance Video</Text>
  <Text Key="B315012E">Watch Power Sculpting Video</Text>
  <Text Key="3A0289FF">Power Sculpting Video</Text>
  <Text Key="1C661CF4">Endurance Challenge Climb</Text>
  <Text Key="B1E36962">Climb</Text>
  <Text Key="5694B250">Workout</Text>
  <Text Key="74D86BA8">Beat Another Sim's Endurance Time</Text>
  <Text Key="820D02C0">Click on a Rock Climbing Wall, and attempt to survive longer than the Endurance Challenge Climb time set by another Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC66D95E">Go Rock Wall Climbing</Text>
  <Text Key="13A11D1E">Click on a Rock Climbing Wall and select Climb.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F5CB92A">Beat a Climbing Challenge</Text>
  <Text Key="ACCA37D2">Click on a Rock Climbing Wall and select an Endurance Challenge Climb.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D4FBB67">Buy a Rock Climbing Wall</Text>
  <Text Key="4FE76949">Purchase a Rock Climbing Wall from Build Mode. Look for it in the Active section of Activities and Skills.</Text>
  <Text Key="E99CEB59">Do a Dance Workout</Text>
  <Text Key="F36BB28B">Click on a TV and select Workout, then select the Plumboomba Dance Video.</Text>
  <Text Key="1C1DFB75">Do a Power Sculpting Workout</Text>
  <Text Key="4278FE1F">Click on a TV and select Workout, then select the Power Sculpting Video.</Text>
  <Text Key="4DCD6FE0">Rock Climbing</Text>
  <Text Key="85EB4862">Wavestone</Text>
  <Text Key="EDA031A4">At One With Stone</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>