<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="D9B61FB8">Sophistico Tile</Text>
  <Text Key="6B5FF962">Let The Hightower Double Bed help you get the rest you need to keep being the boss that you are. Its classic yet luxurious design will help you enjoy sleep like never before, with silky sheets that feel soft and light on your skin. When morning comes, wake up refreshed and ready to conquer the world!</Text>
  <Text Key="780ED5DD">The Hightower Double Bed </Text>
  <Text Key="A03F4112">Add a touch of personality to your space with this stylish free-standing bookcase supported by glass shelves and a sleek metal frame. It's an excellent place to store your designer photobooks, marbled chests, and chic decor, proving you have the finest taste. </Text>
  <Text Key="BE1A482D">Bookcase No. 212</Text>
  <Text Key="ECCA392D">This curtain is designed to bring the ultimate in luxury to your windows. The soft linen panels, and simplistic curtain rod, paired with glass accents, balance contemporary style and timeless elegance. Perfect for any space!</Text>
  <Text Key="CEF88EF8">Legendary Curtain - Left</Text>
  <Text Key="63B8EFDC">This curtain is designed to bring the ultimate in luxury to your windows. The soft linen panels, and simplistic curtain rod, paired with glass accents, balance contemporary style and timeless elegance. Perfect for any space!</Text>
  <Text Key="974FFBB3">Tall Legendary Curtain - Left</Text>
  <Text Key="85E77230">This curtain is designed to bring the ultimate in luxury to your windows. The soft linen panels, and simplistic curtain rod, paired with glass accents, balance contemporary style and timeless elegance. Perfect for any space!</Text>
  <Text Key="A51A01DF">Legendary Curtain - Right</Text>
  <Text Key="E8BD3C59">This curtain is designed to bring the ultimate in luxury to your windows. The soft linen panels, and simplistic curtain rod, paired with glass accents, balance contemporary style and timeless elegance. Perfect for any space!</Text>
  <Text Key="FB5847DC">Tall Legendary Curtain - Right</Text>
  <Text Key="70AF8FB2">This curtain rod is designed to bring the ultimate in luxury to your windows by balancing contemporary style and timeless elegance. Perfect for any space!</Text>
  <Text Key="E54A924D">Legendary Curtain Rod</Text>
  <Text Key="1321109D">Lose the blah and bring some bling to your bedroom with the SoChic Dresser. Featuring a classic four-drawer design and a stunning glass top, this piece is sure to impress and inspire.</Text>
  <Text Key="F64C9C88">SoChic Dresser</Text>
  <Text Key="516E00F3">Be an icon and a legend under the epitome of ceiling light luxury. Now, you can have a room that shines as bright as you!</Text>
  <Text Key="A9CE3122">The Light of Legends</Text>
  <Text Key="7D347496">Be an even bigger icon and legend under the epitome of ceiling light luxury. Now, you can have a room that shines as bright as you!</Text>
  <Text Key="3C922449">The Longer Light of Legends</Text>
  <Text Key="7138B7BA">Why have any basic lamp when you can have this one? Light it up in style with this luxurious table lamp so everyone can see how iconic you are.</Text>
  <Text Key="E936AB65">The Lamp of Luxury</Text>
  <Text Key="A3095336">Add an elegant, minimalist touch to any wall with the Incline Leaning Mirror. This beautiful and modern piece is guaranteed to help you look and be your best.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0698169">Incline Leaning Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="E1D252AB">When you see the Moment, it stops you in your tracks. This high-quality art print encourages you to appreciate beauty, peace, and on occasion, the finer things that life has to offer.</Text>
  <Text Key="731BEFAA">The Moment</Text>
  <Text Key="23AE66F7">Liven up any corner of the home with this beautiful "elevated" planter. Don't let its simple design fool you; there's sophistication in the understated.</Text>
  <Text Key="2AFDB14E">Elevated Taste Planter</Text>
  <Text Key="B0A0F87F">Invite elegance and luxury into your space with the Gilded Intersections Rug. This round rug is a stunning accent piece featuring plushness that can’t be beaten. Add it to any room in your home for a touch of comfort and sophistication!</Text>
  <Text Key="F8722AA6">Gilded Intersections Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="8E03F699">Find the perfect muse for your interior with this elegant sculpture. Crafted from polished stone, this impressive piece of art is hard to resist. Exquisite details and timeless beauty make it the perfect focal point for any room.</Text>
  <Text Key="949E311C">Muse-On-A-Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="C58105A4">Talented. Brilliant. Incredible. Amazing. Show-stopping. Spectacular. Never the same. Totally unique. Completely not ever been done before. The Perfect Pillow will forever be that final touch to any room.</Text>
  <Text Key="60CB02EB">The Perfect Pillow</Text>
  <Text Key="CF3EAC88">"Leeb, Leefuh, Lurve" is a mantra we've all heard before, but this plaque serves as a reminder to live with passion and purpose. Just imagine: as you come home at the end of the day and open your door, you'll see this gorgeous phrase sitting there to uplift you and encourage nothing but good vibes!</Text>
  <Text Key="1E7D0627">"Leeb, Leefuh, Lurve" Plaque</Text>
  <Text Key="B814587A">This luxurious mini bag is perfect for the gals with big things happening and for the bright dreams that they carry. This mini bag is as stylish as its owner and comes with a sleek complimentary clutch and the perfect lipstick duo for any baddie prepared to slay the day.</Text>
  <Text Key="5230AE25">The Baddie's Bag</Text>
  <Text Key="40FC62F1">If you're looking for a stunning way to display your most treasured art, books, and accessories, you need the SoChic Wall Shelf. This one-of-a-kind shelf melds a low-profile metal frame with a sheet of glass to create a work of art that is truly, breathtakingly elegant.</Text>
  <Text Key="65F635C4">SoChic Wall Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="BFB8A1EA">This chair is all about practical luxury—who doesn't want that? The contemporary low-back design, sleek gold frame, and sturdy legs make this chair the perfect spot to kick back in style.</Text>
  <Text Key="E5EA3175">Avant Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="C3861D45">The Dreamer’s Chair is a statement piece that demands attention. Its graceful, rounded shape and beautiful upholstery will add style to any room. Sit back, relax, and let your dreams become a reality!</Text>
  <Text Key="9F916540">The Dreamer's Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="7607D529">The Vintique Record Player combines all the simple elegance of vinyl with the convenience of modern technology in a sleek and compact design. This iconic device will revolutionize your dance moves and always help you march to the beat of your drum.</Text>
  <Text Key="0A794C0C">Vintique Record Player</Text>
  <Text Key="9A318429">Luxury is apparent in every detail of the SoChic End Table, from its modern design and durable metal frame to its thick glass top. This end table is ideal for your bedroom or living room and can store magazines, books, and mementos for a little extra sparkle in your space.</Text>
  <Text Key="B419290C">SoChic End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="2A6BEDC4">Sparkle and shine like a star with the All Glowed-Up Vanity! This stunning vanity is designed to help you glow up every morning by giving you all the space you need for your daily beauty routine. With room for all your products and a beautiful glass surface, this piece will enhance any room.</Text>
  <Text Key="7801388B">All Glowed-Up Vanity</Text>
  <Text Key="2313A64A">Transform your home into a gallery with The ArtFrame TV. This flat-screen TV is disguised as a framed piece of art when turned off and becomes an incredible display of entertainment when turned on. Now you can truly have the best of both worlds!</Text>
  <Text Key="37275855">The ArtFrame TV</Text>
  <Text Key="7145AF62">Livin' Luxe Bedroom</Text>
  <Text Key="E75C22F7">Sophistico Accent Wall</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>