<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="1905A13C">(From Throwing a Coin in a Fountain)</Text>
  <Text Key="5241446F">The offering presented has been found wanting. The Whispering Wishing Well is displeased and wishes are more likely to result in unpleasant outcomes.</Text>
  <Text Key="98B0102F">A suitable offering! The Whispering Wishing Well is satisfied and is now more amenable to granting wishes.</Text>
  <Text Key="13A1C7FE">What a highly generous offering! The Whispering Wishing Well is most pleased and will nearly certainly grant a wish well.</Text>
  <Text Key="C0963AE0">Hello, this is the adoption agency calling for {0.SimName}. Your application papers were above and beyond any we've ever seen. There's no doubt in our minds that you'll be an exemplary {M0.father}{F0.mother}! In recognition of your propensity for parenting, you've been pre-approved for a free adoption.\n\nOh, before you hang up... this is a limited time offer, so please rush to your computer to adopt today!</Text>
  <Text Key="33524682">(From Making a Wish)</Text>
  <Text Key="D0BB6D51">And they say money can't buy happiness...</Text>
  <Text Key="8E81BDA4">A Coin For Good Luck</Text>
  <Text Key="901CC28E">What a sight! Who can resist a smile when seeing a fountain overflowing with soap bubbles?</Text>
  <Text Key="318988B1">Entranced By Suds</Text>
  <Text Key="CE8F769F">Two arms... check! Two legs... check! Can't walk through walls... check! Not only has {0.SimFirstName} returned to the living, but {M0.he's}{F0.she's} formed a pact with the reaper granting instant resurrection in case of any unexpected death. {0.SimFirstName} can sleep soundly knowing {M0.he'll}{F0.she'll} live out a long, full life until passing away at a ripe old age.</Text>
  <Text Key="A473FC46">Miracle Revival</Text>
  <Text Key="90B9A9E2">{0.SimFirstName} is unable to return to life for the time being; the wishing well made that perfectly clear. At least there's peace to be had in knowing one's own fate.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBB3FF5D">Accepted Fate</Text>
  <Text Key="DB35FB3D">What good fortune! The adoption agency must be overflowing with unplaced children to be waiving their standard adoption fees. {0.SimFirstName} should rush to a computer and adopt now!</Text>
  <Text Key="A6B217A8">Adoption Pre-Approved</Text>
  <Text Key="0C3A2AD9">Blinded by the light\nAge stage reset\nThese bones are feeling right</Text>
  <Text Key="70E6CB5C">A Few Years Younger</Text>
  <Text Key="EC012197">{0.SimFirstName} was literally walking on sunshine for a moment there! Such a happy high is contagious; all of {0.SimFirstName}'s happy Moodlets will last even longer than normal.</Text>
  <Text Key="4A66906E">Always Sunny</Text>
  <Text Key="64CF4C56">The Whispering Wishing Well must have been created with the Hates Children trait, as it's cruelly made {0.SimFirstName} temporarily unable to conceive!</Text>
  <Text Key="D2F2AF09">Temporary Infertility</Text>
  <Text Key="62E2C46C">{0.SimFirstName}'s mouth involuntarily stretches wide before forcefully bursting open with laughter...\n"Ho-ho-ha-ha"\n"A-ha-ha-he-he-heh-heh"\n"A-HE-HE-HE-HA-HA"\n"HAHAHAHAHAHAHA"</Text>
  <Text Key="C71883A3">Can't Stop Smiling</Text>
  <Text Key="8EA65946">Oh sweet serendipity, a slice of Ambrosia just manifested itself in {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory! A return to life is just a bite away, should {M0.he}{F0.she} choose to keep it for {M0.himself}{F0.herself} that is...</Text>
  <Text Key="3DEAC2D9">Chance At Life</Text>
  <Text Key="519EE2DF">{0.SimFirstName} thought a flick of a coin would be enough to gain a skill? No, {M0.he'll}{F0.she'll} have to work for it... but {M0.his}{F0.her} wish will provide a boost to any skill gains for as long as this Moodlet remains.</Text>
  <Text Key="80395786">Expedient Learning</Text>
  <Text Key="07EDD3FF">Time is definitely on {0.SimFirstName}'s side... a few additional days have been added to {M0.his}{F0.her} overall lifetime.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0A2E526">Extended Life</Text>
  <Text Key="174B2D64">Happiness is in the air! Specifically, some other Sim's happiness. That can only mean one thing... some poor sap nearby had an unfortunate encounter with a wishing well. Don't let it go to waste!</Text>
  <Text Key="7C28BBAB">Extra Vigor</Text>
  <Text Key="2830DEB7">There's nothing like an extra spring in {0.SimFirstName}'s step to help {M0.him}{F0.her} through the day!</Text>
  <Text Key="B97E5A0E">Feeling Young</Text>
  <Text Key="8B12810F">The temperamental wishing well is displeased at {0.SimFirstName}'s attempts to take shortcuts in life. In {0.SimFirstName}'s forced stupor, {M0.he'll}{F0.she'll} struggle to progress in any skills.</Text>
  <Text Key="7EE7C4D6">Fogged Mind</Text>
  <Text Key="B7475586">{0.SimFirstName} feels cheerful... overjoyed even! That's a fair deal for a single Simoleon!</Text>
  <Text Key="D490DA19">Forever Cheerful</Text>
  <Text Key="A3C62C7E">All of the coins that Sims have wished upon were suddenly regurgitated up and out of the well, and straight into {0.SimFirstName}'s wallet.</Text>
  <Text Key="A516A401">Fortunes Abound</Text>
  <Text Key="C30EAF15">Not only was {0.SimFirstName} dropped a full letter grade, but the school's vice-principal falsely accused {M0.his}{F0.her} of attempting to hack the school's database to change her grades. How could a simple wish go so wrong?</Text>
  <Text Key="8254BC30">Grades Dropped</Text>
  <Text Key="60859A98">{0.SimFirstName} tried to convince {M0.himself}{F0.herself} that {M0.he}{F0.she} was happy... {M0.he}{F0.she} really did. This soul crushing sadness is the result of a wish gone wrong, and an ill-advised attempt to convince oneself otherwise.</Text>
  <Text Key="0AA6BB17">Happiness Doesn't Last Forever</Text>
  <Text Key="C63C5154">As {0.SimFirstName} heard {M0.his}{F0.her} coin splash deep within the depths of the well, two words pierced {M0.his}{F0.her} mind... "Give Up." Well then, no romance for {0.SimFirstName} for awhile.</Text>
  <Text Key="45DC5D3B">Hopeless in Romance</Text>
  <Text Key="2A5A5FE0">{0.SimFirstName} is happy. Happy happy happy. If {M0.he}{F0.she} keeps telling {M0.himself}{F0.herself} that it must be true, right? Happy!</Text>
  <Text Key="650CA62F">I AM HAPPY</Text>
  <Text Key="5E9F7B74">That wasn't quite what {0.SimFirstName} wished for, but the new ingredient that popped into existence in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory ought to help. With a few more ingredients and a dash of cooking skill, {0.SimFirstName} could whip up an Ambrosia recipe that'll return {M0.him}{F0.her} to the land of the living. A few more wishes ought to yield {M0.him}{F0.her} what {M0.he}{F0.she} needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="7ECB34DB">Ingredients of Life</Text>
  <Text Key="00D93C75">{0.SimFirstName} was accused of cheating in an effort to raise {M0.his}{F0.her} grades! {M0.He}{F0.She} tried to escape punishment by arguing that there's nowhere in the syllabus that states that wishing wells aren't allowed, but the vice-principal simply wouldn't listen!</Text>
  <Text Key="1C390910">I Wished For Better Grades!</Text>
  <Text Key="F89BC7AB">{0.SimFirstName} wished for a promotion, not a chance at a promotion! What's this nonsense about needing to work harder to get ahead? That was the whole point of wishing!</Text>
  <Text Key="D4E43EAA">I Wished For The Promotion!</Text>
  <Text Key="97FB66EE">A bundle of "joy" - hah, what a farce. The wishing well foisted an evil child upon {0.SimFirstName} - surely the result of another poor parent's wish to be rid of the brat.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4306091">"Joys" of Children</Text>
  <Text Key="F0EA9133">It's a wishing well miracle! A "wiracle!" {0.SimFirstName} has been rewarded with a brilliant new member of the family!</Text>
  <Text Key="2FC39C62">Joys of Children</Text>
  <Text Key="C595DA5B">Something appears to have gone wrong. {0.SimFirstName} was enveloped in a gleaming light, {M0.he}{F0.she} could feel {M0.himself}{F0.herself} passing back to the realm of the mortals, when suddenly... BAM! Dead once again.</Text>
  <Text Key="1969B83A">Just A Ghost</Text>
  <Text Key="71E0C5F9">The well reached into the depths of {0.SimFirstName}'s mind and revealed {M0.his}{F0.her} dark truth...\n\n"A wish cannot be granted to one who is incapable of possessing."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} recoiled in horror, embarrassed that {M0.his}{F0.her} simple wish exposed one of {M0.his}{F0.her} deepest insecurities.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B28EEFC">Lack of Talent</Text>
  <Text Key="20D6F235">The wishing well bestowed {0.SimFirstName} with a tragic dilemma. Being around others will cause {M0.him}{F0.her} sadness, but nearby sims will find happiness in {M0.his}{F0.her} misery. Oh, delicious schadenfreude!</Text>
  <Text Key="44BBEFD0">Leaking Happiness</Text>
  <Text Key="9D5B7615">With great knowledge comes great power, and the wishing well just bestowed a particularly juicy morsel into {0.SimFirstName}'s mind. It would be quite lucrative to blackmail another Sim in exchange for {0.SimFirstName}'s silence... Is it worth making an enemy in exchange for a pocket full of Simoleons?</Text>
  <Text Key="F6426130">Learned Darkest Secrets</Text>
  <Text Key="012C6CD4">Loss of youth? What about a loss of birthday cake!? {0.SimFirstName} suddenly aged up... Perhaps it was the well's cunning plan to force {0.SimFirstName} to continue to use the wishing well if {M0.he}{F0.she} wants to get through {M0.his}{F0.her} bucket list before {M0.he}{F0.she} kicks it. Does {0.SimFirstName} dare try again?</Text>
  <Text Key="8512D7BB">Loss of Youth</Text>
  <Text Key="1B7A3548">{0.SimFirstName} has been swindled! Despite receiving a large sum of Simoleons from the wishing well, {M0.he}{F0.she} immediately had the inexplicable urge to spend them all (and more!) on cosmetic hats in {M0.his}{F0.her} newest mobile gaming addiction!</Text>
  <Text Key="EB5263E7">Microtransactions!</Text>
  <Text Key="C8594B02">The last thing {0.SimFirstName} remembers is a fleeting moment of clarity, as if all the world's combined knowledge rushed into {M0.his}{F0.her} head... only to have it burst upon discovering a brain too small to store it. It's time for {0.SimFirstName} to take a break from improving any skills for awhile.</Text>
  <Text Key="FD6200FD">Mind Numbed</Text>
  <Text Key="BD71CC63">{0.SimFirstName} can still feel the lick of the flames against {M0.his}{F0.her} skin. {M0.He}{F0.She} was helpless as {M0.his}{F0.her} Simoleons leapt from {M0.his}{F0.her} pocket and flew into the fire. What could reside in the depths of the well to generate such hexed flames?</Text>
  <Text Key="C6A16932">My Simoleons Burned Up!</Text>
  <Text Key="23EAC5AE">The face on the wishing well implanted the ultimate pick up line into {0.SimFirstName}'s subconsciousness. Use it wisely on a target of {M0.his}{F0.her} affection - once the words are uttered they'll be wiped from {0.SimFirstName}'s mind.</Text>
  <Text Key="64804351">Mystical Romance Tips</Text>
  <Text Key="C83C0CB6">That wasn't what {0.SimFirstName} wished for at all! Doesn't the wishing well understand Simlish?</Text>
  <Text Key="EB0975E9">Not What I Wished For</Text>
  <Text Key="60639286">That wishing well tricked {0.SimFirstName}! After pushing {M0.himself}{F0.herself} to unheard of limits, {M0.he's}{F0.she's} crashed back down to reality and {M0.his}{F0.her} body needs time to recover.</Text>
  <Text Key="05C70119">Overexerted Myself</Text>
  <Text Key="099C7090">Power overwhelming! {0.SimFirstName} feels like {M0.he}{F0.she} could run and run and never stop!</Text>
  <Text Key="FC04E4BF">Overflowing Vigor</Text>
  <Text Key="30DA6DD0">As a ghost, {0.SimFirstName} can stay {M0.his}{F0.her} current age forever and ever and ever. This is what {M0.he}{F0.she} wished for, yes? Wait, {M0.he's}{F0.she's} unhappy with the outcome? Perhaps the wishing well can help with that...</Text>
  <Text Key="E4084DFF">Perpetual Youth</Text>
  <Text Key="401ED9D6">Success! {0.SimFirstName}'s wish was granted. On to bigger and better things (or maybe this is an opportunity to kick back and relax for a bit!)</Text>
  <Text Key="F5E8DF89">Movin' On Up</Text>
  <Text Key="D35438E8">{0.SimFirstName} is the proud {M0.dad}{F0.mom} of a new... ghost? And the child seems to have passed in the most tragic of fashions. Well, they certainly don't write parenting handbooks on how to handle this!</Text>
  <Text Key="5A322507">Raising A Ghost</Text>
  <Text Key="4681537C">When {0.SimFirstName} tossed a coin into the wishing well, the well figured {M0.he}{F0.she} could stand to lose a few more.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4C761D3">Sadim Touch</Text>
  <Text Key="7764F487">{0.SimFirstName} has started down the path of mastering a new skill. Check {M0.his}{F0.her} skill panel for tips on further progression.</Text>
  <Text Key="A1CE213E">Skill Learned</Text>
  <Text Key="51D7936B">Were those pheromones that were wafting out of the wishing well? Nonetheless, hurry to your lover; trying for a baby is nearly guaranteed to succeed while Woohooing under the well's blessing.</Text>
  <Text Key="1C7B1C6A">Try For Baby</Text>
  <Text Key="87A54224">Nothing sets the tone for a night of romance like a little flirting. Well... what is {0.SimFirstName} waiting for? Go paint the town red (or pink, as it were)!</Text>
  <Text Key="0F72106B">Ultimate Flirt</Text>
  <Text Key="9117318A">{0.SimFirstName} can check one skill off {M0.his}{F0.her} bucket list... {M0.He's}{F0.She's} a certified master now!</Text>
  <Text Key="DE6EBD95">Universal Knowledge</Text>
  <Text Key="AAFBB3A1">Hey! That wish for happiness came from {0.SimFirstName}! That blasted wishing well gave {M0.his}{F0.her} happiness away to other nearby Sims!</Text>
  <Text Key="5953BE54">Where Is My Happiness</Text>
  <Text Key="D263CEF2">Just because {0.SimFirstName} is a ghost doesn't mean {M0.he}{F0.she} can't appreciate the value of a simoleon. And that one... the one {M0.he}{F0.she} just threw down there in the bottom of the creepy well... appears to have been wasted. Not even a ghost would dare lower themselves in to retrieve it!</Text>
  <Text Key="31BAEE8D">Wish Not Granted</Text>
  <Text Key="EE45935B">{0.SimFirstName} just beat the one in 175 million odds and won the lottery! That's a lotta Simoleons!</Text>
  <Text Key="2CC9933A">Won the Lottery</Text>
  <Text Key="62199022">{0.SimFirstName}... worked... SO... HARD! One simple wish ruined it all? The thought of having to claw {M0.his}{F0.her} way back up the corporate ladder is enough to make one snap!</Text>
  <Text Key="C213259D">Worked So Hard</Text>
  <Text Key="CF1430DC">Play In Park Fountains</Text>
  <Text Key="C1427773">Play in Park Fountains</Text>
  <Text Key="7F1D22C7">Don't Play in Park Fountains</Text>
  <Text Key="4086E0AE">Flutes, volutes... it's totes cute!\n\n...wait, what do you mean someone forgot the flutes?!</Text>
  <Text Key="11D3A451">Incomplete Ionic</Text>
  <Text Key="EDDAB03A">Everything Nice</Text>
  <Text Key="DC0AEFFD">Boyish Charm</Text>
  <Text Key="55177BCC">Dainty And Florid</Text>
  <Text Key="09C72982">Fanciful Garments</Text>
  <Text Key="1B1B1F49">Affable Archetype</Text>
  <Text Key="405ABB18">You can trim the ivy from this fence, but when it looks this elegant why would you?</Text>
  <Text Key="41033497">Ivy League Fence
</Text>
  <Text Key="3710D948">Guaranteed to cause suds.</Text>
  <Text Key="884D0FE7">Detergent</Text>
  <Text Key="0F3BB5DD">Was the name too subtle? Saunter over and have a seat! This classic fountain beckons your buttocks with its comfortable rim.</Text>
  <Text Key="E675C3C8">Fountain of Gluteus Maximus</Text>
  <Text Key="DB07A6C4">A gate this stately demands ivy.</Text>
  <Text Key="8765138B">Ivy League Gate
</Text>
  <Text Key="7062C2E7">Originally crafted in the mid 1800s, this street light has since been retrofitted with sodium-vapor bulbs, giving the globes a warm yellow glow in the evenings.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A887A1E">Retrofitted Garden Gaslamp</Text>
  <Text Key="97C77177">Legend has it that when these path lamps were first introduced to the royal gardens, Princess Cordelia infamously stumbled and tripped over one.</Text>
  <Text Key="882DC8CE">Faux Pas Path Lamp
</Text>
  <Text Key="DA3548B0">These monkey bars have fallen upon hard times. While the Look at Me Monkey Bars (a leading brand in Sim playground equipment might I add) are built of the highest quality materials, they still require the most basic of upkeep to prevent vines from twining around them. This particular set has fallen to the folly of a lackadaisical groundskeeper.</Text>
  <Text Key="AAF6BD5F">Don't Look at Me Monkey Bars</Text>
  <Text Key="F27B1BB2">Although beautiful, green thumb Sims know all too well to never plant Hollyhocks near any crops that they may be growing. Hollyhocks are the perfect host to nefarious little weevils who are all to happy to feast upon a home grown garden. Enjoy this plant's gorgeous flowers from an arm's length.</Text>
  <Text Key="2D7F764D">Hollyhocks
</Text>
  <Text Key="EC2E0555">Sims are taught in botanical school how Iris is derived from the Ancient Greek word for a rainbow. Their flowers don't disappoint, coming in all manner of beautiful colors. Well... at least ten of them!</Text>
  <Text Key="9EC45E70">Iris
</Text>
  <Text Key="84B1026F">Thistles - nature's argument against vegetarians. Sims get converted to carnivores right quick when attempting to nosh on a thistle's prickly leaves. It's best to just let them grow in peace.</Text>
  <Text Key="EE8FABB6">Thistle
</Text>
  <Text Key="7D84086D">It's commonly accepted in Sim culture to confront any Sim who pronunciates the name of this plant as "lou-pine" and chastise them. Consequently, you rarely hear the name of this plant uttered in an effort to avoid derision.</Text>
  <Text Key="40B79938">Lupin
</Text>
  <Text Key="555C81F1">Also sometimes known as "larkspur", the name Delphinium is notable due to the dolphin shaped nectary that grows on its stems. Sims are advised against eating this plant due to an onset of severe digestive discomfort within hours of ingestion. </Text>
  <Text Key="A08E62C4">Delphinium
</Text>
  <Text Key="7B6C51F7">Some would lead you to believe that bushes are an appropriate place to woohoo. It is STRONGLY recommended that you do not attempt such activities within this rose bush.</Text>
  <Text Key="4D6D824E">Overgrown Rose Bush</Text>
  <Text Key="13C3451A">The next time you pass a lot ringed by a wall of roses, consider for a moment its utility as nature's barbed wire. Suddenly the beauty is lost, replaced with the urge to discover just what one may be hiding behind such a barrier...</Text>
  <Text Key="1AABB045">Nature's Barbed Wire - Small</Text>
  <Text Key="99824A83">The next time you pass a lot ringed by a wall of roses, consider for a moment its utility as nature's barbed wire. Suddenly the beauty is lost, replaced with the urge to discover just what one may be hiding behind such a barrier...</Text>
  <Text Key="0ED74AD2">Nature's Barbed Wire - Large</Text>
  <Text Key="72740D58">Were you aware that roses can be trained much the same way one may train a wild animal? These roses in particular are an exemplary example, uniformly climbing this lattice to provide a touch of colorful privacy.</Text>
  <Text Key="86BC41D7">Climbing Rose Lattice</Text>
  <Text Key="37266F20">Were you aware that roses can be trained much the same way one may train a wild animal? These roses in particular are an exemplary example, uniformly climbing this lattice while making way for a window that caters to looky-loos.</Text>
  <Text Key="78BCD06F">Windowed Climbing Rose Lattice</Text>
  <Text Key="927E568D">Lady Chloris was always a lover, protector, and provider of nature. She would have appreciated this statue cast in her honor becoming entangled in an overgrowth of roses.</Text>
  <Text Key="D5386AD8">Where The Green Fern Grows</Text>
  <Text Key="4762E01A">Millennials, who needs 'em? They keep gathering under this arch thinking it's a romantic spot for a wedding. Save that nonsense for a nice practical trip to city hall.</Text>
  <Text Key="6EB19145">Perennials for Millennials</Text>
  <Text Key="0CC79944">Once upon a time, this fountain was the source of great fluid life, infinite with it's stream. It is said that because of it's infinite stream it's owners grew greedy. Relentless in taking from the source without giving back.Relentless in taking, period.\n\nOne day, the fountain decided to rebel against it's owners and stopped it's stream, leaving it's owners to wither, but the fountain suddenly sprouted flowers. Flowers of every color, every kind adorned the fabled fountain delighting young and old, whoever was left...for eternity.</Text>
  <Text Key="B785630B">Where The Sunshine Goes</Text>
  <Text Key="8D478FB2">Not content with its beautiful Victorian craftsmanship alone, this urn insists on being called a vertical cornucopia in an effort to seem fancy. It's overflowing with a flowery bounty!</Text>
  <Text Key="E792924D">Vertical Cornucopia</Text>
  <Text Key="B22DE941">Lady Chloris was foiled by this folly; a prisoner of her own lush landscape. Renown for the beauty of her gardens, her husband Zephyrus encircled her with these follies as she slept. Intended as a loving tribute, instead these private premises led to her early demise. She repeatedly route failed in all attempts to escape and acquire food. Ultimately she starved to death, returning to the fertile soil she'd lovingly cultivated.</Text>
  <Text Key="3F619274">The Folly of Lady Chloris
</Text>
  <Text Key="40FEAABF">Oft pictured together with Maximus's fountain, this arch was erected in tribute to his glorious victory in battle against the onset of the armies of Hemoroydz.</Text>
  <Text Key="3574D9E6">Triumphal Arch of Gluteus Maximus</Text>
  <Text Key="365D9E6D">Author unknown, questionable origin.\n\nRumor has it that she was the muse of a poet, a poet that liked to sculpt. It is said (again, a rumor) that the poet never confessed his feelings for his muse. Pity that a story like this was untold, just a farewell remained like this sculpture before you.</Text>
  <Text Key="73C47B38">The Blossoms' Empress</Text>
  <Text Key="02A5AC5B">This little known piece was crafted during the early years of French sculptor Auguste Simodin. Rejection and failure led to his philosophical musings, and eventually his creation of this sculpture's sister piece, The Thinker. While The Sitter may not enjoy the same level of recognition and respect amongst the public, it's among his peers where the piece is well regarded. An anonymous artist was quoted as saying, "Philosophy? How pretentious! By the 1880s Simodin was just another hipster."</Text>
  <Text Key="318C8E3A">The Sitter</Text>
  <Text Key="3C82CC72">Drawing inspiration from the countryside of Shang Simla, the spitting flowers of Anneslea fragrans are represented in this classical fountain.</Text>
  <Text Key="1C246F0D">Spitting Flower Fountain
</Text>
  <Text Key="5539390E">This elegant lattice adorns the finest of walls. One may be overwhelemed with so many genuses of flowers to select from... might I recommend the last one, the simplest of all?</Text>
  <Text Key="65502431">Artisanal Lattice
</Text>
  <Text Key="17A8C25A">Felis Leo\n\nFabled companion of knights of old.\n\nFelis Leo the noble friend.\n\nFelis Leo now looking for new companionship in the form of a spring.\n\nWon't you have him on your Lot?\n\nWon't you be Felis Leo's new friend?\n\nHe won't bite.\n\n</Text>
  <Text Key="A326FE85">The Wellspring of Felis Leo</Text>
  <Text Key="E303829D">Come, come, and gather at the Marbleized Chesterfield. Unknown history in its details, fables untold.\n\nNobody will ever know how long, we just won't know how long it has been...just sitting there...\n\nCome on and sit and drift away thinking about the fables, about the lives that passed by the Marbleized Chesterfield.\n\nCome on and gather...\n\nCome, come, and gather at the Marbleized Chesterfield...</Text>
  <Text Key="3B255288">Marbleized Chesterfield</Text>
  <Text Key="99215EE2">A bench from far away place, from a foreign Park Place. Enjoy being outside in a park, or your own back yard, and wonder sitting in place in this one of a kind Park Place bench.</Text>
  <Text Key="07830E5D">Sette from the Park Place</Text>
  <Text Key="BE9EF34E">This wall-mounted stereo is intended for use at community venues. It laughs in the face of Classical music's 300 year history. Classic? Pah! Baroque has been topping the charts since the 1600s! Will this stereo stop anytime soon? Not bloody likely!</Text>
  <Text Key="87B85871">Venue Wall Speaker: Baroque</Text>
  <Text Key="3A67079B">Referenced in fairy tales of old, legend says that all your meals come true if this table is used for all meals to be had. The rustic, yet timeless, appearance will give your meal times an enchanting ambiance and a sense of wonder...wonder when the next meal will be that is!</Text>
  <Text Key="60753F7A">Dining Alfresco</Text>
  <Text Key="A8E41DEF">What you see through and through is what you get... Or is it? Find out what secrets lie on either side and be amazed.</Text>
  <Text Key="101F2636">Eye Of The Beholder</Text>
  <Text Key="853AAF97">Step closer, won't you? What's the harm in simply tossing in a coin? You can spare a single coin can't you? You don't believe in "magic" after all... it's just an old well. Did that face just move... did it twitch?! No, it must be shadows playing tricks on you; bear no mind to its appearance. Make a wish... it's all in good fun, right? You've already brushed aside the warnings of the locals in your hubris. They know better than to cast their lot with the Whispering Well.</Text>
  <Text Key="7E21DA6E">Whispering Wishing Well</Text>
  <Text Key="806CB5FA">Baroque</Text>
  <Text Key="DBF96941">Toss Coin</Text>
  <Text Key="7334CFAC">All Park Fountains</Text>
  <Text Key="90DEF528">All Park Fountains</Text>
  <Text Key="DCD346C5">Ask To Play In Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="4AC05DC0">{0.SimFirstName} blackmailed {1.SimFirstName} by threatening to tell everyone about how {M1.he}{F1.she} buys collectible llama dolls off the Sims Shopping Network.\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has earned {2.Money} and is now enemies with {1.SimFirstName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="15029D3E">Blackmail</Text>
  <Text Key="233D6EB6">Be Blackmailed by {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="B9433EE4">Splash From Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="0C61B3E7">Use Ultimate Pick Up Line</Text>
  <Text Key="A7F53EE9">Add Soap</Text>
  <Text Key="19AC39EE">Play In</Text>
  <Text Key="6883F98E">View</Text>
  <Text Key="8629C220">Remove Forced Outcomes</Text>
  <Text Key="283066E3">Turn Off Cooldown</Text>
  <Text Key="6B679941">Turn On Wish Cooldown</Text>
  <Text Key="06711F56">Force Death Outcomes</Text>
  <Text Key="909574A7">Force Negative Outcomes</Text>
  <Text Key="E6C6B21D">Force Neutral Outcomes</Text>
  <Text Key="8FDEC4C9">Force Overwhelmingly Negative Outcomes</Text>
  <Text Key="E6686949">Force Overwhelmingly Positive Outcomes</Text>
  <Text Key="C78FF9BF">Force Positive Outcomes</Text>
  <Text Key="4DD0C8D5">Play With</Text>
  <Text Key="F8B3980D">Splash From Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="B53B141A">Play Together In Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="5B19B9BF">Listen to Baroque</Text>
  <Text Key="CBD4EF13">Listen to Baroque</Text>
  <Text Key="4282A5D8">Present Offering of</Text>
  <Text Key="29FA448F">{0.SimFirstName} has already made a wish recently.</Text>
  <Text Key="736BFD4B">Wish for a Child</Text>
  <Text Key="7260C0B6">Wish for Better Grades</Text>
  <Text Key="0D9CC1D6">Wish for Happiness</Text>
  <Text Key="66C4C93B">Wish for Life</Text>
  <Text Key="F01B789A">Wish for a Promotion</Text>
  <Text Key="07BAE672">Wish for Romance</Text>
  <Text Key="7980EE10">Wish for Simoleons</Text>
  <Text Key="944F915A">Wish for Skills</Text>
  <Text Key="02A61A72">Wish for Youthful Vigor</Text>
  <Text Key="B29C3A2C">Wish for Better Grades</Text>
  <Text Key="EB220B2B">Wish for a Promotion in the {2.String} Career</Text>
  <Text Key="F7ADECC3">Having Wish Granted</Text>
  <Text Key="69CC8FD9">Fanciful Court</Text>
  <Text Key="510190CC">Terrace of Promises</Text>
  <Text Key="BE0C7D2E">Lush Wonderland</Text>
  <Text Key="4AE096AD">Lineage Parkland</Text>
  <Text Key="C6FFB53D">Bottomless Desires</Text>
  <Text Key="75206DCD">One of the richest and most diverse periods in music history.</Text>
  <Text Key="C7C84166">Baroque</Text>
  <Text Key="5C1B2F26">Make an Offering</Text>
  <Text Key="1B73BF78">Force Outcomes</Text>
  <Text Key="03E33593">Make a Wish</Text>
  <Text Key="71678A44">Add Soap to Park Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="E2D5F954">Click on a Park Fountain and Select Add Soap. Make sure there isn't already soap in the fountain, there'd be no point in adding it again so soon.</Text>
  <Text Key="662D9122">Play In Park Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="8FE2A1FA">Click on a Park Fountain and select the Play In Fountain interaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="97618EAC">Make a Wish</Text>
  <Text Key="9D1C40CC">Click on a Wishing Well and select Make A Wish.  Plan carefully! Each sim is limited in how often they can make a wish.</Text>
  <Text Key="F3F89D6A">{0.SimName}? It's the school's vice-principal calling. I'm aware you've been attempting to cheat to improve your grades. Did you think news of the existence of a magical wishing well wouldn't spread around town? Your school performance has been dropped accordingly. You'll need to complete some extra credit work if you "wish" to regain your former status.\n\n...get it? "Wish"? Hah hah hah...</Text>
  <Text Key="40295CBA">Hi {0.SimFirstName}, it's your teacher calling. There's been a miraculous - almost unbelievable - improvement in your recent test scores. As noted in the school's handbook though, 50% of your final grade is based upon completion of homework. I can't increase your grade any further until I've seen more assignments turned in.</Text>
  <Text Key="46793626">Hello {0.SimFirstName}, it's the school's vice-principal calling. Just moments ago I noticed your grades suddenly jump upwards in the school's database, and I'm forced to conclude that you hacked into our system. Perhaps you have a future as a Tech Guru, but such behavior is not to be rewarded as long as you remain in my institution of education. I've been forced to not only return your grade to it's previous level, but I've dropped you one letter grade further as a punitive action. Think of positive ways to channel your knowledge in the future instead of taking embarrassing shortcuts to get ahead.</Text>
  <Text Key="F2AE873A">{0.SimFirstName}, it's your school principal calling. I took a moment out of my busy day to personally call and congratulate you. You've been named "Student of the Day" as your grades are rocketing upwards at a rate leaps and bounds beyond your peers. Keep up the fantastic work!</Text>
  <Text Key="9B6C258E">Hello {0.SimFirstName}, it's your homeroom teacher calling. Your school performance has skyrocketed recently, and I wanted to offer some further words of encouragement. I've singled you out as the most improved student in class; you're right on the cusp of improving your report card. If you meet your other grade requirements, I'll be able to bump you up a full letter grade the next time you're in class. I believe in you!</Text>
  <Text Key="73C25656">Am I speaking with {0.SimFirstName}? {0.SimName}? It's your boss; you know - the one from that job you've been loafing around at. Your name came up in a meeting recently as someone who was hinting at wanting a promotion. Let me unequivocally state that you won't be advancing anytime soon. The gall of you even thinking you're due a promotion... I think I'll knock you down a peg instead.</Text>
  <Text Key="C01C6709">Hello {0.SimFirstName}, this is work calling. We were considering you for a promotion, but upon closer review we've noticed a downward trend in your job performance. You've been placed on probationary status during which we'll be evaluating you closely. We strongly recommend having an exemplary shift the next time you show up or you may be in line for a demotion.</Text>
  <Text Key="9B7A0CCF">Hello {0.SimFirstName}, this is your workplace calling with some wonderful news! Everyone here has been impressed with your work ethic, and we're pleased to give you this bonus. We really wanted to promote you, but due to budgetary restrictions and ongoing headcount limitations that simply wasn't possible. Hang in there, I'm sure we'll take care of you in the next review period!</Text>
  <Text Key="0FFBC951">Hello {0.SimFirstName}, this is the HR department at your workplace calling. We're legally compelled to inform you of punitive actions taken at the conclusion of an internal review. We were made aware of performance issues via complaints levied anonymously by a co-worker. Our investigation left no doubt of the accusations, the records of which have been sealed and are not subject to personal review. Your change in employment status is effective immediately and is not valid for appeal.</Text>
  <Text Key="38B5A7B9">{0.SimFirstName}, this is your workplace calling; we have urgent news to share! Your boss won the lottery and immediately walked out mid-shift. We need to rapidly fill the vacated position, and we think you're the right {M0.man}{F0.woman} for the job. Congratulations on the promotion!</Text>
  <Text Key="29DAC761">{0.SimFirstName}, this is your workplace calling. Your job performance has been outstanding recently; the company's leadership has their eye on you! Provided you've met your other promotion requirements, your next shift is sure to end with a promotion!</Text>
  <Text Key="B973E641">What’s this grin spreading across {0.SimFirstName}’s face? The Whispering Wishing Well has played a devious trick, forcing {0.SimFirstName} to burst into peals of happy laughter.</Text>
  <Text Key="7CF4E670">{0.SimFirstName} convinces {M0.himself}{F0.herself} that {M0.he’s}{F0.she’s} happy through clenched teeth. It seems the Whispering Wishing Well may have ignored {0.SimFirstName}’s plea.</Text>
  <Text Key="3378DF71">Love knows no bounds, and the reaper himself could not keep {0.SimFirstName} from uniting with {M0.his}{F0.her} spectral soulmate.</Text>
  <Text Key="3649A9CA">From the bubbling pitch emerges a Sim so disagreeable, so foul, so despicable, and yet… so… irresistible? {0.SimFirstName} finds {M0.himself}{F0.herself} drawn inexplicably closer to {M0.his}{F0.her} new enemy with benefits.</Text>
  <Text Key="1BD6A36E">Can it be? Clouds of mist and hearts billowed from the Whispering Wishing Well’s mouth, and {0.SimFirstName}’s soulmate formed before {M0.his}{F0.her} very eyes.</Text>
  <Text Key="CA2CF167">{0.SimFirstName} panics; the Simoleons in {M0.his}{F0.her} pocket are the perfect tinder for the hexed flames roaring out from the depths of the well. Clearly the well had no desire to fulfill {0.SimFirstName}’s lust for wealth, and instead chose to make {M0.him}{F0.her} pay.</Text>
  <Text Key="37FBB57B">{0.SimFirstName} thought a flick of a coin would be enough to gain a skill? No, {M0.he'll}{F0.she'll} have to work for it... but {M0.his}{F0.her} wish will provide a boost to any skill gains for a period of time.</Text>
  <Text Key="51B7E7A8">Tendrils of energy flow from the wishing well and surge through {0.SimFirstName}’s body, energizing {M0.him}{F0.her} with an extra spring in {M0.his}{F0.her} step for the day!</Text>
  <Text Key="C4ED6FC2">{0.SimFirstName} suddenly aged up... Perhaps it was the well's cunning plan to force {0.SimFirstName} to continue to use the wishing well if {M0.he}{F0.she} wants to get through {M0.his}{F0.her} bucket list before {M0.he}{F0.she} kicks it. Does {0.SimFirstName} dare try again?</Text>
  <Text Key="81666DF6">The Whispering Wishing Well has heard {0.SimFirstName}’s plea. As an enchanting white light washes over {M0.his}{F0.her} body, {M0.he}{F0.she} can hear the hands of time winding backwards in the recesses of {M0.his}{F0.her} mind. It would seem that {M0.he’s}{F0.she’s} been returned to the beginning of {M0.his}{F0.her} current age stage!</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>