<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="E2599AF9">(From pretending to be a monster)</Text>
  <Text Key="4921D6D4">{0.SimFirstName} is doing something unprofessional! Continue behaving poorly on the job will result in {0.SimFirstName} being fired from the gig.</Text>
  <Text Key="F3ED00EB">One of {0.SimFirstName}’s previous clients referred someone new to {M0.him}{F0.her}! That bodes well for {M0.his}{F0.her} professional reputation!</Text>
  <Text Key="A7AC079C">{0.SimFirstName} has been offered a gig from a previous client. This could be {M0.his}{F0.her} chance to make it up to an otherwise unhappy customer.</Text>
  <Text Key="8322B54B">{0.SimFirstName} has been offered a gig from a previous client. Returning customers bode well for {M0.his}{F0.her} professional reputation!</Text>
  <Text Key="AEC7515E">(From Renovating Current Location)</Text>
  <Text Key="C211B0B8">No such thing as bad publicity, right? {0.SimFirstName}'s work is going to be on &lt;i&gt;Failures ‘N’ Flops&lt;/i&gt;! Tune in and watch on the Dream Home Decorator Network, Friday 8:00-10:00 PM. </Text>
  <Text Key="A005EC44">Who cares if {M0.he}{F0.she} doesn't remember signing a release form, {0.SimFirstName}'s work is going to be on an episode of Ace of Space!\nTune in and watch on the Dream Home Decorator Network, Friday 8:00-10:00 PM.</Text>
  <Text Key="2AFC6A0C">(From Completing a Commercial Interior Decorator Gig)</Text>
  <Text Key="7BD4A4A8">(From Completing a Residential Interior Decorator Gig)</Text>
  <Text Key="9DE814D8">Hello! I'm here on behalf of {0.String}. Just ask me what you want to know. </Text>
  <Text Key="44FF745A">Uh, did you really just quit in the middle of a job? Rude!</Text>
  <Text Key="D78DE682">I'll head out now so you can get started. See you later!</Text>
  <Text Key="D29C47FA">A new Memory Card has been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory. Use it to manage the photos that were taken during an Interior Decorator Gig.</Text>
  <Text Key="55CB11D5">Taking Before and After Photos to document your work as an Interior Decorator is important. Learn how to take control and get that perfect shot in the Taking Photos Lesson under Dream Home Decorator.</Text>
  <Text Key="778E781E">I'm ready to wrap this up!</Text>
  <Text Key="F09E6C05">This was a lot to take in! I'm ready to talk about the changes.</Text>
  <Text Key="108D2E75">I think I've seen enough. Let's go over my thoughts!</Text>
  <Text Key="006EB576">I'm ready to talk about the renovation. </Text>
  <Text Key="130BE047">A picture is worth a thousand words. Not all of these words were good, though. {0.SimFirstName}'s professional reputation took a small hit, but {M0.he}{F0.she} still gained {1.Number} Followers. {0.SimFirstName} now has {2.Number} total Followers. </Text>
  <Text Key="345EA75F">Ouch, the photo wasn't well received. That hurt {0.SimFirstName}'s professional reputation a little, but at least {M0.he}{F0.she} still gained {1.Number} Followers. {0.SimFirstName} now has {2.Number} Followers in total. </Text>
  <Text Key="022B9E7C">Beautiful! This photo has inspired others. {0.SimFirstName}'s professional reputation increased a little, and {M0.he}{F0.she} gained {1.Number} Followers. {0.SimFirstName} now has {2.Number} total Followers. </Text>
  <Text Key="7C4E87DC">Woah, that one might go viral! {0.SimFirstName}'s professional reputation increased a little, and {M0.he}{F0.she} gained {1.Number} Followers. {0.SimFirstName} now has {2.Number} total Followers. </Text>
  <Text Key="0A8316A2">Go Gnome or go home. Or rather, more Gnomes in more homes. As the official Ambassador of The Association of Gnomes are The Greatest, we'd like to encourage you to start placing more Gnomes in the lawns, gardens, nurseries, kitchens, bathrooms, and basements of your Clients' homes. Here, we'll get you started with this. Don't let us down.\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="6EEFAAE4">We're going to be honest with you, your clients could find better refrigerators than the Crisponix line. That said, we could definitely use some good press. If we give you one for free would you consider using a Crisponix refrigerator in one of your next kitchen remodels?\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="6808763A">InvisiView. Why subject your clients to normal TVs when you could be revamping their space with a TV that actually improves their eyesight? Please accept this token of our gratitude with the understanding that you will most certainly be using it in one of your next interior decoration gigs.\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="50A20532">{0.SimFirstName}, this is your lucky day. Hi, I'm Kip from Reclamation Homeware and we'd love to encourage you to start using our classic furnishings as one of your go-to brands when you're working with Clients. As a token of our future gratitude for your support, we'd like to offer you a small gift.\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="2F0BDEA0">Hello, Friend. I am stunned by the beauty your decorated spaces emit. I am Edgar, an avid collector of relics that once belonged to the most breathtaking Princess Cordelia. However, as I grow older and weaker by the day, I fear that if her furnishings aren't passed down her memory may be forgotten... forever. Could you please, please keep my precious Cordelia alive by adorning the homes of future clients with these priceless furnishings? It's growing so dark. So cold. Please accept this heirloom as my last... dying... &lt;i&gt;ggggwwwwwggggggggghhhhhhhhn&lt;/i&gt;\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="B4FD156A">Your decoration skills have earned you quite the reputation. Some might say that you're the whole package. You've got it all; vision, style, creativity. But you're missing one thing: Countryside Caress furnishings will elevate your interiors to a whole new level. Are you ready to start... today?\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="526093AA">Hello, Beautiful. You don't know me, but I've been admiring your Interior Decoration work from afar for quite some time. I think your flawless, brilliant hands would be the perfect vessel to help inspire a revived appreciation of the arts. Please accept a prized piece from my own private collection to use in any of your upcoming decoration gigs.\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="E852E001">Hi, {0.SimFirstName}! I'm Sally, a representative from Kindermade Enterprises. We think your aesthetic is the perfect pairing for the Kindermade brand. We'd love you to consider using some of our playful furnishings in your future decoration jobs. Please accept this gift as a thank you for considering us in future collaborations.\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="C33098C5">Be classy, be spontaneous, be flexible. Be all the &lt;i&gt;Be's&lt;/i&gt; with new &lt;i&gt;Be Modular&lt;/i&gt; shelving. Would you make sure to spread the joy of our new flexible &lt;i&gt;Be Modular&lt;/i&gt; shelving line to all of your clients by featuring our timeless functional pieces in your Decoration Gigs? Here's a taste to get you started.\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="035EF624">MegaMission Furniture Warehouse is on a mission: to convince YOU to feature our sturdy, classic handcrafted furniture in your next decoration job. We'd like to start you off with a free sample from our workshop. Enjoy. And remember: never stop decorating with Mega.\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="9BCB9E59">Here at PostRustic, we believe every kitchen and every bathroom needs a piece of PostRustic flair. We've understood this logic for a long time now, and we've been patiently waiting for the rest of the world to come to that conclusion as well. Would you be able to help PostRustic speed up that realization and start featuring our fine kitchen and bathroom décor items in your Interior Decoration jobs? Allow us to gift you a piece for free to get you started.\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="1DF45136">A happy kitchen is a Schmapple kitchen. Schmapple Headquarters would like to see our line of sexy, revolutionary kitchen appliances in the homes of your clients. They deserve no less than the Schmapple dream. Please consider our offer and accept this token of our appreciation. Schmapple Schmapple.\n\n{2.String} can be found in the Household Inventory.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="441BE6E7">Socialize with Clients</Text>
  <Text Key="412FEE48">Increases Work Performance. Increases Social Need.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC6B473B">Who'd want to work with them anyways! </Text>
  <Text Key="D4C4A755">It takes a keen eye to design the interior for a place of business.</Text>
  <Text Key="5622A470">Business Savvy Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="08CEA6DF">It's very awkward to be back here. {0.SimFirstName} gets the sense that folks are still feeling sour about that job. </Text>
  <Text Key="84756386">Hostile Atmosphere</Text>
  <Text Key="BDA6FA17">It feels good to visit the site of a successful job! {0.SimFirstName} feels like others recognize {M0.his}{F0.her} good work.</Text>
  <Text Key="D567B1EE">Feeling Welcomed</Text>
  <Text Key="8A1EF7CF">Any publicity is good publicity... right? </Text>
  <Text Key="F6A58F96">Failures 'N' Flops</Text>
  <Text Key="55C3FAC7">Feels good to be recognized for a job well done!</Text>
  <Text Key="B05A5F7E">Ace of Space</Text>
  <Text Key="707BD844">Take a gig, complete a gig, take another gig... getting giggy with it!</Text>
  <Text Key="219FF00B">Giggity Gig </Text>
  <Text Key="A2D4A9E3">Reading the Room</Text>
  <Text Key="D5EF5432">Unable to get a good read on the Clients.</Text>
  <Text Key="802356AD">Getting the feeling the job might not be to the Client's satisfaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="9FA669CA">Happy Clients hopefully means a job well done!</Text>
  <Text Key="EDCBB325">The Clients clearly love the new space!</Text>
  <Text Key="2EA0CD89">The Client is waiting for the Design to be Revealed!</Text>
  <Text Key="07CE1BAA">Fee Fi Fo Fum! I will get you, little children!</Text>
  <Text Key="FF969935">I'm a Monster </Text>
  <Text Key="50B18243">Eek! A Monster!</Text>
  <Text Key="81650992">Scared by Monster</Text>
  <Text Key="AE9DFF4F">A world of pure imagination!</Text>
  <Text Key="F13D0E16">Living in My Own World</Text>
  <Text Key="6F0F9C9B">(From Scratched Tent)</Text>
  <Text Key="85DF02C9">This tent is all scratched up. That's very sad.</Text>
  <Text Key="CCEA242C">Shabby Tent</Text>
  <Text Key="C780B113">I see what they were trying to do. I know that I can do that!</Text>
  <Text Key="253167C2">A Home Decorating Show!</Text>
  <Text Key="0784CEE6">That was an interesting home makeover. I'll bet I can do even better!</Text>
  <Text Key="7CD9E34B">I never considered that room arrangement. I have so many new ideas I want to try now!</Text>
  <Text Key="F0E4D7CE">What a beautiful room. I want to try it!</Text>
  <Text Key="2E9A04AF">Remembering an interior decorating job done so well back at home. </Text>
  <Text Key="ABB3EAF6">Home Improvement</Text>
  <Text Key="F291864B">Just the sight of someone can fill a Sim with rage! {0.SimFirstName}'s fury surges back to the surface when {M0.he}{F0.she} is reminded of the terrible decoration job that was done wrong.</Text>
  <Text Key="90F181CA">Tear it Down!</Text>
  <Text Key="78A5F063">It's &lt;b&gt;HIDEOUS!&lt;/b&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="ABADAF73">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Basic Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="68E52DB4">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Boho Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="DBDC863B">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Contemporary Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="E8F43C16">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Cosmolux Décor!
</Text>
  <Text Key="E61C63D6">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates French Country Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="4021F951">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Garden Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="A87C1692">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Gothic Farmhouse Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="339966FD">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Island Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="90E0B406">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Mission Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="99C404D7">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Modern Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="6F57171B">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Patio Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="995BA684">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Queen Anne Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="2701202C">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Mid Century Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="5197AA99">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Suburban Contemporary Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="353C6854">Revolting! Get it away! {0.SimFirstName} hates Storybook Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="49D9D867">Impeccable Taste!</Text>
  <Text Key="6957410F">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Basic Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="F91BE3C0">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Boho Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="3161D8F7">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Contemporary Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="18446FFA">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Cosmolux Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="11C11BA2">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves French Country Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="CA2B375D">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Garden Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="CD3A85A6">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Gothic Farmhouse Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="9F20EEF1">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Island Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="DAD12E72">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Mission Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="543C8B0B">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Modern Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="9DC7AAEF">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Patio Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="84B77120">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Queen Anne Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="D1B53630">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Mid Century Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="FBAC9C9D">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Suburban Contemporary Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="C1C0B9B8">Beautiful! A refined choice! {0.SimFirstName} loves Storybook Décor!</Text>
  <Text Key="5D87F056">Client Budget:</Text>
  <Text Key="DE9D972F">Clients will allot a certain budget to use for the renovations. If you go over budget, the amount will turn red. Going over budget will negatively affect your performance and reputation.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0C7E4C7">Over Budget:</Text>
  <Text Key="38D4046F">Gig Pay:</Text>
  <Text Key="138FCB48">Client Budget</Text>
  <Text Key="7BCEA51D">Over Budget</Text>
  <Text Key="1BBD48C3">C.I.A. (Classic Interior Artisans)</Text>
  <Text Key="DBE48814">{0.SimFirstName} earned {4.Money} but {0.SimFirstName} clients don't appear satisfied with the new look {5.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="E02AC0B4">{0.SimFirstName} brought home {4.Money} today. {M0.He}{F0.She} did some superb Decorating too! {5.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="E715EBF4">{0.SimFirstName} earned {4.Money} but it appears the clients were not very happy with {0.SimFirstName}'s decorating work. {5.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="86EE6841">{0.SimFirstName} brought home {4.Money} today. {M0.He}{F0.She} did some great Decorating, too! {5.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="9A00B544">What a day of Decorating! {0.SimFirstName} is back home and {M0.he}{F0.she} has earned {4.Money}!</Text>
  <Text Key="40113341">{0.SimFirstName} has a Decorator Gig in one hour. Get to the Client's Lot on time to chat with them about what they are looking for before starting renovations!</Text>
  <Text Key="1A9F4F0E">It's time for {0.SimFirstName} to head to the Client's lot. Getting there on time can be a good opportunity to get to know the Client's Likes and Dislikes. Ready to head over?</Text>
  <Text Key="EE474668">Time to Design!</Text>
  <Text Key="C84D1E72">Send Alone</Text>
  <Text Key="0E941F4A">Lets Go To Work!</Text>
  <Text Key="C4C6FE69">{0.SimFirstName} is now {1.String|enAn} at {3.String}. {M0.He}{F0.She} can use the Career Panel to search for clients looking for spaces to be redecorated!</Text>
  <Text Key="5F4F95EB">{0.SimFirstName} has been promoted to {1.String}!\n\n{M0.He}{F0.She} has also received the following bonus:\n{8.String}\n\n{M0.He}{F0.She} may also find more challenging and constraining Interior Decorator gigs from Clients.\n\n</Text>
  <Text Key="253128D8">Residential</Text>
  <Text Key="D82C074B">house</Text>
  <Text Key="DC3CD9BB">Pay: {0.Money}</Text>
  <Text Key="C3B9803C">Client Budget: {0.Money}</Text>
  <Text Key="391484B4">Money Earned: {1.Money}</Text>
  <Text Key="A6FDAE86">{0.SimFirstName} has completed the gig and has received the following results!</Text>
  <Text Key="24C11BE0">Results!</Text>
  <Text Key="57D39217">Stay On Lot</Text>
  <Text Key="18113852">Go Home</Text>
  <Text Key="14625AFE">{0.SimFirstName} put some effort into decorating the space, but the Client didn't seem too impressed. Was it lack of vision? Artistry? Spacial awareness? Maybe another Gig will help make things right.</Text>
  <Text Key="A57CF84F">Well… that went nicely! The Clients seem to really like the new layout! The keen eye for detail seemed to really pay off, both in Simoleons and Reputation.</Text>
  <Text Key="B3CC8FFB">The Clients are shocked! They are incredibly saddened... even at a loss for words upon receiving your Resignation.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B0405D7">Nice work! The clients seem to enjoy the newly renovated space!</Text>
  <Text Key="92001EA6">There's no accounting for taste. But then, maybe it's just the Client's taste and yours don't match...</Text>
  <Text Key="1587D63C">Professional Reputation Dropped</Text>
  <Text Key="E83E2DB4">Professional Reputation Improved Significantly </Text>
  <Text Key="7C148A78">Professional Reputation Improved</Text>
  <Text Key="7358AE0F">Professional Reputation Dropped Significantly</Text>
  <Text Key="214CD9C5">&lt;font color="#0949AB"&gt;Client Name:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font color="#10A317"&gt; {0.String}&lt;/font&gt;\n&lt;font color="#0949AB"&gt;Lot Type:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font color="#10A317"&gt; {1.String}&lt;/font&gt;\n&lt;font color="#0949AB"&gt;Starts:&lt;/font&gt; {2.DayOfWeekShort} {2.TimeShort} &lt;font color="#0949AB"&gt;Ends:&lt;/font&gt; {3.DayOfWeekShort} {3.TimeShort}</Text>
  <Text Key="0382D767">Really interested in adding a new level to our house here, but a little undecided on what it should be exactly... can you help us out? We will let you decide the whole layout for the new level.</Text>
  <Text Key="0E486D04">Level Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="37BB6B65">Celebrity Home Level Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="683D027D">Can you please come and invigorate some style to my boring abode? The Simoleons are not a problem, just bring some life into this place! Some pizazz! Change makes me feel ALIVE!</Text>
  <Text Key="3924FB24">Okay, emergency renovation here! I just found out I might get featured on Ace of Space on the Dream Home Decorator Network! Can you renovate a room in my place? It would pump up my rep for sure!</Text>
  <Text Key="C3B08551">Up and Comer Client Room Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="7EE4A854">So, we've come into a little bit of money, and we were thinking we could really create more space in the house. Can you add a level? We'll pay really well! And you can make anything your heart desires! We just want the space!</Text>
  <Text Key="B5EDBF61">Add a Level to this Home</Text>
  <Text Key="81BCECAD">So look. I need some "me" time. A place I can just unwind, have some juice, and maybe watch TV or play some games. Maybe display some cool stuff... my "trophies" if you will. But basically, I don't want to be distracted by the outside world! Can you make me my own den cave, where only numero uno can enter - me!</Text>
  <Text Key="CD8D51C6">A Level for Him Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="C90196E4">It's so hard to focus these days. What, with everything that's going on. I need a space where I can sit back, and work on my crafts, or read, or sip a glass of juice. Is that too much to ask? Make me my little corner of my domain, and I'll forever be grateful! </Text>
  <Text Key="C3279E11">A Level for Her Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="75366AF7">Basement Gym Level Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="6215020C">So, lately we've been working from home. A lot. I mean, like, we're always here, and I gotta tell you, I'm putting on some of the ol' "L-B's", you know what I'm saying? I need to shed some love handles! I'd go to the gym but... it's sooo faaaar! Turns out, there's this whole space utilized under our home that could be a used for a gym! So, how about helping me get to the gun show?</Text>
  <Text Key="BA36C3D4">Attic Juice Bar Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="7AF404F0">Juicin' in the mornin'! Juicin' in the evenin'! Juicin' all day long! Can you make us a juice bar in our attic? You'd have to add the attic! After it's done, we can juice it up!</Text>
  <Text Key="C84FA647">Photography Studio Level Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="826224E2">Lately I've really gotten into nature and art and seeing the beauty of the world. It's just so grand and awe-inspriring, right? So what I really need is a Photography Studio in my place, and I'd love to get a lot of light into it. The perfect location would be to add a top floor to my home! You can make that happen, right? Just add a floor, no biggie? </Text>
  <Text Key="59B217FA">So, this "work from home" thing is becoming more normal every day. In order to get in the right mind-space, I need to feel like I'm stepping into a place of work. So, I'm thinking we can add a top floor, make it an office. But also, we'll need an extra bathroom up there. Because for some reason, doing work makes me poop. </Text>
  <Text Key="31E3E96C">Top Floor Office &amp; Bathroom Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="3EED1EF9">Family Room</Text>
  <Text Key="D718684C">Top Floor Family Room Level Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="3FC4D3DC">We're fairly satisfied with the current spacing of our home, but we really feel like we could add a family room. So where could we build? We build up! Can you make us a top floor family room? That would just be so swell!</Text>
  <Text Key="162A33F8">We could really use a new look to our place! But we can't seem to agree on a vision... can you help us decide what we want?</Text>
  <Text Key="33A2403D">Level Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="B968F263">Commercial</Text>
  <Text Key="E93CB102">venue</Text>
  <Text Key="B33EFCEA">Bar Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="F99F663E">We need to juice up our bar! Let's be frank - the clientele has been less than desirable lately. I was hoping to draw in some young hipsters, not hip youngsters! Anything you can do to make our bar juicy for these folks would be tremendously helpful!</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE13E04">Café Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="509113C6">Why does this place just feel so... counterintuitive? I feel like you walk in the door, and walk right into a wall! Okay maybe that's not exactly it, but you know what I mean. The flow is just... off. Can you renovate this level and make it more functional?</Text>
  <Text Key="DB88F1B5">Club Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="6D9F11A6">We're in desperate need of a Level Renovation! We haven't seen any apple flavored jeans or fur boots in furever! Please bring the funk back to our club!</Text>
  <Text Key="5B876604">Gym Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="C0EDE8B3">Help us spice up our gym! We've got some new-age clientele, who are into organic juices and healthy life-styles. Folks don't just want to get swole anymore, they want to live longer! Help us help them by giving them a space that says "long live you!"</Text>
  <Text Key="1A6E367C">Library Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="BE1B6B7A">Can you update our Library by redecorating a level? We want folks to know that we're not those dusty old libraries with old books and old people. We can be hip! We can be cool! Show them how with your vision to re-envision our Library!</Text>
  <Text Key="0DD6EA33">Lounge Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="6DEFEB53">It's time to revitalize our lounge and we need professional assistance. It doesn't feel very "loungy" right now, does it? Maybe a change in color, perhaps? Or even the floor, or walls? How about the furniture? Just change SOMETHING, I'm already tired of looking at this place!</Text>
  <Text Key="AB93BCD3">Vet Clinic Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="8E84CFBB">My Vet Clinic hasn't been drawing in the cool cats; just those doggone strays! Can you help me spruce up my clinic so the place doesn't get neutered? 12 out of 10 needs more grooming!</Text>
  <Text Key="9DEEAA9D">I've got the Simoleons, if you've got the vision! I'll pay generously for a level renovation! Because really... I'm just bored with the current layout.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0A319B9">So, our kitchen is just...grossly outdated. We're always ordering out because I can't stand being in that kitchen! We need an update, pronto. I'm not saying my cooking will necessarily taste any better. I'm not even saying I'll actually cook in the kitchen. But at least I'd be happy knowing that it's possible!</Text>
  <Text Key="FAA486DA">Kitchen Level Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="C7B95B2A">Living Room</Text>
  <Text Key="6D1B4932">We can use a new Living Room. Feel free to take as much of the level to renovate as you need! I just need some change in my life! </Text>
  <Text Key="75DCC1BB">Living Room Level Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="D2C78110">Living Room &amp; Kitchen Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="8556088D">This place is pretty old and built with old design aesthetics. We think our living room and kitchen could probably be opened up, and allow more natural light into the area. That support beam? Don't worry about it. This house is supported by the trust I have in you!</Text>
  <Text Key="B9F00A89">GOLDEN BOOKMARK WINNER</Text>
  <Text Key="DEB7CBDF">Another Golden Bookmark has been found in the stacks of a local library! As always, this round’s lucky bookworm is eager to get started on their all-expenses-paid home renovation.\n\nThe Golden Bookmark is a global program to encourage reading. In other words, this gig is great exposure... and it still pays!</Text>
  <Text Key="645B7896">Simucation Council Commission</Text>
  <Text Key="F9A3556D">We of the Simucation Council wish to commission a private installation of artistic excellence for one of our lucky art-lovers. Fill their abode with art!\n\nSupport art and the Simucation Council will support you with exposure and Simoleons.</Text>
  <Text Key="9562E25C">We feel like our place could use a new room... we can afford the space, if you can provide the vision! Just ask us what we're looking for, okay?</Text>
  <Text Key="6219492B">room</Text>
  <Text Key="27193A2D">Arcade Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="52927045">We're trying to get some younger, techy folks into this place of business. We could really use your help to update our venue with some modern PC's and other gaming hardware. These nerds have deep pockets, so let's get them in here!</Text>
  <Text Key="6CE3F728">Bathroom Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="3040F808">With a heavier flow (of foot track) lately we could really use another bathroom! But I really do like the existing space, so try as much as possible to just add to our home, rather than modifying too many walls and floors, cool?</Text>
  <Text Key="6EDE2F49">I'm thinking with all the space in my place, I could use an extra room to hang out or put stuff in. I'll be honest, I don't really have a goal for this room. But use your creative freedom to make this space interesting. I've got the money to spend, because that's just how I roll!  So make me something cool!</Text>
  <Text Key="F7CA2A4A">Pick a Room Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="CEE34FAD">You know how your in-laws come, and you can't really stand them, and wish they wouldn't step one foot in the house? Maybe we can have it both ways? Please build us an In Law unit. That way, they can stay in their space, without soiling the sanctity of our home!</Text>
  <Text Key="B85D0AC6">In Law Unit Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="D3DCE3AB">nursery</Text>
  <Text Key="45D5A081">We would LOVE a nursery in our home! Please add a room for us. We aren't necessarily expecting at the moment, but we just like want to be ready for anything!</Text>
  <Text Key="CCE9C012">Nursery Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="5EA3412D">Gym</Text>
  <Text Key="0E3C10E8">Home Gym Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="55636465">Pumpin' iron.\nGettin' swole.\nThe gun show.\nA Gym.\nIn my home.\nMake it happen!</Text>
  <Text Key="0C9C9D86">Gardening Room</Text>
  <Text Key="6F675E77">Gardening Room Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="1897C691">I am nature's arm. Her Spirit. Heck, I AM mother nature! Come join me, my garden needs tending. But please, we can only do it in my own, personal gardening room. At the end of the day, nature always wins! </Text>
  <Text Key="A5AD2927">Music Studio</Text>
  <Text Key="BBB39E4E">Guitar Music Studio Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="BF2B5817">My Axe deserves her own room, ya dig? She needs to be front and center, and maybe on the side, I can put her to practice. But I won't be worthy until you make me a Music Studio where I can bring my heavenly guitar skills to life!</Text>
  <Text Key="6E47A946">Hobby Room</Text>
  <Text Key="7E30AA37">Hobby Room Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="5CAA404B">Look, I got an A in woodshop, and never looked back. So now that I'm a home-owner, I could really use a space to dedicate my craft in handiness. I could really use a hobby room where I can put all my different handy skills to the test!</Text>
  <Text Key="4E6AD69F">Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="D99B9A96">Home Bar Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="BFD900B7">Some times, at the end of a hard day, you just want to get your drink on, know what I mean? Or perhaps, a little something to kick start the morning. Maybe a nightcap? Everything goes with brunch, right? Whatever the case may be, a new home bar would really help. Can you make it happen?</Text>
  <Text Key="A7D92B81">Art Studio</Text>
  <Text Key="14C7D9EC">Art Studio Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="116391B2">Some would say, I'm kind of an artiste! But who can create from the mind's eye in these conditions? I need a new Art Studio. Just make a new room where I can paint to my heart's desire, with inspiration! </Text>
  <Text Key="9404520D">Photo Studio</Text>
  <Text Key="60DABCD7">Photography Studio Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="1DE2DDF1">Taking the perfect picture is definitely a craft, but it also needs the right conditions. Can you build me a Photo Studio? Something good for lighting and staging things.</Text>
  <Text Key="AC6E5FE4">The art of playing the piano takes finesse. And the only way to fine-tune one's finesse is to practice with the proper acoustics and inspiration. Will you kindly make me a Piano Room? The symphony must start somewhere!</Text>
  <Text Key="8511A911">Piano Music Studio Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="DA715443">Tech Room</Text>
  <Text Key="61C79591">Tech Room Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="E02BA71C">My buddies and I need to FOCUS our MAD HAXORS Skills till the early AM. But we can't wake my folks, yo! We NEED our own SPACE, and it NEEDS to be LIT. Something to get our PROGRAMMING skillz LIT. And keep the lights LOW, ya hear?</Text>
  <Text Key="B3D5FB20">Game Room</Text>
  <Text Key="CCEF1B66">Game Room Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="4AC2ADF9">We're all about the gaming life! I can play with friends and I can play with myself! But gaming requires specificity - and I can only get that in a dedicated gaming room! Once I get that, let the games begin!</Text>
  <Text Key="59FF9998">closet</Text>
  <Text Key="8A7041E0">Need to add a Walk In Closet to my beautiful bedroom so I have room for all my new shoes and clothes to show off to guests! You used to hide things in your closet, but think of this one as a fancy display case for all the things I wear!</Text>
  <Text Key="13A3E7D5">Walk In Closet Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="AED748D7">We suddenly came into a few Simoleons and thought, what the hey - let's change things up! Can you renovate a room for us? Just a change of pace? Give us a holler and we can tell you some things we like or don't like.</Text>
  <Text Key="FAC0E092">bathroom</Text>
  <Text Key="938E3EDA">Love to get our Bath Room renovated to be more spacious. Right now, it feels like I can take a poop and wash my hands without even standing up. Okay that doesn't sound like a bad thing, but it is! I feel like I can't breathe, and not just because of the poop! Help open up this bathroom for me!</Text>
  <Text Key="53E03693">Bathroom Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="027A43AA">bedroom</Text>
  <Text Key="5A07E2B2">This bedroom... it's starting to have that smell. You know the smell. We just don't talk about the smell. It could really use a fresh coat of paint. Can you help us get rid of this smell with a new scent?</Text>
  <Text Key="5CC4563B">Bedroom Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="73381085">Remember me? I heard you do good work, so I’ll let you decide which room needs the most help!</Text>
  <Text Key="21EB768E">Returning Client: Room Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="14BC6A05">Just pick a room and go for it. This is your chance to make up for last time. Don't make me regret it!</Text>
  <Text Key="0CD315F1">The room to renovate is up to the expert. That's you! We're looking forward to working with you again. </Text>
  <Text Key="CE5B2853">Referral: Room Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="23291244">Looking for a Living Room. I feel like I could spread out, you know? Sit comfortably, watch some TV. Feel free to make use of the space, Simoleons is no object!</Text>
  <Text Key="E3265071">Fabulous Living Room Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="7AF66DAA">Kid's Room</Text>
  <Text Key="F641E0B2">Kids these days... they're all over the place, right? Just, from one thing to the next...maybe ten things in the span of twenty minutes! What the kids need is their OWN space; at least keep them confined. I'm not saying make us a prison, but... if you can put a lock on it, I'm not complaining! A kids room, please!</Text>
  <Text Key="6BB5F03B">Kid's Room Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="61B1F64E">kitchen</Text>
  <Text Key="ED1BB0DE">This kitchen is SO late eighties. Or is it early ninties? I can't tell, it just feels old to me. Let's get cookin' and spice things up with a kitchen renovation! Can you update it? </Text>
  <Text Key="39C9240F">Kitchen Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="A6259D74">office</Text>
  <Text Key="35A6CED4">My office (if you can call it that) just isn't working out for me. I can't focus! Help redesign my place so it has an actual, functioning office.</Text>
  <Text Key="29566AE1">Office Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="9E43BCC5">We all know how it feels to wake up after a long night out... It’s not always great, which is why neighborhood bars started the semi-regular renovation raffle! Winners get to wake up (or sleep the juice off) in a brand new, beautiful bedroom!\n\nBars are a key part of the social scene wherever they are. Do this job and we’ll make sure you get the community recognition you deserve!</Text>
  <Text Key="1F96C8CE">Palatial Pass-Out Pad Raffle Winner</Text>
  <Text Key="21684B43">The Local Gym Alliance is looking to sponsor a bathroom reno for a valued member, because sometimes a quick wash in the communal showers just isn’t enough!\n\nThe Alliance anticipates this job notably improving locker room smells and water bills. For your service, the Alliance is ready to get your name out there! Also, pay. The Alliance will pay you too.</Text>
  <Text Key="FDC91D08">PUMP! UP! THAT! BATHROOM!</Text>
  <Text Key="4FCC0707">OH EM GEE SHOES! I need a walk in closet to display some sweet clothes and sway shoes! Help a Sim with a functional and visually appealing home for things I wear?</Text>
  <Text Key="DB5D8324">Walk In Closet Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="A0075D7E">Room Addition </Text>
  <Text Key="D0146667">Room Renovation </Text>
  <Text Key="3FFAAF56">Interior Color Consultant</Text>
  <Text Key="D7342758">Median Gig Pay: §600</Text>
  <Text Key="20CEC8BB">{0.SimFirstName}'s dream of taking someone's building and reimagining it in fun ways is starting to take shape. Every new home {0.SimFirstName} enters is like a blank canvas, ready to be filled with new and interesting décor styles.\n\nFind a gig to start renovating!\n\nNext Promotion: Interior Design Technician</Text>
  <Text Key="78C81452">Median Gig Pay: §900</Text>
  <Text Key="3F854386">Certified Interior Designer</Text>
  <Text Key="F47C3999">Being certified has its benefits, like no boss except the Client, no laws but the zoning laws and no rules but the rule of the Decorator. {0.SimFirstName}'s gig opportunities are as abundant as ever, and the pay ain't so bad as well!</Text>
  <Text Key="308096F5">Median Gig Pay: §600</Text>
  <Text Key="28F3EDF9">Interior Design Technician</Text>
  <Text Key="F01838E2">Crazy Colors, Wacky ideas, Clients have some strange requests, Good thing {0.SimFirstName} will take those requests and turn them into a reality. Although {0.SimFirstName}'s career is still early, there's a lot of potential for creativity with new Clients.\n\nNext Level Promotion: Space Manager</Text>
  <Text Key="41F8A65A">Median Gig Pay: §600</Text>
  <Text Key="EEA7803E">Space Manager</Text>
  <Text Key="B92885C1">{0.SimFirstName} is moving up in the world, so much that new opportunities are presenting themselves! {0.SimFirstName} can now accept gigs for Level Renovations.\n\nNext Level Promotion: Decorating consultant</Text>
  <Text Key="5D829E1F">Median Gig Pay: §600</Text>
  <Text Key="15429B77">Decorating Consultant</Text>
  <Text Key="448B1CC0">With this promotion comes an increase in Simoleons, and a little more respect in the world. Clients will listen to {0.SimFirstName}'s ideas and not scoff, for a change!\n\nNext Level Promotion: Building Space Planner</Text>
  <Text Key="A3984F04">Median Gig Pay: §700</Text>
  <Text Key="2E34AD5C">Building Space Planner</Text>
  <Text Key="2A680037">{0.SimFirstName} is moving up in the world, so much that new opportunities are presenting themselves! {0.SimFirstName} can now accept gigs from Commercial Venues. With Commercial Venues comes potentially higher pay and different types of asks.\n\nNext Level Promotion: Home Organizer</Text>
  <Text Key="9DBC49C1">Median Gig Pay: §775</Text>
  <Text Key="E10C6875">Home Organizer</Text>
  <Text Key="A59CDC3E">Some bring happiness, others bring sadness… organize one's life by {0.SimFirstName}'s three simple rules:\n1. Is it safe? \n2. Does it look cool? \n3. Will the Client like it?\nWords to live by.\n\nNext Level Promotion: Home Decorator
</Text>
  <Text Key="CFC81F76">Median Gig Pay: §800</Text>
  <Text Key="E429494A">Home decorator</Text>
  <Text Key="55A4067D">{0.SimFirstName} has made it! It's official; the business card reads "Home Decorator," and with the title comes all the power to fix those sad, tiny living spaces.\n\nNext Level Promotion: Business Interior Designer</Text>
  <Text Key="64D3208B">Median Gig Pay: §800</Text>
  <Text Key="96539DF3">Business Interior Designer</Text>
  <Text Key="CCFA04FC">{0.SimFirstName} has been officially recognized for the design vision and expertise in the business field. The pay is obviously pretty good, but so is the potential; more Clients and more recognition can help reach even higher than before. \n\nNext Level Promotion: Interior Designer</Text>
  <Text Key="E53885D0">Median Gig Pay: §800</Text>
  <Text Key="DB655028">Interior Designer</Text>
  <Text Key="6BB03273">Whether it's a home office, or an office building, or not an office at all, {0.SimFirstName} can decorate the brick out of it. The title says it all: "Interior Designer." No other qualifier - {0.SimFirstName} can do anything!\n\nNext Level Promotion: Certified Interior Designer.</Text>
  <Text Key="9E0C5A4D">Being an Interior Decorator is about two things:&lt;ol type="1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Having a good eye for design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building relationships with Clients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;\nHaving people skills and some artistic vision will lead to a bright future and possible recognition. You may start small with some simple home renovations, but eventually with enough hard work, bigger Clients and buildings could get you the recognition you deserve!</Text>
  <Text Key="E0B7DB98">Interior Decorator</Text>
  <Text Key="87FD4540">Interior Decorator</Text>
  <Text Key="CAED971C">Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="BA9D9708">Sims can have some... varied opinions about interior design. Sims may occasionally bask in their refined taste, or scoff at questionable décor.</Text>
  <Text Key="2B81A3A0">Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="DBEA48D4">Unlock by reaching level 3 in the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="3076983D">Unlocked by reaching level 6 in the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="55137208">Unlock by reaching level 7 of the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="115E0945">Unlock by reaching level 3 in the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="DFC47754">Unlocked by reaching level 6 in the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDDC8BC9">Now that I've had some time to think on the renovation... I still hate it. Thanks for that.</Text>
  <Text Key="20D7C0CE">It's OK to make mistakes, but you really pushed the limit. I wish you never set foot on my property.</Text>
  <Text Key="205853CE">I shared photos of my &lt;i&gt;“improved”&lt;/i&gt; place on Simstagram. Don’t worry, I was &lt;b&gt;VERY&lt;/b&gt; clear about who was responsible.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0FD4547">Remember me? I hope your day is as terrible as your so-called design sense.</Text>
  <Text Key="2A1753A2">Hey {0.SimFirstName}. I’m amazed, I’ll admit it. How someone like you ever got started with interior design must have taken a miracle.</Text>
  <Text Key="DED874D6">I just noticed some of the details you included in the renovation. That was a really nice touch!</Text>
  <Text Key="3EA40629">My friends are shocked when they visit me. They can't believe how nice this place is now! Wouldn't have happened without you :)</Text>
  <Text Key="D8C3C6E3">I'm &lt;b&gt;SOOOO&lt;/b&gt; happy with the renovation. It's a problem, seriously! My face can't take anymore smiling :D</Text>
  <Text Key="A2890BA7">{0.SimFirstName}, guess what? Guests keep giving me compliments on the new place! You did a great job!</Text>
  <Text Key="6143C07B">I can’t explain it, but after the renovation, I feel happier at home! Makes everything a little easier, you know?</Text>
  <Text Key="3AE95918">Word on the street is you're an amazing interior decorator! Maybe I’ll reach out to your agency for a job I have planned...</Text>
  <Text Key="B573FFDC">I’m looking to refresh my home, and the {2.String|enHouseholdNamePlural} referred me to you. I’ll get my people to talk to your people. </Text>
  <Text Key="92CC9DD6">I love what you did for the {2.String|enHouseholdNamePlural}! Maybe I should hire you for some work…</Text>
  <Text Key="7527A2AA">Hey {0.SimFirstName}. Against my better judgement, I’ll give you a chance to make up for that last gig. Keep an eye out for my offer.</Text>
  <Text Key="7637C46A">You &lt;b&gt;ABSOLUTE disaster&lt;/b&gt;!! How can you charge people for such &lt;b&gt;TERRIBLE&lt;/b&gt; work?! You &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;BETTER&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; make it up to me! &lt;b&gt;AT A DISCOUNT&lt;/b&gt;!!!</Text>
  <Text Key="A6FCBF3F">I won’t lie. I’m not happy with the renovation, but I also believe in second chances. I’ll consider hiring you again, just do me right this time!</Text>
  <Text Key="B436ED45">The renovation turned out so well that I figured why stop here? I hope you’ll work with me again on this next job.</Text>
  <Text Key="8F4F46D8">Are you looking for another gig by chance? Working with you was such a good experience that I know I can trust you.</Text>
  <Text Key="224B4CA5">Hey {0.SimFirstName}! You did such a good job last time, I want to hire you again!</Text>
  <Text Key="FE650438">It was nice having you over the other day! Your visit got me thinking that this place could still use some work. Good thing I know just the person for the job ;) </Text>
  <Text Key="19F19EF6">Was it weird to visit a home you worked on? I hope not, because I’ve been thinking about another job…</Text>
  <Text Key="02B00E71">HAHAHAHAHA best episode of &lt;i&gt;Failures ‘N’ Flops&lt;/i&gt; yet! I can't believe you did that. But seriously, let me know if you can recommend a good interior designer. I'm thinking of renovations...</Text>
  <Text Key="CE48692B">Hey, I saw &lt;i&gt;Failures ‘N’ Flops&lt;/i&gt;… I didn't think it was that bad. Keep your chin up, ok?
</Text>
  <Text Key="AF11D4C4">Did you watch &lt;i&gt;Failures ‘N’ Flops&lt;/i&gt; tonight? I'm here if you need me...</Text>
  <Text Key="B86C884E">There was someone who looked JUST like you on &lt;i&gt;Failures ‘N’ Flops&lt;/i&gt; tonight! Wild stuff.</Text>
  <Text Key="B3977053">I heard about &lt;i&gt;Failures ‘N’ Flops&lt;/i&gt;. Don’t worry, I’m sure there’s &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; who actually liked it! Beauty is in the eye of the beholder :D </Text>
  <Text Key="537070FE">Congratulations? You caught the attention of the Dream Home Decorator Network. Your recent work will star in a special feature of &lt;i&gt;Failures ‘N’ Flops&lt;/i&gt;, Friday 8:00-10:00 PM. </Text>
  <Text Key="8BB312DE">I thought you were an interior decorator, not a TV star! But seriously, glad to see that work is going well. </Text>
  <Text Key="2182A0CA">Loved seeing your work on Ace of Space! I shared it all over Simstagram. </Text>
  <Text Key="8DFB5B5E">Get this. I think I saw your doppelganger on TV just now!! That's so dope! </Text>
  <Text Key="116B2C41">I SAW YOUR WORK ON ACE OF SPACE???! CONGRATS!!! </Text>
  <Text Key="86650C84">Just finished watching an episode of Ace of Space - so cool! I liked your work the best. </Text>
  <Text Key="D74075CE">Congratulations! You caught the attention of the Dream Home Decorator Network. Your recent work will star in a special feature of Ace of Space, Friday 8:00-10:00 PM. </Text>
  <Text Key="9411E348">You did such a great job with the renovation, I thought it’d be nice to invite you over. Want to come over?</Text>
  <Text Key="6C821062">Must reach level 9 in the Interior Decorator Career</Text>
  <Text Key="3B4E4786">Must reach level 3 in the Interior Decorator Career</Text>
  <Text Key="AC87D321">Must be a higher level in Decorator Career, complete other Decorator gigs to level up!</Text>
  <Text Key="45143CC0">Must reach level 5 in the Interior Decorator Career</Text>
  <Text Key="6A78F134">Design Dreaming</Text>
  <Text Key="405E3A02">Prime of Design</Text>
  <Text Key="AB710C6E">Handiest Little Helper</Text>
  <Text Key="1C053B14">Dream Home Dreams</Text>
  <Text Key="C17B008C">Casual Consultant</Text>
  <Text Key="B96DBC18">Space Curator</Text>
  <Text Key="F9057B90">Style Starter</Text>
  <Text Key="D79307F8">Décor Director</Text>
  <Text Key="8543566A">Handiness Required</Text>
  <Text Key="8ADD5B37">Organizing Specialist</Text>
  <Text Key="3A5705F6">A versatile shape that could match any bathroom. At first glance, might not seem like much, you know... from afar. But what you want in a bathtub is not a very ornate or loud design, you just want a bathtub that works, amirite? The Unseeable is perfect for those who want to bathe in modest luxury, after all we can pretend in any tub to be an aristocrat while we read or relax in it.</Text>
  <Text Key="A363AF29">Unseeable Bathtub</Text>
  <Text Key="ED7E248C">A Bathtub with legs, who knew?\n\nFully supported by the propriatery sturdy and stylish leg system, the patented "P1Z H01D TH1S 2.0", the Unseeable Bathtub gets another version for those who seek a bath while looking just a little bit taller. Simple and trendy, sleek design makes this tub almost a work of art. Versatile enough to go almost anywhere, don't hesitate to experiment!</Text>
  <Text Key="4E3DED43">Unseeable Supported Bathtub</Text>
  <Text Key="CE27D1FD">Calling all the Kids! Actual Children... that is.\n\nBe cradled in comfort with this kids bunk bed. The feeling of cozy warmth will make your dreams be merry and not all filled with fright. So make sure you choose this bunk bed, and have all a good night.</Text>
  <Text Key="F308D968">Naturally Nestled Top Bunk</Text>
  <Text Key="E21F13AA">Sleep soundly as if you were sleeping in a cloud... ok not literally, but this top bunk might make you feel like you're in a cloud just by its height alone. Simple, yet efficient, this upper bunk is the comfort you need at the right height.</Text>
  <Text Key="39480135">Serene Repose Upper Bunk</Text>
  <Text Key="73C39674">Be ready for anything that school can throw at you with this sleek wooden top bunk. Give yourself the space that you need for a desk, a computer, or a nook to study in for that big test.</Text>
  <Text Key="1F3695DB">Too Cool for School Top Bunk</Text>
  <Text Key="A10AB9EF">Get the best night of sleep in your life with this ultra comfortable bed. Using only the finest responsibly sourced wood and the softest bamboo sheets, you can rest assured that you are sleeping while saving the planet!</Text>
  <Text Key="8B583A36">Smooth Slumber Upper Bunk</Text>
  <Text Key="5DE44B89">There once was an urban princess who wished to wed a very wealthy urban prince. However, the prince's mother - the queen -  was very possessive of him and told the prince he could only marry someone of a refined delicate nature. She came up with a plan to give the princess an impossible test so she could fail her and then go back to spending way too much time coddling her adult son.\nThe queen planned to put a pea under the most cushiony mattress in the family estate, but realized since she never cooked for herself and had no idea where the peas were. Instead she resorted to using a whole pineapple left over from her latest home-spa facial treatment. Much to her disappointment, the Princess felt the pineapple under the mattress and could not sleep, passing the test. The prince and princess were wed and everyone enjoyed some nice pineapple juice. The moral of the story is if you love something, let it go. Also, always know where the peas are. You never know when you'll need to try to trick a princess or make a risotto.</Text>
  <Text Key="702633EC">The Princess and the Pineapple Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="F54DF48B">One of the first things they teach you in fancy art schools is the concept of negative space and how it impacts design. Negative space: it's a positive! This bed was designed with that concept in mind. Notice the subtle yet lovely shapes created by the adjoining rectangles at the foot and head of the bed. Yes, in order to fully comprehend the beauty of certain furniture you really do have to learn to see the space that the designer chose not to use. Alright, your art school education is complete so that'll be 200,000 please. Wait, 200,000, really?! Yeesh. Talk about being put in a negative space.</Text>
  <Text Key="DB88200A">The Beauty of Negative Space Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="030BE8C7">This may be a Kid's bed, but it is not child's play. Kids will be cradled in comfort while sleeping without sacrificing their growing sense of style.</Text>
  <Text Key="8432C97E">Naturally Nestled Single Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="269A0F34">This comfortable, simple yet elegant bed, offers a night (or day) of comfort without sacrificing space or your Lot's looks. Its stylish quilted headboard is the perfect balance to this wooden crafted bed. Sleep soundly in serenity.</Text>
  <Text Key="D9CCA09B">Serene Repose Single Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="B932276E">Just because you're single doesn't mean you have to have a sad single bed. Embrace your ability to sleep without worrying about being woken up by the person sleeping next to you, or worrying about accidentally punching them in the face after an unconcious struggle to maintain control of the blanket majority. That's right - you get the whole bed to yourself, so make it a nice one!</Text>
  <Text Key="9FBFBA11">Swingin' Single Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="7A0D3A7E">Stylish and trendy, this bed is a great option for space saving while looking quite smart. The knobs give it a nice decorative touch without disrupting the flow of its construction.</Text>
  <Text Key="1F826E01">Single Bed With Knobs</Text>
  <Text Key="75F225B1">Get the best night of sleep in your life with this ultra comfortable bed. Using only the finest responsibly sourced wood and the softest bamboo sheets, you can rest assured that you are sleeping while saving the planet!</Text>
  <Text Key="A385D584">Smooth Single Sumbler</Text>
  <Text Key="5C4F0673">Book of Basics, you cannot start dipping your toes in Interior Design without DesignCraft... Vol. I.\n\nLearn to navigate your first color palette, your first Client, your first... experimental room.</Text>
  <Text Key="A94F49A2">DesignCraft Vol. I</Text>
  <Text Key="14DD91C0">Why would this floor-placed bookcase want to be anything else when it could just Be Modular?\n\nThat's right, even this sturdy and sharp bookcase can be attached to other elegant floor-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="74E54E8F">The Acute Floor-Placed Bookcase by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="C4A0C506">This lovely curved floor-placed bookshelf stands just as proudly on its own as it does attached to other floor-placed furnishings. Partner it up with TV stands, coffee tables, or other bookshelves in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="EE5B1099">The Rounded Floor-Placed Bookcase by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="6E28C5B8">Stick it to the wall, or use it not at all. While that proverb may not ring true for most things, it certainly rings true for this particular wall-mounted bookcase.\n\nThis bookcase can be attached to other wall-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="009728B7">The Acute Floating Wall Bookcase by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="7FFCBEAE">THE book connoisseur, I. Inserra, decided to create a new bookcase design that could revolutionize the book world. The smooth, wall-hanging design of this bookcase from the Be Modular line will add sleek functionality to any room it adorns.\n\nThis bookcase can be attached to other wall-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="23F2DE51">The Rounded Floating Wall Bookcase by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="C4F57060">Discover the secrets of famous Interior Designers of old... and beyond. Learn from the wisdom of others, all the stories, and wonder. Learn to navigate Clients, specially their indecisiveness. Learn it all, and survive it all, with this Book Of Décor.</Text>
  <Text Key="3FF7EFAF">The Book Of Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="FFEFD07D">Quite the modern cabinet by IliInserra. The two tiered reticulated rectangular design allows you to store things out of sight as well as in plain view... are they there? Are they not there? You decide!</Text>
  <Text Key="006B8CE8">Reticulated Rectangles by IliInserra</Text>
  <Text Key="22275101">Nothing beats a good old square cabinet - except a paper cabinet! Wait, no, I don't think that's how that works... Is that how it goes? &lt;i&gt;reads script frantically&lt;/i&gt; OK, let me start again...\n\nThis cabinet will be a perfect match for your other items from the Mikulino line down to the squareness of it all.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF898834">Be There Or Be Squared Cabinet by Mikulino</Text>
  <Text Key="1BDA041E">Cutting edge technology at your fingertips. Processing power enough to have this laptop fly away on its own. Let your ideas be realized with ease with this powerful piece of equipment that will be part of you so much so that you won't live without.\n\nWe won't judge if you only use this for Blicblock though.</Text>
  <Text Key="7C92DB21">S.I.Mac P.R.O. Laptop</Text>
  <Text Key="AF0A5815">Unlock by reaching level 10 of the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="F974743A">Unlocked by reaching level 10 in the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="CF622DAA">It's all about the feet! Our designer MilaMila, got inspired by the way cat feet looks when they are picked up from surfaces. &lt;i&gt;"Feet, they need room sometimes."&lt;/i&gt; she says. These classic styled kitchen island has enough room for some fancy footwork.</Text>
  <Text Key="7B922F35">Ressessed not Recess! Kitchen Island by MilaMila</Text>
  <Text Key="907ABC10">Who doesn't like a good overhang? Your roof has'em, now you can have a Kitchen Island with that look too! Just don't hit your head when picking up stuff that rolled under this modern looking kitchen island. Ouch!</Text>
  <Text Key="8E4EEF3F">Modern Kitchen Island by Mikulino</Text>
  <Text Key="C7210C01">In the kitchen, you need room and storage space to make sure your tools are safe. Young designer IliInserra had inspiration from her cat as it found things over a drawerless counter to knock over them to the floor. &lt;i&gt;"Drawers, are more than just a place for things to be forgotten, they are a safe space for things to not get lost"&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="1E43C934">Drawerized Counter by IliInserra</Text>
  <Text Key="C6B634C5">Mikulino's philosophy is of Kitchen, meet counters and cabinets. This marries the perfect balance of industrial and modern, and let's appliances get introduced to their surfaces effortlessly.</Text>
  <Text Key="CA4F13C0">Modern Countertop by Mikulino</Text>
  <Text Key="533DDCC6">Enjoy all the benefits of curtains without shutting the outside world out! You may be a curmudgeonly miser at heart but thanks to these friendly little curtains, no one else needs to know. Let the world enjoy your softer side and let your windows look fabulous doing it.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B2AF559">Friendly Little Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="140E7E63">Enjoying the Friendly Little Curtains? Say no more! If you have slightly taller wall space, you can use this variation to continue to let the world enjoy your softer side. The taller they are, the more friendly the seem.</Text>
  <Text Key="2214DF32">Slightly Friendlier Little Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="4FCF7CB8">Even more wall height space? Not a problem, the Super Friendly Little Curtains are the best option for those who have impossible tall walls and want to partially shut the world away in a polite way, and being fabulous about it.</Text>
  <Text Key="728F9DB7">Super Friendly Little Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="3F0D531B">The perfect desk for aspiring and inspiring interior designers everywhere. Comes already equipped with rulers and protractors, as well as a nifty little space for pens and measuring tapes (and includes one!). And the pièce de résistance is that it comes pre-stickied with sticky notes written with random doodles, and things you can forget about jotting down later.</Text>
  <Text Key="F19749FA">Draft With Style - Specialized Designer Desk</Text>
  <Text Key="F6185922">You are all about that modern look, but still want that rugged, woodsy feel? Search no further. Slabs On Sticks is the perfect desk solution for those that need a compact and functional space, without sacrificing their sense of style. Minimal setup required, in fact this desk is as minimal as its setup, it comes already assembled!</Text>
  <Text Key="2D13309D">Slabs On Sticks - Modern Desk Solution</Text>
  <Text Key="40CED0BD">Sometimes as adults we reminisce of our youth, specially our school days. Those times in a classroom, being assigned a desk and making it your home... and dealing with a desk companion that you kinda couldn't stand halfway into the school year... just me? Oh OK &lt;i&gt;ahem&lt;/i&gt;. Here in L.U.M.B.E.R we believe in elegant simplicity with a touch of retro, and this desk has got it. This desk offers the style resembling that of your school years without reliving them. Built from simple polished wood and a fresh and clean coat of paint, this desk offers quite enough space for all your desk needs that potentially makes you feel younger, without all the angst.</Text>
  <Text Key="1A31A028">Studious Retro Desk By L.U.M.B.E.R</Text>
  <Text Key="8E72A48F">Sure. A desk is nice, but an impressive organizationational structure surrounding that desk is divine.\n\nThis desk can be attached to other floor-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="BEDFD756">The Acute Desk made for Discerning Space Savers by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="D6FBF4F3">Take functional to the next level with actual work or school productivity paired with flexible shelving design.\n\nThis desk can be attached to other floor-placed items in the Be Modular line, particularly Awestruck Erik. Do please impress him.</Text>
  <Text Key="1D6DCD22">The Rounded Desk... brought to you by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="49EC24AA">Door designer Owen Sesame in his life long studies of doors, realized that a double door is not complete without frosted glass to have some privacy. The perfect blend of visual interest and intrigue is displayed in its exquisite frostness without added frills which makes this door intriguing to the visitor.</Text>
  <Text Key="20506435">No Peeking Frosted Glass Simple Double Door</Text>
  <Text Key="43F5A933">Door designer Owen Sesame has spent his entire life studying the design of doors, and has unveiled one of his proudest achievements in door design. This frosted double door with wooden inlay was a result of years of travel and research. The perfect blend of visual interest, functionality, and frostiness to keep your private life private without a big "keep out" sign.</Text>
  <Text Key="EC496462">No Peeking Frosted Glass Double Door</Text>
  <Text Key="3B7C3BE0">When decorators keep giving choices\nthat will make you fall in love... or not\nWhen decorators keep rearranging\nbut you can't seem to get settled on an option\nLet this door be your door\nLet this door be your door\nLet this door be your door\nto your Lot</Text>
  <Text Key="E7D37A2F">Let This Door Be The Door</Text>
  <Text Key="B2E50A7A">It's time to free your tailored duds from the confines of those stuffy dressers! Give your suiting some fresh air by snapping them to the bar of any of the Be Modular Clothes-Hanging Shelves.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C002425">Sophisticated Suits Hanging Clothes</Text>
  <Text Key="34DA3F43">Boo to fold lines. Some pieces of clothing just need to &lt;b&gt;hang&lt;/b&gt;. And now so they shall! Pair these pretty yet professional frocks with with the welcoming bar of any Be Modular Clothes-Hanging Shelves.</Text>
  <Text Key="4518B092">Professional Fashionista Hanging Clothes</Text>
  <Text Key="1BBEAED8">Maximize your floor space by saying bye bye to big bulky dressers and hello to a more space-saving option. These casual clothes pair well with any of the Be Modular Clothes-Hanging Shelves.</Text>
  <Text Key="8ACF6E57">Everyday Casual Hanging Clothes</Text>
  <Text Key="B9BE08F9">Kids clothes don't want to be locked away in boxy dressers. It's dark in there! Ask these cuties to come out and play by displaying them proudly on the wall with any of the Be Modular Clothes-Hanging Shelves.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0A747FC">Hanging Clothes for the Kids</Text>
  <Text Key="70E17E28">This simple yet stylish full-sized dresser is just fine on its own. Happy even! A classic, versatile piece that doesn't need anybody or anything else to define it.\n\nBut sometimes, this chic treasure gets lonely. Don't you think it could use a Be Modular floor shelf or two not only for company but also up the ante on your bedroom storage game?\n\nThis dresser can be attached to other floor-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="B48B1847">The Rounded Dresser by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="DB8AEE22">More storage? You got it! &lt;i&gt;I Love MyShelf Inc.&lt;/i&gt; doesn't just do shelving. You can get into our drawers too! This full sized set snaps conveniently to any other modular floor furniture, it's like a puzzle piece... that can go alone, or with others!</Text>
  <Text Key="024CDF9D">Get Your Drawers Off the Floor - Full-Sized Edition - by I Love MyShelf Inc.</Text>
  <Text Key="44BF2A22">A Lamp that looks like it's wearing a bonnet? So cute! This was the same thought the designers at GeoWerx had when they created the Bonnet Bonnet Lamp after the success of the Lighting set by the same name. Fabulous, cute, and functional just like we love our lighting.</Text>
  <Text Key="E9FCD39D">Bonnie Bonnet Lamp by GeoWerx</Text>
  <Text Key="41B8E6B1">The designers at Seymore Lighting not only decided to make a Lamp Trio inspired by cupcake wrappers, but also decided to add to the collection a single lamp version for those rooms that need a focal piece all on its own. After all, all those origami lessons and papercuts had to be worth it!</Text>
  <Text Key="28EC4884">Cupcake Lamp by Seymore Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="8E823811">What's better than good lighting? According to GeoWerx focus group testing, the answer is good lighting that looks like it's wearing cute little bonnets. Yes, our of everyone surveyed, this was the most popular answer, though there were some close runner ups including scented lighting, edible lighting, and lighting that compliments how you look every time you step into a room.</Text>
  <Text Key="08B7EB64">Bonnie Bonnet Lighting by GeoWerx</Text>
  <Text Key="03841EBE">One night in the Seymore Lighting design studios, our designers were running out of ideas. Staring at the blank whiteboards and the naked lightbulbs, their task to design the new fall season's most innovative lighting was proving to me more daunting than they ever imagined. In need of a sugar rush, they dove into a box of cupcakes when the idea hit them... lampshades inspired by cupcake wrappers! Eureka! After several origami classes and papercuts, this classy, crinkly shade was born. Sometimes grasping at crumbs can be a good thing, especially cupcake crumbs!</Text>
  <Text Key="D7085141">Cupcake Lamp Trio by Seymore Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="58C6AFFC">Eventually after developing a million different kinds of lamps, our lighting designers got frustrated and threw this one against the wall. Fortunately, the resulting wonkiness really worked aesthetically and it makes a great conversation starter. Ah, anger makes such great art.</Text>
  <Text Key="61C7CF53">All the Rage Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="E31FD6C9">This perfect little cube-on-a-stand light will add a touch of brightness to your day, and who doesn't need a little extra brightness? We first offered this cube light back in the 90s. At the time, it had a dial-up-modem and a fax machine attached. We've since removed both features and invested more time and energy into improving its lighting capability and aesthetics. We know some people might miss the dial-up-modem, but you can always make modem sounds on your own at home if you're feeling nostalgic. If you're too young to know what a dial up modem is, search for videos online and enjoy the soothing sounds.</Text>
  <Text Key="F96C602C">Cube 2.0 Light by Seymore Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="735B581E">Presenting a completely unique lighting shape - the spherocylinder! Not quite a sphere, and not quite a cylinder. It's your favorite two shapes smooshed together to create one single super shape, and a super lighting solution. Patent pending. Patents take a while though so please don't steal our idea in the meantime.</Text>
  <Text Key="2AEE9721">Spherocylinder Lighting Capsule by Seymore Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="F9096F64">You know those scenes in musicals when the protoganist is singing to themselves in the mirror as they're starting their day? That could be you! This mirror is the perfect companion piece for gazing at your reflection while amping yourself up with a power anthem or belting out a wistful ballad. Get ready world, here you come! Works for soul-less non music lovers too since its, well...a mirror.</Text>
  <Text Key="A92BE1AB">Amped Up Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="D27E185B">Two mirrors, both alike in dignity on the wall where we set our scene.\nBoth able to provide clear scrutiny\nIn the bathroom where you scrub and clean.\nAll drama aside, it's a mirror.</Text>
  <Text Key="3292123A">A Mirror Divided</Text>
  <Text Key="5FD771D0">This fiery beast will set your meals ablaze - in a good way. Here at Blazin' Ladles we believe if you're not cooking with gas, well, then you're not cooking at all!</Text>
  <Text Key="CFA819FF">Standard Gas Oven By Blazin' Ladles</Text>
  <Text Key="16548663">Ever dreamed of electricity, cooking your food to a fragrant, crisp perfection? The Electric Baker will not fail you or your mutton pot roast. Entirely harmless if used as directed.</Text>
  <Text Key="DC787732">Electric Baker's Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="22ACD686">Have ample countertop space but cannot give up any more shelf space? Been there. Introducing the Blazin' Ladles' Over The Counter Oven - Bake to your heart's content without having to squat or bend your back! Just acquire and place, without instructions, no fuss given!</Text>
  <Text Key="05178D19">Blazin' Ladles' Over The Counter Oven</Text>
  <Text Key="989815A6">Don't want to give up any more cabinets to the appliance monster? Put your baking needs waist high and let the cakes fly - just don't call it a toaster or it might get mad... very mad.</Text>
  <Text Key="403362B9">"No Space" Electric Oven Space Saver</Text>
  <Text Key="F0016266">Package</Text>
  <Text Key="6713ABA1">The lonely painter, Leyland, knows how color and travel can calm the mind. However, not everyone has the luxury of time to travel. Leyland traveled to get inspiration, so you can have a window to the world. Leave traveling to them, and feel the excitement of travel, from the comfort of your home.</Text>
  <Text Key="2FAA2654">Leyland Home Travel</Text>
  <Text Key="1B6474F8">Do you want to be more outdoorsy, but do not &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; wish to be outside? Why not bring one of these abstract paintings home and experience Nature abstractly from the most comfortable place you know: your couch.</Text>
  <Text Key="726CFDF7">Outdoorsy indoors</Text>
  <Text Key="CD5F806D">paperSml_GP10GENpaintSamples Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="18008138">paperSml_GP10GENpaintSamples Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="E65A6E47">Letter from Client</Text>
  <Text Key="135F9A70">This floofy foliage is the poodle of plants! Bring elegance and playfullness to any space with its soft flowing tufts of pettable petals. </Text>
  <Text Key="ACA3E51F">Pampas Grass</Text>
  <Text Key="F1F9ACCF">Little plant pots on the wall... who are the fairest plants of them all? The Itty Bitty Plant Committee won't talk to you (or can they?), but that won't stop you from talking to them. These little cute planters with accompanying plants will brighten any room in the Lot in a stylish and modern way.</Text>
  <Text Key="405D9E96">The Itty Bitty Plant Committee</Text>
  <Text Key="B9CB7B46">Most things in life can be improved by adding tassles. This rug is a perfect example! Before tassles were added to this rug, it was doing poorly in school, hanging out with a bad crowd and just not applying itself. Since adding tassles, this rug has transformed into an upstanding citizen (well, more lying flat than upstanding).</Text>
  <Text Key="A2AC88D9">Hassle-Free Tassled Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="7A1DAC07">A timeless pattern with a pop of color! Perfect for those who are afraid of some color in their décor, this rug has enough pattern and color that will stand out, but not completely break the mutest of styles.</Text>
  <Text Key="1583AFBE">Patterns And Shapes - Modern Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="0E0769AA">Unlock by reaching level 5 in the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="D3DC4F31">Unlocked by reaching level 5 of the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="C50E4379">Years ago, a struggling rug shop realized they had no choice but to go out of business. Heartbroken, they put up a "going out of business" sign in the window advertising that everything must go. They suddenly found themselves overrrun with the most customers they had ever seen. It was too bad they had advertised they were going out of business and would soon have to close. Or would they? The owner had the idea to leave the "going out of business" sale in the window for just a few more weeks to see if customers would still show up. It worked, so the owner decided to leave it up for just another month longer, and then just another year longer... and that was now seven years ago. To this day, customers still flock into the perpetually closing store to make bids on fine rugs such as this one. Support small businesses by buying large area rugs!</Text>
  <Text Key="DE75EF7C">"Everything Must Go!" Area Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="A0A6878C">Do you need a storage with easy access? Children and toddlers can easily make a mess, and sometimes it just needs to be put away fast. This storage is ideal for a quick clean-up, as well as having the perfect place to hide all your knick-knacks and trinkets.</Text>
  <Text Key="2773A643">Closed Storage Space</Text>
  <Text Key="57778363">Any place could use this smart and useful storage space. The open boxes are the perfect place to put your books and files, that you need easy access to. Just like the closed storage space, this has a closed box, where you can stuff your small items.</Text>
  <Text Key="E586DE32">Partly Open Storage Space</Text>
  <Text Key="176968CE">What sparks Happiness? This is the basis and everything that Simie Ondo our design and organization specialist believes in. Spread the good vibes by having neatly folded items in a basket you will never use again, or maybe move it around a few times. Spread the joy of organized chaos by displaying this beautiful piece in your room.</Text>
  <Text Key="4CDAC0F1">Joyously Wicked Wicker Basket</Text>
  <Text Key="0FE5DAE7">Everything folded, and everything in its right place to spark a bit of Happiness. Simie Ondo, the design and organization specialist, believes in this piece as a way to bring organized disorder into the lives of Sims everywhere that are looking to make their Lot a better place. Why have it be around the Lot anywhere? Have it look nice and neat with this beautiful basked instead.</Text>
  <Text Key="F2F6421E">Joyously Wicked Smaller Wicker Basket</Text>
  <Text Key="37BB773D">From the team that brought you the Future Cube comes "Present Day Multi-Cube." It has no special powers or functions, but we think that merely existing as a 3-Dimensional multi-sided cube within the confines of space and time is still pretty cool.</Text>
  <Text Key="4911CBA8">Present Day Multi-Cube by Paltry Predictions</Text>
  <Text Key="A730A942">This bowl is much classier and more special than any other bowls. You can tell since it's a functional bowl, but it's &lt;i&gt;empty&lt;/i&gt;. Now that's class right there. It will definitely elevate your decor and social status since everyone knows that high society people often have functional items around that are never used at all. In high society things are to be looked at rather than touched.\nGo into anyone's mansion and the first thing you'll hear is &lt;i&gt;Don't sit on the good chair. Don't use the special dishes. Don't use the good vase.&lt;/i&gt;\nPoor rich people. Cursed with wealth, they will always admire the bowl from afar, never knowing the sweet taste of cereal.
</Text>
  <Text Key="28920E3D">Forbidden Cereal Bowl</Text>
  <Text Key="336BDCFC">An assorted set of color swatches by the mysterious, avant garde, Sevillan art collective 'SlothLoverEEE' - as stylish as they are mysterious, they make exquisite designs. Slowly.</Text>
  <Text Key="4A65C653">Color Swatches By SlothLoverEEE</Text>
  <Text Key="769CEBE1">You cannot call yourself a Decorator if you don't own every issue of &lt;i&gt;Terrain Tools Digest&lt;/i&gt;,&lt;i&gt; Interior... Design?&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Decent Lots and Gardens&lt;/i&gt;, and a Sim favorite - &lt;i&gt;Decorator Living.&lt;/i&gt; Get inspired by looking at the colorful and trendy pages and soon all the ideas will start to flow!</Text>
  <Text Key="33E5A594">Issues of Interior Design Magazines</Text>
  <Text Key="2369DFDC">Unlock by reaching level 2 of the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="E334A9AF">Unlocked at level 2 of the Interior Decorator career.</Text>
  <Text Key="DFFBC50D">A sculpture of a jack from the noble game of jacks. Many people are led to believe that the game of Jacks AKA "Knucklebones" is steeped in a rich history dating all the way back to the ancient Greeks, but what they don't know is that it was actually invented by a lumberjack named Big Jacks McGee who would carve jacks out of wood and hurl them at anyone in his town who offended him. Since he was easily offended, people started amassing bunches of these tiny little star-shaped doohickies and decided to start playing with them. True story! Ask any scholar. Just don't ask the internet because that's not a credible source of information.</Text>
  <Text Key="CFE06E58">Big Jack</Text>
  <Text Key="E538C399">Stop worrying, all is good and stored together\nOh silly me, why haven't I found my socks yet then?\nCan I store my things here in these Bins?\nCan't find my trinkets or my swimwear here in this Bins\nWhere are my clutter items please?\n\nIt's all there for you...\nSoooo, you just need to search these through</Text>
  <Text Key="D099081C">Bins Bins Bins</Text>
  <Text Key="BEA7E7CC">Bins, Bins, Bins, Bins\nBins, Bins, Bins, Bins\nWhen I want to find\nWhen I want to find all the things I packed\nWhenever I feel I have lost a thing, all I have to do is go to the\nBins, Bins, Bins, Bins\n\nWhen I feel I have lost a thing in the night\nAnd I need it right away\nWhenever I want a thing, all I have to do is go to the\nBins, Bins, Bins, Bins</Text>
  <Text Key="CD935283">Bins Bins Bins Bins</Text>
  <Text Key="CBE7890F">No walk-in closet is complete without a hearty collection of classic pumps. Proudly line your walls and shelves with these soothing slip-ons. Edge to edge. Corner to corner. There's no such thing as too many shoes.</Text>
  <Text Key="41C85CD6">Classic Pumps</Text>
  <Text Key="535A5836">Perfect for any occasion, it's always handy to have a few pairs of Casual Kicks on hand. For your feet.</Text>
  <Text Key="D6138069">Casual Kicks</Text>
  <Text Key="147263C1">Always understated, always in style. I dare you to find someone who doesn't live for their favorite pair of sneakers. And if and when you do find them, ask them if their feet are sore.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B58F9F4">Don't Forget the Sneaks!</Text>
  <Text Key="793E68C0">Whether it's date night, brunch with besties, or just a day out on the town, always be prepared with a small stash of Flirty Footwear.</Text>
  <Text Key="67B2238F">Flirty Footwear</Text>
  <Text Key="88AE6AEF">Don't throw out this cardboard box, you're not unpacking anyway\nTake a look at things inside\nNever trust that old dust pile\nSippin' coffee in my room, while playing all the Metal tunes\nAll spruced up for reveal day, keep on storing things anyway</Text>
  <Text Key="0EE27D36">Trippin' On My Cardboard Box</Text>
  <Text Key="80052C16">More than one box appeared in the room\nI wonder now what's inside\nTake a look when you can, too much to decorate tonight\nAnd when you're done, you can rest\nAnd all these boxes may be gone\nSo keep the clutter near, just keep things near, keep on putting things in here anyway</Text>
  <Text Key="050FB2C9">Trippin' On My Cardboard Boxes</Text>
  <Text Key="12FCBFA5">A Surprise in each and every one! This box is made from a luxurious soft material that will hold your valuables while looking good doing so.</Text>
  <Text Key="294A6020">What's In The Box? Storage Box</Text>
  <Text Key="981CFC38">Need more than one fancy box? We've got you boo! These luxurious boxes will hold anything, not reveal anything, and looking good doing so. The more of them the merrier, they even look good stacked neatly with each other.</Text>
  <Text Key="87D90437">What's In The Boxes? Storage Boxes</Text>
  <Text Key="BBFD2907">Lana the Llama spent her childhood wishing she was a moose, but has since embraced her llama-ness and is eager to show you just how much of a llama she can be. Nestle her onto your favorite surface and prepare to be dazzled by her doing what she does best: sitting around being a llama sculpture!</Text>
  <Text Key="B31F96BE">Lana the Llama</Text>
  <Text Key="F4760892">Don't merely call this a Collage... as if! This board is more than random pieces of things put together in a relatively organized way, no sir, no way, no how! This is a inspiration piece, a carefully crafted collection of things that make you go about your day, discuss goals, where and what you want to be. So take a good look, be inspired! Be bold!</Text>
  <Text Key="B6CD06AD">Such A Mood - Moodboard</Text>
  <Text Key="F9423F32">A statement piece by master whittling artist and woodworker, Jack Whittler. This particular wooden mosaic is an abstract portrait of his mother, and depicts their uneven, often splintery relationship. A great conversation starter for when you'd like to direct discussion topics toward the complexity of family dynamics or the art of whittling.</Text>
  <Text Key="7CFC88CD">Whittler's Mother</Text>
  <Text Key="3887158E">This slim, tall, handsome piece of flexible furniture is imploring you, "[Playername], please, attach me to a TV stand, smash me into a desk, make me feel whole again. You know how it is." Are you daring enough to make The Tall Rounded Floor Shelf with a Single Hatch by Be Modular's dreams come true?\n\nThis floor shelf can be attached to other floor-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="1E0211B1">The Tall Rounded Floor Shelf with a Single Hatch by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="1DD6F193">Is it a wardrobe? Is it a display case? By the powers that be, girl, you tell me. You can make this versatile floor shelf the base of any complicated shelving structure your imagination can imagine.\n\nThis floor shelf can be attached to other floor-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F074142">The Acute Trinket Displayer by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="283E095A">Extend your walk-in closet display needs with this self-containing clothes box. If you see the bar, that means you can hang the clothes. Compatible with Hanging Clothes.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE862385">The Acute Self-Containing Clothes-Hanging Cubby by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="23204123">Proudly line your walk-in closet with this rectangular display that hangs your favorite clothing and displays your shoes. Compatible with Hanging Clothes.</Text>
  <Text Key="33DF54F2">The Acute Clothes-Hanging Shelf by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="B8BA715E">Break up the monotony in your curvy luscious walk-in closet with this wall-hanging, clothes-hanging masterpiece. Compatible with Hanging Clothes</Text>
  <Text Key="3EE0BE61">The Rounded Clothes-Hanging Cubby by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="6B7ABC77">At first glance, this may look like a normal Be Modular rounded rectangular shelf, but if you look closer you'll see a very useful bar for hanging clothes. Go on... try it... hang the clothes. That's right.. hang the clothes.</Text>
  <Text Key="5FBFB9CE">The Rounded Clothes-Hanging Shelf by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="A77B18BF">A true inspiration for any walk-in closet, this floating wall unit is a stunning way for you to display your shoes, hold your knick-knacks and make a statement.\n\nThis floating shelf can be attached to any other wall-placed shelving in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="EDC2C3E6">The Acute Large Glass Floating Shelf by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="A0677EF9">For our more introverted clients who lead the private lives, we understand the need to lock precious positions away from prying eyes. Because it's all fun and games until your friend judges you for collecting porcelain giraffes.\n\nThis wall shelf can be attached to any other wall-placed shelving in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA5DC9FC">The Acute Hide-Away Shelf by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="5034A384">Who says being organized can't also mean being stylish? This fine, simple piece combines nicely with other wall shelves and it's subdued visuals are perfect for displaying your most prized posessions.</Text>
  <Text Key="C3312F4B">The Acute Double Drawer Shelf by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="0D919326">There's nothing more satisfying than taking small objects and containing them within other objects. NOTHING! If you are an organizer at heart, you understand the satisfaction... no... the need for containment of the right size and shape. Don't worry. This little rectangle shelf with its cute little glass cube on the end has got you covered.\n\nThis wall shelf can be attached to any other wall-placed shelving in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="E7246339">The Acute Glass Display Cutie Cube by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="EF8A3D44">An organizer's dream. This little cubby has literally a zillion uses. Stack a crew of these little cuties with each other to make an artistic wall display for all your tiny knick knack and doodad displaying needs. Or use them as a complimentary punctuation with any wall shelving from the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A440F0B">The Acute Cutie Cube Cubbie by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="875ACA68">During a shelving retreat at &lt;i&gt;Be Modular&lt;/i&gt; we encouraged our employees to discuss everything they'd want in their ideal shelving unit. After hours of chatting about shelf height, storage capability and of course, wood grain, our design team got to work on a "employee's choice" shelf. Hopefully it ticks all your boxes too when it comes to storage!\n\nThis floating shelf can be attached to any other wall-placed shelving in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4D62187">Employee's Choice Cabinet by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="D1DB214D">Furniture with sharp edges? We say nay! This stunning shelf piece from &lt;i&gt;Be Modular&lt;/i&gt; is the perfect connection between other rounded tall shelves, squat shelves, or anything in between.\n\nThis floating shelf can be attached to any other wall-placed shelving in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="C58B8098">The Double Knob Rounded Wall Shelf by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="C98C89C6">Here at Be Modular, we encourage you to punctuate your shelving masterpieces with this tall, versatile, sleek 3-knob piece of shelving mastery.\n\nThis floating shelf can be attached to any other wall-placed shelving in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB8D6C59">Thrice Knobs Tall Rounded Wall Shelf by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="722AD3B1">This single-door rounded wall shelf is the perfect partner to the rest of the rounded wall pieces from the Be Modular line. Stack ‘em, pile ‘em, put ‘em right next to each other! No matter what you do, you will have furniture to match.</Text>
  <Text Key="0BD47F84">The Rounded Rectangular Cubby by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="ECFD1CB8">The sky is the limits when it comes to decorating options offered by these unassuming, yet spectacular little cubbies. Use them for an intricate piece of functional wall art or surprise your secret crush by writing their name on your living room wall. They'll be far too impressed by your creative organization resourcefulness to be weirded out, we promise.</Text>
  <Text Key="69667DB7">The Rounded Cube Cubby by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="19ED9402">The taller, older sibling of the Rounded Cube Cubby is simple, yet sophisticated with two compartments for the placement of your finest items.\n\nThis floating shelf can be attached to any other wall-placed shelving in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA2A8BFD">The Rounded Tall Wall Shelf by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="48EBB80B">Most companies encourage their designers to "think outside the box," resulting in thousands of designs being tossed aside just for being boxy. Here at BoxWorks, we believe in thinking inside the box, so much so that our newest line of sinks is entirely box-forward. Why mess with the classics? This perfectly cubed box sink is here to stay!</Text>
  <Text Key="9E87128A">Boxed Sink by BoxWorks</Text>
  <Text Key="4AAE5C0B">What's better than a stack of pancakes? A stacked pedestal sink! And while you probably shouldn't be pouring syrup over it, it can definitely help you wash syrup off your hands in the most stylish way. A must have for messy brunch guests!</Text>
  <Text Key="7E45BE8A">Super Stacked Sink</Text>
  <Text Key="AAE2EC53">Often times humanity wonders what life will be like in the distant future. What kind of new technology will change our lives? More importantly, what kinds of furniture will we sit on? This quilted bar stool is the product of such a wonder. Made of space-age material used aboard several crafts, this chair brings the comfort of tomorrow to your bottom... today!</Text>
  <Text Key="E23B1802">Tomorrow's Bar Stool</Text>
  <Text Key="C5546BCF">Humanity wonders what life would be like tomorrow... but today. What will things look like? How they will work? Will they work? We sure hope so!\n\nIn the future you can always count on eating, and where there is eating... there is seating. This dining chair is sleek, modern, minimal sure, but it holds enough comfort to get through the rituals of dinners everywhere from the past, present, and future.
</Text>
  <Text Key="A3A3AB96">The TrendSitter</Text>
  <Text Key="2F7E3D7C">For anyone with back problems, this plush-yet-firm chair cradles your back but still manages to be firm. Kind of like one of those kindergarten teachers who is really sweet to you but still won't let you make faces at Kelly Schwartz even though she was totally out of line for taking the last graham cracker during snack time.</Text>
  <Text Key="4A75FFD3">Plush-yet-Firm Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="08EE6835">A plush, no-nonsense chair made of space-age futuristic foam. Cradles your backside so well, you'll wish the future would have gotten here years ago.</Text>
  <Text Key="FB5C71D0">No-Nonsense Butt-Hugger Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="54046FA4">Why just accessorize with accessories? If you're going to spend time planning and agonizing over an outfit, you should make sure your surrounding furniture compliments it as well. This unfussy ottoman gives anyone's outfit a nice boost. With its sleek lines and simple silhouette, it's sure to look fabulous in the background of any Simstagram selfie.</Text>
  <Text Key="BB4520EB">Goes-With-Anything Ottoman</Text>
  <Text Key="8505810A">It took our furniture engineering team years to figure out how to design the perfect blend of style and comfort, but they did it. Years of staying late in the furniture lab, missing family dinners, birthdays, graduations, anniversaries, weddings, and PTA meetings. But putting their relationships, social lives and wellbeing at risk was worth it for the comfort of your backside. Once you sink into this cushioned masterpiece, you'll agree.</Text>
  <Text Key="84219415">Masterpiece Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="CF071DB2">This ultra swanky chair was made fun of by all other chairs for a long time due to its extra large back, which, in the chair world is the equivalent to having an extra large forehead. The chair was teased relentlessly, excluded from many sleepovers in elementary school, and forced to eat alone at lunch on the playground. Then one day a furniture scout spotted the chair and the rest is history. Suddenly the chair was featured in catalogues and showrooms all over the world. Bidding wars ensued about which shop was going to sell the chair, and auctioneers ran out of breath taking offers from multiple designers. The chair is now available to the public, to those who respect its unique look, of course. The moral of the story is beauty is in the eye of the beholder, but also, don't be a jerk to someone just because they look different than you.</Text>
  <Text Key="81FFDC4D">Rags to Riches Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="30C10A58">Enjoy this stylish chaise's options of armless, double-armed, left armed, right armed, or even nestled into your sectional sofa. No living space is complete without the tender touch of the Tough and Tufted Chaise Lounge.</Text>
  <Text Key="4B28A8D7">Tough and Tufted Chaise Lounge</Text>
  <Text Key="1B4ADE4E">Stretch out your weary legs at the end of the day on this masterful chaise that looks just as fine at the end of your sofa as it does on its own.</Text>
  <Text Key="29922971">A Lounge Evolved: The Sectional Chaise</Text>
  <Text Key="2AEACA84">Yet another piece of furniture without arms? Have we lost our minds? Nope, we're just embracing minimalism. You should try it! This sleek bench is great for anyone who has visitors they want to impress, but not the kind of visitors they want getting &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; comfortable in their living room.</Text>
  <Text Key="A75CF44B">Superficially Social Sitting Bench</Text>
  <Text Key="EDB2BBBB">This may not look like the traditional loveseat since it's got no arms, but neither does the Venus de Milo and she's doing quite well for herself. So, cuddle up to that special Sim-one and enjoy! You may not be able to rest your arms anywhere, but you'll find things to do with them.</Text>
  <Text Key="1747C01A">Special Sim-One Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="BC4C886A">The sky is the limit when it comes to configuration options for the Tough and Tufted. Dare to leverage the full suite of seating shapes this stylish sectional has to offer and you surely won't regret it.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA9C1CF5">Tough and Tufted Sectional Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="BDFF377B">More than a loveseat, more than a sofa. A Couch Evolved Sectional can be twisted, turned, capped, cornered, and extended to suit any home's comfort needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="1A005DDA">A Couch Evolved: The Sectional Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="2AF09D04">According to the largest community for interior decorating, Residence Remedy, this large swoopy-back couch is all the rage to become the hottest trend. It's got it all. Squishy, butt-supporting cushions, carefully placed pillows and of course, that elegant swoop-back. Swoop swoop!</Text>
  <Text Key="79A8E3CB">Swoopy Backed Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="8D7C0B88">If fire isn't your thing or if you would like to benefit from safe and renewable power sources, look no further than the Induct'o'Matic! This stylish induction stove will cook any meal you throw at it with only low chances of burning down the house.</Text>
  <Text Key="19A8F327">Induct'o'Matic</Text>
  <Text Key="B2AD712A">It has been said that the key to some cuisines is firepower. We're not big on ancient philosophy but here at Blazin' Ladles we believe in a good, steady flame to warm your heart and your stomach. Whether you're just sauteeing some veggies or stir-frying up a gourmet storm - look no further than this modern take on an old classic.</Text>
  <Text Key="BB21A1B5">Modern Gas Stove By Blazin' Ladles</Text>
  <Text Key="2F7E9D10">Got me a coffee table\nAnd set it afloat as it looks like a boat\nAnd sailed it home\n\nFound me a cofee table\nAnd I made it my own\n\nGot me a coffee table\nThat is amazing to care for\nFor my tchotchkes and trinkets\nFor my perfect home</Text>
  <Text Key="88A2C23F">"It looks like a Boat" Coffee Table</Text>
  <Text Key="FB84478A">Perfectly sided surface for all your knick knacks and things you don't want your visitors to touch! Equitative sides to make things even so none of your items fight for their space, it all fits! This is quite the magnificent square.</Text>
  <Text Key="62DE1F95">It's Good To Be Square - Coffee Table</Text>
  <Text Key="DF8A133D">The perfect partner to a sectional sofa, The Acute Coffee Table by Be Modular can be snapped into any configuration to match whatever wild shape your sectional takes.</Text>
  <Text Key="F2C2DFA8">The Acute Coffee Table by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="0720F4C1">As a rather social coffee table, this little sweetie loves to be paired up with other Be Modular furnishings like desks, floor shelves, or even other coffee tables! Go ahead, find creative ways to make this little lovie happy.</Text>
  <Text Key="B24DDCF4">The Rounded Coffee Table by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="59D78E67">A six legged table?! Unconventional? Yes, but sturdy? Definitely! I mean it works for ants and an ant can lift 5,000 times its own body weight. We're not saying you should start stacking 5,000 of these tables on top of this table, but if you're looking for a place to put that rock solid fruitcake, this will do.</Text>
  <Text Key="7BCE049E">Rock Steady Six-Legged Table</Text>
  <Text Key="AE6F074A">Centuries ago after the great table wars, society found themselves with a shortage of tables since so many were lost in battle. A local fisherman who had only built boats before volunteered to craft one for his seaside village, but as he had no experience building tables, he wasn't quite sure how to attach individual table legs. Instead, he constructed the supports the same way he would have built a boat rudder. Thankfully it worked, and people were once again able to eat dinner on a table rather than a plank of wood they stretched across their laps. Whew!</Text>
  <Text Key="EFE9AB55">Tabley McTableface the Table</Text>
  <Text Key="AF171F00">Centuries ago during the great table wars, Cuthbert B. Table the 4th led all circular end tables to victory against the square end tables. The road was long and some tables came out looking quite shabby on the other side - lack of varnish, missing legs, chipped surfaces and water stains from lack of coaster usage, but it was all worth it. As a tribute to his legacy, please use this replica of Cuthbert B. Table with pride. They don't teach this sort of thing in schools or the internet, but now you know the true history.</Text>
  <Text Key="55CCB7CF">Cuthbert B. Table</Text>
  <Text Key="406135CB">Calling all enjoyers of muffins, scones, and flakey croissants! Presenting: the Crumbcatcher. With built-in crumb-catching technology, this little end table is perfect for those times when you've just eaten a large platter of granola bars, got up off the couch, reached for the remote only to have a cascade of crumbs follow you in your wake. Instead of hitting the floor, this little table collects them for you, making cleanup easy. It only works on two sides though, so... take note and plan your crumb dusting accordingly. Maybe some day science can figure out how to make it work on all sides of the table, but we're just not there yet.</Text>
  <Text Key="09CA784A">The Crumbcatcher End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="4378E668">This precious piece is as perfect at the end of your sofa as it is nestled next to you in bed. At just the right quaint size to fit nearly everywhere coupled with its agressive matchable quality to other Acute items the Be Modular line, we dare you to not overuse this piece.\n\nThis end table can be attached to other floor-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="D35DB587">The Simply Squared End Table by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="BC6293BE">This delightfully emotive coffee table embodies the wonderment we feel at Be Modular when we see our modular furnishings pushed to their glorious organizational extremes.\n\nAwestruck Erik can be attached to other floor-placed items in the Be Modular line.\n\nWe're confident you'll properly shock him.</Text>
  <Text Key="E8FFA041">Awestruck Erik by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="DB0C5360">The designer of this table couldn't decide whether or not to make the table a classic square shape or a softer, more modern circular shape. In the end, indecisiveness won so we present to you the Squircle table. It's a square, but with rounded edges! We think it's quite catchy. Squircles will be everywhere this spring so jump on the bandwagon while you can!</Text>
  <Text Key="79B128AF">The Squircle Hallway Table</Text>
  <Text Key="8A23F870">This tent will not protect your children from the dangers of the wild, but it will unlock the wilds of their imagination!</Text>
  <Text Key="AE669F1F">Fantastical Play Tent</Text>
  <Text Key="6C674C34">This TV stand is unconventional in the best way. It's made from solid oak so it won't fall apart during your favorite show, which, if you think about it, is really all you can ask from a good TV stand.\n\nThis TV stand can be attached to other floor-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="3045C79B">The Acute Floor TV Stand by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="B6AAB69A">All in all, a great smooth-cornered TV stand.\n\nThis TV stand can be attached to other floor-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="005C4CC5">The Rounded Floor TV Stand by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="33F5CF8F">Elevate not only your TV-watching experience, but also your entire entertainment center.\n\nThis wall-mounted TV stand can be attached to any other wall-placed items in the Be Modular line.</Text>
  <Text Key="F91B6856">The Acute Wall Mounted TV Stand by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="18D2FDF3">And it goes without saying, being part of the Be Modular line and all, it's just begging to be turned into some crazy boss entertainment center with the help of some additional Be Modular wall shelving. Are you ready? Because we are. Ready, that is. For a boss entertainment center. Bring it.</Text>
  <Text Key="8E029822">The Rounded Wall Mounted TV Stand by Be Modular</Text>
  <Text Key="82682D9D">Call Clients to Lot </Text>
  <Text Key="2ACE4F9C">Take Before Photos, enter Build Mode and modify the Lot, and take After Photos before calling Clients back.</Text>
  <Text Key="D76DB86B">Are you sure you would like to cancel the Decorator Gig?</Text>
  <Text Key="6AEFF73E">Cancel Decorator Gig? </Text>
  <Text Key="F89CE8D7">Cancel Gig</Text>
  <Text Key="7A96C80E">The letter’s contents are indecipherable. {0.SimFirstName} can’t make out what it says.</Text>
  <Text Key="8B900000">{0.SimFirstName},\n\nIf there's a higher power, then they will judge you for what you've done.\n\nWith ingratitude,\nThe {1.String|enHouseholdNamePlural} </Text>
  <Text Key="723BFE08">{0.SimFirstName},\n\nI find myself wondering if you have roommates. If you do, I admire them. It must take a certain strength to live with someone with your design sense. Hah! Imagining the horror that must be your home makes me feel a bit better about my own lot. Anyways, there’s no need to write me back.\n\n{1.String} </Text>
  <Text Key="613A5C1C">Dear {0.SimFirstName},\n\nMay all your toast fall butter-side down.\n\nWishing you the worst,\nThe {1.String|enHouseholdNamePlural}</Text>
  <Text Key="39E57A52">{0.SimFirstName},\n\nPlease consider taking a break from work. Or better yet, a change of profession! After the renovation, we can’t sleep at night thinking that others may fall victim to your designs. It’s really the least you could do.\n\nThanks,\nThe {1.String|enHouseholdNamePlural} </Text>
  <Text Key="DB1BBB22">Dear {0.SimFirstName},\n\nThere was a study about how being in well decorated spaces increases happiness. Well, we can attest to that! We love love LOVE what you did with the place!\n\nBest,\nThe {1.String|enHouseholdNamePlural} </Text>
  <Text Key="1EF301BD">{0.SimFirstName},\n\nI am so lucky that you took the job! Every time I look at my new space, I think of how lucky I am that you were there for me.\n\nSincerely,\n\nThe {1.String|enHouseholdNamePlural}</Text>
  <Text Key="04B8DD4B">Dearest {0.SimFirstName},\n\nI do hope you're well. I'm writing to let you know how much I still love the renovation. Sometimes I catch myself just standing there in awe. You did such a terrific job! We’re all thrilled over here.\n\nSincerely,\nThe {1.String|enHouseholdNamePlural} </Text>
  <Text Key="5040967D">Dear {0.SimFirstName},\n\nI can't believe the work you did! The space just feels that much more inviting and open, and I didn't think it could be done. Kudos to you and wishing you more projects in the future!\n\nWith gratitude,\nThe {1.String|enHouseholdNamePlural}</Text>
  <Text Key="0B915051">This is not addressed to {0.SimFirstName}. </Text>
  <Text Key="6781C2D7">Open Letter</Text>
  <Text Key="0FF00EFB">Open Package</Text>
  <Text Key="77F0EA73">Travel to Client's Lot</Text>
  <Text Key="3C220EA2">Go to Front Door</Text>
  <Text Key="CC17F561">Inspect {1.ObjectName}</Text>
  <Text Key="6D6723E6">Are you sure you want to send the Client away? You won't be able to discover any more of the Client's Likes or Dislikes once they leave. </Text>
  <Text Key="1F10DBC0">Send Client Away </Text>
  <Text Key="86C04573">Send Client Away</Text>
  <Text Key="97A2D14E">Check This Out</Text>
  <Text Key="DEE7ACFB">Check on Client</Text>
  <Text Key="0E8311ED">Reveal Renovations to Client</Text>
  <Text Key="89FD9C22">Are you sure you want to delete these photos? You cannot recover them if you do.</Text>
  <Text Key="CDC2743C">Delete Photos?</Text>
  <Text Key="5E156E03">The response to {0.SimFirstName}'s article is good! The top comment reads: &lt;i&gt;“{0.SimLastName} did all that? &lt;b&gt;PLEASE&lt;/b&gt; I need this kind of upgrade in my life! Do you think {M0.he}{F0.she} will accept a shout out as payment? I have &lt;b&gt;A LOT&lt;/b&gt; of followers on Simstagram."&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="C00EBE46">{0.SimFirstName}'s article wasn't received well. That's… discouraging.</Text>
  <Text Key="C59C19FF">The response to {0.SimFirstName}'s article is good! The top comment reads: “I heard about {M0.him}{F0.her} from the {2.String|enHouseholdNamePlural}. Apparently {M0.he}{F0.she} does a first-rate job!"</Text>
  <Text Key="34D0670E">The response to {0.SimFirstName}'s article is good! The top comment reads: &lt;i&gt;“WOW! This gave me so many ideas... I wonder how much of this I can DIY.”&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="970358A8">{0.SimFirstName}'s article was received surprisingly well, considering {M0.his}{F0.her} current track record. </Text>
  <Text Key="78BD1197">{0.SimFirstName}'s article got pretty good reception! Seeing it out there now is encouraging, to say the least. </Text>
  <Text Key="35E8E5C5">{0.SimFirstName}'s article got outstanding responses! {M0.He}{F0.She} is humbled by all the praise and surprised by the outpour of love.</Text>
  <Text Key="C5107A53">The response to {0.SimFirstName}'s article is great! The top comment reads: &lt;i&gt;“That one reno you did for the {2.String|enHouseholdNamePlural} is literally my ♥ DREAM ♥ I'm trying to convince them to let me check it out in person, but no luck yet...”&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="3D88CC7E">{0.SimFirstName}'s article wasn't received well. The top comment reads: &lt;i&gt;“I must be getting old, because I don’t get it. When I was young, a house looked like a house. A kitchen looked like a kitchen. A bedroom looked like a bedroom. You get the picture. Anyways, I have no idea what this is supposed to be."&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="9C754CDA">{0.SimFirstName}'s article was not received well. The top comment reads: &lt;i&gt;“Did you really think we would ignore what you did to the {2.String|enHouseholdNamePlural}? Please.”&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="62CBEC6F">{0.SimFirstName}'s article was not received well. The top comment reads: "Aren't you the one who ruined the {2.String|enHouseholdNamePlural}’ life? You couldn’t pay me to hire you." </Text>
  <Text Key="60F1BECA">The response to {0.SimFirstName}'s article is great! The top comment reads: &lt;i&gt;“&lt;b&gt;YOU DONT UNDERSTAND&lt;/b&gt; I am obsessed with these design ideas ♥♥♥”&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="C504B3F2">{0.SimFirstName}'s article wasn't received well. The top comment reads: &lt;i&gt;“I’m crying, was that supposed to be someone's actual room? Like, someone has to LIVE like that? On what planet??”&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="3E89E6FD">The response to {0.SimFirstName}'s article is great! The top comment reads: “Ughhh I love this but it’s hard seeing other people live your dreams. I’m so jealous of the {2.String|enHouseholdNamePlural}’ new place.” </Text>
  <Text Key="94C88E95">{0.SimFirstName}'s article didn't gain any traction. Maybe it’s time to brush up on {M0.his}{F0.her} writing skill or even *gasp* do better at work!</Text>
  <Text Key="F2B1FD74">Write Interior Decorator Article</Text>
  <Text Key="A053C099">After</Text>
  <Text Key="BEBE1178">Before</Text>
  <Text Key="DED313CA">Room Renovations</Text>
  <Text Key="469103B4">Level Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="1EDB80D8">Level Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="67AF8094">Room Addition</Text>
  <Text Key="26C5E79C">Select Gig</Text>
  <Text Key="DF4FBA69">Add 1 Unprofessional Action (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="FBFF94A8">Schedule any negative client call (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="19053584">Schedule any positive client call (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="BBC4B11D">Create Client Letter in Inventory (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="61D69B41">Create Sponsor Package in Inventory (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="5E481F03">Someone in this household is already going to be featured on TV. (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="4C72307E">Schedule Negative TV Show Call (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="C47BB43A">Schedule Positive TV Show Call (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="554DF110">Learn All Gig Preferences (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="3764D2AE">{0.SimFirstName} needs this during the gig.</Text>
  <Text Key="4699A9FC">Throw Away</Text>
  <Text Key="2D6016F7">{1.SimFirstName} has already given a verdict.</Text>
  <Text Key="FAEA98C6">{1.SimFirstName} is still looking around. Once ready, an indicator will appear above {1.SimFirstName}'s head.</Text>
  <Text Key="58EB19FF">Reveal: It's Bad (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="2BE401EF">Reveal: It's Good (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="23047D1A">Reveal: It's Ok (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="957B3F1E">Reveal: Do Final Reaction (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="E9C95766">It's too scary to use the tent right now!</Text>
  <Text Key="43AB8F11">(From Playing Make Believe in the Tent)</Text>
  <Text Key="F4DFDC76">Make Believe</Text>
  <Text Key="7D04AE1D">Nap</Text>
  <Text Key="C3928584">Play Inside</Text>
  <Text Key="546608D4">(From Being Scared by a pretend Monster)</Text>
  <Text Key="44A5BCB2">The kids are too scared to play Monster right now.</Text>
  <Text Key="8E34F518">Play as Monster</Text>
  <Text Key="0130B038">Play With</Text>
  <Text Key="F60AA003">Scared By Monster</Text>
  <Text Key="09FB4ECE">(From Sleeping)</Text>
  <Text Key="D9E0E2BD">Sleep</Text>
  <Text Key="6DF83D75">Discuss Latest Trends</Text>
  <Text Key="10D5F19C">Suggest Bold Home Makeover Ideas</Text>
  <Text Key="1DEF243D">Select Photos for the Reveal</Text>
  <Text Key="8A89AE5B">Too many After Photos selected.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F547E2F">Select Photos to Delete</Text>
  <Text Key="A892BC78">Manage Current Gig Photos</Text>
  <Text Key="41906904">{0.SimFirstName} should focus on the client right now. </Text>
  <Text Key="C9580591">Choose one before photo for each after photo.</Text>
  <Text Key="9AB18DA9">Not enough After Photos selected. </Text>
  <Text Key="CA7CB427">Too many after photos selected.</Text>
  <Text Key="E24B2440">Not enough Before Photos selected.</Text>
  <Text Key="0AA58FBC">Too many before photos selected.</Text>
  <Text Key="D1910833">Preview Montage with Current Gig Photos (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="CB20643F">Too many Before Photos selected.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0CEA512">Select Before and After Photos</Text>
  <Text Key="1A67C72D">Take After Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="E1F6BFBC">You must renovate in Build Mode before taking an After Photo.</Text>
  <Text Key="C4315E62">Take Before Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="50A006DA">Take "Before" Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="C4CDA9E8">Do you want to personally show off the renovated space to the Clients?</Text>
  <Text Key="54E98656">Host Reveal Event?</Text>
  <Text Key="DEFAAAB0">Meet up with Client</Text>
  <Text Key="5B2C293C">(From Liking the Décor)</Text>
  <Text Key="D55C2A1C">(From Disliking The Décor)</Text>
  <Text Key="8E54ED7B">Ask About Favorite Designs</Text>
  <Text Key="21A816F7">Ask to See Simterest Board </Text>
  <Text Key="AAFA44AA">Ask to See Mood Board</Text>
  <Text Key="F6649830">Ask to See Inspirations</Text>
  <Text Key="8CC26942">Discuss Décor Trends </Text>
  <Text Key="7F673A3E">Discuss Designs</Text>
  <Text Key="68DEF2A3">Sorry, but I can't trust you with this job. I thought I hired a professional! </Text>
  <Text Key="31133AEA">Talk about Previous Projects </Text>
  <Text Key="BD881855">Show Portfolio</Text>
  <Text Key="44351E2C">Suggest Different Color</Text>
  <Text Key="05C0B78E">Suggest Different Décor Style</Text>
  <Text Key="371C1291">It might not be what was asked for, but I like it! Definitely appreciate the effort!</Text>
  <Text Key="5C2D0FBF">I guess you did a good job… it's just not my taste. Technically, all the boxes were checked… just not feeling it.</Text>
  <Text Key="23799941">Ask for Final Verdict</Text>
  <Text Key="C2F409AC">Look, I appreciate what you’ve done here… but you’ve overstayed your welcome.
</Text>
  <Text Key="10EA4B15">You’ve done enough. Please see yourself out. Now how do we undo some of this...</Text>
  <Text Key="7D02C8C5">Love what you did with the place, but I’m going to have to ask you to leave now.</Text>
  <Text Key="DBF43778">I can’t take it anymore! GET OUT!! </Text>
  <Text Key="24E07988">Guide Client</Text>
  <Text Key="49555B3F">Recount {2.String|xxUpper} Renovation</Text>
  <Text Key="0B4472A0">Enthuse about Design Vision</Text>
  <Text Key="B9B4463D">Promise Successful Renovation </Text>
  <Text Key="625D7AD1">Thank for Opportunity </Text>
  <Text Key="C5766BDB">Ask about taste in Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="55DE78AC">Complain about Restrictive Budget</Text>
  <Text Key="01D46913">Insult Taste in Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="63BEA8FF">Dream Home Decorator Channel shows can give your Sims ideas! Don't miss out!</Text>
  <Text Key="474E4EED">Watch Dream Home Decorator Network</Text>
  <Text Key="7ED2C9EF">Watch &lt;i&gt;Failures 'N' Flops&lt;/i&gt; on Dream Home Decorator Network</Text>
  <Text Key="4697A19C">Watch &lt;i&gt;Ace of Space&lt;/i&gt; on Dream Home Decorator </Text>
  <Text Key="79B3D568">Clean Lines for Cleanliness</Text>
  <Text Key="80D733C6">Sleep Styled</Text>
  <Text Key="203F7959">All-in-One Personal Space</Text>
  <Text Key="011BC482">Imagination Space</Text>
  <Text Key="3F73B216">Sleep 'N' Study</Text>
  <Text Key="3C265B9A">Demure Dining</Text>
  <Text Key="D39F1913">Space Saving Kitchen</Text>
  <Text Key="09DCA62C">Centric Kitchen Space</Text>
  <Text Key="9FBBB163">Premier Space</Text>
  <Text Key="1843E97C">Entertainment Living</Text>
  <Text Key="DC53C263">Offline Relaxation</Text>
  <Text Key="AACC4CC7">Professional Design Consultory</Text>
  <Text Key="71FC6A76">Spectacular Study</Text>
  <Text Key="1426393C">Walk-In Closet Goals</Text>
  <Text Key="92E4607A">Personalized Dressing Room</Text>
  <Text Key="AC3B1FFE">Dressed Up Den</Text>
  <Text Key="B6616DCA">Don't Throw Out Those Tchotchkes!</Text>
  <Text Key="1B0365DA">Elevated Living on a Budget</Text>
  <Text Key="CA214A68">My Space: A Look into the Mind (and Home) of an Interior Decorator</Text>
  <Text Key="C87B65AE">This is an Interior Design book.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE102351">To Décor or Not to Décor: The Definitive Decoration Guide</Text>
  <Text Key="3DE19BB5">This contains copies of {0.SimFirstName}'s before and after photos for the Interior Decorator Career. Use it to manage photos taken during a Gig.</Text>
  <Text Key="BF532526">Watch Dream Home Decorator</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE48C67">Dream Home Decorator</Text>
  <Text Key="E3C20A53">Kids these days just end up cramming for tests or staying up in the wee hours of the night studying. How convenient, then, is having your study desk right below your bed? This Bunk Bed/Desk combo makes studying so much more efficient and space saving!</Text>
  <Text Key="35D21202">Naturally Nestled Bunk Desk Combo</Text>
  <Text Key="0073A829">Sometimes dreams are hard to remember. You have them, they make you all emotional, but then you forget them. Well, fix that as soon as possible by writing those dreams down! Just wake from your slumber and mosey on to your desk, right below your bed. This Bunk Bed/Desk combo makes it so easy to remember your dreams, that you'll sleep easy remembering every little detail!</Text>
  <Text Key="723E550C">Smooth Slumber Bunk Desk Combo</Text>
  <Text Key="95DC3A0E">When you absolutely need three Sims to sleep in the same space, take this combination of bunk bed and double bed to maximize energy recovery!</Text>
  <Text Key="CE175731">Serene Repose Bunk Double Bed Combo</Text>
  <Text Key="57656933">Yes, you probably sleep IN your clothes. But have you slept on top of our clothes? Well you can now, with this bunk bed/dresser combo! Rest assured that your clothes are kept nicely tucked away underneath your top bunk bed.</Text>
  <Text Key="580CA462">Serene Repose Bunk Dresser Combo</Text>
  <Text Key="47928256">Take a seat. Take a nap. Take a seat. Take a nap. Lazily lounge around with your choice of posture with this living chair/bunk bed combo.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E4A7109">Too Cool For School Bunk Living Chair Combo</Text>
  <Text Key="0FE41390">Visit Client's Lot </Text>
  <Text Key="F671E60D">Visit the Client's Lot during Gig Hours to Decorate.</Text>
  <Text Key="2145C78C">Get to Know the Client (Optional)</Text>
  <Text Key="08C3DDE9">Learn the client's likes, dislikes, and most importantly, their preferences for this gig! Click on client Sims to perform Interior Decorator socials, or click on objects to Inspect them.</Text>
  <Text Key="95FE2AB7">Take Before Photos</Text>
  <Text Key="EDD7E238">Document the renovation process by taking Before Photos. Click on your Sim, phone, cameras, or the ground to "Take Before Photo."</Text>
  <Text Key="D3923A56">Enter Build Mode and Make Renovations</Text>
  <Text Key="D455E6AF">Once you have Sent the Clients Away, open Build Mode to start making changes to the Client's Lot based on the Gig Type.</Text>
  <Text Key="504C216D">Take After Photos</Text>
  <Text Key="3E7EDB62">Document the renovation process by taking After Photos. Click on your Sim, phone, cameras, or the ground to "Take After Photo."</Text>
  <Text Key="A98982F1">After decorating the space to fit the Client Sim's Preferences, Click on the Decorator Sim, use the Phone or use the Relationship Panel to Call the Clients back to the Lot.</Text>
  <Text Key="188C5A0B">Reveal Newly Decorated Space to the Client </Text>
  <Text Key="DD545CA1">Interior Decorator</Text>
  <Text Key="3A1DEBC1">Interior Decorator Debug</Text>
  <Text Key="616D44B9">Interior Design</Text>
  <Text Key="6E75E675">From Bauhaus to wainscoting, share your know-how with the world.</Text>
  <Text Key="92B3B50B">Client </Text>
  <Text Key="7B72BABD">{1.SimFirstName} sure knows what {M1.he}{F1.she} is doing when it comes to interior decorating! The remodeling job that {M1.he}{F1.she} did for {0.SimFirstName} was outstanding. </Text>
  <Text Key="BD23D535">Happy with Decorator Home</Text>
  <Text Key="EB0FD478">{1.SimFirstName} came in and destroyed {0.SimFirstName}'s home! {0.SimFirstName} may have a hard time keeping calm around {1.SimFirstName} for a while. </Text>
  <Text Key="432C8D72">Furious over a Interior Decoration Gig gone bad</Text>
  <Text Key="A6CF8DA2">You can now Discuss Latest Trends.</Text>
  <Text Key="74E67571">You can now Write Interior Decorator Article on computers.</Text>
  <Text Key="04608D47">You can now Suggest Bold Home Makeover Ideas.</Text>
  <Text Key="60F7AAA0">Find out about the Client's preferences, then send the Client away to start decorating.</Text>
  <Text Key="4CF78C22">The Reveal! </Text>
  <Text Key="8373908A">It's time to celebrate and unveil the new space! You can end the Reveal at anytime, but remember your deadline. The Client will wrap things up when the gig ends or after they've shared their Final Verdict.</Text>
  <Text Key="B9BAB3AE">Visit Past Client</Text>
  <Text Key="F08E9166">Enjoying a visit with past Clients. </Text>
  <Text Key="74358734">Ask Client for their Final Verdict</Text>
  <Text Key="B1227E44">Click on Client sims to Ask for Final Verdict. Clients will let you know when they're ready.</Text>
  <Text Key="7BCE7631">Chat with Clients</Text>
  <Text Key="3AE98EC0">Reveal Renovated Space!</Text>
  <Text Key="6008CCFF">Show Off Objects</Text>
  <Text Key="01C1D6DF">Client</Text>
  <Text Key="22B5EFA4">A followup client call is already scheduled for this sim. (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="D2071858">The tent has no Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="46F557CD">The tent is fully occupied</Text>
  <Text Key="78E760C7">(From Seeing Client Reactions) </Text>
  <Text Key="CD12FF1D">Interior Decorator</Text>
  <Text Key="3E6ED863">Interior Decorator</Text>
  <Text Key="E37CB633">Dislikes Basics Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="37DC40E9">Dislikes Basics Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="69F46700">Dislikes Boho Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="4ED0C388">Dislikes Boho Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="2F9E62EB">Dislikes Contemporary Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="4635E581">Dislikes Contemporary Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="5939BFCA">Dislikes Cosmolux Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="A0090A5A">Dislikes Cosmolux Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="F65A0B3A">Dislikes French Country Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="5FBF30EA">Dislikes French Country Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="796D5549">Dislikes Garden Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="782094E7">Dislikes Garden Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="E80A78DE">Dislikes Gothic Farmhouse Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="D0CA2FC6">Dislikes Gothic Farmhouse Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="3A007CFD">Dislikes Island Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="47EC29C3">Dislikes Island Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="63ADD8EA">Dislikes Mission Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="605E837A">Dislikes Mission Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="57F3484F">Dislikes Modern Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="1EA0BECD">Dislikes Modern Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="58A4880B">Dislikes Patio Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="72F4D1A1">Dislikes Patio Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="B8FAEAC0">Dislikes Queen Anne Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="09422848">Dislikes Queen Anne Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="4846E5B8">Dislikes Mid Century Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="F1A85C60">Dislikes Mid Century Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="5C02D581">Dislikes Suburban Contempo Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="22478E9F">Dislikes Suburban Contempo Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="7FFA5A70">Dislikes Storybook Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="0F2B0858">Dislikes Storybook Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="E322E9F7">Likes Basics Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="FA2FABD5">Likes Basics Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="238A58CA">Basics Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="0AAAED44">Likes Boho Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="FCD4CD54">Likes Boho Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="68B1C26B">Boho Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="BE34708F">Likes Contemporary Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="1C8AE20D">Likes Contemporary Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="11366992">Contemporary Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="203E5C36">Likes Cosmolux Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="2241E01E">Likes Cosmolux Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="DC62A689">Cosmolux Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="BD950F3E">Likes French Country Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="91AB4226">Likes French Country Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="B0B2EC61">French Country Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="4924395D">Likes Garden Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="B4C033A3">Likes Garden Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="0DD82B8C">Garden Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="3E14B5BA">Likes Gothic Farmhouse Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="7F944C6A">Likes Gothic Farmhouse Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="2E7BE415">Gothic Farmhouse Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="AD75A989">Likes Island Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="4F796E27">Likes Island Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="565A0210">Island Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="0843BFAE">Likes Mission Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="73BD6B36">Likes Mission Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="951B4531">Mission Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="24D1329B">Likes Modern Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="61601151">Likes Modern Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="D53C04E6">Modern Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="3ECD9FD7">Likes Patio Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="2826BBB5">Likes Patio Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="F0381BAA">Patio Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="E1091154">Likes Queen Anne Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="509F44C4">Likes Queen Anne Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="623D671B">Queen Anne Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="A92FE0A4">Likes Mid Century Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="BE55DD34">Likes Mid Century Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="1B54C04B">Mid Century Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="85875F5D">Likes Suburban Contempo Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="41E4B5A3">Likes Suburban Contempo Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="56E81D8C">Suburban Contemporary Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="85523D5C">Likes Storybook Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="BCEE0C8C">Likes Storybook Decor</Text>
  <Text Key="24959113">Storybook Décor</Text>
  <Text Key="2F254B82">Getting to know the Client can make the difference between a decent renovation and a great one. Sims can have many different Likes and Dislikes, but they’ll focus on a few preferences for a gig. More experienced Interior Decorators can learn preferences quickly and suggest different colors or décor. If you’re not feeling chatty, you can send the Client away and get right to work.</Text>
  <Text Key="62896E5F">Each successful gig brings you closer to the top! Gain experience to access a wider variety of gigs. Interior Decorators not only need to manage their Career Performance (just like other Careers), but also their Professional Reputation. Professional Reputation can open the door to even more opportunities, whether that’s a second chance from a disgruntled Client or attention from the Dream Home Decorator Network.</Text>
  <Text Key="93729382">Enter Build Mode to start making renovations. The Gig Information Panel displays the Client’s budget, preferences, and any requirements or restrictions. You can click on discovered preferences to quickly see relevant objects.</Text>
  <Text Key="F9E1772F">Once you’re happy with the renovations, it’s time to call the Client back. You’ll be prompted to select the photos you want to showcase and decide how to handle the Reveal. You can either host the Reveal personally or leave it to the Client to check out on their own time.</Text>
  <Text Key="8B7E0FDA">You’ll need to document the renovation process by taking Before and After Photos. You can take photos from your phone, camera, or by clicking on the ground where you want to take the shot. Check out the Taking The Perfect Decorator Picture Lesson to learn more.</Text>
  <Text Key="B454A018">When it's time to start a gig, you’ll be prompted to make a choice. You can either send Sims off by themselves or you can go with them. If you choose to go with them, you will travel to meet the Client at the lot in need of renovation. Once there, you can direct your Sim through the renovation process by following the Gig Tasks in the Career Panel.</Text>
  <Text Key="06158D38">Some gigs require you to add an entire room or level. With these gigs, you can only add objects to the added tiles. For renovation gigs, you can add objects anywhere, but can't move the existing walls or floors. </Text>
  <Text Key="699C431A">Tired of your neighbors' terrible décor? Wish you could share your impeccable taste with the world? Then it’s time to join the Interior Decorator Career! Interior Decorators bring their Client’s renovation dreams to life one gig at a time. Once you join the Career, use the Career Panel to Look for Gigs.</Text>
  <Text Key="12E9288B">Hosting the Reveal lets you show off the new space and see how the Client really feels. After looking around, Clients will be ready to share their Final Verdict. Everyone wants to be heard, and even an upset Client will appreciate the effort.</Text>
  <Text Key="2866FEF3">Interior Decorator Career</Text>
  <Text Key="58E72BE1">The first item placed is the “parent” of the object chain. Every subsequent piece of shelving or furniture that you place is a “child” of that parent object.\n\nDetach single pieces of furnishings or entire groups by trailing down the chain to see the portion of the family you’re detaching based on what’s highlighted.</Text>
  <Text Key="DE30554A">You will see an almost magnetic attachment the Modular Shelving pieces have to each other as you place them next to each other. Listen for a subtle little audio cue to confirm when items have been successfully slotted or un-slotted.\n\nMove the entire group by clicking and dragging the parent object. Whatever piece in the family you hover over, the parent will always have a gentle pulse highlight to keep you grounded.</Text>
  <Text Key="324E81F9">Modular Shelving is a collection of curated furniture pieces that can be snapped together to customize and create more unique and creative storage options than ever before.\n\nTo narrow down the specific set of items that can mix and match with each other, simply type the key word “Modular” into the Build catalog’s Search field and hit Enter. </Text>
  <Text Key="A7963C93">The Sims 4 team at large encourages you to please make the most extravagant entertainment centers you can imagine, plaster your soulmate’s name on your living room walls with small cubbies, and in general please just have fun with Modular Shelving.</Text>
  <Text Key="DB850A3F">There you will find a classy and sassy array of not just wall shelving, but also a small set of floor-placed furniture that are compatible snapping partners.\n\nFloor-placed furniture can only attach to other floor-placed furniture options and wall-placed furniture can only attach to other wall-placed furniture items.\n\nThis functionality is not just limited to shelving, but also includes some specific TV Stands, Dressers, Bookshelves, End Tables, and Coffee Tables. And don’t forget the Wall-Hanging clothing shelves for the most extravagant walk-in closets!</Text>
  <Text Key="8AD7030C">Modular Shelving</Text>
  <Text Key="1279B998">While taking pictures:\n\nUse the W, A, S and D keys to move forward, left, backward, and right.\nUse the Q and E keys to move the camera up and down.\nUse the Scroll Wheel to zoom in and out.\nLeft Click to switch control between moving the mouse and the camera.</Text>
  <Text Key="272952BA">The photos you take will be in your Sim’s Inventory just like when you take a normal photo. These are your photos to do whatever you want with. The Memory Card in your Sim’s Inventory saves the photos for the Client. You can view and manage the Client copies from the Memory Card or a computer. If you ever lose the Memory Card, a new one will be given to your Sim at the start of a gig.</Text>
  <Text Key="ABCACE51">Sims can take Before and After Photos from the phone or a camera. You can also click on the ground where you want to take the picture. Once you’re looking through the viewfinder, it’s time to get that perfect shot.</Text>
  <Text Key="D5DFDB53">During an Interior Decorator Career Gig, Sims can take photos to document the space before and after renovations. Whether it’s due to a slight fisheye or trade secrets, taking photos is a little different when your Sim is on the job.</Text>
  <Text Key="093F2FE9">Taking The Perfect Decorator Picture</Text>
  <Text Key="04462367">Trilateral Ornamentations</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>