<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="23332B75">Thrills minus the frills! This simple, sturdy double bed complements any loft space and lets people know you were once an art major who took a welding class one semester. Fun fact: never weld galvanized steel, but if you have to, some welders advise drinking milk before and after so you don't get "metal fume fever". Science, or old wives tale? Either way, this bed turned out great.</Text>
  <Text Key="9CF5A610">"I Took a Welding Class Once" Double Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="059669F7">Understated statement pieces at their finest! These lovely wall vignettes come pre-distressed so it looks like you've put in the effort, but aren't trying &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; hard.</Text>
  <Text Key="77204A4E">Subtle Expressions Wall Vignettes</Text>
  <Text Key="FEA4D76A">Made of reclaimed iron, this behemoth of a double door is pulling double duty! Functioning as both doors and windows, it makes for a great statement piece in any loft or space in need of a light, airy feel. A gridded layout ensures minimal bird splattage.</Text>
  <Text Key="4C45D9F5">Phoenix Ironworks Double Door</Text>
  <Text Key="B49CA68A">Knock knock! Who's there? Why it's isolation and solitude! Keep out a variety of undesirables with this massive double sliding door! Say goodbye to solicitors, nosy neighbors, and concerned friends with state-of-the-art sliding door technology. So long, social life.</Text>
  <Text Key="11AB0C95">Anti-Social Sliding Double Door</Text>
  <Text Key="D0344BFC">&lt;i&gt;Lost and Furniture&lt;/i&gt; strikes again! We spend our time sifting through secondhand stores for first-rate treasures so you don't have to. This beautiful armoire-style dresser was discovered in an alley in San Myshuno. It was in need of some TLC but the structure of it was too good to pass up. There is even some speculation from our appraiser that it was originally designed by La Vatea Inc. -- one of the most upscale furniture manufacturers there is! Finders keepers!</Text>
  <Text Key="DA25E353">Finders Keepers Dresser </Text>
  <Text Key="D57A2BAA">This lighting does exactly what it's supposed to do: emits brilliant light while holding stationary to the ceiling on a metal track. However, this particular set of track lighting has a dark past. Once the star lighting fixture at Foxbury Institute, after being replaced, this track lighting didn't know what to do with itself.\nDimmed and forgotten about, it turned to unsavory activities such as loitering around trash bins and flashing passersby with high beams. After being a nuisance to society for years, it was picked up by an art student who recently moved to a loft in the city. Now, its purpose has been restored and it's back to brightening lives.</Text>
  <Text Key="45BDC935">Back-On-Track Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="6A3E4B7F">This lighting does exactly what it's supposed to do: emits brilliant light while holding stationary to the ceiling on a metal track. Its parent lighting company, who manufactured it, never had any particular hopes or dreams for it: only that it went to a good home and provided great lighting. Maybe someday it will strive to shine brighter or give up entirely, but for now, it's right on track.</Text>
  <Text Key="DC13B3A6">Right-On-Track Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="13D250E4">This lighting does exactly what it's supposed to do: emits brilliant light while holding stationary to the ceiling on a metal track. However, its parent lighting company, who manufactured it, always wanted it to be in a hospital or a legal firm so it's a little disappointing that it's been "just a home light" thus far. Its parent company loves it anyway though, despite its lack of ambition to shine any brighter.</Text>
  <Text Key="40E5CE2B">Slightly-Off-Track Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="C4B6B58F">What better way to contrast a stark, industrial feel than upping the floof factor! This dried pampas grass sets a warm, inviting tone and makes a great pet substitute as well, so long as no one catches you petting them or dressing them up in little sweaters. Floof!</Text>
  <Text Key="099D3A56">Uptown Floof Pampas Grass</Text>
  <Text Key="B7E1100A">Reclaimed plants? Yes indeedy! Here at Greenie-Go-Round we adopt plants that others have tossed aside and give them a new life... with you! Add some color to your space with this refurbished plantstand, complete with bins and plant-related reading material including &lt;i&gt;Can't Touch This: Guide to Cacti&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Romaine Calm and Garden On&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Ok, Bloomer&lt;/i&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="8D711115">City Roots Plant Stand by Greenie-Go-Round</Text>
  <Text Key="CBCDF82A">This adorable succulent terrarium is the perfect way for you to justify getting "just one more" succulent. Yes, your squishy plant-addled brain is telling you: &lt;i&gt;All you need is one more little friend and your collection will be complete.&lt;/i&gt; And you should listen to it 100%! Okay, so technically this particular succulent is three more succulents, but that's still okay since they're all in one container, right? Right? RIGHT? Of course it's okay. You're a proud plant parent surrounded by your ever-growing brood of cacti warriors who will shower you with love and affection until the day you die. And when that day happens you'll be featured on the news under a scrolling banner of "WORLD'S BIGGEST CACTUS HOARDER FOUND".</Text>
  <Text Key="B7BE86B5">Prickle Your Fancy Succulent Terrarium</Text>
  <Text Key="94774376">As you enter your apartment, you toss your keys and bags on the counter and head to the living room. You plop down on the sofa and turn on the tv, excited for an evening of soap operas and drama. You suddenly feel a soft, relaxing feeling on your feet. Almost like a massage. As you look down, you see your newly bought Super-Fuzzy Fuzz Rug and say "Yeah. I could get used to this".</Text>
  <Text Key="3F8CEFA9">Super-Fuzzy Fuzz Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="DEA57FF6">Ventilation ducts are essential for moving climate-controlled air around your home or for re-enacting scenes from your favorite Hollywood action films.* This particular section of galvanized steel duct is angled for use in corners. *Please do not crawl around in ventilation ducts, throw things from ventilation ducts, or drop out of ventilation ducts wearing a harness.</Text>
  <Text Key="1431FD29">Action-Packed Corner Ventilation Duct</Text>
  <Text Key="22E1FCE9">Ventilation ducts are essential for moving climate-controlled air around your home or for re-enacting scenes from your favorite Hollywood action films.* This particular section of galvanized steel pipe is straight and can be attached to another straight section but is also open to hooking up with a corner or vented version. *Please do not crawl around in ventilation ducts, throw things from ventilation ducts, or drop out of ventilation ducts wearing a harness.</Text>
  <Text Key="C632ACCC">Action-Packed Straight Ventilation Duct</Text>
  <Text Key="08487C6E">Ventilation ducts are essential for moving climate-controlled air around your home or for re-enacting scenes from your favorite Hollywood action films.* This particular section of galvanized steel pipe comes with a built in vent. *Please do not crawl around in ventilation ducts, throw things from ventilation ducts, or drop out of ventilation ducts wearing a harness.</Text>
  <Text Key="E518A911">Action-Packed Vented Ventilation Duct</Text>
  <Text Key="C720A154">There's nothing like the feel of a cool fan on a hot summer night in August when the air is thick and humid... except for maybe a hot summer night in January in the Southern Hemisphere. Whichever hemisphere you're in, this fan will cool you down.</Text>
  <Text Key="63B84D3B">Hot August Nights Fan</Text>
  <Text Key="26E7C3E3">By the time I hit the top step of my second-floor loft, they had been relentlessly chasing me on foot for nearly 5 blocks. I jammed my key in the door. Twisting it to the right, it sprung to life with a mighty roar. I bolted inside slamming the door behind me. Clutching the pipe wheel with both hands, I threw my trusty loft into drive and floored it, leaving them in the dust. As the cool night air rushed through my hair from the open patio door, I thought to myself - “Yeah, this loft handles like a dream. Too bad it’s a pain to park.”</Text>
  <Text Key="DB8AB7B2">Pipe Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="EDC44177">When it comes to anything HVAC, Ray Rays's got your back. In fact, Ray Rays has the largest selection of new and used HVAC parts in the Tri-State area. Like this refurbished Gorbin &amp; Schnitzer 2150 thermostat with revolutionary outdated analog technology. Think of it. None of the convenience at a price you can’t afford. The upside is that what it lacks in practical functionality, it more than makes up for in beautifferousness.</Text>
  <Text Key="10EB38CE">The Art of HVAC – by Ray Rays Recycled</Text>
  <Text Key="185B91AF">If you're a young city-dweller on the go, you realize how important every moment of your day is. The act of sitting down may not seem too time consuming, but think about how frequently we all sit on a daily basis, then multiply that number by days, weeks, months and suddenly those few seconds turn into hours! This barstool significantly cuts that time down. Designed with the perfect posterior-height in mind, instead of wasting precious seconds engaging your leg muscles to sit down, simply back your booty into it and you're done. Think of everything you can do with your newfound time!</Text>
  <Text Key="7C3901F6">Back it Up Barstool</Text>
  <Text Key="8BD03E86">After Johnny Zest was disowned by the Landgraab family he had no possessions nor money to buy furniture, so he had to get resourceful. After taking a quick trip to a Landgraab construction site, he swiped several raw materials including pipes and particle board, and built a surprisingly comfortable chair. Functional, comfortable revenge is the best kind!</Text>
  <Text Key="F0D54519">Johnny Zest's Sweet Revenge Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="6891F5FC">After Johnny Zest was disowned by the Landgraab family he had no possessions nor money to buy furniture so he had to get resourceful. Sure, he could have gone to a thrift shop, but there's no fun in that. Instead, Johnny took a trip to one of his family's construction sites, swiped building supplies and cobbled together a big, squishy sofa which could rival anything bought in a fancy upscale furniture store. Hopefully, he cleaned the pipes before assembling...</Text>
  <Text Key="2A9AC153">Johnny Zest's Sweet Revenge Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="ECC3A87E">What's better than one table? Two tables! This lovely split-level coffee table gives you a large table for all your tabling needs, plus a slightly smaller table on top of that one just in case the first table isn't tabley enough for you. Great for entertaining, especially when you have guests of varying heights.</Text>
  <Text Key="F35E5801">Smalls &amp; Talls Split Level Coffee Table</Text>
  <Text Key="D21FAF40">Bring the joys of bar food into your own space with this exquisitely crafted table - great for snacking with friends or eating an entire plate of sliders and fries alone in your sweatpants. We won't judge!</Text>
  <Text Key="630E2F0F">Casual Eats Table</Text>
  <Text Key="BAACFF81">Crafted from what was once a large flat-filing cabinet, this elegant storage solution is great for keepsakes, knick-knacks, and bric-a-brac. Its organizational compartments paired with its unfinished iron frame say you're responsible, but you still had cold pizza for breakfast this morning.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0564BB4">Organized Entrepreneur Hallway Table</Text>
  <Text Key="714CD985">&lt;i&gt;I was fresh off solving a case when I heard a knock at the door. I wasn't too keen on getting up from the sofa, but the intrigue was too great. Who was on the other side of the door? My mind raced. Sal? Tony? Kochanski? Any one of those mugs would be eager to tell me off after I helped the cops bust them for stealing that Bizarre Idol from the museum.\nThe knocking continued. I whipped open the door to my loft like I was ripping off a bandage. "Let's get this over with." - Words that could have been my last, except that instead of some two-bit henchmen, I was greeted by a delivery person holding a large box. "Uh, somebody order a nightstand?"&lt;/i&gt; - Excerpt from &lt;i&gt;San Myshuno Confidential&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="23E6DD80">Nightstand Noir</Text>
  <Text Key="C1DE85B3">Tired of living in eternal darkness? Vitamin D deficient? Looking for something to steam up with a significant other? Look no further! Rise from the darkness and up your loft's natural light with these upcycled iron-framed windows! Perfect for lofts, penthouses, studios or regular 'ole homes.</Text>
  <Text Key="ABDC51E2">Phoenix Ironworks Window</Text>
  <Text Key="EAD2E38C">Iron Heights Living</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>