<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="8D2F92F6">(From a Voidcritter Battle)</Text>
  <Text Key="CE948493">(From Performing a Puppet Show)</Text>
  <Text Key="2064C19A">(From Watching a Puppet Show)</Text>
  <Text Key="5DB243F6">A good game and good sportsmanship go hand in hand. There's still honor in losing a battle you tried your best in.</Text>
  <Text Key="3F750929">GG</Text>
  <Text Key="020F91BB">{0.SimFirstName} studied {M0.his}{F0.her} opponent's moves carefully as {M0.he}{F0.she} was handed a close loss. That won't happen again...</Text>
  <Text Key="02FA621A">The Art of Battle</Text>
  <Text Key="59DE4F00">There's no blaming lag for that loss... That was just an all around stomping. {0.SimFirstName}'s opponent's ELO must have been off the chart.</Text>
  <Text Key="AC1B47CF">Humbling Loss</Text>
  <Text Key="07E5D754">What a sweaty match against a tryhard... Forget that!</Text>
  <Text Key="35760F3B">Got Rekt</Text>
  <Text Key="B14B14BC">{0.SimFirstName} brought {M0.his}{F0.her} "A" game and walked away a winner.</Text>
  <Text Key="0A9E4213">Voidcritter Victor</Text>
  <Text Key="CEFFFC7C">Ugh, puppets. Ugh... kids. Are those... UGH yes they are, they're puppets of kids! {0.SimFirstName} is sick of it all.</Text>
  <Text Key="3B810CD3">Annoying Puppets</Text>
  <Text Key="A7B05AD4">A theatrical tour de force! That puppet show certainly tripped {0.SimFirstName}'s "d'aww" meter.</Text>
  <Text Key="47DF41BB">Delightful Puppet Show</Text>
  <Text Key="5B172567">{0.SimFirstName} isn't going to nitpick a poor puppet performance. It was still a fun show despite the mistakes!</Text>
  <Text Key="0D7B199E">"A" For Effort</Text>
  <Text Key="216E549D">Well, not literally of course! {0.SimFirstName} put on a wonderful puppet performance!</Text>
  <Text Key="52692888">Broke a Leg</Text>
  <Text Key="DF2DAD12">Ooof... that show could have gone better. Next time {0.SimFirstName} will try to imagine the audience in their underwear while performing.</Text>
  <Text Key="9481CC2D">Nervous Nellie</Text>
  <Text Key="82FB5A03">Too mature for kids, too cool for adults. Just right for {0.SimFirstName}... BEtween!</Text>
  <Text Key="65AE6152">Watched BEtween TV</Text>
  <Text Key="EFCB27AB">Battle With Voidcritters</Text>
  <Text Key="234F5B24">Battle With Voidcritters</Text>
  <Text Key="6056F35A">Don't Battle With Voidcritters</Text>
  <Text Key="8D0F8348">Perform Puppet Shows</Text>
  <Text Key="BEF19F47">Perform Puppet Shows</Text>
  <Text Key="8084C12B">Don't Perform Puppet Shows</Text>
  <Text Key="6B897D12">Graphic To A Tee</Text>
  <Text Key="2C6590F9">Rock 'N Chic</Text>
  <Text Key="80CE73BB">Topical Tropical</Text>
  <Text Key="CBC95CF9">Touch Of Sparkle</Text>
  <Text Key="07F8844F">All The Graphics</Text>
  <Text Key="0FC738FF">Ready To Play</Text>
  <Text Key="A81FB135">Tough It Up</Text>
  <Text Key="F9EDBE5A">Mischief Maker</Text>
  <Text Key="143C57A5">Battle With Voidcritters</Text>
  <Text Key="17B4A150">Children who are going to bed...\nPull the covers up over your head...\nTuck all limbs under the sheets...\nBefore the monster comes out to eat!</Text>
  <Text Key="8631907F">Beddy Bye Sleeper</Text>
  <Text Key="18A10C74">Parents, nothing says "serious" like a child committed to their studies. You no longer need to listen to their petulant demands to be heard by their elders. Stock this bookshelf chock full of educational materials to whip them into shape and cure their internet speak forever!</Text>
  <Text Key="C54917DB">Take Me Srsly Bookshelf</Text>
  <Text Key="99F64A27">Parents, it's time to get serious. Commit to the education of your child, and the eradication of internet speak. This bookshelf is the answer. With twice the space for educational goodness compared to the "Take Me Srsly Bookshelf", you'll double your child's potential to learn!</Text>
  <Text Key="71CFE05E">This Time It's Srs Bookshelf</Text>
  <Text Key="E6B0A7DE">This clock does not use binary mathematics to tell the time, although it'd be pretty neat if it did. It makes up for it with a wild variety of patterns that are perfect for creating a room with a fun vibe.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E8899E1">The Not Binary Clock</Text>
  <Text Key="27608D53">A booster pack containing a Voidcritter card. Has a higher chance of being a common card.</Text>
  <Text Key="94502B02">Voidcritter Booster Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="B1AB43E4">A booster pack containing a Voidcritter card. Has a higher chance of being a rare card.</Text>
  <Text Key="8728372B">Voidcritter Booster Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="84DBC8D2">The Avesu, or Gem Snatching bird, lives high in the mountains on its home world. The species struggled to adjust to sea level conditions after its appearance in our world. As it became acclimated to highly populated areas, it developed an attraction to shiny objects and precious stones.\n\nEpisode 5 saw Leif’s rich uncle Mervin attacked by an Avesu, which was particularly charmed by his bedazzled cuff links. Subsequently, Leif and his friends tracked the bird to its nest where they discovered the Avesu had adapted to use the gemstones to protect their eggs from predators.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B42D5ED">Avesu</Text>
  <Text Key="57F4F25B">The flying serpent Dicoatl is a skilled hunter of the skies. Its battle abilities include creating strong gales of wind with its wings, and a gem on its forehead which it can illuminate to signal other Dicoatl.\n\nA heartfelt moment in episode 10 brought the species to prominence. Leif’s classmate Ellie used her Meduso to defeat an aggressive Dicoatl, then sympathetically offered to take the critter under her figurative wing. Since then the two have been inseparable, with Ellie often seen teaching it dogfight maneuvers in the local park.</Text>
  <Text Key="0BAB803A">Dicoatl</Text>
  <Text Key="CBD334B0">The gelatinous texture of Meduso’s body can be deceptive. Its amorphous shape is as weightless as the feathers that adorn its head, giving it the ability to drift through the air and avoid danger. While often mistaken as a mouth, the cavity in its face is in fact an enlarged nostril, giving it a predilection to track down the source of intensely fragrant smells.\n\nEpisode 20 saw a flock of Meduso latch themselves onto a perfume saleswoman, causing chaos at the local mall. Leif cleverly helped lure the Meduso away with the scent of succulent meat when he fired up the grill in a nearby park.</Text>
  <Text Key="9354C15F">Meduso</Text>
  <Text Key="D0F53371">Often found resting high above the ground on a self-made cloud, Nimbus tend gardens of their own creation by supplying them with daily rain.\n\nA Nimbus first clashed with Sims in episode 15. One Nimbus created an impeccable garden on the outskirts of Leif’s hometown, but several teens playing hooky brashly decided to vandalize the carefully cultivated land. The Nimbus responded in kind, harassing the teens daily with thunder, lightning, and hail. Leif was eventually able to convince them to return to the scene and till the soil so that the land could grow once again.</Text>
  <Text Key="330EBF44">Nimbus</Text>
  <Text Key="1413149A">These helpless looking critters mimic the budding plants that share their forest home. Generally slow moving and lacking extremities to defend themselves, Nymphaea prefer to use their pollen to charm others into protecting their groves. When under extreme duress, they’re known to produce fungal spores that invade animal hosts and allow them to propagate their species in a safer environment.\n\nEpisode 19 dealt with several Nymphaea that took over a flower shop and started reproducing at an alarming rate. It took all of Leif’s ingenuity to free his friends from their hypnotizing pollen and relocate them to a remote nature preserve.</Text>
  <Text Key="ECCB06C5">Nymphaea</Text>
  <Text Key="8D146A63">Encased in living stone that it can shape at will, ancient Mythemes are thought to have created the Voidcritter’s lands and islands in millennia past. Despite their slow pace, their absolute command of the elements makes them a difficult foe in battle.\n\nLeif’s friend Barry had a near death experience in episode 4, when a parkour mishap at a construction site caused a section of scaffolding to give way. A powerful Mytheme happened to be nearby, and it rapidly shifted a pile of gravel to brace the collapsing structure, giving Barry just enough time to scramble to safety. Indebted, Barry swore an oath to protect and battle alongside all Mythemes.</Text>
  <Text Key="B42AE332">Mytheme</Text>
  <Text Key="89556478">With a keen ability to sniff out metals buried deep in the earth, Suintors build their homes out of the rocks and soil they dig through to find their food. Unlike the ivory tusks of our planet’s boars, a Suintor’s tusks are made from lonsdaleite. This has led scientists to hypothesize that their home planet was ravaged by meteorite impacts during the time when Suintors evolved to take their current form. \n\nWhen a Suintor found its way into Leif’s town in episode 9, it built its home on the median of a busy street to stop the delish meals that it observed passing by at high speeds. Leif took pity on the confused critter and convinced it that vehicles are not good sources of food, saving it from a fate of being hunted by insurance adjusters.</Text>
  <Text Key="F365B477">Suintor</Text>
  <Text Key="44DC1E19">At home in landscapes littered with cylindrical rock formations, Simgaia traversed their unique biome by swinging from pillar to pillar using the vines of plants that hung from outcroppings. Such behavior reinforced the musculature in their front limbs, causing them to pack quite the punch.\n\nEpisode 14 focused on a troop of Simgaia attempting to settle amongst a block of high-rise apartments, using electrical cables they’d ripped from poles to swing to and fro. After causing a massive power outage, Leif was able to coax them to the outskirts of town where they would be less disruptive.</Text>
  <Text Key="9EB70F9C">Simgaia</Text>
  <Text Key="06F37BBC">The small dog-like monster called a Yorier lives among large rock formations found in its home world’s deserts. Burrowing deep into the soft rock, Yoriers breathe fire into their dens before dusk to heat the earth until morning.\n\nEpisode 3 saw Leif receive a letter from his pen-pal Lora in Oasis Springs. She spoke of befriending a Yorier who she’d nursed back to health after discovering it on the verge of death. The poor thing had attempted its nightly ritual of breathing fire onto the desert rocks before laying down for the night, only to suffer from a heatstroke. The critter was blissfully unaware that it never actually gets cold in Oasis Springs.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC8CC713">Yorier</Text>
  <Text Key="29EE12C9">A powerful critter, the Canis is able to coat its ashen black fur in flames burning at greater than 1400 degrees Celsius. This naturally destructive power makes it an outcast amongst other species, despite its naturally pleasant disposition. Canis are left to wander lands recently ravaged by forest fires in an attempt to not be run off by those fearing an uncontrolled burn.\n\nIn episode 8, Leif races against time to put out fires started by an out of control Canis. The fear of suddenly appearing in another world caused the normally peaceful Canis to rampage through the town, creating a crisis for a municipality with no local fire department.</Text>
  <Text Key="F2CA542C">Canis</Text>
  <Text Key="EB84109E">Floating along in air currents produced by its own body warmth, Cyprin live near the mouths of active volcanos. While Cyprin’s outward appearance is fishlike in nature, its tails and fins are actually flames it manipulates to help propel itself.\n\nWhen they warped into existence in Leif’s hometown in episode 13, Cyprin interrupted a county fair by warming themselves over grills at the various food stands. While they were immediately shooed away due to health codes regarding food preparation, they found themselves at home in the tent of a traveling fire eater who was performing at the fair.</Text>
  <Text Key="024258A1">Cyprin</Text>
  <Text Key="76B02ED3">Born from volcanoes, Fissures burst forth from the ground when they reach adulthood after eating their way through the planetary crust. They’re known to form a symbiotic relationship with Cyprins that act as their eyes and ears, in return for enabling Cyprins to survive in regions that lack magmatic activity.\n\nIn episode 18, Leif tripped over a Fissure that had entered a dormant state due to a lack of sufficient heat to keep its body molten. He was able to help the creature by convincing a local smelter to let it bathe in her furnace during work hours.</Text>
  <Text Key="31625782">Fissure</Text>
  <Text Key="4263D192">Drawn to the gloomy like a moth to a flame, Wisps feed on negative emotions. These tiny critters have a ravenous appetite, but have found this planet full of emotional Sims to be quite hospitable. They possess the ability to phase in and out of our visible dimensions, and Sims who find their mood inexplicably improving are often unwittingly serving as hosts to a hungry Wisp.\n\nIn episode 6, Leif first encountered Wisps when a trio of them attached themselves to a classmate. He initially tried to ward them off, only to realize their presence was actively helping his classmate’s mood improve.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE6A11AD">Wisp</Text>
  <Text Key="9FBD391B">Mysterious and unidentified, Veild are known to appear and disappear within a strange fog that it commands at will. It’s said that Sims become transfixed in the presence of a Veild. Looking upon their form gives the impression of gazing deep into the galaxy itself, as the pattern of a star map shifts across their skin. The tribal necklace they wear seems to indicate an ancient form of space magic that the Veild wield.\n\nAn enigmatic force in the show, Veild have both aided and hindered Leif and his friends on several occasions. No one knows what a Veild’s motives are, but they appear to watch over the other critters that have come to our world.</Text>
  <Text Key="40B61BFA">Veild</Text>
  <Text Key="4D440070">Wickyn are the embodiment of terror, who control a foe by probing their mind and manifesting their greatest fears. They lower their enemy’s defenses by crossing their eyes and projecting a derpy appearance, causing their opponent to massively underestimate them.\n\nThroughout the series Wickyn have been seen aiding antagonists by coercing other powerful critters to do their bidding. They control these docile critters via projected hallucinations, with the promise of freeing them after their dirty work is complete. Leif has vowed to stop this critter from causing further havoc, but has yet to devise a plan to shield his mind during battle.</Text>
  <Text Key="4038371F">Wickyn</Text>
  <Text Key="60328831">In the depths of the Mauven Forest on its home world, Vulpes’ used their ability to manipulate gravity to blend in with the violet leaf canopy when hunting their prey. While the Vulpes’ dark purple and blue coat has made it difficult to conceal itself in its new surroundings here, its gravity bending powers experienced a substantial boost, as its original home is 114% the gravity of our own planet.\n\nIn the show’s premier, Leif found his Vulpes while it was under control of a mysterious force. Since saving him, the pair have been inseparable, dealing with the trouble other critters cause around town.</Text>
  <Text Key="D75C7504">Vulpes</Text>
  <Text Key="537FA363">Originally from the salt waters of their homeworld, the friendly demeanor of Kampos’ causes them to commonly gather in large schools near harbors in densely populated areas.\n\nLeif first discovered the Kampos in episode 12 when he followed their lilted song to the water’s edge, where a gathering of Kampos bobbed on the water’s surface while performing under the moonlit sky.</Text>
  <Text Key="54E53E32">Kampos</Text>
  <Text Key="DA7E4D9A">The amphibious Pleuro are known as the lake protectors, shooting powerful jets of water at predators to keep them at bay.\n\nThey were introduced in episode 7, when they caused an uproar at Leif’s local community pool. After storming the pool to claim it as their new nesting ground, they were seen enjoying the toys and refreshments that were left behind as sims fled.</Text>
  <Text Key="8D8561C5">Pleuro</Text>
  <Text Key="342482E5">These gentle giants are often found floating in the middle of lakes, feasting on underwater or shoreline plants. If threatened, Bubalus will charge their offender with surprising speed.\n\nThis critter was introduced in episode 2, when Leif’s friend Finn met his Bubalus after it took up residence in his backyard fish pond.</Text>
  <Text Key="70D46060">Bubalus</Text>
  <Text Key="E4B67B4C">A prideful critter that inhabits its world’s artic waters, the Arcticorn uses its sharp icicle horn to hunt and joust against other Articorns to prove superiority.\n\nArticorns were introduced in episode 17, when the first one to arrive in this world speared a pack of fish that was being hauled in by a fishing boat’s net. The Articorn turned aggressive as it thought the fisherman were attempting to lay claim to its kill. Leif was forced to battle the Arcticorn, and the Articorn was convinced to live in harmony with the fishermen once a pecking order was established.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C6BB503">Arcticorn</Text>
  <Text Key="AE58F14C">This set of four earth element Voidcritter decals includes Nymphaea, Mytheme, Suintor, and Simgaia.</Text>
  <Text Key="3BBD3703">Earth Voidcritter Decal</Text>
  <Text Key="64CEBB02">This set of four fire element Voidcritter decals includes Yorier, Canis, Cyprin, and Fissure.</Text>
  <Text Key="10E750FD">Fire Voidcritter Decal</Text>
  <Text Key="74AEB664">This set of four void element Voidcritter decals includes Wisp, Veild, Wickyn, and Vulpes.</Text>
  <Text Key="38BB06AB">Void Voidcritter Decal</Text>
  <Text Key="9455505B">This set of four water element Voidcritter decals includes Kampos, Pleuro, Bubalus, and Articorn.</Text>
  <Text Key="F3823A3A">Water Voidcritter Decal</Text>
  <Text Key="215ED574">This set of four air element Voidcritter decals includes Avesu, Dicoatl, Meduso, and Nimbus.</Text>
  <Text Key="A45622DB">Wind Voidcritter Decal</Text>
  <Text Key="7441798B">In an effort to put the voting public at ease, Bosley Robotics struck a licensing deal with Big Bod Wall Decals Co. It was thought that a targeted PR campaign to plaster Bosley Bots on walls throughout the community would assist in getting the public to subconsciously feel at ease in their presence. The effort proved to be an unmitigated disaster. Sims of voting age described the Bosley Bots as omnipresent, dystopian, unjustly authoritative, and exuding an indifferent omnipotence. Fear gave way to anger, and Bosley Bot Big Bod decals were routinely vandalized until the campaign was halted. Surviving Big Bod decals went on to find an unlikely popularity amongst children, who were inspired by their imposing strength and “cool colors.”</Text>
  <Text Key="AE919F0A">Bosley Bot Big Bod</Text>
  <Text Key="BA2F37E6">A first glance this desk appears symmetrical. That would have been the easy route, one might even say "lazy" if you're feeling cynical. But no! This desk has an innovative new safety feature designed to keep the filing cabinet fixed in place. It's a revolutionary new desk technology that we call STAAP - Stubbed Toes Are All Preventable - which keeps that filing cabinet neatly in place, and the toes of any Sims passing by feeling good.</Text>
  <Text Key="5934A9F9">STAAP Desk</Text>
  <Text Key="48670FCD">This ordinary wardrobe can come through in a pinch should you find yourself without a puppet theater. Remove the backing, throw open the front doors, and viola! Show time!</Text>
  <Text Key="59170418">Puppeteer's Wardrobe</Text>
  <Text Key="D12EE24A">Leif. Barry. Lora. Finn. Ellie. Revered names of Voidcritter trainers, masters of the five elements. Will you add your name to their legacy?\n\nChoose your element. Find your critter companion. Train them and grow stronger together. Lead them into battle. Fulfill your destiny!\n\n*CHOKING HAZARD - Small parts not for children under 7 years.</Text>
  <Text Key="3ADC4C55">Voidcritter Battle Station</Text>
  <Text Key="81F2CF89">A fun (and practical!) craft project for kids. This set of do it yourself lanterns comes with three basic shapes, and stretchable cloth in fun patterns. Mix, match, stretch, and hang... you'll light the way to lovely room in no time!</Text>
  <Text Key="83427FEC">DIY Paper Lanterns</Text>
  <Text Key="0C150783">This lamp has an incredibly unique feature... no power cord! So just how does it manage to cast light? A miniature micro-combustion rocket engine fires up every time the lamp is turned on! Of course, this does require that owners fill its tank with a thimble of gasoline every few weeks.</Text>
  <Text Key="7DA8F1D2">Blastoff! Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="318C4509">A special collection of photos... friends, family, lands traveled, and places yet to visit. You'll see them all as you drift to sleep underneath these starry lights.</Text>
  <Text Key="A5A1E86C">Say Goodnight Little Lights</Text>
  <Text Key="6B45CAE8">A mirror that's a reflection not only of your appearance, but of your very soul. The stickers affixed to its surface tell a bit about the Sim that chooses to place it in their room.</Text>
  <Text Key="D5CE3B07">Mirror Me!</Text>
  <Text Key="8CF21916">A projected image of a wind based Voidcritter.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E78E9C9">Wind Voidcritter Hologram</Text>
  <Text Key="3247F1CE">A projected image of an earth based Voidcritter.</Text>
  <Text Key="42EE0BF1">Earth Voidcritter Hologram</Text>
  <Text Key="F340127C">A projected image of a fire based Voidcritter.</Text>
  <Text Key="0EF96ED3">Fire Voidcritter Hologram
</Text>
  <Text Key="E579C6B1">A projected image of a Freezer Bunny training dummy.</Text>
  <Text Key="CC98E884">Freezer Bunny Training Dummy Hologram</Text>
  <Text Key="EA1374D6">A projected image of a void based Voidcritter.</Text>
  <Text Key="C2DDC089">Void Voidcritter Hologram
</Text>
  <Text Key="6370AE09">A projected image of a water based Voidcritter.
</Text>
  <Text Key="3C20D36C">Water Voidcritter Hologram
</Text>
  <Text Key="F511CAE0">These discarded mirrors are a mashup of found art and fine art. They were rescued from the trash heap, their glass shattered and paint chipped, but taken and repurposed as cute picture frames. Adorable!</Text>
  <Text Key="7430F72F">Thrifty Mirrors</Text>
  <Text Key="3733D272">A poster commemorating the cast of Voidcritters. Collect them all!</Text>
  <Text Key="313CA10D">Voidcritter Poster</Text>
  <Text Key="6CB759F4">Bring your tools; you're sure to need them (and a little luck) when attempting to nail this pentaptych to the wall. When hung properly, the combined image is quite magnificent!</Text>
  <Text Key="0657885B">Plenty O'Paintings</Text>
  <Text Key="AE4D7481">Six artists were locked in a cage;\nwork conditions caused them to rage.\nAt the end of the day,\nthey still wanted their pay,\nand settled for minimum wage.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2F39AB4">Triptych Limerick</Text>
  <Text Key="822856A2">What do faeries, monsters, soccer players, and tween pop stars all have in common? Absolutely nothing! But you can select your favorite duo when hanging these colorful posters on your wall.</Text>
  <Text Key="487FB11D">Pop &amp; Locke Posters</Text>
  <Text Key="FB060D57">A puppet's hand, or the hand of a puppeteer? Ah, the eternal dilemma...</Text>
  <Text Key="397F042E">Puppet Hand</Text>
  <Text Key="6BDC5460">A puppet's magnifying glass.</Text>
  <Text Key="916F5BAF">Puppet Magnifying Glass Prop
</Text>
  <Text Key="291A76A5">Doomed with an alliterative name, Peter Punchinello was born into puppetry. After struggling with bouts of severe denial in his teenage years, he finally accepted his life's calling. Scraping together the last of his savings, he now travels between cities in an RV to educate families on the Punchinello Puppetry Club &amp; Academy program, and sell do-it-yourself puppet theater kits, such as this one!</Text>
  <Text Key="50F7D520">Punchinello's Theater of Fine Puppetry</Text>
  <Text Key="C62288D0">Built for privacy, the Don't Peek! Room Divider ended up being recalled when a manufacturing defect resulted in a larger than expected gap between the hinged panels. Those that grabbed one before they were removed from store shelves are left with simple wooden paneling ideal for personal customization.</Text>
  <Text Key="039FAEFF">Don't Peek! Room Divider</Text>
  <Text Key="00E1FBBC">Born from a freak accident involving a koala and a jellybean in the cloning machine at FutureSim Labs, Coolala Bears have become infamous for their nasty disposition. Despite their adorable appearance, Sims have learned that such creatures are better observed, not held.</Text>
  <Text Key="32104713">Coolala Bear</Text>
  <Text Key="BE7C273C">The year 2013 saw the rise of Bosley Robotics, a company brimming with inspiration. They were guided by an unwavering belief in their CEO Bill Bosley's vision for the future of Simanity. Bill promised to be the evolutionary spark to merge man and machine, and he had the wherewithal to put these plans in motion. It was not meant to be though. A governmental advisory Committee on Ethics in Technology convened, and a quorum determined that this proposed next step in evolution was a radical departure from the morals that drive Sim culture. During the proceedings Bosley Robotics put this friendly faced robotic toy on the market to give the company a softer image and rebrand itself as family-friendly, but the effort proved futile in swaying public officials. Not only were his ideas branded as quixotic, but they were further rated EC-10 condemned, and the company's research laboratories were torched by a team of sweepers.</Text>
  <Text Key="2A07F193">Bosley Bot</Text>
  <Text Key="3CB5B649">♪ Super bright, in the night! These butterflies are sure to delight.\n\nLight up wings, start to glow. Light so bright, you'll say "woah!"\n\nNight bright, taking flight! Butterfly friends ward off night frights! ♪</Text>
  <Text Key="CD60E6AC">Night Bright Butterflies - Left</Text>
  <Text Key="FF2AD3FC">♪ Super bright, in the night! These butterflies are sure to delight.\n\nLight up wings, start to glow. Light so bright, you'll say "woah!"\n\nNight bright, taking flight! Butterfly friends ward off night frights! ♪</Text>
  <Text Key="42B2FB53">Night Bright Butterflies - Right</Text>
  <Text Key="CB1CD280">A framed FC Barbacoa soccer jersey, signed by the team captain himself.\n\nNote: Jersey and signature are replicas; thus the quite reasonable price for this otherwise highly prized item!</Text>
  <Text Key="D0A07A4F">FC Barbacoa Jersey</Text>
  <Text Key="61807912">Sumptuous walnut wood. Gilded metallic framing. This is a shelf for champions. You could remove the trophies and put something else in their place, but why would you? You're a champion.</Text>
  <Text Key="AD28702D">Shelf of Champions</Text>
  <Text Key="8340BA9B">An adorbs shelf to display knick knacks and hang odds and ends. Includes a picture frame for cute inspirational images to brighten your day!</Text>
  <Text Key="725DE87A">Sarah's Scrapbook Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="08E00F42">♪ These shelves are big... "Yeah yeah yeah!" They're not small... "No no no!" These honeycomb shelves, have got the space... to solve all your storage needs! ♪</Text>
  <Text Key="8397603D">Interlock-Me-Not Honeycomb Shelving</Text>
  <Text Key="299C6CBB">A desk chair for the aspiring mega conglomerate executive in all of us. Don't worry, by the time you're ready to step into that role you'll have outgrown this colorful cloth chair.</Text>
  <Text Key="B8C4031A">My First Desk Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="DB6328B8">When lined up side by side, it's clear that a section of this otherwise sectional chair is missing. Where's the missing section?!</Text>
  <Text Key="6762E1B7">Section of Sectional Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="E0944610">Each Hippopottoman comes with a lifetime warranty. To guarantee the durability of this ottoman, the manufacturer famously tests each one before it leaves the factory by having a 4,000 pound hippopotamus lay upon it. Buy with confidence!</Text>
  <Text Key="F7716D3F">Hippopottoman</Text>
  <Text Key="3E70CDEA">This wall-mounted stereo is intended for use at community venues. Once tweens pop, they can't stop (and neither can this stereo!)</Text>
  <Text Key="6A02F575">Venue Wall Speaker: Tween Pop</Text>
  <Text Key="18DFC206">What's the square root of an end table? That sounds like the kind of question a square would ask. The real answer is that it doesn't matter, because you'll be too busy admiring this square-shaped end table's fine craftsmanship.</Text>
  <Text Key="4DFD7799">Squared End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="37AD3367">This traveling trunk, now decommissioned, lives out the remainder of its days as a chest for toys. It yearns for the days of globe spanning adventures; and bitterly glares at the spinner and roller bags that have forced it into obsolescense.</Text>
  <Text Key="DBA3E39E">Traveling Trunk</Text>
  <Text Key="D0B2483A">With profits from their sowing division in steep decline, Kindermade Co. needed a hit new product...\n\nIntroducing the Rightsized Thimble, a trash can for tots. With a simple adjustment of their factory's thimble mold, thimble production was scaled 15x in size to produce this resplendent receptacle.</Text>
  <Text Key="C77574E5">Rightsized Thimble</Text>
  <Text Key="48CDDCFC">Cultural norms mean that unlike your own childhood, a TV is now perfectly acceptable in a kid's bedroom. You want to fit within cultural norms right? Better buy your kid a TV, pronto! The Get 'Em Young TV stand will fully support your decision.</Text>
  <Text Key="68EBC653">Get 'Em Young TV Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="7C729A9F">Children can use this card on the Voidcritter Battle Station when it's placed in their inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="59024EE6">Attack</Text>
  <Text Key="4A2D878E">Watch Battle</Text>
  <Text Key="7FDC662B">React to Battle</Text>
  <Text Key="F8C1A93B">{0.SimFirstName} must have a Voidcritter card to use this object. {M0.He}{F0.She} can buy a booster pack from a Computer.</Text>
  <Text Key="E7270423">Battle Voidcritter Against</Text>
  <Text Key="70D27BE9">Train Voidcritter</Text>
  <Text Key="67CD3B72">Select Voidcritter</Text>
  <Text Key="6B79C97D">Battle Voidcritters</Text>
  <Text Key="8582557D">Train Voidcritter</Text>
  <Text Key="22EADEAB">Set to Max Power Level</Text>
  <Text Key="FA9C3C79">Acquire All Monsters</Text>
  <Text Key="64ABBD36">Look for Discarded Toys</Text>
  <Text Key="5EC972C8">{0.SimFirstName} recently searched through a trash can. Maybe {M0.he'll}{F0.she'll} be up for digging through the trash again later.</Text>
  <Text Key="F14BF4DA">Sit in Puppet Theater</Text>
  <Text Key="0C1E03E3">Ask to Trade Voidcritters</Text>
  <Text Key="8C0D2E5D">Read Card</Text>
  <Text Key="976D8F98">Trade Voidcritter</Text>
  <Text Key="30CD422F">Watch Battle</Text>
  <Text Key="5C7807BE">Open Booster Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="62061E08">Trade Card With</Text>
  <Text Key="0FF52643">Purchase Voidcritter Booster Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="09C83F1B">Purchase Voidcritter Booster Pack x5</Text>
  <Text Key="9BA7E194">Invite To Watch</Text>
  <Text Key="28665ED6">Lost In the Woods</Text>
  <Text Key="A3574585">My Pet Monster</Text>
  <Text Key="78FA96EE">School Life</Text>
  <Text Key="901D73A4">The Creature of Granite Falls</Text>
  <Text Key="0BBE01C0">Search for the Notebook Snatcher</Text>
  <Text Key="B48F1490">Wait for Puppet Show to Begin</Text>
  <Text Key="765C80A8">Watch Puppet Show</Text>
  <Text Key="58830E41">Perform For...</Text>
  <Text Key="A7B04F1C">Perform "Lost in the Woods" For</Text>
  <Text Key="3B95E847">Perform "My Pet Monster" For</Text>
  <Text Key="86277CC4">Perform "School Life" For</Text>
  <Text Key="178CE5C6">Perform "The Creature of Granite Falls" For</Text>
  <Text Key="19F9750E">Perform "Search for the Notebook Snatcher" For</Text>
  <Text Key="532209A2">React to Puppet Show</Text>
  <Text Key="1037CD55">Listen to Tween Pop</Text>
  <Text Key="22A25A5E">Listen to Tween Pop</Text>
  <Text Key="C4F00BFF">Child Sims can watch the latest pop culture music and shows on this channel.</Text>
  <Text Key="63C577ED">Watch BEtween TV</Text>
  <Text Key="74172B65">Master Playroom</Text>
  <Text Key="B5CD4355">All To Myself</Text>
  <Text Key="AA1A2AF3">Can Have It All</Text>
  <Text Key="2F3FABEE">{1.Money}\nRarity: {0.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="349478BE">Element: Wind</Text>
  <Text Key="C5B7EA5B">Element: Water</Text>
  <Text Key="6A243BEE">Element: Earth</Text>
  <Text Key="B0211D12">Element: Void</Text>
  <Text Key="C71B2B4A">Element: Fire</Text>
  <Text Key="6AA6043C">Power Level: 6</Text>
  <Text Key="B50C853F">Power Level: 1</Text>
  <Text Key="A0AD50C5">Power Level: 3</Text>
  <Text Key="EC23071D">Power Level: 2</Text>
  <Text Key="3F4A9608">Power Level: 4</Text>
  <Text Key="714A0EAF">Power Level: 8</Text>
  <Text Key="B58B77AE">Power Level: 9</Text>
  <Text Key="D9F6971A">Power Level: 10</Text>
  <Text Key="1B6AA56D">Power Level: 7</Text>
  <Text Key="40820213">Power Level: 5</Text>
  <Text Key="D68FC9A7">Limited Edition Foil Card</Text>
  <Text Key="708FD0C3">Counting down the top tween hits!</Text>
  <Text Key="1255B588">Tween Pop</Text>
  <Text Key="0A0AB0BA">Watch BEtween TV</Text>
  <Text Key="903ABC73">BEtween TV</Text>
  <Text Key="146D746C">Perform Puppet Show</Text>
  <Text Key="C2A77537">Perform Puppet Show For</Text>
  <Text Key="6B725293">Battle a Friend</Text>
  <Text Key="8E26319D">Click on a Battle Station and select Battle Voidcritter.</Text>
  <Text Key="CF2CD48A">Buy a Voidcritter Booster Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="2DF6CAB2">Click on a Computer and select Purchase Voidcritter Booster Pack under the Order category.</Text>
  <Text Key="1ADF6CA9">Buy a Puppet Theater</Text>
  <Text Key="A5284E9B">Purchase a Puppet Theater from Build Mode. Look for it in Kids' Activities.</Text>
  <Text Key="FD47F076">Find a Voidcritter</Text>
  <Text Key="32555946">Children can search inside logs and outdoor trash cans to try and find a discarded Voidcritter card.</Text>
  <Text Key="529F0550">Perform a Puppet Show</Text>
  <Text Key="73073718">Click on a Puppet Theater and select Perform Puppet Show. Then select a show to perform.</Text>
  <Text Key="C86744E7">{0.SimFirstName} didn't find anything interesting.</Text>
  <Text Key="0C5F5811">{0.SimFirstName} found a discarded toy. A perfect addition to {M0.his}{F0.her} toy box back home!</Text>
  <Text Key="D186F93A">{0.SimFirstName} purchased a Voidcritters booster pack. {M0.He}{F0.She} can open it from {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory to discover which monster is hidden inside!</Text>
  <Text Key="9CE272A0">{0.SimFirstName} purchased several Voidcritter booster packs. {M0.He}{F0.she} can open them from {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory to discover which monsters are hidden inside!</Text>
  <Text Key="7E4823AA">{0.SimFirstName} found a discarded Voidcritters booster pack. {M0.He}{F0.She} can open it from {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory to discover which monster is hidden inside!</Text>
  <Text Key="1782F5B3">{0.SimFirstName} tore open the booster pack and discovered a {1.ObjectName} Voidcritter card inside!</Text>
  <Text Key="FA854D8E">{1.ObjectCatalogDescription}</Text>
  <Text Key="5BE5A8E8">{1.ObjectName}</Text>
  <Text Key="3C34F1D8">{0.SimFirstName} traded away {M0.his}{F0.her} Voidcritter and got a {1.ObjectName} card in return.</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>