<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="DA8AE956">The delightful aroma of sweet treats brings joy and coziness to the heart!</Text>
  <Text Key="9728F609">Smells Like Something Sweet!</Text>
  <Text Key="934423BE">Nothing says you're a grilled cheese aficionado more than this mini-library! With this on your shelves, there's no question what your life's aspiration is.</Text>
  <Text Key="51CF5041">Melt Master's Mini-Library</Text>
  <Text Key="A9E17AB9">Sometimes, when your alarm clock goes off, you need your bed to push you out and launch you into the day. While this alarm clock can't provide that exact amount of motivation, it'll at least get every Sim up at the right time!</Text>
  <Text Key="603211BC">"Blast Off!" Alarm Clock</Text>
  <Text Key="9B6B37F4">Where function meets style and, most importantly, comfort! The Comfy Gaming Computer is a high-end PC setup harmoniously equipped with everything you may need to ensure endless hours of comfy gaming sessions. </Text>
  <Text Key="A5D0C25B">Comfy Gaming Computer</Text>
  <Text Key="3FA6420B">It's safe to say that most people have owned a desk like this at some point. In fact, who could blame them? Its elegant lines and simplistic design truly tie any office together. Assembly not included.</Text>
  <Text Key="47BC908A">The Skrivbord</Text>
  <Text Key="BB176116">These high-end candles are just as fragrant as they are cute! You may not have needed all these scents, but that "Buy 9, Get 1 Free" promotion really grabbed your attention.</Text>
  <Text Key="4BD641C9">Culinary Confections Candle</Text>
  <Text Key="A8FD0E47">For the comfy gamer who has everything! This lamp may incite fear of alien abductions, but perhaps that's just the next great adventure. Either way, it is the perfect combination of functionality and cuteness!</Text>
  <Text Key="11AA41FE">"Beam me up, Blarffy" Novelty Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="F8CD3645">No gamer room is complete without your very own gamer tag displayed in a brilliantly bright neon sign!</Text>
  <Text Key="94596040">Neon Gamer Tag Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="827C88C4">These rare and collectible art prints are guaranteed to show off your love for some of your favorite games! Pick your favorite cover and display it with pride.</Text>
  <Text Key="7C8A198B">Sims Forever! Collectible Art Prints</Text>
  <Text Key="B2324447">We already knew where you were headed when you grabbed these out of the catalog. These books are practical and versatile, but we know you'll try to see how high you can stack them first.</Text>
  <Text Key="F1B803FE">The Endless Book Pile</Text>
  <Text Key="92F0A510">You'll be amazed at how quickly this camera can take you from Simsta-Stranger to Simsta-Famous!</Text>
  <Text Key="06CA5A3F">InstaSimsta Camera</Text>
  <Text Key="06A45A4E">Maybe they're born with it; maybe it's actually a plant. (But actually... don't try to use conditioner.)</Text>
  <Text Key="D82DDD71">Luscious Locks Mini Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="59253B20">This adorable plant is perfect for adding a little greenery to your space without any risk of being eaten by a real cowplant.</Text>
  <Text Key="C8A7746F">The Covert Cowplant</Text>
  <Text Key="EE53019F">Sometimes, a nice textured rug is all you need to tie a room together. This rug features a fantastic array of neutrals and pastels, so you're sure to get a lot of use out of it!</Text>
  <Text Key="16C2AD46">Woven Area Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="41B6E6FF">The "Free the Computer Tower!" movement is upon us. Will you place it on the desk, under the desk, next to the desk, near the desk, by the desk, here, there, anywhere? Well, now you can!</Text>
  <Text Key="E17BAE26">Ultra Sleek Computer Tower</Text>
  <Text Key="4E3F2923">This sleek display is perfect to show off your high-tech keyboard!</Text>
  <Text Key="65B78CF2">Esteemed Keyboard Display</Text>
  <Text Key="67CA8EB5">Everything you need is now in this convenient and elevated Desk Organizer. Look at you- staying on top of things!</Text>
  <Text Key="D7F31D50">PerfectPlastik Desk Organizer</Text>
  <Text Key="FD39578F">PixelPerfect is a leading brand in video game and electronic tech. Upgrade your gaming experience with this sleek and durable controller! </Text>
  <Text Key="94FF8056">PixelPerfect Controller</Text>
  <Text Key="35A277FD">PixelPerfect is a leading brand in video game and electronic tech. These ultra-comfortable headphones will take your gaming and music experience to the next level!</Text>
  <Text Key="E30BEB68">PixelPerfect Headphones</Text>
  <Text Key="5075FCC4">A stylish drink container is the perfect way to make any space feel lived in. It even comes with stickers!!</Text>
  <Text Key="1E94358B">But first, Boba Cup</Text>
  <Text Key="CF8D10E1">"She stared into the telescope but didn't quite see what she expected. Instead of a stunning night sky, she found that she was about to be-" ... because sometimes your reading is interrupted!</Text>
  <Text Key="2D030494">The Paused Book</Text>
  <Text Key="A8330DBF">What's better than tabletop frames? Tabletop frames in dusty pastels with the cutest art prints you've ever seen!  </Text>
  <Text Key="950E92E6">Terrific Tabletop Frames</Text>
  <Text Key="14233F09">A quick glance at any of these covers will instantly bring a rush of precious, nostalgic memories!</Text>
  <Text Key="95E1B66C">Collection of Nostalgic Games</Text>
  <Text Key="97570285">Elevate your decor with an upgraded pencil cup that features sleek materials and clean lines... your pencils will thank you!</Text>
  <Text Key="5E6B0880">PerfectPlastik Pencil Cup</Text>
  <Text Key="C9D95485">It's a proven fact that stickers make the world a better place!</Text>
  <Text Key="3F5D5E80">MySticker Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="53F79BA3">StackIt's patented modular system allows you to customize and curate your collectibles in style. With StackIt, you can now show off your treasures with endless possibilities!</Text>
  <Text Key="87595C72">StackIt Pegboard - Panel</Text>
  <Text Key="F106BB40">StackIt's patented modular system allows you to customize how you curate your collectibles and trinkets. This full-sized shelf is perfect for displaying an extensive collection of treasures!</Text>
  <Text Key="58BD930F">StackIt Pegboard - Full Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="1142D599">StackIt's patented modular system allows you to customize how you curate your collectibles and trinkets. This mini shelf is the optimal size for knickknacks or items you want to display on their own.</Text>
  <Text Key="44169E1C">StackIt Pegboard - Mini Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="823F0886">When it comes to gaming chairs, you don't want to compromise on quality, and now you don't have to, thanks to CozyComforts! Its ergonomic support and memory foam padding will provide endless hours of gaming comfort!</Text>
  <Text Key="F6738319">CozyComforts Gaming Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="4C03EEB2">Despite how delicious some of these pillows look, we cannot reiterate enough that these are in no way edible. But they are genuinely stylish!</Text>
  <Text Key="AE0B7F4D">Precious Pillow Pouf</Text>
  <Text Key="FA4DAD79">Another hallmark of the perfect gaming setup- cubbies! They're so versatile and perfect for giving your treasures the attention they deserve.</Text>
  <Text Key="B8640D7C">Cubed Cubbies</Text>
  <Text Key="264C2F10">A Player's Paradise</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>