<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="2B456D99">(From Watching Birds)</Text>
  <Text Key="BA842F32">(From Bird Attack)</Text>
  <Text Key="8C49DD3D">(From Viewing Spinning Flower)</Text>
  <Text Key="85FDCA6C">(From Lawn Water Slide)</Text>
  <Text Key="3242B822">Aargh! Those greedy birds have {0.SimFirstName} feeling so ANGRY!</Text>
  <Text Key="74761D9D">Birds!</Text>
  <Text Key="0798F606">The melodious chirps of birds are always a nice pick-me-up...\n\nCaw! Ca-caw!\nChaw! Chee-chaw!\nA-coodle-doodle-do!\nCoo-coo-ca-chaw!\nCluck! Cluck! Cluck-ahhh!</Text>
  <Text Key="62BAD399">Bird Watching</Text>
  <Text Key="EDD1916A">Around and around the flower goes, where it stops nobody knows!</Text>
  <Text Key="DEDAE7F5">Around and Around</Text>
  <Text Key="C7842038">Pretty, spinny, shiny, oooOooOOo...</Text>
  <Text Key="9E5D3037">Mesmerized by Spinny Things</Text>
  <Text Key="FA24D78D">Who knew a thin tarp and a little water is the difference between a nasty friction burn and a bunch of fun? That sliding was sublime!</Text>
  <Text Key="14B21DD8">Backyard Water Park</Text>
  <Text Key="B0B6A169">The bubbles, they tickle! If {0.SimFirstName} gets tired of looking like a soapy yeti, {M0.he}{F0.she} can take a shower or change outfits to clear the suds away.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8AE724C">Foamy Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="899358BE">Ouch! That's going to leave a bruise on the behind... and perhaps an even bigger bruise to {0.SimFirstName}'s ego.</Text>
  <Text Key="7BBCDF41">Too Slippery</Text>
  <Text Key="F55DAE74">Flips, spins, and poses galore... {0.SimFirstName} has demonstrated {M0.his}{F0.her} prowess over the lawn water slide.</Text>
  <Text Key="B4395DDB">Trick Slide Master</Text>
  <Text Key="625D2043">Oh no, was anyone watching?? That trick went spectacularly wrong...</Text>
  <Text Key="54B98392">Tricktastrophe</Text>
  <Text Key="222A92BC">Shaka-bra! That slide was siiiick bro!</Text>
  <Text Key="E3885C13">Bro Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="57694BAA">Watching other Sims perform trick slides is nuts! {0.SimFirstName} is amped up!</Text>
  <Text Key="C4212935">Great Tricks</Text>
  <Text Key="DD8A26D2">That lawn water slide looks like a great time... maybe {0.SimFirstName} should get sliding!</Text>
  <Text Key="BAA38FED">Looks Like Fun</Text>
  <Text Key="DFD130D6">Nothing wrong with taking pleasure in the failure of another Sim that attempted to showoff with a fancy trick slide. Serves 'em right!</Text>
  <Text Key="8EF23489">What A Showoff!</Text>
  <Text Key="E61F866B">Oooohhh OUCH! Wipeout! It's all fun and games when it isn't {0.SimFirstName} flopping on the lawn water slide.</Text>
  <Text Key="4CDA856A">Slide FAIL!</Text>
  <Text Key="3F00AE1E">Err... ouch! It hurt just watching that Sim wipeout on the lawn water slide.</Text>
  <Text Key="B112B921">That Had to Hurt</Text>
  <Text Key="913583D2">If {0.SimFirstName} was taller, {M0.he'd}{F0.she'd} rip those wind chimes down when nobody was looking.</Text>
  <Text Key="621D16ED">Annoying Chimes</Text>
  <Text Key="43042F12">The melody of the wind chimes is like a massage for the mind.</Text>
  <Text Key="8FD9B22D">Soothing Chimes</Text>
  <Text Key="7B07022A">If the wind could speak, it would do so through these lilting chimes, whose harmonious balance is an aural treat.</Text>
  <Text Key="AD2784B5">Sounds of the Wind</Text>
  <Text Key="9B0AF542">Use Lawn Water Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="85B4B0F1">Use Lawn Water Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="C824B161">Don't Use Lawn Water Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="D9FE418B">For Fun And Games</Text>
  <Text Key="56AEF55B">Ready For The Summer Sun</Text>
  <Text Key="D8CC5B91">Midsummer Trend</Text>
  <Text Key="49EC3498">Sunny Days In Town</Text>
  <Text Key="B0433A3B">Casual Weekender</Text>
  <Text Key="1FE41885">For The Off Days</Text>
  <Text Key="2F10DFA4">A classic white picket fence for your own little slice of suburbia! Unless you choose to paint it another color that is... in which case just ignore that first part.</Text>
  <Text Key="48DF70EB">White Picket Fence
</Text>
  <Text Key="A6458678">This bird feeder is for the birds! ...err no, wait... it's so fowl it's foul! Ugh, that isn't right either... just remember to wipe away the bird poop every so often.\n\nAt the end of the day, just fill it with seed off and on and you'll treat yourself to the chirping melodies of local bluebirds, cardinals, and finches that are hungry for a nibble.</Text>
  <Text Key="5D987A77">Birdy Trotz's Bird Feeder</Text>
  <Text Key="E1296D1E">A box of bird seed.</Text>
  <Text Key="0B62C621">Bird Seed Box</Text>
  <Text Key="48F7D39A">Enjoy arranging flowers? Then try positioning these floral decals on your home's walls. The possibilities are endless!</Text>
  <Text Key="CA8F13C5">Floral Arrangement - Wall Decal</Text>
  <Text Key="F7F2AB3B">Feeling froggy? These colorful frog decals will cheer you right up! The vivid colors and busy patterns add eye-popping pop art to any setting.</Text>
  <Text Key="CDFD769A">Feelin' Froggy - Wall Decal</Text>
  <Text Key="33BF711F">A bottle for holding soap.</Text>
  <Text Key="2655E3C6">Soap Bottle</Text>
  <Text Key="F499E09B">A powdered drink mixture - just add water!</Text>
  <Text Key="24B47A7A">Flavored Drink Mix</Text>
  <Text Key="0D29D580">This is the perfect pitcher for mixing a thirst-quenching drink on a bright sunny day. Create lemonade, iced tea... even Citrus Swig (You remember their infamous jingle, right? ♪"Hot as a pig? Drink Citrus Swig!"♪) There's plenty to share, so gather your friends and kick back with a cold one.</Text>
  <Text Key="8A22134F">Summer Drink Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="326148E9">These glasses fit perfectly on the Summer Drink Tray.</Text>
  <Text Key="8DB6D0CC">Summer Drink Glass</Text>
  <Text Key="92E62FC8">A classic white picket fence is only as welcoming as the gate that accompanies it. Well, look no further! Also available in other colors... but seriously, it's a picket fence.</Text>
  <Text Key="57284B67">White Picket Fence Gate</Text>
  <Text Key="22189D1F">Groovy, man. This far out light will light the path to your eternal illumination. Gaze into its depths and you just might get purple dazed.</Text>
  <Text Key="F581A7C6">Flower Power</Text>
  <Text Key="D258F4D4">This counterfeit candle may be a knockoff, but your guests will be none the wiser. Make it the centerpiece of your next backyard feast!</Text>
  <Text Key="B261EFBB">Tawdry Tawny Truedawn</Text>
  <Text Key="40678E6F">The lANTern is a fully functional ant deterrent device, that doubles as a heavy-duty lamp. Place it on your outdoor dining table and... presto! No ants; guaranteed.</Text>
  <Text Key="5A958FB6">lANTern</Text>
  <Text Key="030C4246">Ah, the poor man's bug zapper. Experience freedom from cicadas (and other winged pests) with this rustic citronella. The extra-thick wick creates a sizable flame; ideal for lighting a patio after the sun goes down.</Text>
  <Text Key="89362DD9">Scented Citronella</Text>
  <Text Key="0B6CDA82">Have you ever taken a moment to think where light comes from? Sims think about it all the time. That's why they enjoy stringing these lights together to mimic the shape of their favorite constellations.</Text>
  <Text Key="4100977D">Constellation Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="8F1AE4FD">Let me wax lyrical about these wax paper prints: Stylish art, colors so fine, these gorgeous prints will blow your mind.</Text>
  <Text Key="ED3FA268">Waxing Perennial</Text>
  <Text Key="6D0F4B8F">Step up your decorating game. This repurposed step-ladder makes the perfect perch for your potted perennials.</Text>
  <Text Key="A4F71C56">Next Level Perennials</Text>
  <Text Key="35ECE8E8">A pitcher for mixing drinks in.</Text>
  <Text Key="243D3507">Glass Pitcher</Text>
  <Text Key="FDE04C58">This flowering Gumdrop plant is in full bloom! Observe its natural beauty... and don't you dare pot it.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA7ECED7">Wild Gumdrop</Text>
  <Text Key="165CBFA7">Unapparent to the casual observer, these flowers aren't potted at all! In actuality, they're bouquet holders - for those times when you find yourself in desperate need of flowers. With three sizes to select from for any occasion, you can't go wrong!</Text>
  <Text Key="D70648DE">Tres Bouquets</Text>
  <Text Key="5CE7E77F">Only the freshest live flowers come in this vibrant vase.</Text>
  <Text Key="2965C7A6">Potted &amp; Dotted</Text>
  <Text Key="0A9DD7C8">Is there a sadder sight than a potted Gumdrop plant? Scientists are baffled by the behavior they exhibit after being moved to a ceramic cage. Within days their flowers wilt and fall away, never to grow again.</Text>
  <Text Key="D5EEC367">Potted Gumdrop</Text>
  <Text Key="ED3BBA6E">Enjoy arranging flowers? Then try positioning these floral rugs on your home's floor. The possibilities are endless!</Text>
  <Text Key="62720311">Floral Arrangement - Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="04A3FBFF">Feeling froggy? These colorful frog rugs will cheer you right up! The vivid colors and busy patterns add eye-popping pop art to any setting.</Text>
  <Text Key="291CDD26">Feelin' Froggy - Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="CA5F41FD">You'd think the Sun Rug would be round, but you'd be wrong. The name is derived from the synthetic threads used in the rug's stitching. When the sun reflects off it just so, it gleams with a blinding radiance.</Text>
  <Text Key="36342968">Sun Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="6A06E6AC">Some plum actually sealed the opening to this birdhouse to prevent any birds from getting inside! What good is a birdhouse that can't house any birds? Placing it in your yard may raise a few eyebrows from the neighbors.</Text>
  <Text Key="12931CE3">Decorative Birdhouse</Text>
  <Text Key="255C617C">Spread your wings and fly... oh, if only. For now, this lawn ornament will have to be content accentuating the landscaping.</Text>
  <Text Key="2CAF2BD3">Just Wanna' Fly</Text>
  <Text Key="DF277127">Hopefully your Sim is feeling better than this frog.</Text>
  <Text Key="067CA55E">Feelin' Froggy - Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="90D28E59">Everything you possibly need for a delicious backyard BBQ is thoughtfully stored away in the Completionist's Condiment Caddy...\n\n...wait a second, where's the mayonnaise!?</Text>
  <Text Key="12939DDC">Completionist's Condiment Caddy</Text>
  <Text Key="C825B734">Pucker up buttercup; you'll want to have practiced your best pursed lips before you get a taste of the contents of this vase.</Text>
  <Text Key="45CF189B">Taste of Tart</Text>
  <Text Key="CF5063ED">Take the classic folding chair design and remove the expensive metallic joints, and you're left with this practical seating! It may not collapse for easy storage, but you'll want to collapse into the comfortable patterned padding that's been amply added to the seat.</Text>
  <Text Key="A94ED3B8">Formerly Folding Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="00FE3594">While the name of this chair is commonly thought to be a reference to its cushion, it's actually the chairback where the manufacturer drew inspiration from.</Text>
  <Text Key="DC29317B">The Flowery</Text>
  <Text Key="585AB5A1">Can love bloom in the backyard? This sly fox certainly likes to think so. Let Hana Hal's Loveseat help set the mood.</Text>
  <Text Key="91DD2454">Hana Hal's Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="D1F10438">It's adventure on the high seas! Conquer your fears and slide through the jaws of death... will you come out stronger on the other side?</Text>
  <Text Key="97869C37">AAAHH! Jaws of Death - Lawn Water Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="B551CEEC">Simple fun on a simple slide. That's what the Justa Lawn Water Slide promises, and that's what it delivers.\n\nJusta LLC is a limited liability corporation. Your usage of this product implies agreement that you will not hold Justa LLC liable for any injuries sustained when using the product responsibly... or otherwise.</Text>
  <Text Key="A36A9B23">Justa Lawn Water Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="3B9C0CA3">Carbon dating on this boombox indicates it comes from hundreds of years... into the future?? Applying an electrical current to its circuitry causes the parts to amplify local radio waves and output their signal with crystal clarity. Some Sims speculate that this may be the head of an advanced cyborg... but that can't be possible, right?</Text>
  <Text Key="C589DF72">Plumbot Box</Text>
  <Text Key="BB239620">A coffee table that helps inspire coffee talk? How novel! Creating small talk has never been simpler, as you marvel with others over the millefleurs pattern in the table's runner.</Text>
  <Text Key="B80D956F">Milly's Coffee</Text>
  <Text Key="5E645EAB">Dine out tonight... out in your backyard that is. A quick nosh will settle a rumbling tummy, allowing you time to appreciate the great outdoors.</Text>
  <Text Key="2BDC53AA">Milly's Dining</Text>
  <Text Key="698C7268">With seating for up to six Sims, this large umbrella table is meant for entertaining! The umbrella material is made from a finely stitched together mesh that's ideal for looking out... or for looking down in.</Text>
  <Text Key="C5EA9987">Voyeuristic Large Umbrella Table</Text>
  <Text Key="5AF82599">Here's a nifty lifehack for the hungry Sim...\n\nWhile the Perfectly Patterned large umbrella table has room to seat six, you could only provide three chairs, thus doubling the available space for a Sim to serve themselves a meal. Makes perfect sense, right? Neat!</Text>
  <Text Key="91958E1C">Perfectly Patterned Large Umbrella Table</Text>
  <Text Key="9861E421">The Square Meals Dining Table proved so popular that the furniture factory ordered a second run. Unfortunately, a defect in the factory's tooling resulted in a dining table approximately two inches too short. Ever fastidious, the manufacturer refused to pass their problem along to you, and is instead offering this defective dining table as a fully functional end table!</Text>
  <Text Key="567667D4">Square Meals Factory Defect Table</Text>
  <Text Key="42FDA078">This clever ensemble is comprised of a rugged patterned doormat draped over a solid wooden table. With such sturdy materials, it's shelving that's well suited for all your outdoor knick-knacks.</Text>
  <Text Key="3A31A877">Rug Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="47108002">A funnel used to pour bird seed into the feeder.</Text>
  <Text Key="04078FFD">Bird Seed Funnel</Text>
  <Text Key="4E9E54F2">Oh Windemere! When its musically gifted citizens aren't busy creating tourist videos for their sister city of Windenburg, they're honing their age-honored tradition of wind chime craftsmanship. Now you can bring the sound of Windemere into your own home!*\n\nChoose from bamboo, ceramic, or metallic chimes.** Set the pitch of your chimes by changing the length of the rods. Mount them on your wall, or hang them from the ceiling.*** No matter if you have a single wind chime or group them together, you're sure to love the melodic notes wafting through your yard.\n\n*AA Batteries included for indoor operation.\n**Bamboo and aluminum chimes sold separately.\n***Wall mounted wind chimes sold separately.</Text>
  <Text Key="FA37A08D">Wind Chimes of Windemere - Ceramic / Hanging</Text>
  <Text Key="BE5690ED">Oh Windemere! When its musically gifted citizens aren't busy creating tourist videos for their sister city of Windenburg, they're honing their age-honored tradition of wind chime craftsmanship. Now you can bring the sound of Windemere into your own home!*\n\nChoose from bamboo, ceramic, or aluminum chimes.** Set the pitch of your chimes by changing the length of the rods. Mount them on your wall, or hang them from the ceiling.*** No matter if you have a single wind chime or group them together, you're sure to love the melodic notes wafting through your yard.\n\n*AA Batteries included for indoor operation.\n**Bamboo and ceramic chimes sold separately.\n***Wall mounted wind chimes sold separately.</Text>
  <Text Key="2F3FCAB8">Wind Chimes of Windemere - Aluminum / Hanging</Text>
  <Text Key="DD6CC9D1">Oh Windemere! When its musically gifted citizens aren't busy creating tourist videos for their sister city of Windenburg, they're honing their age-honored tradition of wind chime craftsmanship. Now you can bring the sound of Windemere into your own home!*\n\nChoose from bamboo, ceramic, or aluminum chimes.** Set the pitch of your chimes by changing the length of the rods. Mount them on your wall, or hang them from the ceiling.*** No matter if you have a single wind chime or group them together, you're sure to love the melodic notes wafting through your yard.\n\n*AA Batteries included for indoor operation.\n**Ceramic and aluminum chimes sold separately.\n***Wall mounted wind chimes sold separately.</Text>
  <Text Key="D7062B24">Wind Chimes of Windemere - Bamboo / Hanging</Text>
  <Text Key="AA3987F3">Oh Windemere! When its musically gifted citizens aren't busy creating tourist videos for their sister city of Windenburg, they're honing their age-honored tradition of wind chime craftsmanship. Now you can bring the sound of Windemere into your own home!*\n\nChoose from bamboo, ceramic, or aluminum chimes.** Set the pitch of your chimes by changing the length of the rods. Mount them on your wall, or hang them from the ceiling.*** No matter if you have a single wind chime or group them together, you're sure to love the melodic notes wafting through your yard.\n\n*AA Batteries included for indoor operation.\n**Bamboo and aluminum chimes sold separately.\n***Ceiling hanging wind chimes sold separately.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F7C1622">Wind Chimes of Windemere - Ceramic / Wall Mounted</Text>
  <Text Key="1F65D6EC">Oh Windemere! When its musically gifted citizens aren't busy creating tourist videos for their sister city of Windenburg, they're honing their age-honored tradition of wind chime craftsmanship. Now you can bring the sound of Windemere into your own home!*\n\nChoose from bamboo, ceramic, or aluminum chimes.** Set the pitch of your chimes by changing the length of the rods. Mount them on your wall, or hang them from the ceiling.*** No matter if you have a single wind chime or group them together, you're sure to love the melodic notes wafting through your yard.\n\n*AA Batteries included for indoor operation.\n**Bamboo and ceramic chimes sold separately.\n***Ceiling hanging wind chimes sold separately.</Text>
  <Text Key="CFD83323">Wind Chimes of Windemere - Aluminum / Wall Mounted</Text>
  <Text Key="DDB3AE42">Oh Windemere! When its musically gifted citizens aren't busy creating tourist videos for their sister city of Windenburg, they're honing their age-honored tradition of wind chime craftsmanship. Now you can bring the sound of Windemere into your own home!*\n\nChoose from bamboo, ceramic, or aluminum chimes.** Set the pitch of your chimes by changing the length of the rods. Mount them on your wall, or hang them from the ceiling.*** No matter if you have a single wind chime or group them together, you're sure to love the melodic notes wafting through your yard.\n\n*AA Batteries included for indoor operation.\n**Ceramic and aluminum chimes sold separately.\n***Ceiling hanging wind chimes sold separately.</Text>
  <Text Key="46320D3D">Wind Chimes of Windemere - Bamboo / Wall Mounted</Text>
  <Text Key="BE255B0B">Set to Spoiled</Text>
  <Text Key="30E7AFA3">Set to Empty</Text>
  <Text Key="758F7FF3">Empty Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="0072A37A">Mix Citrus Swig</Text>
  <Text Key="088A71C2">Mix Iced Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="6F604BF4">Mix Lemonade</Text>
  <Text Key="0EAF9FF7">Pour Drinks</Text>
  <Text Key="8F0241E8">Gross! There aren't any fresh drinks to take from the tray.</Text>
  <Text Key="B4AC353D">Grab Drink</Text>
  <Text Key="39272868">This object must be placed outside to be filled with bird seed.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0844638">Add Bird Seed</Text>
  <Text Key="CA63D5A0">Force Bird Attack (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="04177AA9">There are no birds feeding at this time.</Text>
  <Text Key="7DB005E8">Watch Birds</Text>
  <Text Key="971D8D3B">Add Soap</Text>
  <Text Key="90A7D888">Set Auto Water Controls</Text>
  <Text Key="352A94DC">Keep Water On</Text>
  <Text Key="5D7FF410">Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="81EF919F">Trick Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="D1080076">Watch Sliders</Text>
  <Text Key="7D944411">Turn Off</Text>
  <Text Key="B9A4DDE7">Turn On</Text>
  <Text Key="169FB2E1">Ceramic</Text>
  <Text Key="0C493B70">Metal</Text>
  <Text Key="E27173FA">Bamboo</Text>
  <Text Key="0387DB9C">High Pitch</Text>
  <Text Key="1F5B8140">Low Pitch</Text>
  <Text Key="C0BBB919">Medium Pitch</Text>
  <Text Key="F3D2DA66">React to Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="B50C9A56">Waiting to Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="8252BA2E">Slide With</Text>
  <Text Key="967409DD">Trick Slide With</Text>
  <Text Key="DDA53B16">Flowery Escape</Text>
  <Text Key="80848D17">Backyard Dreamscape</Text>
  <Text Key="E842BB9A">Serious Waterworks</Text>
  <Text Key="2F720CEE">{0.ObjectName}</Text>
  <Text Key="746D06A5">Spoiled</Text>
  <Text Key="F03061A0">Fresh</Text>
  <Text Key="9F7E36D4">Full</Text>
  <Text Key="557AD095">Empty Pitcher</Text>
  <Text Key="50BB894F">One Serving Left</Text>
  <Text Key="1FD4092D">Lemonade</Text>
  <Text Key="96B41F2F">Iced Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="5E492C9E">Citrus Swig</Text>
  <Text Key="DE6638E6">Mix Drink</Text>
  <Text Key="765824D0">Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="E99D9F69">Change Material</Text>
  <Text Key="5F32B3A4">Change Pitch</Text>
  <Text Key="7870ABC8">Citrus Swig</Text>
  <Text Key="CF49BD64">Iced Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="44638AD6">Lemonade</Text>
  <Text Key="0E5F63C3">Perform Trick Slides</Text>
  <Text Key="CC6D65CD">Click on a Lawn Water Slide and select Trick Slide.</Text>
  <Text Key="E469A7D4">(From Wind Chime)</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>