<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="E5467655">Greenhouse Pavers</Text>
  <Text Key="0C87F80B">Make the most of your greenhouse with this gorgeous pair of double doors. The wide glass panels and sleek design will ensure maximum sunlight exposure for your menagerie of plants. Revolutionize your space and create the ultimate greenhouse of your dreams! </Text>
  <Text Key="B227D28A">Greenview Double Doors</Text>
  <Text Key="580199CE">Looking for a way to really make your greenhouse stand out? This pair of double doors is just what you need! If it doesn't do something for you, we're not sure what will.</Text>
  <Text Key="081A83F1">Tall Greenview Double Doors</Text>
  <Text Key="5AB158C5">The Greenview Door offers superior security and visibility. Easy to use and maintain, this greenhouse glass door lets you monitor the growth of your plants and all that goes on inside. Now's the time to put down the houseplants and embrace your inner green thumb.</Text>
  <Text Key="024F3FC0">Greenview Door </Text>
  <Text Key="B05E38C8">Not enough sunlight? Worry no more—the Solar Wall Light is here! Fuel your plants with solar light and they'll bloom like never before. Watch as this lamp promotes rapid growth, giving your plants a brighter future and ensuring that even the smallest of greenhouses are filled to the brim with vitality. </Text>
  <Text Key="96D01667">Solar Wall Light</Text>
  <Text Key="78C0060E">If you want to add a little whimsical touch to your home, or just want something green to spruce up your outdoor space, then look no further. This tiny vine plant is the perfect addition. Carefree, easy to care for, and practically indestructible, this mini plant will surely impress with its tiny size and resilient demeanor. Let this little guy live its best life in your garden or keep it in a pot on the windowsill. It'll be happy either way!</Text>
  <Text Key="51A0FB31">The Miniature Vine</Text>
  <Text Key="E3CEBA23">At the moment these planters are still in your shed, serving as pretty intermediate storage for the fluffs from your tumble dryer. But you're planning to use them for new plants... soon... ish...</Text>
  <Text Key="AD7F6FF2">Planters for Future Plants</Text>
  <Text Key="F899D6A7">Do you have plants that are outgrowing their pots? Well, now you can get them a new home! These planters are empty but ready to be filled to the brim and take on the job of holding your larger, more mature plants. As an added bonus, they stack vertically and don't take up much floor space!</Text>
  <Text Key="7833DDDE">The Vertical Stack</Text>
  <Text Key="F5B66EBA">This wooden trunk is a sturdy and stylish storage solution for any Sim's collection of gardening supplies. Whether you're looking for a practical storage solution or want to store your tools in rustic style, this wooden chest will be the perfect addition to your garden space.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E042065">GardenStash Storage Chest</Text>
  <Text Key="F593545C">An essential collection of tools that no gardener could live without. You'll surely find yourself reaching for these classic and timeless tools every time you need to get your hands dirty in the garden. </Text>
  <Text Key="D7710133">The Gardener's Haul</Text>
  <Text Key="E1B1FEAF">Let your neighbors know that you mean business in the garden with this surprisingly messy collection of gardening supplies. From the soil filled pot with the well-used trowel, to the crumpled bags of mulch, it tells everyone around that you have the ultimate green thumb. </Text>
  <Text Key="73A6B8F6">Mulch-to-do about Planting</Text>
  <Text Key="E5281DA2">You've managed to come this far. You helped to create new life and now you've transferred your fresh grown seedlings from their seed pot to their own individual pots. Everything is going according to plan. Stay calm! There's nothing that can go wrong at this point... right?</Text>
  <Text Key="8216561D">Out of the Woods Seedlings</Text>
  <Text Key="96E627BC">The truth behind every green thumb's gift—a collection of elixirs especially concocted to put the pep back into your perennial's step! (Results not guaranteed.)</Text>
  <Text Key="824D0B13">Green Thumb's Secret Solutions</Text>
  <Text Key="8C962A07">A classic piece—these pots are essential for every gardener and if you're looking for something a bit more rugged than a typical planter, these are just right. With their timeless look and sturdy design, they're ready to stand up to anything you can throw at them... except a rock.</Text>
  <Text Key="BDE8C9BE">Ceramic Planters</Text>
  <Text Key="C8050E6B">What are plants without pots? Or hats without heads? They may be nothing crazy, but they are the best way to get a small houseplant started. </Text>
  <Text Key="2D049D6A">The Ceramic Stack</Text>
  <Text Key="46568F6E">You're growing a plant. The labels say annual, and you don't know what that means. It seems like you gave it the right amount of water, despite the yellow leaves. If you water it way too often, could it thrive to the point of only just looking dead? Give it another go with this seedling...</Text>
  <Text Key="05B07211">Starter Seedling</Text>
  <Text Key="9F7D2426">You are confident that this time it will work. And the fact that this is your fifth seedling starter set means nothing...</Text>
  <Text Key="7D404639">Hopes and Dreams Seedpot Set</Text>
  <Text Key="AB881C1A">Give your plants the air they crave! With The AirCycler's powerful airflow, removing stale air and bringing fresh air into your greenhouse has never been easier. The ventilation will provide a stable breeze that keeps your plants both healthy and happy all year long. </Text>
  <Text Key="C2648545">The AirCycler</Text>
  <Text Key="B74F3307">This ventilation grate will be the crowning touch to your greenhouse. After all, the best greenhouse ventilation isn't just an option, it's an essential element to the success of your plants.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F8394BE">The Green Gable</Text>
  <Text Key="6EF98336">Bring color and life to any space with this vibrant hanging basket. Perfect for your patio, balcony or poolside, these blooming flowers are sure to brighten up your space.</Text>
  <Text Key="1FE31169">The Blooming Basket</Text>
  <Text Key="919341AE">This is where it all begins—a seed planted and watered, where creation happens. From there, it’s up to you how you will fill your space. Will it be with a splendid array of wildflowers or a quaint collection of vegetables? Whatever the case may be, with this workbench, you have all the tools and supplies to plant and create the ultimate garden your heart desires.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AD8F751">The Gardener's Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="AE06E6AF">You may have dabbled in gardening, but now it's time to take things up a notch—literally. This workbench will give your plants space to grow while keeping all your garden essentials handy. We don't know how you'd live without this table, but if you do, it's probably because you're lost deep inside a greenhouse! Tidy up and get your plants prioritized with this timeless design.</Text>
  <Text Key="3740F0F6">The ShedShelves Table</Text>
  <Text Key="81573185">Get your plants off the ground with The Plant Platform by Plant-It! This simple shelf is the perfect way to organize all your plants and keep them in the sunlight.</Text>
  <Text Key="CCC66580">The Plant Platform by Plant-It</Text>
  <Text Key="559F0EE0">A breeze through a greenhouse window is one of the purest experiences in life. So, here's your chance to enjoy it by opening up your space to the delights of the outdoors. You'll live on the edge by letting more than a breeze inside, but it has the perfect amount of drama for you and your garden. Precarious isn't just the perfect word to describe the current climate, it's also the perfect word to describe this window. </Text>
  <Text Key="B30D832F">Open Greenview Window</Text>
  <Text Key="0408C605">More natural light? Yes, please. We know you've been waiting for an excuse to let the sun in and finally, the Greenview Window has you covered. This window will let you embrace your inner botanist and be surrounded by an opulent abundance of greenery.</Text>
  <Text Key="3865FB00">Greenview Window</Text>
  <Text Key="22218834">This is one of the tallest and largest greenhouse windows ever made. No matter what the weather is outside, this window will maximize the use of the sun's rays and provide the ultimate experience in greenhouse care. </Text>
  <Text Key="2AA7BB9B">Tall Greenview Window</Text>
  <Text Key="6AB7DBD9">Paned Planting Space</Text>
  <Text Key="9417E00B">No matter how you look at it, a greenhouse roof is the key to growing your plants, so let the sun shine in completely uninhibited!</Text>
  <Text Key="BC830A8A">Greenhouse Glass Roof</Text>
  <Text Key="4A7805C6">Greenhouse Wall</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>