<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="79D5503D">(From Being Near Algae at Night)</Text>
  <Text Key="37B354A3">(From Picking Grapes in the Wild)</Text>
  <Text Key="76894743">(From Picking Tartosian Flowers)</Text>
  <Text Key="2CA70D97">(From Romance at the Lover's Tree)</Text>
  <Text Key="4997831A">(From Sea Swimming)</Text>
  <Text Key="E1CBDF0F">(From Tossing a Coin in the Fountain)</Text>
  <Text Key="541E31F6">(From Romance in the Village Square)</Text>
  <Text Key="23FDDDC1">(From Swimming Near the Waterfall)</Text>
  <Text Key="8693EA85">(From Asking About Wedding Day)</Text>
  <Text Key="B037F803">(From Being Asked About Wedding Day)</Text>
  <Text Key="050F79F8">{0.SimFirstName} found a message in a bottle buried in the sand!</Text>
  <Text Key="77CD50D0">(From Putting Down A Bouquet)</Text>
  <Text Key="05C84656">(From Doing a Group Wedding Dance Together)</Text>
  <Text Key="BFA61BDA">Gossip fresh off the grapevine!</Text>
  <Text Key="D229A224">The City Hall offers quick weddings for those visiting who can't wait another day. Sometimes love just won't let you wait, eh?</Text>
  <Text Key="29C48308">They say Lady Matilda Tartosa used to live in a grand castle close to Hideaway Falls. Nobody can find the ruins, though. We do know that she used the Falls for illicit trades with pirates, but perhaps the castle ruins lie elsewhere.</Text>
  <Text Key="48E91267">Ages ago, a local shipwright carved the likeness of Princess Cordelia and her pirate lover, Rodrigo De Pablo, into the figurehead of a ship. When the ship sank those who remembered their love carried the figurehead to the top of the hill by Hideaway Falls as a reminder. A year passed and it magically began to sprout leaves and branches, a sign that their love lived on even though Rodrigo had passed. Today, you can visit the tree, and if your heart is pure, some of that love magic will rub off on you!</Text>
  <Text Key="DE7AE859">Don't forget to visit the local patisserie in Tartosa. We're famous for our fruit tarts and pastries, but it's also great if you want to sample some of the amazing wedding cakes they can whip up.</Text>
  <Text Key="438906BE">Aren't the hot air balloons in the sky romantic?</Text>
  <Text Key="DD9768EA">It's a common rumor around here that when the Thebe Estate was built, construction was funded using a chest of pirate's gold. There's another rumor that after he built the Villa, Rodrigo Thebe buried the rest of the gold somewhere near the village. If you could find it, you'd be rich! Then again, they sure seemed to spend an awful lot to make that place look luxe, didn't they? Maybe all that's left is a bit of pocket change.</Text>
  <Text Key="325842DA">Everyone knows about the glowing tides at night. It's said the strange glow used to draw in lost pirates, in fact. But the beaches have even more surprises in store, you know! If you search the shores, you'll sometimes find a message in a bottle. They wash up fairly regularly.  </Text>
  <Text Key="0411EF87">Sims around here are always talking about how Arnessa Thebe once sailed a little rowboat over Hideaway Falls? She broke a leg—literally. That's why they put in the bridge—to keep Sims from trying to sail over!</Text>
  <Text Key="18B8C2D1">Did you know that the fruit we use in our world-famous tarts is local fruit? Yeah! You could even go out and pick your own if you wanted.</Text>
  <Text Key="5B49E8A4">Have you noticed the flower cart in town? They get their flowers locally, for the most part. If you wanted, you could probably even go out and pick some of your own. </Text>
  <Text Key="6655FB58">We see so many proposals here! It's the romantic aura of the land. Also, it's great for dates! Off the top of my head, you could take a dip at the base of Hideaway Falls, watch the glowing waves at night, take a walk on the beach, or visit Porto Luminoso's Village fountain. The Lover's Tree is also a popular destination, of course.</Text>
  <Text Key="9D8226D6">Did you know that if you visit the beach at night you might see the ocean glow? Some say that's what attracted Princess Cordelia to Tartosa back in the day.</Text>
  <Text Key="64153C40">The Porto Luminoso fountain is always a romantic spot to visit. I always see couples cuddled up on the edge.</Text>
  <Text Key="ED6289B0">Everyone loves the area's fruit tarts. I'm more of a macaron person myself. I suppose it seems a little, well, on the nose for someone like me but I don't actually like putting on airs, you know. Hand me a box of macarons from the patisserie here and as soon as I'm on my own, I'll devour it all in seconds. Don't tell anyone else that, though. I suppose I might want to preserve some element of aloofness here and there.</Text>
  <Text Key="97A3398E">If you're here to find out where the pirate's gold is buried, I'll tell you what I tell everyone. I don't know. Please stop asking. </Text>
  <Text Key="74849903">I hope you're having a lovely day, and perhaps a day with a little touch of romance. This is the perfect place to find love... or see it flourish. Of course, good relationships require careful cultivating!</Text>
  <Text Key="122CBA05">I've gotten up to a bit of mischief in my day. I certainly won't own to any of it though! Though I will say, they did a spectacular job of repairing the fountain in the village square after, well, as I said: I won't own any of it. Mischief is best left to that Markovic man, don't you think?</Text>
  <Text Key="9A2203BC">Where's my favorite place in the area? Well, I've always felt drawn to the ocean. I love seeing the glowing tides at night. It makes me feel like I'm part of something truly mysterious and interesting. Isn't nature spectacular in that way?</Text>
  <Text Key="10EE16EE">I never say who my favorite grandchild is. Do I have one? Yes, of course. Nobody will ever find out who though! Not unless you want to bribe me with some macarons...</Text>
  <Text Key="BCC995FB">Oh, everyone says I'm related to Princess Cordelia. Who knows. That was such a long time ago. I'm not really one for nostalgia, you know. I live my life in the moment as much as I can. Don't you think that's the best way to go about things?</Text>
  <Text Key="CF214A09">I don't really enjoy comedy. It was always a favorite of Hilary's though... For entertainment, I've always vastly preferred music. I've been playing the piano since I was three. I'm quite proficient. Lest you think I'm only interested in stuffier music, however; I'm actually quite interested in jazz improv!</Text>
  <Text Key="A4BB19D7">To be honest, when I was younger, I always felt a little overwhelmed by all of the Princess Cordelia talk. That's a lot to live up to. I think I've forged my own path through life now though. I'm quite pleased to have lived the life I have. I just wish people didn't assume that I'm a snobby, unfriendly person. Nothing could be further from the truth! I just appreciate taking time to get to know a person before I open up too much. You have to keep yourself safe, you know.</Text>
  <Text Key="F42A6860">What happened to Hector's father, you ask? Years ago, our stove malfunctioned and caught on fire. It certainly wasn't his cooking skill. He was an excellent chef. I remember how he used to make the best macarons. It was a tragic accident, but while I miss my husband I prefer to keep looking ahead. I can't wait to see what my grandchildren do with their lives. </Text>
  <Text Key="541BD255">People ask me all the time if I'm sad I'll be the last Thebe of the area. "It's such an old name..." they say. Perhaps, yes, and it's a bit sad. But I wanted my son to grow up without the same level of notoriety I experienced. There were times I felt like a curiosity rather than a person. Today, I'm glad Hector has his father's name. Its one of the ways I can remember him. </Text>
  <Text Key="22704378">We're close enough, I'll admit it. Yes, my family does trace their lineage back to Princess Cordelia. City Hall has records from when my grandfather arrived, and we have historical artifacts all around the house. But speak with the town historian if you want to learn more, friend. Believe it or not, she's much more attuned to these matters and knows more about my family than I do!</Text>
  <Text Key="A02E810E">I've been reading through old letters I received years ago. I rather miss my Aunt Queen and Uncle Eetion. My father and I used to visit them from time to time when I was a little girl. Those were my first trips on the ocean. To think that I have ancestors who spent time on pirate ships or submersibles! I thought I was quite the wild child just going out on a sailboat from time to time. </Text>
  <Text Key="50063749">There's some evidence suggesting that Princess Cordelia and Lady Matilda Tartosa were very close during her stay here. It's unlikely they were lovers, given the Princess' feelings for Rodrigo. Still, the princess and Lady Tartosa spent a lot of time together at the beach, sailing the coast and devouring tarts. There's also evidence suggesting their relationship ended on rocky terms, but nobody knows for certain why. Some think Lady Tartosa had an affair with Rodrigo. Others believe she stiffed Princess Cordelia on a fruit tart, which was a serious offense back in those days. Frankly, it's a serious offense these days as well, given the quality of the tarts here.</Text>
  <Text Key="968F3189">A few years ago, famous artist, Igor Klobučar, was paid by Porto Luminoso to create an installation around the theme of romantic love. You'll find his finished piece, The Glass Heart, over in the gardens. The material represents the fragility of something as precious as love and the twists and turns we go through to find it. The two strands reminds us that its a journey you take with another person, too. They intertwine; crossing ways as Sims in love often do.</Text>
  <Text Key="C532CDCA">Tartosa is famous for its history with pirates. In the old days, they used to steal llamas and bring them here for a quick trade. Sometimes for gold, sometimes for tarts and pastries (and lots of them, I'd wager). Porto Luminoso is almost as famous for its tarts and pastries as it is for its history with pirates.</Text>
  <Text Key="80E3344D">Lady Matilda Tartosa is perhaps the area's most famous noble. We don't have lords or ladies here anymore, of course. She was the youngest of three children and the last to inherit her title. Her eldest sister, Gianna, loved maps and left to chart the world, never returning. Her brother, Luca, was next in line and something of an astronomer. He would spend his nights looking up into the sky through a telescope he invented himself. It's said one night he simply disappeared. Nobody knows what happened to him. They both left Matilda here on her own, and she proved to be a very fruitful steward of the area. Most notably she increased trade and gave the area its first real staple: desserts. </Text>
  <Text Key="474C7737">There's a long list of pirates who visited here. Some of the most famous were Rodrigo De Pablo, of course, Two-Eye Charlie - later known as One-Eye Charlie -  plus Captain Rachael the Fearsome, Raider Rad who, well, raided, Dash who was the shortest yet fastest pirate ever, Five Finger Fran, First Mate Barnacle Bob, and even the Dread Pirate Morgan on the Red Annie.</Text>
  <Text Key="93FF50B8">History will never know exactly why Princess Cordelia left Tartosa. We know she was one of the first Sims to explore the arctic waters in her submersible, the Eppsilon, and that was after she had already left. But why? Perhaps she, like the locals, was afraid it was only a matter of time before the dreaded sloths swam to our shores. Or perhaps she was an adventurer at heart, unable to settle in one spot for long. Maybe it was the death of her beloved Rodrigo that pushed her away? We'll never know for sure, but I certainly love thinking about it.</Text>
  <Text Key="F4ED1AC7">Rodrigo De Pablo was Princess Cordelia's third pirate boyfriend - yes, third! - and perhaps the greatest love of her life. It's said he was rather clumsy, and there's a lot of historical speculation around how he actually died. Some say his peg leg caught on fire aboard the Eppsilon, the Princess' ship. Others say he had an affair with Lady Tartosa and Princess Cordelia hired a witch to trap him inside a glass bottle she cast out to sea. I've also heard he choked on a tart, which seems the least ridiculous to me. Either way, history knows that when Princess Cordelia departed Tartosa, her beloved Rodrigo was not with her.</Text>
  <Text Key="B391195D">Lady Matilda Tartosa was the last of the nobles in Tartosa. She never married, nor had a lover—despite having a dazzling array of suitors. Nobody knows why. What we do know is that she lived out her days here, a diligent steward of her position and privilege, eventually dying of old age. In her last days, she saw the land given back to the people who have run it together ever since. </Text>
  <Text Key="7E495D61">People are always asking me why its assumed that Arnessa Thebe is related to Princess Cordelia, since its well-known that Princess Cordelia left. Well, after a bit of digging, I discovered some evidence at City Hall stating that twenty years after she left, a gentleman by the name of Rodrigo Thebe returned. He claimed that his father had died here and his mother was the late Princess. With his vast fortune, Rodrigo had Thebe Estate built. Supposedly, there are some ancestors still around today.</Text>
  <Text Key="E3236DFB">Why is Tartosa famous for its pastries? Well, its where the tart was invented! Lady Matilda Tartosa loved fruit, you see, and one of her suitors created the dessert to impress her- going so far as to name it after her. Demand for the confectionary went up when the pirates started arriving to trade their stolen llamas. At that point, there was what is now known as 'The Great Tart Crisis." Due to a lack of supply, other pastries had to be made to satisfy the needs of supply and demand. Lucky for me, I can also grab a macaron anytime I like, too.</Text>
  <Text Key="471359FE">Back in the old days, pirates were always arriving at port to trade their stolen llamas for tarts and treats. There was one llama, however, that became something of a town legend. His name was Doug. They say he could spit over forty feet, which is utterly ridiculous. But that's not why he's famous, in fact. One day, a Pirate named Two-Eye Charlie arrived to steal back the llamas, and the villagers were too terrified to fight back. Doug wasn't afraid. He spat directly into Two-Eye Charlie's eye, renaming him One-Eye Charlie. He left in rather a hurry soon thereafter!</Text>
  <Text Key="47A52232">No, Princess Cordelia wasn't originally from here. Her kingdom was not too far away across the sea. When the Great Sloth Invasion took place, she escaped on her submersible, the Eppsilon, with her first pirate boyfriend Captain Long John Buttercups. They didn't come here though. She came here much later—and with a different pirate. That Cordelia certainly had a type, didn't she? </Text>
  <Text Key="EA715346">I asked about the Lover's Tree when I arrived here. Most believe that long ago, a local shipwright carved the likeness of Princess Cordelia and Rodrigo De Pablo into the figurehead of a ship. When the ship sank, those who remembered their love carried it to the top of the hill by Hideaway Falls as a reminder. A year passed, and it magically began to sprout leaves and branches: a sign that their love lived on even though Rodrigo had passed. But I think, as romantic as that is, sometimes a tree is just a tree. Dominique is utterly fascinated by it all the same, though.</Text>
  <Text Key="97A4B42E">The Tartosa area was originally settled by the Tartosa family. They had a castle along the cliffs, but the section it was on fell into the water, never to be seen again. I occasionally wonder if it would be worthwhile to dive and look for artifacts, but Dominique tells me that it'd be a fool's errand.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E1FBCF6">Was Thebe Estate built with pirate's gold? Most people seem to think so, but there's no substantial evidence in the City Hall records. It &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; quite an expensive investment, but who knows where the money came from. </Text>
  <Text Key="65E55113">The Tartosa locals at the time of the Great Sloth Invasion were terrified the sloths might make it here. After all, sloths are surprisingly strong swimmers. They use their long arms to propel through the water at an alarming speed they're never able to attain on land. Thankfully, they never reached our shores. We might not be here today if they had. I shudder to think!</Text>
  <Text Key="7596F145">Greta Laurent resembles the descriptions I've read about Princess Cordelia. Mostly her adventurous nature, but perhaps it's also her penchant for mischief. Arnessa has that as well. I think Greta is her favorite. </Text>
  <Text Key="AB08A5DA">Something I've learned in life... choose to live somewhere you love. You'll find so much more enjoyment in the day-to-day. </Text>
  <Text Key="0A6F3D71">My favorite piece of life advice: Always invest in those you care about. Relationships fade over time if they are not properly tended. They're like flowers in need of care. </Text>
  <Text Key="B4BAF4B9">Dominique and I were friends long before we fell in love. We almost didn't end up together. I'm thankful every day we did.</Text>
  <Text Key="4CFA3438">I love talking about the area's history. Most around here don't have the same thirst for knowledge I do, so I'm pleased that you are interested. </Text>
  <Text Key="6636C511">I absolutely adore Mateo's melodies. If you've never heard that man play on the piano, you really should hire him and have the opportunity. What a lovely &lt;i&gt;and talented&lt;/i&gt; person. </Text>
  <Text Key="8101FBA3">No, I'm not originally from Tartosa. Camille and I met here, became friends here, and were eventually married here. We always knew that when we retired we would once again be... here.</Text>
  <Text Key="C0F96B06">Sure I know all of the best locations for picture-perfect paintings. But I'm not about to just share all of my secrets with anyone, am I. Great art must be experienced through adventure!</Text>
  <Text Key="4F130F36">I've lived all over the world, actually. Windenburg was lovely, and probably my second favorite. Tartosa is where I'll live out the rest of my days, though. If you don't live in your favorite locale, are you even living?</Text>
  <Text Key="71237853">I do love a good book, you know. A nice cozy mystery or, better still, a romantic story set against the backdrop of a historical moment. I've been trying to get Camille to write one about the area for years. A historical fiction, drama'd up to be fun.</Text>
  <Text Key="575ACAB0">Oh, I had the opportunity to meet Igor Klobučar when he was in Porto Luminoso installing his sculpture. Artist to artist! Can you imagine? What a charming Sim. Did you know he used to be a hatmaker for llamas? Hated it. You have to chase your dreams, even if it does lead you away from llamas from time to time. </Text>
  <Text Key="48E89611">What is my favorite book? Could I even pick one?! The Chronicles of Rodiek by Dominick VanDeesel is very good as is A Game of Groans by Greg Q.Q. Vartin. I could go on all day, really, but I won't. </Text>
  <Text Key="C875E129">Faiz is a poetic soul. I do hope he finds love soon. He's too sweet a rose to go unnoticed, don't you think?</Text>
  <Text Key="0C7BB123">I do love dancing. Any sort really, but slow dancing is by far my favorite. What's more romantic than twirling on a dance floor with the one you love, moving with grace and charm... it makes me want to get married all over again!</Text>
  <Text Key="6C532954">I don't think about the family feud between the Markovics and the Laurents much. It's such a lovely area. Why doesn't everyone try and get along for once? Let bygones be bygones. If I felt like holding a grudge, I still wouldn't be speaking with one of my dearest friends after she critiqued my last art installation!</Text>
  <Text Key="CBEB8C7B">About a decade ago, I spent a lot of time painting Thebe Estate. Camille was fascinated by its history and it inspired something in me as well. Arnessa was always kind enough to bring tea out to me as I worked. A spot of black tea really gets the mind percolating.</Text>
  <Text Key="58F569FC">You want to find some of the most beautiful, underappreciated views in Porto Luminoso? Follow the trails behind the buildings. Mazes, beaches, overlooks - all of it gorgeous. Wait for the sunlight to hit them just right, and you have a special setting for your art.</Text>
  <Text Key="F123DAE2">Maybe it's obvious, but Hideaway Falls is one of the most beautiful spots in Tartosa. When Camille and I met, we spent most of our time there. That was my favorite painting subject at the time. Well, after her, of course.</Text>
  <Text Key="CF4CF664">I can't tell you how many times I've painted the Lover's Tree. From every angle, mind you! As intimate as I am with it as a subject, I can't help but feel it does have a connection with the Sims who come to visit—even if the rumors aren't true.</Text>
  <Text Key="D83F072C">Have you noticed the hill on the side of Porto Luminoso? You can get the most beautiful top down views of the village from there. A new perspective does wonders to shake things up if you're feeling a bit stuck.</Text>
  <Text Key="003601BB">If you want to paint something colorful, try the marina. The boats are splendidly vibrant and who doesn't love a good seagull?</Text>
  <Text Key="F837DECF">Down the coast in Terra Amorosa, there is this darling grove of trees. A lot of Sims who come here to get married take pictures there, but it's beautiful for paintings as well. Just imagine what some of those old trees have witnessed in days gone by. If I stand still enough, I sometimes swear I can hear the trees communicating. But that's silly, isn't it? I know, I sound like an overly whimsical artist, don't I? </Text>
  <Text Key="6F3B2F74">Sometimes I paint Sims and not scenes. After Camille, Faiz is my favorite. He has such a light in his eyes. It's the exuberance of youth, I imagine, though there's something unique about Faiz that I truly admire. </Text>
  <Text Key="EB7A6AEC">My favorite spot to paint? Right here in Porto Luminoso. The people, the sea, the painted buildings. Nature is lovely, but this is life as it's meant to be experienced: right in the thick of things!</Text>
  <Text Key="44F10773">Everyone loves the fruit tarts around here, and I do too! But I also love the macarons. And the cake. Okay, maybe I just have a sweet tooth. But if you live here, it's practically a requirement. You try running a flower cart with the smell of amazing things baking nearby all the time without developing one!</Text>
  <Text Key="2D923180">Hey there! I hope you're having a lovely day. If you didn't know, I run the flower cart in the village. Feel free to come by anytime to pick out the best flowers the area has to offer, or just to say hello. I always love chatting with people.</Text>
  <Text Key="ADC3ED56">Once I picked up the book, "Pickup Lines for the Flirtatiously Inept" by Dr. Phyllis. I'm not sure it was very helpful; I much preferred "Diplomacy for Dummies" by Dimitry Hard. Of course, Dimitry tends to skimp a bit on the romance, but nobody's perfect.</Text>
  <Text Key="211BE3AC">Yes, I sell flowers from my cart. But as a tip, if you need to save some money.... you can always find wild flowers growing outside the village around here. They're lovely, too, and hand-picked flowers always send a special message when you give them to others.</Text>
  <Text Key="853BD7E0">Most people don't know it, but I also really enjoy photography. There are some great places around here to take pictures. If you're close with Dominique, she might give you some pointers. As a painter she's already found all the best spots. Once I found her hanging upside down from the Lover's Tree to "get a new perspective" on life. Artists, eh?</Text>
  <Text Key="D601ADFF">Do you have a favorite poet? Mine is Mabel Eloise Clift. She works with post-modern verse, and her poems are surprisingly short. Very impactful though. I like the one called Rose. I can recite it from heart. It goes like this: "Red. A rose." </Text>
  <Text Key="E6CB7A24">Did you know I love writing poetry? Of course I do. Flowers. Romance. It speaks to my soul! I could tell you chapter and verse just about how much I love to write, well, chapter and verse!</Text>
  <Text Key="B32570AF">I spend a lot of my day daydreaming—when I'm not speaking to a customer, of course. There's so much I want out of life, especially love. </Text>
  <Text Key="CAD9635F">I really appreciate it when people take time out of their day to talk with me. Even though things seem a little more laid-back on Tartosa, sometimes people get so absorbed in the day-to-day that they don't stop to, well, smell the roses. Sorry, that's so corny! But I'm happy to talk with you more!</Text>
  <Text Key="AFABC7F0">How are you enjoying things in Tartosa? You know my family lives in the Laurent Villa. Many still call it the Thebe Estate. My family decided to change things up a bit. Maybe pull a little attention away from some of the family history, y'know? Anyway, I live there and we also own a couple other spots around here. Hopefully, you'll get to see them all.</Text>
  <Text Key="57CFBB00">Sure, you can get married at City Hall if you're in a big rush, but why not opt for a big ceremony and reception? My family's great at helping everyone set up the best wedding you can buy, even on a smaller budget. Ask anyone! Well, don't ask Mateo Markovic. The guy's nice enough, but, well, local rivalries die hard I guess.</Text>
  <Text Key="1F70AA70">My kids, Greta and Jace, can be a bit of a handful sometimes. But I bet if you asked my wife, she'd say I'm just as much of a handful. What can I say? I can be a bit of a party creature from time to time. But that Greta, wow, can she get into some serious mischief when your back is turned.</Text>
  <Text Key="26D18F1B">Have you tried the roast duck down in the village where the restaurants are? You absolutely have to! That's one of my wife's family recipes, you know. Well, a lot of the recipes in those shops are. Her parents started those restaurants and kind of had a restaurant empire of sorts here on Tartosa. If you don't like to eat meat, there are some pretty fantastic veggie dumplings, too. </Text>
  <Text Key="E040B66E">Everyone always talks up Hideaway Falls and don't get me wrong, they're beautiful, but I love just standing out near the beach and looking towards the sea. There's a whole world of possibility out there, you know? Sometimes I wonder if I'd like to travel the world a bit, but then I remember that I have everything I need right here at home. </Text>
  <Text Key="BE1F3985">We don't talk about a lot of the local legends within my own family. I heard a lot of stories about Princess Cordelia and pirate lore just from being in school. When I was little, I searched the house up and down for secret doors. I was convinced that there was a hidden room filled with pirate treasures. You know what I found? One antique button, a hair bow, and a whole lot of dust bunnies.</Text>
  <Text Key="13C05FCF">My marriage to Hilary is pretty amazing now, but for a while I wasn't so sure we'd get that storybook ending. I admit it: I've been kind of an insensitive guy in the past. I broke someone's heart a while back, and it's been hard to forgive myself. But Hilary sees through a lot of my faults and we work together to be better people.</Text>
  <Text Key="5D9656AC">I've thought about taking my mother's last name. There's a lot of expectation that comes with it though. Some locals seem annoyed I wouldn't want it, but it's my life. That's just the way I was raised. I'm privileged, no doubt about it, but I work hard too and want all that work to be seen as something of my own doing. </Text>
  <Text Key="2C520310">Did you know there is a playground just outside of town? It's the perfect place to take the kids. Pirate themed, of course, given our history. My husband comes from a family with swashbucklers, you know?</Text>
  <Text Key="4F5FBFC0">I love cooking. It's just so much fun and there are always interesting new recipes to try, or ways to experiment to make your own. I have a lot that were handed down to me by my parents, but I'm always working to create my own new recipes.</Text>
  <Text Key="A655467C">I wasn't born here. My parents were chefs in a big city and wanted to raise me in an environment that's a little bit quieter. I guess they visited Tartosa for a day when they were traveling on their honeymoon, and it made a lasting impression. So much so that they moved out here just to start up a restaurant, then two, and then start catering for weddings.</Text>
  <Text Key="D8B76A26">When Jace and Greta were toddlers, I used to take them to the waterfall. The lagoon has a shallow area that was perfect for them to splash in. They were so cute! I know it sounds trite, but the saying's true: they really do grow up too fast.</Text>
  <Text Key="773D9825">Have you met the Markovics yet? They're really sweet. Lucia is my best friend; I can tell her anything. Mateo can be a little standoffish with my family because I think he thinks of us as rivals, but I think of our families as complementing one another. We all work together to make this place better for everyone.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C81CF58">I've always wondered what Tartosa was like before it became a stopping place for pirates. It's hard to find a lot of traces of people before then, so maybe no one was living here. It seems hard to believe now, given how many people travel through here each year. </Text>
  <Text Key="4B0BB601">Even though cooking has been a family affair for me, I'm hoping my kids choose a career path that they like. I secretly hope they do something completely different, even. Greta is so interested in the flowers around here; maybe botany is for her? Jace is more of a wild child, though he's very social and chatty.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CC90451">When I first met Arnessa, I was absolutely terrified. I mean, you know the rumors are true, right? She's related to Princess Cordelia. As soon as I heard that she was basically royalty, I was on notice. I expected her to be a bit of a snob, but she's not at all. Whether she admits to it or not, she has a real penchant for mischief. She loves playing little pranks on people. I'm wondering if that's rubbed off a little too much on the kids...</Text>
  <Text Key="716278F6">When I was younger, I loved going up to the Lover's Tree and sitting there for hours with a good book. It just has a nice aura about it. There are a lot of legends about where it came from; something about a figurehead? I've also heard something about how it grew in a way that looked similar to doomed lovers who traveled here once. While I love a good story, personally, I think it's just a very old - and very nice - tree.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE60955D">I've been playing guitar as long as I can remember. Sometimes I don't even really think in words or images, I just think in music. If you're passionate about music, I'm sure you understand.</Text>
  <Text Key="83FF5321">At first glance, it seems like Tartosa is all about the wedding industry. If you ask Mateo, he'd say the same - he's pretty absorbed in it. But it's also a beautiful place with a really unique history!</Text>
  <Text Key="37239EDB">Have you met my daughter, Tomi, yet? She has the most interesting mind! She's going to amaze everyone someday with an amazing piece of art or music - just you wait. </Text>
  <Text Key="DE884674">The cuisine here is so interesting! My best friend, Hilary, is this amazing chef. Her family was in the restaurant business. She keeps an eye on the market stalls she opened up in Porto Luminoso. You absolutely have to try the mutton biryani. If you don't eat meat, I totally understand, but if you do: it's practically a transcendent experience the first time you sample it!</Text>
  <Text Key="28A36C1A">There's definitely a bit of tension and, well, drama around here. I don't like getting into it too much because gossiping really isn't my thing. But I suppose it's like any other place; you know who you friends are, and you know who you might want to keep an eye on!</Text>
  <Text Key="4D54C662">It's really funny, you know. Mateo and I have wanted to get married for ages - before our daughter was born, in fact, but the stars never really aligned. We became a musical duo, then started playing for everyone else's wedding. One day we woke and realized... we never even had our own. Don't worry, though, we'll be changing that soon.</Text>
  <Text Key="D3A9181F">You know I really don't like gossip, but since he's kind of inescapable given that he's, well, the big wheel of the wedding industry: Hector can be a little tricky. He and I dated once and he was a pretty big jerk. But he's married to my best friend, so I do my best to keep my mouth shut and keep the peace.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA6FB783">When Mateo and I met, he was so sweet. I'd been going through a real rough patch and he was playing piano at the lounge for tips. He locked eyes with me and immediately began playing this beautiful composition - almost moved me to tears! Now, we make music together.</Text>
  <Text Key="F69AA44D">I bet you've heard all about the Thebe Estate and pirate gold and all that. One thing I wanted to mention, though, is that Arnessa Thebe may seem like a really difficult-to-approach woman, she's actually a real doll once you talk to her. She just doesn't like being made to feel like she's being mined for details about her unique family.</Text>
  <Text Key="D6D959E5">Both Lucia and I can sing. She plays the guitar though and I the piano. Our skillsets complement each other well. </Text>
  <Text Key="5799E9FB">I've been playing piano since I was five. My grandmother used to have me play for her when I'd visit, so I started taking classes. It was never easy to impress her! But I always managed. </Text>
  <Text Key="A8564DB7">Sure, the Laurents have been here longer... well the &lt;i&gt;Thebes&lt;/i&gt; have been here longer; the distinction matters a bit. But the Markovics are just as passionate about the wedding industry! What do you remember more about a wedding: the amazing music or the venue? To me, music is always what makes the biggest impression.</Text>
  <Text Key="14604BB5">Hector Laurent is trying to hog all of the good wedding business around these parts. The Laurents have a stranglehold on the wedding industry, and they don't make room for others. Lucia and I have had to work very hard to keep our business booming. </Text>
  <Text Key="90B3E1B1">Tartosa really is the perfect place to get married. That's why business is so good here in the wedding industry. I mean, between the Falls and the ocean views you're hardly hurting for a great locale, and everything about the ambiance here spells love. </Text>
  <Text Key="B56BE378">You know, sometimes I wonder if I would trade a pastry for a llama. The answer is, yes. I would totally do that. I actually would really like a llama. Do you think Lucia would agree to getting one? She seems Llama-friendly, right? </Text>
  <Text Key="B5145DE9">I've been called a goofball before, but I ask you... would a goofball ever pursue a minor in puppeteering? Granted, I never graduated.. but I think my endeavor speaks for itself!</Text>
  <Text Key="C7C0425F">Am I more of a business man or a family man? You know, if I had to pick, I'd choose family every time. Even when we've had some tough times, Lucia and Tomi and I have always had each other to rely on. Can't beat that, can you?</Text>
  <Text Key="D6736667">When Lucia and I moved here we lived in Porto Luminoso, but it was a little too close to the Laurents for my liking, so we moved to Terra Amorosa to get a little space and quiet. And wouldn't you know it, that move turned out for the best. The muses speak to me a little more out there. Or is that me just talking to myself?</Text>
  <Text Key="E54C5FF2">Between you and me, I was sad Tomi was more interested in painting than music... at first. I've really grown to appreciate her preferences the past few years. She's going to be an amazing artist! Or whatever she decides she wants to be! </Text>
  <Text Key="530F9475">I'm devoted to my daughter, Tomi. I've never known a prouder father. I'm sure she'll be an extraordinary painter someday. She's already very advanced! The stuff other parents might just put on a fridge is stuff that, from Tomi, really belongs in a museum. She's dabbling in this new style called post abstract impressionist style. I have no idea what those words mean, but I know it means my daughter is pretty incredible.</Text>
  <Text Key="294F739E">(From Walking The Aisle)</Text>
  <Text Key="A6880176">How sweet! It's so beautiful to see a love like that.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6C6C9A9">Blissful Marriage</Text>
  <Text Key="57D8B586">Who just gave a killer speech? Me!</Text>
  <Text Key="5CC6FA19">Confident Delivery</Text>
  <Text Key="44BB2F95">Now that was a speech to remember!</Text>
  <Text Key="D5D955B0">Good Speech</Text>
  <Text Key="0B3E5F9E">How are they still married?</Text>
  <Text Key="9A7215A1">Honeymoon Is Over</Text>
  <Text Key="B173AA75">These vows are my promise to always be true to you.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC80F310">I Swear</Text>
  <Text Key="692E5AF3">The &lt;i&gt;true&lt;/i&gt; power of love personified in a speech. &lt;i&gt;*sniff*&lt;/i&gt; So beautiful, can we hear it again?</Text>
  <Text Key="0C8C1F22">Beautiful Speech &lt;i&gt;*sniff*&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="4CC40A82">Remember that time we did that mildly illegal thing? Or when we did very childish things? Now everyone knows about them!</Text>
  <Text Key="75FF277D">Questionable References</Text>
  <Text Key="16DCD26F">What a terrible story! That's not the wedding story I'd want to share...</Text>
  <Text Key="C6AA1BB6">Run Away!</Text>
  <Text Key="0BBEFCF8">That's just too many things to remember, especially since it didn't seem to work for them...</Text>
  <Text Key="D9E615F7">Old, New, Borrowed, Blue</Text>
  <Text Key="46CBE3BA">My heart! Every word was perfect.</Text>
  <Text Key="74F06F65">Those Vows</Text>
  <Text Key="654A4871">Come on. Is there anything better than blowing bubbles for some newlyweds?</Text>
  <Text Key="E267EE44">Wedding Bubbles</Text>
  <Text Key="FEAFC828">Our wedding day was so perfect, I can't help but sharing.</Text>
  <Text Key="FB2FD647">Wedding Day Inspiration</Text>
  <Text Key="288EA634">I can't believe things went so wrong. I'll never forget that day.</Text>
  <Text Key="B588B59B">Wedding Day Not To Do's</Text>
  <Text Key="1CCC9C8C">A single kiss to mark the start of a wonderful marriage.</Text>
  <Text Key="B36FD543">Wedding Kiss</Text>
  <Text Key="960A37E1">Throwing rice at a wedding? Yes, please!</Text>
  <Text Key="ABD3C994">Wedding Rice</Text>
  <Text Key="21B935EC">I can't believe that story was just shared in front of everyone! Yikes!</Text>
  <Text Key="0F662023">What?! Oh no...</Text>
  <Text Key="F190DAC9">I hope that my wedding can be that special.</Text>
  <Text Key="C1282C2C">Wishing And Hoping</Text>
  <Text Key="030B594A">Just as a circle has no end, this ring symbolizes that our love will last forever.</Text>
  <Text Key="880A0155">With This Ring</Text>
  <Text Key="51C632FE">Dancing with someone you care about can bring up plenty of fond memories—and make new ones, too!</Text>
  <Text Key="7412EF81">Sentimental Swaying</Text>
  <Text Key="1CFB5BAC">Dancing is clearly more perilous than you'd think.</Text>
  <Text Key="AAEC6BE3">That's My Foot!</Text>
  <Text Key="DC4EBE08">{0.SimFirstName} has conjured up soothing fall memories with {M0.his}{F0.her} cup of cozy apple juice tea.</Text>
  <Text Key="4B0582A7">Cozy Apple Juice Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="E37566D6">This tea may not breathe fire, but it will certainly help keep you focused!</Text>
  <Text Key="251CF689">The Black Dragon</Text>
  <Text Key="4216F42F">Soothe away stress with this lovely floral tea.</Text>
  <Text Key="CF90A176">Calm and Collected Chamomile</Text>
  <Text Key="9A8ACDDB">That citrus tea was a tad bit tart, but now {0.SimFirstName}'s feeling pretty dang smart!</Text>
  <Text Key="D1673ABA">Citrus Bloom</Text>
  <Text Key="338F9131">This smiley is feeling beachy keen. </Text>
  <Text Key="19A34004">Silly Sandy Smiley</Text>
  <Text Key="A4F5F2AA">{0.SimFirstName} has witnessed a symbol of love, etched with purpose and intent.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4086E35">Romance Writ Large</Text>
  <Text Key="6205647B">The romantic sands have inspired {0.SimFirstName} to create &lt;i&gt;art&lt;/i&gt;! </Text>
  <Text Key="AEF154DA">Sandy Sentimentality</Text>
  <Text Key="F35199D4">{0.SimFirstName} feels happy after viewing that smiley. It's like some other Sim left {M0.him}{F0.her} a message that said, "Hi! I like you." </Text>
  <Text Key="1C30CEBB">Smiles for Miles</Text>
  <Text Key="7467E7D3">{0.SimFirstName}'s snowy smiley face left {M0.him}{F0.her} feeling all warm inside. </Text>
  <Text Key="255A3282">What's Snow Funny?</Text>
  <Text Key="917E7D12">The romantic snow drifts have inspired {0.SimFirstName} to create &lt;i&gt;art&lt;/i&gt;! </Text>
  <Text Key="19FB3C2D">Snowy Sentimentality</Text>
  <Text Key="4D0A5E9B">Best sand ever! One Star! It is so special and perfect!</Text>
  <Text Key="4D81947A">Starry Sands</Text>
  <Text Key="29226BAC">Best snow ever! One star! Would do this again!</Text>
  <Text Key="DD949BE3">Starry Snow</Text>
  <Text Key="F292EBA9">Quality Teatime with a friend sure makes you feel a lot closer with them!</Text>
  <Text Key="3E09C78C">Tea for Two</Text>
  <Text Key="1B94A3EB">{0.SimFirstName} is still thinking about all the fun they had at the tea party!</Text>
  <Text Key="B72C65EA">More Tea, Please</Text>
  <Text Key="A3A33682">{0.SimFirstName} is feeling fluttery after flaunting {M0.his}{F0.her} first dance footwork.</Text>
  <Text Key="EBDCEB7D">Two to Tango</Text>
  <Text Key="5B9DE5CB">Even as time has passed, {0.SimFirstName}'s memory of {M0.his}{F0.her} first dance as a married couple lives on!</Text>
  <Text Key="9481884A">Dance Floor Feelings</Text>
  <Text Key="F3CE1633">Some Sims are the light of the party. Looks like {0.SimFirstName} was the opposite and got kicked out.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B9D1B62">No Party, No Fun</Text>
  <Text Key="EEACD5BA">Being kicked out of a wedding event still stings! Doesn't anyone appreciate {0.SimFirstName}'s party energy?</Text>
  <Text Key="4C7CA565">Bad Party Memories</Text>
  <Text Key="F775554F">Serving tea smoothly is not as easy as it may seem.</Text>
  <Text Key="A4573016">Prim and Proper</Text>
  <Text Key="BD37511F">Serving tea during a wedding event shows respect to loved ones and receiving it is a sign of acceptance of the marriage. </Text>
  <Text Key="4F7783C6">Traditional Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="1EBB301F">Can't believe it's today!</Text>
  <Text Key="4CAEF0C6">Wedding Excitement</Text>
  <Text Key="EFE6F216">Can't believe it's today!</Text>
  <Text Key="CD5E24C9">Wedding Nerves</Text>
  <Text Key="97924034">Dancing alone can be challenging, but synchronized? {0.SimFirstName} feels like {M0.he's}{F0.she's} really part of the celebration now!</Text>
  <Text Key="782C639B">All Synced Up</Text>
  <Text Key="CBE01B02">Snazzy, luxurious, trendy, gorgeous clothes! {0.SimFirstName} has &lt;i&gt;truly&lt;/i&gt; seen fashion today.</Text>
  <Text Key="249D70FD">Couture Craver</Text>
  <Text Key="A618BBBD">I'm pretty sure someone was there to catch it...</Text>
  <Text Key="97857128">There was a Bouquet Toss!</Text>
  <Text Key="2327157B">With the strength of two, we sundered the cake.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA9597DA">We Cut the Cake!</Text>
  <Text Key="2BEF3894">They played our song too! What a magical moment.</Text>
  <Text Key="7316CA7B">Our First Dance</Text>
  <Text Key="C1778609">It was super awkward and yet felt right!</Text>
  <Text Key="5D4DDB6C">There was a Big Dance!</Text>
  <Text Key="0420E17C">It was perfect and beautiful!</Text>
  <Text Key="6CD4ABD3">We had a Bouquet! </Text>
  <Text Key="FB001D4E">Naturally! A party without an oversized cake is a dull affair.</Text>
  <Text Key="95DFB671">We had a Wedding Cake!</Text>
  <Text Key="1B4B8937">You know, I've got some great people in my life.</Text>
  <Text Key="A2C1518E">Honor Us</Text>
  <Text Key="CE086755">I hope there's cake! </Text>
  <Text Key="2321E470">Invited to Wedding</Text>
  <Text Key="69BFFC92">Guess who just became a Sim of Honor? ME!</Text>
  <Text Key="34E0A2AD">It's an Honor</Text>
  <Text Key="8418C10E">Thankfully they still fit!</Text>
  <Text Key="C7483C31">We exchanged Rings!</Text>
  <Text Key="83F35AE2">My get butterflies in my stomach just remembering it! </Text>
  <Text Key="5220425D">We Kissed at the Altar! </Text>
  <Text Key="8EC67D5B">Like breathing, It's really weird to walk when you're manually doing it!</Text>
  <Text Key="59C4313A">We Walked down the Aisle Together!</Text>
  <Text Key="416204F2">{0.SimFirstName} Has caught the Wedding Bouquet, and feels a great sense of relief about their love life.</Text>
  <Text Key="96D3B08D">Caught Wedding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="17778930">If I can't catch the bouquet, I'm going to complain about it to everyone involved.</Text>
  <Text Key="7DD096DF">Every Rose Has A Thorn</Text>
  <Text Key="842B9DBB">Or, don't let them hit the floor. Catch them like a champion!</Text>
  <Text Key="E238C61A">Let The Flowers Hit The Floor</Text>
  <Text Key="FF4F76A5">There's a thorn in there somewhere and of course I'd find it.</Text>
  <Text Key="2386D520">Ouch! Sharp!</Text>
  <Text Key="1C635137">Did you see that throw? Did {0.SimFirstName} practice that?</Text>
  <Text Key="896E298E">Set Hike!</Text>
  <Text Key="2FEBD3C7">When you really love someone, you can marry them again and again and again and...</Text>
  <Text Key="78689A7E">All Over Again</Text>
  <Text Key="82333EFB">{0.SimFirstName}'s toast was awful, but it's not as if {M0.he}{F0.she} gave it at an important event or anything, right?</Text>
  <Text Key="0BA6DC5A">Toast-Tastrophe</Text>
  <Text Key="1E36F0D8">What poise! What finesse! {0.SimFirstName}'s toast has uplifted the guests!</Text>
  <Text Key="E8E09457">Elegant Elocution</Text>
  <Text Key="50EB57B5">Now THAT'S a Bach Party even a famous composer might be envious of!</Text>
  <Text Key="94B92850">Party Hearty</Text>
  <Text Key="2B2ECE9A">Being showered with compliments and attention makes any momentous day even better.</Text>
  <Text Key="45FD14C5">Talk of the Toast</Text>
  <Text Key="4BB53A3B">{0.SimFirstName} has felt the cool, night sea against {M0.his}{F0.her} skin as {M0.he}{F0.she} pushed through the luminous waves. Revitalizing and refreshing. </Text>
  <Text Key="C751F39A">Bioluminescent Burst</Text>
  <Text Key="31D0C5E1">A grape for {0.SimFirstName}. And another for {0.SimFirstName}. And look! That's another grape for {0.SimFirstName}! Aren't Tartosian grapes the best? </Text>
  <Text Key="57A61394">Grape Thief</Text>
  <Text Key="669F2181">What's sweeter or more romantic than hand-picking wildflowers? </Text>
  <Text Key="73EF11B4">Hand-Picked</Text>
  <Text Key="664AF8E5">When {0.SimFirstName} looked closely at the Lover's Tree, {M0.he}{F0.she} could see the branches tangling like two embracing lovers. Could the rumors be true?</Text>
  <Text Key="7A71E260">A Lover's Mystery</Text>
  <Text Key="4539E2C8">{0.SimFirstName} has taken a dip in the crystal, coastal waters of Tartosa. </Text>
  <Text Key="985EF467">Coastal Plunge</Text>
  <Text Key="A2AA527D">The locals say that tossing a coin into the Porto Luminoso village fountain will bring luck in love. {0.SimFirstName} can dream!</Text>
  <Text Key="FB2F72E8">Lucky in Love</Text>
  <Text Key="329BAB34">Porto Luminoso is one of the most romantic settings in the world. The tiny village shops! The flower fountain! The ocean! Who wouldn't feel a little inspired by love? </Text>
  <Text Key="03A6B49B">Love is in the Air</Text>
  <Text Key="A6AC1D1F">There are a lot of things to fall in love with in Tartosa, but {0.SimFirstName} might just be falling for the falls. </Text>
  <Text Key="4FE427C6">Waterfall Wistfulness</Text>
  <Text Key="33B741EE">Petals to the Metal</Text>
  <Text Key="23EBD968">Perfectly Two Tiered</Text>
  <Text Key="BF606C64">Keeper of the Rings</Text>
  <Text Key="A1CC11B0">One Piece Enchantment</Text>
  <Text Key="76B0D5E3">Beauty in Tradition</Text>
  <Text Key="85746D8C">Easy Ethereal</Text>
  <Text Key="7B02483F">After Party</Text>
  <Text Key="3FEE5F17">Flourishing Statement</Text>
  <Text Key="698DAC33">Oh l'amour... the flowers, the greenery: don’t get distracted by this fence gorgeously decorated and exuding all the charm of the lovey-dovey life enclosed by its simple and elegant patterns. Add a touch of loveliness and sentimentality to your house by fencing it with this poetic and charming fence. Love will be all around you.</Text>
  <Text Key="547BFD62">Poetic Flowered Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="1C5CEC96">Petal Lined Wedding Aisle - Long</Text>
  <Text Key="878A2629">Hidden Wedding Aisle - Long</Text>
  <Text Key="20E66283">Walk down the aisle in class with perfectly lined petals, in a selection of colors to match most any decorations and a variety of lengths to fit your needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="571812D2">Petal Lined Wedding Aisle - Short</Text>
  <Text Key="7CDE3EBA">This more subtle Wedding Aisle will allow you to place your aisle almost anywhere such as over any rug, carpet, tile, wooden floor or flat ground you desire. It will almost be as if this disappears to leave your decorations in pristine condition.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC529065">Hidden Wedding Aisle - Short</Text>
  <Text Key="23601A23">Petal Lined Wedding Aisle - Medium</Text>
  <Text Key="AFA4B23C">Hidden Wedding Aisle - Medium</Text>
  <Text Key="15A2F0DA">Let your passion drag you out and salute friends and family from this spectacular bowed balcony that echoes the roundness and fullness of your love life and commitment… Oh yes, marriage means commitment, too… having second thoughts? Cold feet? Look at the sinuous lines of this balcony rails, focus on its harmony and simple beauty and you’ll forget your worries while you lose your thoughts in the ecstasy of the curvy lines. Already feeling better huh? Lovely and loveful!</Text>
  <Text Key="49294205">Romantic Bowed Balcony</Text>
  <Text Key="4E19B17B">Ever notice that everyone seems to gravitate to the refreshments at a wedding celebration? Why is that? Well, in the case of the Bar Magnet, the explanation is in the name. Guests feel drawn to this libation preparation installation because it actually has a powerful bar magnet right inside the front panel. That’s why even the most negative guest goes away feeling more positive.</Text>
  <Text Key="AC72ABDA">The Bar Magnet - by Notorious B.A.R.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF963F3A">A wedding cake topper featuring a loving pair of Cowplants</Text>
  <Text Key="C621A9E5">Cowplant Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="85C1A4AA">A wedding cake topper featuring a trio of bats</Text>
  <Text Key="18D8E435">Bat Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="7560F8E3">A wedding cake topper featuring a loving pair of ghosts</Text>
  <Text Key="61D646B2">Ghost Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="71A1F2F8">A wedding cake topper featuring palm trees</Text>
  <Text Key="A11117F7">Palm Tree Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="5A4E1679">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a blue suit and one in a red dress</Text>
  <Text Key="0676F87C">Blue Suit and Red Dress Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="08028A47">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a red suit and one in a red dress</Text>
  <Text Key="3389F5FE">Red Suit and Red Dress Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="E885710C">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a grey suit and one in a black suit</Text>
  <Text Key="61012AC3">Grey Suit and Black Suit Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="48EEB8D9">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a green suit and one in a green dress</Text>
  <Text Key="B023155C">Green Suit and Green Dress Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="BFA7352E">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, both in a red suit.</Text>
  <Text Key="060379D1">Red Suits Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="AB790723">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a grey suit and one in a white suit</Text>
  <Text Key="1DE2C6F2">Grey Suit and White Suit Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="FFE10638">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, both in a white suit</Text>
  <Text Key="9AF30237">White Suits Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="7AC0C9A5">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, both in a red dress</Text>
  <Text Key="3C645E20">Red Dresses Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="B096CF5A">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a white dress and one in a red dress</Text>
  <Text Key="E8899585">White Dress and Red Dress Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="4C851D4F">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, both in a white dress</Text>
  <Text Key="D56C0816">White Dresses Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="4F9BE986">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, both in a white dress</Text>
  <Text Key="4A825619">White Dresses Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="7D411491">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a grey suit and one in a white dress</Text>
  <Text Key="76ECD8E4">Grey Suit and White Dress Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="A25A2C50">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a blue suit and one in an orange suit</Text>
  <Text Key="1F86417F">Blue Suit and Orange Suit Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="783AB87B">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a black suit and one in a white dress</Text>
  <Text Key="332910DA">Black Suit and White Dress Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="BAF49FF2">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, both in a black suit</Text>
  <Text Key="E442918D">Black Suits Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="D4142E1D">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a yellow dress and one in a red dress</Text>
  <Text Key="8EB87D08">Yellow Dress and Red Dress Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="AC24961C">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, both in a white dress</Text>
  <Text Key="53235DF3">White Dresses Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="9D8A2917">A wedding cake topper of two mini sims, one in a blue dress and one in a white dress</Text>
  <Text Key="69FC0EEE">Blue Dress and White Dress Mini Sims Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="CB99C72F">A wedding cake topper of Red Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="0AEAAA76">Red Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="24B0E035">A wedding cake topper of Yellow Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="D3AA59D0">Yellow Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="6CC2D69C">A wedding cake topper of Pale Blue Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="59513773">Pale Blue Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="5E286997">A wedding cake topper of Blush Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="7029E86E">Blush Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="8C44F82A">A wedding cake topper of Pink Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="517386B5">Pink Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="AB8D8EF5">A wedding cake topper of Pale Pink Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="1A487890">Pale Pink Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="457C0848">A wedding cake topper of Black Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="D1F96CE7">Black Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="0397BEB3">A wedding cake topper of Blue Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="A120ACE2">Blue Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="103A2A06">A wedding cake topper of White Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="50B02F99">White Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="3DDF5511">A wedding cake topper of Purple Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="7D1AB264">Purple Rose Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="6A17776C">A wedding cake topper of Red and Orange Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="7F222CA3">Red and Orange Tropical Flower Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="E438BA85">A wedding cake topper of Yellow and Magenta Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="0572B080">Yellow and Magenta Tropical Flower Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="8A741BBA">A wedding cake topper of White and Purple Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="C0839765">White and Purple Tropical Flower Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="E9C6A0A7">A wedding cake topper of Pink Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="55AC1BDE">Pink Tropical Flower Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="E8A19AEC">A wedding cake topper of Yellow and Orange Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="14783F23">Yellow and Orange Tropical Flower Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="646B1F39">A wedding cake topper of White Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="A0BCD73C">White Tropical Flower Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="C822A98E">A wedding cake topper of Black and Purple Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="79188DB1">Black and Purple Tropical Flower Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="321E6A8B">A wedding cake topper of Magenta Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="D103A20A">Magenta Tropical Flower Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="AB00BBE0">A wedding cake topper of Blue Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="7E38FA2F">Blue Tropical Flower Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="E96A7937">A wedding cake topper of Silver Interlinked Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="400B218E">Silver Interlinked Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="A9AD51C4">A wedding cake topper of Gold Interlinked Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="7680248B">Gold Interlinked Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="287AC6BF">A wedding cake topper of Rose Gold Interlinked Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="6BB66DE6">Rose Gold Interlinked Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="69F33C52">A wedding cake topper of White Interlinked Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="DD1FD86D">White Interlinked Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="578B0EFD">A wedding cake topper of Black Interlinked Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="74640068">Black Interlinked Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="B0EAA830">A wedding cake topper of Rainbow Interlinked Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="0531C3DF">Rainbow Interlinked Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="5FD842BC">A wedding cake topper of script and Pale Pink Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="B8C26C13">Pale Pink Roses and Platinum Script Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="17C498B5">A wedding cake topper of script and White Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="C1CF1B50">White Roses and Silver Script Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="DC1FACEA">A wedding cake topper of script and Blush Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="7DCB6275">Blush Roses and Silver Script Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="45672657">A wedding cake topper of script and Pale Blue Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="4E74FF2E">Pale Blue Roses and Platinum Script Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="6FFD125C">A wedding cake topper of script and Yellow Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="3665DB33">Yellow Roses and Bronze Script Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="C4DC67E9">A wedding cake topper of script and Red Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="21AFFDCC">Red Roses and Black Script Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="ED1ADD3E">A wedding cake topper of script and Orange Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="011B44C1">Orange Roses and Blue Script Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="AB8F2DBB">A wedding cake topper of script and Magenta Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="F0EE761A">Magenta Roses and Pink Script Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="F75155C7">A wedding cake topper of Tan Flag Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="DB3D807E">Tan Flag Banner Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="C8EFC634">A wedding cake topper of Grey Flag Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="00A2159B">Grey Flag Banner Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="8C98A2EF">A wedding cake topper of Red Flag Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="C39BA536">Red Flag Banner Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="4BCE1EC2">A wedding cake topper of Tan Pennant Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="52BD76BD">Tan Pennant Banner Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="0A9726ED">A wedding cake topper of Rainbow Pennant Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="21D1ACB8">Rainbow Pennant Banner Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="870446A0">A wedding cake topper of Grey Pennant Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="5A97BEEF">Grey Pennant Banner Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="3DBE0C4B">A wedding cake topper of Red Pennant Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="4FA433CA">Red Pennant Banner Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="30B61C4E">A wedding cake topper of White Pennant Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="DED38371">White Pennant Banner Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="E235B7F9">A wedding cake topper of Black Pennant Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="39D124FC">Black Pennant Banner Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="B08873CE">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing LGBTQ+ Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="CD63F1F1">Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="B5BCC27C">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Genderqueer Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="6B707ED3">Genderqueer Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="DBE3BF77">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Bigender Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="5D9552CE">Bigender Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="2923745E">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Intersex Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="3CB65761">Intersex Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="4E7B4589">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Genderfluid Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="2A6601EC">Genderfluid Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="C7B99528">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Agender Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="CA99AD47">Agender Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="E0114893">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Pangender Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="F9289642">Pangender Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="C3F1998A">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing LGBTQ+ Pride for all.</Text>
  <Text Key="BBA17595">More Color, More Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="F1988555">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Lesbian Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="25FBDE70">Lesbian Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="74F9FCC4">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Lesbian Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="9CE0358B">Lesbian Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="F3C771BF">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Lesbian Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="92167EE6">Lesbian Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="F4C84AE7">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Bisexual Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="AA32921E">Bisexual Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="A3250E7F">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing the continued progression of LGBTQ+ Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="9B768CA6">Progress Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="9CD43E2C">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Pansexual Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="23248B63">Pansexual Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="0649C2C5">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Asexual Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="8DF85DC0">Asexual Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="A6F275FA">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Polysexual Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="AA6D8EA5">Polysexual Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="28E7AAC3">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Aromantic Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="B3861B12">Aromantic Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="0FCC1A58">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow and the ally symbol representing allies of LGBTQ+ people.</Text>
  <Text Key="F93CD8D7">Pride Ally Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="350024A1">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Transgender Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="30A44154">Transgender Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="4F852096">A wedding cake topper of a rainbow representing Non-binary Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="DF0C6849">Non-binary Pride Rainbow Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="834F5CC9">A wedding cake topper of Metallic Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="91B8122C">Metallic Stars Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="481F4077">A wedding cake topper of Gold Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="ECBE05CE">Gold Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="21F8437C">A wedding cake topper of Rose Gold Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="FA9931D3">Rose Gold Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="BAB6C689">A wedding cake topper of Silver Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="B98EB4EC">Silver Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="E44741F6">A wedding cake topper of White Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="B887A329">White Stars Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="49257C81">A wedding cake topper of Black Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="6E6D32B4">Black Stars Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="5B90DF80">A wedding cake topper of Gold Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="39B5114F">Gold Stars Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="3B77962B">A wedding cake topper of Rose Gold Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="B299622A">Rose Gold Stars Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="CAB02CA2">A wedding cake topper of Silver Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="B2C3531D">Silver Stars Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="9F738F4D">A wedding cake topper of Metallic Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="906D6A98">Metallic Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="89C9098C">A wedding cake topper of White Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="D8EF8C43">White Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="A94622C7">A wedding cake topper of Black Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="AB78577E">Black Hearts Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="8162956D">The Mediterranean climate means gorgeous summers, but also cold winters. You will need to keep your Sim riviera house warm during the bad season, but look at the bright side: you’ll have an excuse to decorate the roof of the house with this simple and elegantly functional chimney. Add that mediterranean touch to any house and improve your roof with a simple and inconspicuous addition.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B03B038">Mediterranean Style Chimney</Text>
  <Text Key="B2A686E2">A glass bottle with a message rolled up and secured inside. How mysterious! How exciting! What could it say? </Text>
  <Text Key="5F3A065D">Message in a Bottle: A Bold Reminder</Text>
  <Text Key="D3C0E6D5">A glass bottle with a message rolled up and secured inside. How mysterious! How exciting! What could it say? </Text>
  <Text Key="8EBC4AF0">Message in a Bottle: A Lover's Grudge</Text>
  <Text Key="2AE6C155">A glass bottle with a message rolled up and secured inside. How mysterious! How exciting! What could it say? </Text>
  <Text Key="6ED9D270">Message in a Bottle: A Scandalous Invitation</Text>
  <Text Key="844371AB">Message in a Bottle: An 'Imminent' Warning</Text>
  <Text Key="407AE6D4">Message in a Bottle: Sunlit Wishes</Text>
  <Text Key="BB801F36">Message in a Bottle: The Little Genius</Text>
  <Text Key="5EEFD7E6">Message in a Bottle: A Love Poem</Text>
  <Text Key="CD7178A1">Message in a Bottle: A Threat from Beyond</Text>
  <Text Key="6CD0D59E">Message in a Bottle: An Inspiring Role-Model</Text>
  <Text Key="619F8B4C">Message in a Bottle: A Pirate's Joke</Text>
  <Text Key="FE91298C">Message in a Bottle: Unrequited Love</Text>
  <Text Key="964E2356">Message in a Bottle: A Cursed Message</Text>
  <Text Key="7F815631">Message in a Bottle: A Wish of Adventure</Text>
  <Text Key="EDE1898F">Message in a Bottle: The Clumsy Pirate</Text>
  <Text Key="48D34843">Message in a Bottle: Till Death...</Text>
  <Text Key="C6443EA1">Message in a Bottle: A Grim Promise</Text>
  <Text Key="65A39B9E">Message in a Bottle: Moonlit Musings</Text>
  <Text Key="5A72514C">Message in a Bottle: A Bright Hello</Text>
  <Text Key="2B38FF8C">Message in a Bottle: A Pledge of Love</Text>
  <Text Key="BC0F75EE">A glass bottle with a message rolled up and secured inside. How mysterious! How exciting! What could it say? </Text>
  <Text Key="32C15D91">Message in a Bottle: A Thousand Leaves</Text>
  <Text Key="26DE8D00">Elegant and simple, perfect to decorate for the wedding of your dreams and keep curious uninvited guests at bay with these beautifully crafted curtains. Sewn from cloth from the best seamsters of Tartosa, this curtain will make your wedding party look clean and somewhat vintage chic.</Text>
  <Text Key="5A0BA1CF">Effortless Cinched Curtain</Text>
  <Text Key="15DABFA9">If your venue has a bit of a higher ceiling, this version of the Effortless Cinched Curtain is for you! The more area it covers the more effective is at keeping those undesired guests peeping in at bay. Like its original version, this curtain is exquisitely crafted by Tartosa seamsters putting a touch of Tartosa in your wedding to remember.</Text>
  <Text Key="FFF1038C">Slightly Longer - Still Effortless Cinched Curtain</Text>
  <Text Key="E233DAA6">If a cinched look is not in your taste or needs for your venue décor, this version of the Effortless Curtain line is the right choice. Some may think it is just cut cloth but don't let its effortless look deceive you, Tartosa seamsters carefully cut and pleated these fabrics with love and care so your venue looks perfect so all the newlyweds shine!</Text>
  <Text Key="3641A1B9">Effortless Straight Curtain</Text>
  <Text Key="32F2D2C3">A bit of more fabric makes everything seem more magical! Perfect for weddings, and who knows maybe you can use them to twirl in the dancefloor if you don't have a partner to dance with. </Text>
  <Text Key="C9EF1312">Slightly Longer - Still Effortless Straight Curtain</Text>
  <Text Key="D9D330FB">Dance like you are an inspirational quote about dancing! Remember, you don't have to be perfect to be incredible. Dancing, even poorly, is better than never having danced at all. Dancing will set your soul ablaze and free your desires. And you should never stop. But really... if you never stop, that's probably a bug. </Text>
  <Text Key="1840125A">The Eloquent Occasion Dance Floor - Petite</Text>
  <Text Key="A2303343">Need more room to dance like you are an inspirational quote about dancing? Remember, you don't have to be perfect to be incredible. Dancing, even poorly, is better than never having danced at all. Enjoy this welcome space and have fun!</Text>
  <Text Key="D5904C92">The Eloquent Occasion Dance Floor - Med</Text>
  <Text Key="BB76734B">A dance floor sizable to impress. The more space, the more you can show your inspirational dancing skills. You don't have to be perfect, it is better if you are not actually. Just make sure you take breaks, and if you can't... well, maybe it is a bug... maybe.</Text>
  <Text Key="DCC2B8CA">The Eloquent Occasion Dance Floor - Grande</Text>
  <Text Key="72569AAC">Ideal for a reception hall or to decorate your house with grandeur, this classical double door conveys style and solidity. The decorative segmental arch on top adds elegance and harmony while the square corners convey firmness and solemnity.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B4BF8E3">Classical Hall Door</Text>
  <Text Key="9BE18669">Tall and impressive, this double door speaks of grandeur and underscores it with its round arch top. What solemnity, what gravity. Classical elegance and style in one massive door worth of a palace or a mansion of ancient lore.</Text>
  <Text Key="7A00114C">Majestic Hall Door</Text>
  <Text Key="96043E3C">An arch-way has style and classical elegance, but a three-pointed arch adds that exotic and romantic character that improves the classical shapes with its spiky gothic style. Elegant in its own peculiar way, acute like its angle, this archway combines classical harmony with gothic sophistication. For connoisseurs only.</Text>
  <Text Key="83268693">The Trinity Archway</Text>
  <Text Key="F9F37FEE">drinkCupTea_GP11GEN Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="AE3B5B91">drinkCupTea_GP11GEN Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="FF03CA54">drinkCupTeaHandle_GP11GEN Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="4A77783B">drinkCupTeaHandle_GP11GEN Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="7FA550B8">Deliciously and elegantly fizzy!</Text>
  <Text Key="F8C0D9B7">Sparkling Juice</Text>
  <Text Key="1A07A478">Dal Makhani</Text>
  <Text Key="EC554954">Gulab Jamun</Text>
  <Text Key="700B199F">Mutton Biryani</Text>
  <Text Key="CC15AC01">Bowl of Dal Makhani</Text>
  <Text Key="584DAC69">Bowl of Gulab Jamun</Text>
  <Text Key="49BF9A9C">Bowl of Mutton Biryani</Text>
  <Text Key="10D34763">Sweet Bun</Text>
  <Text Key="F87CD18C">Roast Duck</Text>
  <Text Key="CEE072A8">World-Famous Tartosian Fruit Tart</Text>
  <Text Key="CF834EB6">Sweet Buns</Text>
  <Text Key="084BC5C7">Plate of Roast Duck</Text>
  <Text Key="1F01AFD9">World-Famous Tartosian Fruit Tart</Text>
  <Text Key="F30B6ADD">Sweet Buns</Text>
  <Text Key="AEF37C3C">Floral Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="36465C74">Heart Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="39490D33">Pillow Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="8C670E77">Hexagon Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="1ADADB48">Square Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="DFA785A8">Round Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="F9F364B7">Square Design Round Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="4C44FD06">Beachy Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="C072AE11">Cupcake Wedding Cake Display</Text>
  <Text Key="CC5551D6">You never forget your first gravy boat. But having a gravy fountain at your wedding. Well, that’s what every kid dreams about. I mean, it’s just part of growing up. So, when that special time finally arrives, make sure it’s completely special with the Gravy Fountain Mark IV. It serves up to 7 kinds of piping hot gravy “your way” and a bunch of other stuff your guests might wanna scarf on. It just doesn’t get any better than that.</Text>
  <Text Key="8D52C789">The Gravy Fountain Mark IV Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="60E80684">Whimsy! Love! Enchantment! This fountain will make you feel none of these things if you aren't first willing to inspire yourself with its elegant form. Really, it's up to you. Look upon the cascading water, the beds of flowers, and allow it to transport you to a magical realm of romance. </Text>
  <Text Key="9917E84B">The Garden of Romance Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="50F2FEEF">Complete your lovely fenced abode (and provide an entrance to your house) with this fantastic gate: a stone archway supports a double gate opening to the intimacy of your house or keeping it private. It gives a touch of elegance and loveliness to any fence, yard and house. Don’t be surprised if your neighbors stop to admire it and don't worry: their initial envy will be melted and conquered by its loveliness.</Text>
  <Text Key="31A3F936">Lover's Gate</Text>
  <Text Key="91E03945">In modern times, the dragon represents the wealth and strength for the groom while the phoenix represents the bride, signifying grace and renewal of life. Together, the co-existence of two mythical creatures represents happiness, love, and prosperity. Have this intricate dragon design represent the strength of love in your wedding and may your marriage be in perfect harmony.</Text>
  <Text Key="780CF940">The Light of the Dragon</Text>
  <Text Key="9A99392D">Ever heard your significant other say "Love you to the Moon and back"? You can create that warm feeling when you heard this phrase for the first time at your wedding or event by placing this light orb anywhere and as many of them as you like. This lamp creates a moonlight like glow that will make you reminisce of the greatest night of your life. If marriage is not in the picture, this lamp is perfect for pondering as well as giving your Lot an aesthetic feel to it.</Text>
  <Text Key="81358EF8">To the Moon and Back - Orb Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="549007E2">Light up your thousand and one romantic nights with this elegant lamp that will add a touch of eastern style to your halls and rooms. Admire the flowery pattern and the suggestive lines of the onion shaped dome. What a magic atmosphere this gracious lamp can provide. You’ll love it and be surrounded by a genuine and sophisticated atmosphere.</Text>
  <Text Key="A40CB95D">Exotic Elegant Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="E1300162">Give tribute to your favorite couple's happiness, or why not - your own! This centerpiece is perfectly aligned with candles and a beautiful flower motif to inspire romance to any occasion and location.</Text>
  <Text Key="42F06DDD">Blooming Centerpiece</Text>
  <Text Key="B252C86E">Create a romantic atmosphere with this exquisite composition of nature and fire. Admire the balance of simple natural elements: the leaves, the bark, the majestic anthurium with its lovely heart-shaped leaf. Add the sublime touch of candlelight and you’ll have the perfect combination. And did you know that the Anthurium flower symbolizes hospitality? It’s also toxic, but that’s another story and you shouldn’t eat it, anyhow.</Text>
  <Text Key="D04DCD11">Candlelight Composition</Text>
  <Text Key="0378E899">This modern-vintage lantern creates an aura of old world charm. It is an eye-catching piece perfect to any surface that can host it. Its light is warm as the love in a newlywed couple's hearts.</Text>
  <Text Key="78A6671C">The Light of the Heart</Text>
  <Text Key="4DCCD7F4">Perfect to create the right atmosphere for a ceremony, or to transport that kind of semi-sacred air to your house. The warm fire light accompanied by the natural colors and scent of the wooden support… And it seems to me that you’d like your house with a candle on the wall. No wind will blow it out (disclaimer note from the manufacturer: resistance to wind has not been certified by our laboratories - ongoing studies and tests have been indefinitely put on hold due to the unsatisfactory ROI reports).</Text>
  <Text Key="AE03A25B">Lone Candle in the Hall</Text>
  <Text Key="B69344EC">Where Sims can purchase Flowers and Wedding Bouquets without stress!\n\nWhen it comes to your special day, the last thing you wanna do is get too hung up on all those pesky details. You have enough to worry about with that whole “no white shoes after Labor Day thing”. So, when it comes to a bridal bouquet, might I suggest Petals to the Metal Mobile Flower Traylah? They’ll come right to you so all you gotta do is grab a fist full of flowers on the way into your ceremony. They have a huge selection of gently used bouquets to fit even the lowest budget. No fuss, no muss (whatever that means).</Text>
  <Text Key="29691D23">Petals to the Metal – The Mobile Flower Traylah</Text>
  <Text Key="DF41A21E">Delicious Chinese food from Porto Luminoso.</Text>
  <Text Key="005B5521">The Porto Luminoso Chinese Market Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="AA390832">Delicious Indian food from Porto Luminoso.</Text>
  <Text Key="3D6493CD">The Porto Luminoso Indian Market Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="204A61EA">Delicious pastries and cakes from Porto Luminoso.</Text>
  <Text Key="0B737175">Porto Luminoso Patisserie Market Stall</Text>
  <Text Key="25E7D4C8">Give your wedding or event the elegance of this grand piano. Effortless in its design, this grand piano is perfect for those events that evoke romance with its laced lid and a natural touch with a bouquet that complements your décor.</Text>
  <Text Key="36C22A67">Swooning Grand Piano</Text>
  <Text Key="38F6ED62">Looks can be deceiving, and this is not your everyday, neighborly barrel. Perfect for those weddings that want to evoke simpler and outdoorsy themes. This barrel promises to keep whatever it is put on top safely without taking away the spotlight from it. Guests can probably make it a game to guess the contents of the barrel, just don't think there is nectar inside.</Text>
  <Text Key="037971DD">Barrel of Promise</Text>
  <Text Key="F6CCF857">Three tiers to hold, three tiers to make a statement. This tiered pedestal is perfect for those corners that need something to make them pop! From plants to small lanterns and lamps, make this piece a shining part of your décor.</Text>
  <Text Key="C7B9D52E">Tiers Not Tears</Text>
  <Text Key="C6E25A50">The Skyscraper Bouquet is so enormous that all air traffic will need to be rerouted around it during your gala event. It’s just that big. If it can have that kind of an impact on world travel, just imagine how cool your wedding guests will think you are for having one.</Text>
  <Text Key="C8AB6B7F">The Skyscraper Bouquet - by Colossus Arrangements</Text>
  <Text Key="5A182A53">What's better than getting a bouquet of flowers? A Scepter of Flowers! Its elegant fluted base is perfect for any party or for those parts of your Lot that you want to make a little more fancy! Colorful flower arrangements complement the delicate shape of the base. Make no mistake, this might look delicate but carries mighty décor power to embellish your Lot.</Text>
  <Text Key="C6BA7202">Scepter of Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="5E57A716">It is said if you put things or people in a pedestal, the harder they will fall. But with this arrangement you don't have to worry about anything falling off of it! This modern base is the perfect receptacle for the variety of delicate flower arrangements it comes with. Perfect for those corners that we never really know what to do with, its square shape is perfect for a pop of color with this item.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AF833C9">Bouquet Pedestal</Text>
  <Text Key="577AB8EF">Celebrate with the newlyweds with this expression of their happiness. This tabletop flower arrangement of roses and other flowery friends paint a picture of happiness and bliss that will permeate to the whole venue they are part of.</Text>
  <Text Key="255A0736">Tabletop Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="CAFBFB91">A monetary gift that will bring the happy couple good luck.</Text>
  <Text Key="378ADDE4">Red Envelope</Text>
  <Text Key="18949C00">Missing the magic of walking on a path of flower petals to the altar? Or just want to experience the thrill? This lovely carpet with floral pattern decoration will make you feel like every day is the best, happiest day of your life. Walk on it to keep dreaming and add a lovey-dovey touch to any room. You know you want this carpet. Do you?</Text>
  <Text Key="FBE29ECF">Follow the Flowery Road</Text>
  <Text Key="67B49FD0">Imagine a wedding as if you were getting married like maidens of old fairytales... with nature around you and holding the hands of your love. This pergola will add a touch of the natural in a sensible and sophisticated way with its flourishing foliage elegantly brushing past its posts. Give your wedding day a touch of fantasy with this serene addition to your Lot.</Text>
  <Text Key="A8BC43FF">Fairytale Pergola</Text>
  <Text Key="78359733">The fact is, at your wedding you’re gonna get photographed more times than your aunt Edna at that red light traffic camera on main street. So, to keep those snaps lookin’ fresh, you’ll need some professional help. Maybe it’s time to call SnapHappy Rentals. They’re the folks with The BackDropper Pro. Simply stand in front of it and The Backdropper Pro does the rest – making even the most hideous bridesmaid dresses look spiffy. </Text>
  <Text Key="3389CE62">The BackDropper Pro - by SnapHappy Rentals</Text>
  <Text Key="0B612696">One couple put some banners in the name of love\nOne couple, they come and go\nOne couple here to dance\nOne couple to decorate\n\nIn the name of love\nOne banner in the name of love\nIn the name of love\nWhat more in the name of love\n</Text>
  <Text Key="89B59A49">Banners for Love</Text>
  <Text Key="1EEA335C">From the outside it may look like a regular post, fit for holding any regular banners. But this post is special, this post is &lt;i&gt;the&lt;/i&gt; post that can hold banners filled with love. Strong as anybody's first love, this post is made with solid wood reclaimed from many of the pirate ships that graced Tartosa. Legends say it was built mostly from the very ship that hosted one of Princess Cordelia's loves so you know that if you use this post with your love banners, your love will be of legend.</Text>
  <Text Key="EDB16E33">Strong Post</Text>
  <Text Key="559F2E7B">Flowers are a symbol of happiness at weddings and this pergola shows that in perfect harmony. This beautifully arranged pergola will be the greatest complement to your venue and wedding, making it an enchanting space for the newlyweds and guests to share their happiness and love.</Text>
  <Text Key="3E2092DA">Enchanting Pergola</Text>
  <Text Key="6566D735">It is said that no eyes must pry while the newlyweds get ready for the wedding, this screen can help with prying eyes - No peeking! Oh the anticipation you feel now will be just a memory after your ceremonies and celebrations finish. You can also take this room divider to your Lot as a functional element and a constant reminder of your wedding day.</Text>
  <Text Key="5B2C8ED0">Room Divider of Anticipation</Text>
  <Text Key="2DD4A449">Weddings are expensive so you might as well get your money's worth. That’s where the Wedding Tent comes in. At your wedding it’s an ostentatious covered walkway for your guests. At home it will keep the sun &amp; dust off that engine puller &amp; those auto parts on your lawn. Now that’s real value anyone can see.</Text>
  <Text Key="A70E50AC">The Wedding Tent - by Cheapskate Industries</Text>
  <Text Key="4BCC55BC">It’s been said, weddings are expensive so you might as well get your money’s worth. First, have your wedding at night. That’ll save you a bunch. And this is where the Lighted Wedding Tent comes in. At your wedding it’s an ostentatious covered walkway for your guests. But this one is lighted so, it’ll keep you from getting sued if someone falls off the walkway. At home it will keep the dust off that engine puller &amp; those auto parts on your lawn. Plus, now you’ll be able to rummage around in them at night! That’s real value!</Text>
  <Text Key="922C3513">The Lighted Wedding Tent - by Cheapskate Industries</Text>
  <Text Key="BA1B8101">Staked through the... erm... grass? And you are to blame!\nYou give décor... a good name\n\nWould you be content to see me in your party\nAfter all those little places you put me through\nAfter all that decision making, now I'm lying content\nIsn't it nice to just look at me?</Text>
  <Text Key="4BCF1834">Stakes to the Heart</Text>
  <Text Key="DFBFCBAD">Legend says that if you hear the sounds of bells, it is that love has blossomed in Tartosa. The sounds of this bell will inspire romance to anybody near. So let yourself go once you hear the bells of Tartosa, and let happiness hold you dear.\n\nYou cannot see this bell in buildings in Tartosa anymore, but as a builder you might want this to give to your Lot a piece of history.</Text>
  <Text Key="9387BE78">Love Bell of Tartosa</Text>
  <Text Key="D949E3B6">You see these alot at weddings - they’re practically wedding beacons. Most people call them steeples but they’re actually called a Cupola. You can get this one and put it on the roof for your Wedding, if you want. It’s the original one designed by the famous Norwegian, Francis Fjord Cupola. What?</Text>
  <Text Key="FA4D4AE9">Wedding Beacons</Text>
  <Text Key="D939D08F">You approach the toasting bucket. All eyes on you. 
You give your speech. Listen, feel, but please do not boo!
Will their hands start clapping? Will there be laughter, tears? 
Trying to read their faces, you're flooded with fears!
But then they start laughing and smiling and crying! Your heart is warmed. 
Another successful toast! You've outperformed! </Text>
  <Text Key="7BF59B56">Toasting Celebration Bucket</Text>
  <Text Key="219DD52B">Marigolds are popular in Hindu weddings as they represent the sun, meaning brightness and positive energy. They are also associated with Lord Vishnu and Goddess Lakshmi, who are considered an ideal couple in Hindu mythology. This flowery garland might seem a simple arrangement, but its meaning exudes a powerful meaning.</Text>
  <Text Key="D569EF2A">Colourful Marigolds Garland</Text>
  <Text Key="0D91039F">Don’t you hate it when you’re at a wedding and you can’t get your drink on ‘cause it looks like it’s the Libation Engineer’s first day? Well, being organized is what it’s all about when you’re doling out the bevies at a fancy wedding. And the only sure way to keep those frosties flowing quick and all night long is with the new Hoops, There It Is back bar. It’s got multi-hoop technology assuring the refreshments are close at hand and ready to deal. So, you’ll say hoops, there it is again and again.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0B91346">Hoops, There It Is</Text>
  <Text Key="F0D0A0C9">It has been said that “love is like sandwiches” and “love is never on time”. But, no one has ever said that “love was gonna be easel”. Well, the folks at Dicey Ventures Rental understand this and have done their best to make it easel with the Love Ain’t Always Easel, Easel. You see, this easel is the perfect marriage of style and messaging that make it more easel for you to direct your guests to the reception, buffet, libations or parking at your gala wedding event. All in one, handy, reusable easel. Now, that was easel. Wasn’t it?</Text>
  <Text Key="BD309E2C">Love Ain’t Always Easel – by Dicey Ventures Rental</Text>
  <Text Key="FAD165FC">It wasn’t some big cloudy mystery. You’d been dating for 5 years and the signs were all there. Humongous signs. Signs that read you were about to have your tickets punched for the slow ride to wedding town. Call me a hopeless romantic. Call me a sap with a fist full of Simoleans but I just had to buy you those very signs as your wedding gift. Keep the change - ya happy couple.</Text>
  <Text Key="C15E1153">Those Signs... of Love!</Text>
  <Text Key="FB9A6B02">A sophisticated option for your wedding or event. Perfectly cushioned for long ceremonies, this chair will make your guests stay through the whole of the ceremony, even when it seems it might never end. Its foldable structure is perfect for reuse as it stores nicely away.</Text>
  <Text Key="CB1B60FD">Adored Folding Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="FEA22CD0">Minimalistic yet distinguished chair for your wedding or any event that needs a little spark of life. Comes in a variety of options, this chair is as dependable as the weather, just don't try to water the lovely flowers - your guests won't appreciate that.</Text>
  <Text Key="61055AFF">Adored Adorned Folding Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="62568E95">If you’re looking to assure that your special day turns out well, special, then you better procure the latest in innovative and stylish matrimonial seating from Wisely Wedding Industries. Specifically, their gracefully appointed Mullet Chair is all about Ceremony in the front and Celebration ‘round back. Remember, from this point forward, ‘till death do you part, your wedding seating will be judged by your friends against all weddings yet to come. Choose Wisely.</Text>
  <Text Key="74BF42B0">The Mullet Chair - by Wisely Wedding Industries</Text>
  <Text Key="6503A184">Modeled in strong and weather resistant materials, these chairs are a modern vision of chairs used by Tartosa royalty. Comes in a variety of colors to make your gatherings and weddings stand out in the right places. This chair is discreet yet sophisticated and won't ghost you in performance.</Text>
  <Text Key="3DD1C94B">Not Quite the Ghost Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="0B790E1B">A weaved chair generally has a casual but cool appeal, and the Weaved with Love is no different. The weave pattern supports your back comfortably as well as its gorgeous and simple seat. This is especially handy for those ceremonies that go long and is perfectly neutral for modern sensibility and makes sure that you as a guest stand out.</Text>
  <Text Key="A8078AFA">Weaved with Love Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="AEBEC497">Another option for the Weaved with Love series, this chair has the same weave detailing in the back that makes it casual chic but with added flair as its back is also adorned with flower bouquets that compliment every color of it.</Text>
  <Text Key="37D8096E">Flowered and Weaved with Love Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="ED43C0DD">Made to bask in the sun in the gorgeous summers of Tartosa, this lounge chair is made to impress. With simplicity and elegance, lounge like those famous Sims when they are photographed while they are on holiday. Feel the breeze, the sun, and feel expensive while doing so.</Text>
  <Text Key="1F69F4C8">Riviera Lounge Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="4FDA2D37">Sit your newlyweds in this plush and regal looking loveseat. Made from exquisite fabrics and frames - including a garland of beautiful marigold - your newlyweds, and anyone really, will feel like sitting in the happiest and most comfortable of clouds on their special day.</Text>
  <Text Key="C923FD8E">Harmonious Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="CCF8BEE1">I know this loveseat looks like your uncle Smellvis has been lolly-gaggin’ on it non-stop over the better part of a 3 day weekend during football season. And you’d think that this pew might just have a PU of its own - but you’d be wrong. See, where I come from, we call that antiquing the wood. Makes it look real pretty. And the fine folks at Winds of Change Inc have added that “Just Married Smell” to it. Perfect for your little get together - when the winds are a changin’ for you.</Text>
  <Text Key="5C7AAE94">An Antiqued Pew – by Winds of Change Inc.</Text>
  <Text Key="A65C6AF8">Well, now your dreams have all come to fruition. You’re the proud owner of the Gravy Fountain Mark IV. But if you plan to deploy it at your upcoming nuptials, you’ll need a mighty platform from which to operate. Enter the Gravy Fountain Mark IV Platform. It’s the only apparatus guaranteed to accommodate the genuine Gravy Fountain Mark IV. With plenty of space to stretch out and serve up all 7 kinds of piping hot gravy “your way” and a bunch of other stuff your guests might like to scarf up on, this deluxe, multi-tier platform is a veri-table dream maker. It ain’t no heartbreaker.</Text>
  <Text Key="02C6FFF7">The Gravy Fountain Mark IV Platform</Text>
  <Text Key="607F764E">A perfectly suited banquet table for those who like their wedding or event to be al natural. This construction is perfect for those weddings that can get... quite festive, so you can count on this banquet table to perform best when things get a bit too much. Perfect for hosting those drink fountains, or some great fixings, this table will go through it all with you.</Text>
  <Text Key="C95C7171">Wooden Banquet</Text>
  <Text Key="31E0CDD9">Remember what you were doing when you heard that Fenwick the IV became Fenwick the V? Of course you do. It was one of “those” moments. Well, if you want people to remember what they were doing when you got married, then you need to do 2 things. No.1, invite them to your wedding and No.2, rent the very table at which Fenwick the IV was seated when he got one numeral bigger. You can tell that it’s the real deal by the big V shaped supports holding up the top. Throw the ultimate wedding and be remembered forever like old what’s his face the 5th.</Text>
  <Text Key="10C3445C">Fenwick the V Banquet Table</Text>
  <Text Key="978955CC">You never know who you might end up sitting next to at the reception. Your “good time” is a make or break deal depending on the arrangement of those enigmatic place cards. Well, not anymore because now, every table is The Fun Table when you rent The Fun Table from Dicey Ventures - Guaranteed! Using some highfalootin tech algorithmical stuff you wouldn’t understand, it assigns only folks that you’re compatible with to your table every time. Great for family get togethers too. Make your next wedding a table of fun with Fun Tables. </Text>
  <Text Key="16003C83">The Fun Table – by Dicey Ventures Rental</Text>
  <Text Key="AF4F42E5">A traditional Chinese-Inspired tea set, perfect for showing respect and offering best wishes.</Text>
  <Text Key="80D8A060">Double Happiness Tea Set</Text>
  <Text Key="CAEB5D78">A classic, English-inspired tea set. Think of it as a little, warm hug in a cup. Warning: It might solve all your problems. </Text>
  <Text Key="A4244F77">Just a Spot of Tea, Tea Set</Text>
  <Text Key="AEA51CE0">Bubble solution to make bubbles.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B864D2F">Bubble Bottle</Text>
  <Text Key="65A266DA">For fun with bubbles!</Text>
  <Text Key="6301C405">Bubble Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="C0D0392A">No, this is not a gate into an unknown and uncertain future. This is a minimalistic and elegant wedding arch that will be the perfect frame to your wedding ceremony. As you walk down the aisle you picture yourself embarking in a journey of a lifetime with your significant other.</Text>
  <Text Key="94FF79B5">Glimpse into the Future</Text>
  <Text Key="7E3E2029">Everybody knows that Sims' love is engraved in their heart. You can say it is set in stone, as long as Simmers don't make them fall for other Sims. Nothing could break Sims apart, their love is unshakeable! No matter where they go, route fail, wherever they are. Their love is set in stone forever and never apart.</Text>
  <Text Key="42243D0C">It's all Set in Stone</Text>
  <Text Key="2E70BE0D">Say all the things that make you both smile\nMaking good conversation\nHold each other's hand under this arch\nYou know what I mean\nWe came to Tartosa\nThen lounged by the beach\nThere's nothing left to talk about\nUnless it's on our wedding\n\nLet's get littoral, littoral\nWe're getting married all littoral\nLet's get into littoral\nLet me hear the vows tonight</Text>
  <Text Key="030C0958">Let's Get Littoral</Text>
  <Text Key="C9028A87">There comes a time in every person's life when they must realize that it’s time to hang up the old college toga and settle down with that special someone. What better way to symbolize this precious moment than with the new “The Shindig’s Over” decorative photo op archway where, together, you literally hang up your togas over the top rail. At that point, there’s really nothing left to do but pose for the picture that will sit on your end table until the end of time. How appropriate.</Text>
  <Text Key="FBE7033E">(Hit the lights) The Shindig’s Over</Text>
  <Text Key="294CEBCF">Most dream of their own weddings as events like those in fairytales. The beautiful trees, gardens, and even the birds chirping. Everything showered with colourful flowers and dangly things that shine such as this wedding arch. May your ceremony have a happy ever after!</Text>
  <Text Key="45252B96">Like From a Storybook - Really!</Text>
  <Text Key="6D0A053A">Wedding Bouquet of Red Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="8E861BE5">Red Rose Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="11122903">Wedding Bouquet of Pale Blue Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="294B9E52">Pale Blue Rose Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="0084F198">Wedding Bouquet of Blush Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="29071017">Blush Rose Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="470108B9">Wedding Bouquet of Pastel Garden Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="6EBF5BBC">Pastel Garden Flower Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="AAB8930E">Wedding Bouquet of White Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="471B1231">White Rose Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="CC5C8A27">Wedding Bouquet of Colorful Daisies</Text>
  <Text Key="23AEA05E">Colorful Daisy Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="CB37846C">Wedding Bouquet of Rainbow Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="E27AC3A3">Rainbow Rose Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="6990385D">Delicate Wedding Bouquet of Red Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="500EC348">Red Rose Delicate Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="9F7E0190">Delicate Wedding Bouquet of Pink and Orange Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="5022C7BF">Pink and Orange Rose Delicate Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="91492FBB">Delicate Wedding Bouquet of Colorful Daisies</Text>
  <Text Key="1D98DC1A">Colorful Daisy Delicate Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="25E0FCC6">Delicate Wedding Bouquet of Blush Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="856A5559">Blush Rose Delicate Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="5AFF8DD1">Delicate Wedding Bouquet of White Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="8AFB3724">White Rose Delicate Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="EFC03924">Delicate Wedding Bouquet of Pink Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="3613456B">Pink Rose Delicate Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="9D5E951F">Delicate Wedding Bouquet of Black Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="E6020FC6">Black Rose Delicate Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="C1D9AEEA">Delicate Wedding Bouquet of Blue Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="AA75C875">Blue Rose Delicate Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="D4934A85">Wedding Bouquet of Daisies</Text>
  <Text Key="5F5D6080">Daisy Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="E748D59C">Wedding Bouquet of Purple Crocus</Text>
  <Text Key="B7B50473">Purple Crocus Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="9CE0706D">Wedding Bouquet of Dahlias and Begonias</Text>
  <Text Key="D7D05138">Dahlia and Begonia Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="EA311C0B">Wedding Bouquet of Lilies and Begonias</Text>
  <Text Key="9BD1FE8A">Lily and Begonia Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="6E9C051C">Wedding Bouquet of Birds of Paradise, Daisies, and Dahlias</Text>
  <Text Key="B6C07AF3">Bird of Paradise, Daisy, and Dahlia Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="3584B291">Waiting my savior\nNo room for air, I can't breathe, I would give a window for one more day for a gaze through my heart\n\nI'd give, a window\nFor one more day as the window of your heart\nI'd give a window, for one more day</Text>
  <Text Key="CA8952E4">Window for a Heart</Text>
  <Text Key="38DB6B37">What am I waiting here for, expecting only my heart made of glass?\nCome, wave at me\nJust for a moment of my time, I have a fractured visage where I
should have a heart\nI'm not made of wood\nI'm not falling apart\nBut I would give a kingdom for a window to the heart</Text>
  <Text Key="5947578E">Window of a Heart</Text>
  <Text Key="D59B31BB">Like a window with glass, clearly a good choice\nWindow with a heart, and a frame\nWindow with a peculiar name\n\nNow I know you will never love me, I'm a window without an edge\nI'm a window with a heart\nI'm not allowed to feel human feelings\nI'm king of the wall, I'm a ruler of the focal point, but I'd give it away in a moment.\nIf I only had one moment of looking through your eyes</Text>
  <Text Key="728B421A">Window with a Heart</Text>
  <Text Key="A80B4F66">Alone... so alone... a window to the soul of the world outside... people passing by... no one for me, even with open arms. </Text>
  <Text Key="AC365879">The Longing Window</Text>
  <Text Key="4B35ACA5">A window to the soul of the world outside, people passing by... will one of them look my way? Just me... by the sea as I yearn for a soul to share my life with.</Text>
  <Text Key="3AD79720">The Slightly Less Longing Window</Text>
  <Text Key="7CBA3649">Dancing</Text>
  <Text Key="A894D0FB">Hit the dance floor as a group or sway sentimentally to the music—either way, you're here to have a fun time.</Text>
  <Text Key="D9FD2F31">Partake in desserts that are almost as sweet as time spent with friends and family.</Text>
  <Text Key="C3B52B99">Click on a Dessert dish and then choose to Eat.</Text>
  <Text Key="F75164B3">Desserts</Text>
  <Text Key="5B078D81">Dine together and enjoy festive food for your special occasion. </Text>
  <Text Key="C052D569">Celebration Feast</Text>
  <Text Key="9BACFB33">Let loose and enjoy each other's company with a bit of celebratory juice.</Text>
  <Text Key="B07226D0">Drinks</Text>
  <Text Key="6FD2BBE0">Formally serve tea to close family or more casually share with friends. </Text>
  <Text Key="54308DCB">Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="09647660">Blow Bubbles</Text>
  <Text Key="096D6A7E">Click on a table, a chair, a wedding aisle, or the wedding couple and select blow bubbles.</Text>
  <Text Key="5C9976B5">Blow bubbles for the wedding couple as a celebration of their special day.</Text>
  <Text Key="47B6B90F">Have the wedding couple cut the wedding cake</Text>
  <Text Key="C9A8C585">Cut Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="498DC17D">Time to celebrate and cut the cake in front of your guests.</Text>
  <Text Key="60132DCD">Dancing</Text>
  <Text Key="93BBA046">Click on a dance floor or source of music while music is playing to begin dancing.</Text>
  <Text Key="55C6B37A">Slow or fast, dramatic or silly... dancing is all about movement, expression, and celebration!</Text>
  <Text Key="3C0B5971">First Dance</Text>
  <Text Key="4F669C83">Enjoy your First Dance as a wedding couple in front of your guests.</Text>
  <Text Key="6AE1BAA3">Click on a Dance Floor or your significant other and slow dance with them.</Text>
  <Text Key="F40AFE08">Let loose and enjoy each other's company with a bit of celebratory juice. </Text>
  <Text Key="15536DEB">Click on a Bar to Order a Drink, and Drink it.</Text>
  <Text Key="71FA1A86">Drinks</Text>
  <Text Key="87DF7602">Raise your glasses for a speech in honor of the Wedding Couple.</Text>
  <Text Key="730EFA07">Have Toasts</Text>
  <Text Key="39E7E8C6">Click on the Toasting Celebration Bucket and make or request a toast.</Text>
  <Text Key="3855FBAE">Dine together and enjoy festive food for your special occasion. </Text>
  <Text Key="2B9034DC">Celebration Feast</Text>
  <Text Key="53C89A41">Click on any food to Call To Meal or select any interaction to Eat.</Text>
  <Text Key="9242B6F4">Have Speeches</Text>
  <Text Key="BDCD4849">Click on a wedding guest and ask them to give a speech.</Text>
  <Text Key="12E05723">Perform or Request a Speech for the wedding couple and the guests.</Text>
  <Text Key="7A50BCA0">Spousal Kiss</Text>
  <Text Key="81158FB8">Show your love and devotion to your new spouse with a kiss.</Text>
  <Text Key="26AB50DB">As a member of the wedding couple, click on your sim's partner and select Spousal Kiss.</Text>
  <Text Key="08F16190">Throw rice to celebrate the wedding couple!</Text>
  <Text Key="B342FBD1">Click on a table, a chair, a wedding aisle, or the wedding couple and select Throw Rice.</Text>
  <Text Key="2ADA01D2">Throw Rice</Text>
  <Text Key="DF44E947">Exchange Vows with your significant other to express the long lasting love and dedication you promise to each other.</Text>
  <Text Key="06A81E92">Exchange Vows</Text>
  <Text Key="A2BE5BDF">Click on the Wedding Arch or your Sim's Partner and Exchange Vows.</Text>
  <Text Key="8C23377D">Place a wedding aisle and click on it to send your Sims down the aisle.</Text>
  <Text Key="E3629191">Send important guests or the wedding couple down the aisle in preparation for exciting wedding moments.</Text>
  <Text Key="18DD2C7D">Walk Down the Aisle</Text>
  <Text Key="D69D3AF9">Visit Tartosa's Villa Vigna and enjoy Porto Luminoso's breathtaking cliffside views. Stay in and enjoy all the amenities this rental has to offer or take a walk down through the vineyards and visit the village for a small shopping trip. Just don't forget to try the local cuisine!</Text>
  <Text Key="1B5165EE">Villa Vigna</Text>
  <Text Key="7176783E">Thebe Estate is one of Porto Luminoso's historical buildings—its origins are draped in rumor and are often gossiped about by curious locals. The Thebe family, now the Laurents, have lived here for generations as noted by their fine collection of family heirlooms.  </Text>
  <Text Key="4404A66F">"Laurent" may be a newer name in the area, but the family certainly isn't. For generations, they've owned the local wedding venue, the cornerstone of the wedding industry in the area. And Hilary's family opened the first food stall in the village square back when they moved to the area. Now she's a chef in her parent's restaurant, and the local food market has flourished. Together, this family forms a wedding-industry powerhouse.</Text>
  <Text Key="C03157B6">Laurent</Text>
  <Text Key="F57322B5">Thebe Estate</Text>
  <Text Key="2CAF0DB3">The La Coppia Serena may be the local go-to for wedding ceremonies, but every Sim knows Celebrazioni d'Amore is the best place to host a true party. Afterwards, head into the gardens for a stroll or back behind the lounge for a romantic view of the sea. </Text>
  <Text Key="68D1A860">Celebrazioni d'Amore</Text>
  <Text Key="58FC55C8">Tucked snugly along Tartosa's sunset coastline, Baia dell'amore offers the best of the area: soft and sandy beaches to share with a lover, plus nighttime bioluminescent shores that are perfect for lighting up a romantic dip... and only a short stroll from Porto Luminoso.</Text>
  <Text Key="BEB0EB77">Baia dell'amore</Text>
  <Text Key="7C8DB7CD">Situated just off the Terra Amorosa estuary, close to Hideaway Falls, and overlooked by the Lover's Tree, Via Romanza is a prime piece of real estate. Its location in the heart of Tartosa's love industry begs the question: what will this plot of land become? The wedding industry's next big venue? A rental for the many coupled lovebirds who return on honeymoon? Or simply a home for those who find themselves moved by the land's romantic ambiance?</Text>
  <Text Key="A42B162A">Via Romanza</Text>
  <Text Key="EA72B578">This adorable home hides off Porto Luminoso's shore on tiny Piccola Luce island. Its decor pulls from nature around it—the sea's cerulean waters and the coast's famous, apricot sunsets. There's no better home for a Sim seeking solitude in a love-laced land. </Text>
  <Text Key="4AF29CE7">Piccola Luce</Text>
  <Text Key="A2DF9E47">The golden crown of Tartosa's wedding industry. Sims travel from all around the world to partake of the area's many romance-oriented accommodations, and it all comes together here on the day of each Sim's wedding. Indoor or outdoor, this venue has hosted a multitude of dream weddings and will continue to do so for generations to come. </Text>
  <Text Key="699AE82C">La Coppia Serena</Text>
  <Text Key="8DA02032">The woods surrounding this home create a natural barrier of privacy and peace, the perfect place for a Sim seeking to benefit from the area's attractions yet retain sweet solitude. Years back, this building was the local nectary, but the establishment has since been refurbished into a home for the Markovic family. </Text>
  <Text Key="D25558FB">The Markovic family are locally-renowned for their contribution to the musical-side of the wedding industry, despite having put off their own wedding time and time again. This is in no small part due to relations between them and the Laurent family being rather strained. Mateo believes the Laurents have a stranglehold on local wedding business and works hard to retain relevance. While Lucia's animosity is directed at Hector, a former lover, all the drama and work has kept them busy and unwed!</Text>
  <Text Key="F25E0A5A">Markovic</Text>
  <Text Key="420DBFD1">The Old Wood Nectary</Text>
  <Text Key="61D8EAE9">At first glance, it's obvious this starter is a steal. Scenic views overlook Hideaway falls, the entirety of the Terra Amorosa estuary area, and the Lover's Tree. However, it's the hidden history that makes this spot so particularly notable to the locals. Shhh. It's a secret, though! A bit of sleuthing and you're bound to discover what makes this lot one of the best that Tartosa has to offer. </Text>
  <Text Key="FC3DE29E">Rifugio dei Pirati</Text>
  <Text Key="A05D7DCF">Faiz is a poetic, hopeless romantic living in an area that specializes in the wedding industry—a constant reminder of his single status. He spends his days in the village square, selling flowers, and daydreaming of his missing soulmate. Perhaps one day, his dreams will come true. But until then... he has a flower for everyone.</Text>
  <Text Key="A5EE4196">Jaleel</Text>
  <Text Key="F611E633">Years ago, Dominique and Camille were married in Tartosa. Each year they returned on vacation in hopes of re-experiencing the love - and rich local culture - only Tartosa offers. Once both women retired, they decided to make their yearly trip more permanent. \n\nDominique is an artist who now spends her days painting landscapes and portraits in the village square and Camille is a writer who has taken an interest in the area's storied history. Many consider her to be the Porto Luminoso historian and she can often be found enjoying the outdoors alongside Dominique while chatting about local history with anyone willing to listen.</Text>
  <Text Key="E87F8B62">Sotos</Text>
  <Text Key="08B1130B">(From Viewing a Sand Drawing)</Text>
  <Text Key="83491A7D">(From Viewing a Snow Drawing)</Text>
  <Text Key="88394078">View Sand Art</Text>
  <Text Key="A99AD74A">Kick Out of Wedding Event</Text>
  <Text Key="3D83150F">Serve Dal Makhani</Text>
  <Text Key="841CF6CC">Serve Tartosian Fruit Tarts</Text>
  <Text Key="B95786E3">Serve Gulab Jamun</Text>
  <Text Key="18A79930">Serve Mutton Biryani</Text>
  <Text Key="9B148D25">Serve Roast Duck</Text>
  <Text Key="54ECC707">Serve Sweet Buns</Text>
  <Text Key="96F29719">(From Visiting the Dress Shop)</Text>
  <Text Key="803C53FC">(From Blowing Bubbles)</Text>
  <Text Key="ECC4C820">Blow Bubbles</Text>
  <Text Key="4186236E">(From Giving a Good Speech)</Text>
  <Text Key="A7C274A9">(From Hearing a Good Speech)</Text>
  <Text Key="421D78F5">(From Hearing a Bad Speech)</Text>
  <Text Key="B9CFE91D">(From Giving a Bad Speech)</Text>
  <Text Key="74DC5120">Give Speech</Text>
  <Text Key="631E3E36">Give Speech</Text>
  <Text Key="368AEFFA">Listen To Speech</Text>
  <Text Key="B8E6813A">Ask about Wedding Day</Text>
  <Text Key="B290A87A">Ask To Be Ring Bearer</Text>
  <Text Key="6CF1A35B">Exchange Vows</Text>
  <Text Key="0F9999D8">Exchange Vows with Officiant</Text>
  <Text Key="40CCABE2">Exchange Vows with Officiant and Kiss</Text>
  <Text Key="314DCD35">(From The Wedding Kiss)</Text>
  <Text Key="DA18C019">Spousal Kiss</Text>
  <Text Key="23185861">(From Performing Vows)</Text>
  <Text Key="28141D14">(From Performing Vows)</Text>
  <Text Key="F92597B9">Exchange Vows</Text>
  <Text Key="E69C939B">Exchange Vows and Kiss</Text>
  <Text Key="6855F82F">(From Throwing Rice)</Text>
  <Text Key="ED04027A">Throw Rice</Text>
  <Text Key="44EEDF25">Close (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="C11FFAFD">Open (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="B299A7F3">Reach Cooking Skill 5 to unlock Gourmet Cooking</Text>
  <Text Key="8ADF202A">Cook Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="E39F5414">Wedding Group Dance</Text>
  <Text Key="55EAD6C9">This dance floor is already in use.</Text>
  <Text Key="25F6DD47">Must be in a group of at least two Sims to perform this interaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="ECFCE715">(From Disliking Dancing)</Text>
  <Text Key="2412606B">(From Liking Dancing)</Text>
  <Text Key="62151AC3">Opens: 9am, Closes: 6pm</Text>
  <Text Key="37A720F7">{0.SimFirstName} doesn't have any items in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory that can be sold here.</Text>
  <Text Key="C49577EF">Sell Flowers...</Text>
  <Text Key="6DDB147D">Buy Discounted Wedding Bouquet...</Text>
  <Text Key="D4560800">Buy Wedding Bouquet...</Text>
  <Text Key="1CA43163">Buy Discounted Flowers...</Text>
  <Text Key="EE101DF2">Buy Flowers...</Text>
  <Text Key="A13A8D86">Admire Newlyweds</Text>
  <Text Key="0E794535">{0.SimFirstName} can't wait to tell everyone about {F0.her}{M0.his} engagement. It's {F0.her}{M0.his} favorite topic of conversation because {F0.she}{M0.he} just can't keep it inside anymore. Now onto the wedding planning...</Text>
  <Text Key="EA8BF4A2">Announce Engagement</Text>
  <Text Key="C771A923">Ask for Blessing to Marry</Text>
  <Text Key="75FBA96A">Ask to be Flower Person at Wedding</Text>
  <Text Key="2C20F28C">Ask to be Sim of Honor at Wedding</Text>
  <Text Key="4EE6A910">Ask to be Officiant at Wedding</Text>
  <Text Key="EB1A826A">Ask to be Ring Bearer at Wedding</Text>
  <Text Key="7CEB95FC">Congratulations! We're so excited for your engagement, and can't wait for the wedding.</Text>
  <Text Key="BDD6F0CA">Congratulate on Engagement</Text>
  <Text Key="F0443AC3">Wow, you're married now! Congratulations, is it really the best day of your life like they say?</Text>
  <Text Key="F8896287">Congratulate on Marriage</Text>
  <Text Key="74D1DD8F">Enthuse about Upcoming Wedding</Text>
  <Text Key="AC51B061">Express Doubts about Marriage</Text>
  <Text Key="8EBC15B8">Gaze Lovingly at New Spouse</Text>
  <Text Key="9403B66C">Make Joke about Marriage</Text>
  <Text Key="5EA01F07">Purchase Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="D4E93018">Reminisce About Wedding Day</Text>
  <Text Key="7C85F9D6">(From Expressing Anger About The Bouquet Toss)</Text>
  <Text Key="D50C15A9">Express Anger Over Wedding Day Bouquet Toss</Text>
  <Text Key="8AF2F699">Ask About Flower Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="7E00F9D5">Ask for Bouquet of Flowers Back</Text>
  <Text Key="0EC686A7">(From Expressing Joy About The Bouquet Toss)</Text>
  <Text Key="33032BFE">Express Joy Over Wedding Day Bouquet Toss</Text>
  <Text Key="8D373AA4">(From Asking to Come to a Wedding)</Text>
  <Text Key="2E6CA263">Ask for Invitation to {1.SimFirstName}'s Wedding</Text>
  <Text Key="6A642E20">(From Asking to be Part of the Wedding Party)</Text>
  <Text Key="DB87CEFC">(From Accepting Someone into your Wedding Party)</Text>
  <Text Key="AA0A5330">(From Telling a Wedding Story)</Text>
  <Text Key="C9D9C758">Ask to be {1.SimFirstName}'s Sim of Honor</Text>
  <Text Key="08871BE1">Tell Wedding Story</Text>
  <Text Key="6964F843">Grapevine Gossip</Text>
  <Text Key="B0FB3EC1">Listen to Grapevine Gossip with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="FCD024E4">(From Exchanging Rings)</Text>
  <Text Key="6AF2D925">Select Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="2E747247">Roses</Text>
  <Text Key="3B896A7A">Cutout</Text>
  <Text Key="68F1BB09">Floral and Script</Text>
  <Text Key="3CAD85EF">Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="5F12F24E">Hearts</Text>
  <Text Key="2F993B4B">Mini Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="9DDE1462">Tropical Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="16A34F65">Rainbows</Text>
  <Text Key="161E0598">Cowplant</Text>
  <Text Key="B6059526">Banners</Text>
  <Text Key="037D084A">This cake already has a topper.</Text>
  <Text Key="1F10C3B3">Place Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="CBF2F872">Select Cake Topper From {0.SimFirstName}'s Inventory</Text>
  <Text Key="C01D3632">Plan Wedding Event</Text>
  <Text Key="A84698D8">Plan Formal Outfits...</Text>
  <Text Key="F157B7F6">Buy Wedding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="E6E762A4">Buy Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="23159045">Select New Cake Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="3911249D">Pillow Two-Tiered</Text>
  <Text Key="CF1FD428">Beachy Four-Tiered</Text>
  <Text Key="8744197A">Square Design Round Four-Tiered</Text>
  <Text Key="1200E394">Round Two-Tiered</Text>
  <Text Key="66F323BB">Cupcake Display</Text>
  <Text Key="B8821B58">Heart Two-Tiered</Text>
  <Text Key="1706F8E0">Round Four-Tiered</Text>
  <Text Key="F7B9ADDB">Hexagon Three Tiered</Text>
  <Text Key="5277B225">Square Three Tiered</Text>
  <Text Key="CF4E2D54">Thanks for ordering! The cakes {0.SimFirstName} purchased can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="89EC1430">Purchase Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="BA5908D2">Thank you for your business, {0.SimFirstName}! I hope you enjoy the cake! The cakes {0.SimFirstName} purchased can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="2AFE793E">Purchase Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="EB228213">Add a personal touch to your cake topper!</Text>
  <Text Key="3515E833">Add a special message here.</Text>
  <Text Key="B9BF8BC2">Who is getting married?</Text>
  <Text Key="B685B6A1">Inscribe Wedding Cake Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="32D8D440">Inscribe Wedding Cake Topper</Text>
  <Text Key="5084E395">Dig in Sand Pile</Text>
  <Text Key="5DBBF2CE">Destroy</Text>
  <Text Key="AE24DDF5">Draw in Sand</Text>
  <Text Key="EC00015A">Read Message</Text>
  <Text Key="AC520DF5">"Stubbed my foot yesterday on an anchor, so I'm spending the day beachside. I thought it might be interesting to write my first message in a bottle. Today's thoughts: Sims are always asking me what happened to my ship, Peggy Leg. Well, she sank. Technically... I sank her, but I prefer to avoid technicalities of such a nature. It was an incident involving some kelp, a Mersim, and a dolphin. Anyways, I hope if anyone finds this letter they're in healthier condition than me. Stay safe out there. It's a dangerous world.  - Captain Rodrigo De Pablo." \n\nThe corner of the letter is stained in ink, as if an inkwell was clumsily tipped and spilled over the paper. </Text>
  <Text Key="C5A7F1E5">"Hello! My name is Jace. Tomi told me that she threw a message in a bottle into the sea a few days ago, so I decided to try it too! I am 6 years old, and my favorite color is blue. I like listening to cool kids music and talking with my friends, especially Tomi. In my free time, I've been trying to find buried treasure like a pirate. My favorite place to play is on the pirate playground. Do you have a favorite color? I hope you have a nice day!  - Jace"</Text>
  <Text Key="B03F1518">"Hi! My name is Elsa Bjergsen, and I'm five and a half years old. I read that a message in a bottle once traveled for seventeen months over 14,500 kilometers from where it was cast into the sea. Isn't that neat? I hope mine goes even farther, and also that whoever finds it is having a very nice day. Please write me back. I live on the Crumbling Isle in Windenburg. P.S. My sister says this won't work, but I bet her five simoleons it would!"</Text>
  <Text Key="D45350D5">"I be sending off a short riddle, matey. Solve it if ye can! Why are pirates &lt;i&gt;pirates&lt;/i&gt;?"\n\nWritten on the other side in large letters is the answer: \n"They just Arrrrr!" </Text>
  <Text Key="5A7DF30E">"I'm sorry Temperance, but your calcium-rich sister has stolen my heart. Maybe in another life things could have worked out between us. - G."</Text>
  <Text Key="10D3FF0E">"Hand in hand, we, Camille and Dominique, have pledged ourselves to each other. We send this message off on the day of our wedding. Two souls united in friendship and in love." </Text>
  <Text Key="D2B2036D">"The endless waves crash to and fro,\nwho this reaches I may never know.\nDo your eyes sparkle as you read this?\nThe thought of my rose smiling makes me feverish.\nI hope you feel the same as I,\n that our hopeful love may never die.\n And if you should ever find your way here,\nyou have a heart, a home, and endless cheer."\n\nThe message is signed with "FJ" encased in a small heart. </Text>
  <Text Key="121B9C90">"I'm neither a pirate, nor the adventure she craves, but rather a dear friend. And so I'll send her off with everything but my unrequited love. A secret I share with the sea and no other, for they are alike. While I resemble the tides as they test the boundaries of these shores, returning each night in brilliance. She is as relentlessly free as the sea, untamed and trackless, a force to behold. I would not tame her even if I could." \n\nThe letter is signed with an elegant flourish, "Lady Matilda Tartosa"</Text>
  <Text Key="97D7DD13">"It's taken me a long time to get over Hector, and maybe I haven't truly forgiven him. Our relationship was doomed from the start. But I do really care for Hilary, and I'm glad she seems so happy. I'll always think she deserves better than him though. - Lu" </Text>
  <Text Key="289BFE7F">"Was it my desire for pirate gold or for the sweet, silly faces of the llamas? Surely no Sim would fault me for the latter. I've hid my dealings well, so perhaps history will never know how influential I was in Tartosa's privateer trade—that I invited them here. It wouldn't be proper of a lady, but then again... I've always been a bit of a rebel. Either way, my land thrives."  \n\nThe letter is signed with an elegant flourish, "Matilda" </Text>
  <Text Key="64A2C8B9">"I took the train to visit the sea today. My husband doesn't know. Ever since we moved to Senbamachi, I can tell something is... off. The leaves are beautiful and it's much quieter. I think the fresh air is good for the children, but is it good for my husband and me? - J"</Text>
  <Text Key="D7D2855B">"I'm not leaving due to sorrow. Rather, John's sudden death has reminded me how precious life is. A life of adventure would be most fulfilling, and I intend to make the most of every day. Perhaps I will return to the arctic waters and see the lights in the sky once again."</Text>
  <Text Key="B076F9E9">"Ye be readin' the letter I wrote, arrrr ye? Well, now you're cursed! Ha. Me and me trusty parrot will be free! - Captain Y. Eet"</Text>
  <Text Key="E637FF3B">"I meet everyone eventually. Even you. - Grim" </Text>
  <Text Key="8B9D27E7">"You're Next!" The message is followed by an oddly off-kilter smiley face and a date from about seventy years prior.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0A90295">"If you don't leave this bottle where you found it, the next time you're in a room alone, the door will disappear!" </Text>
  <Text Key="FE6E89B0">"When I was young, I lived in the shadow of a legend, but I decided to tell my own story. I've explored the world—from historic Al Simhara to tiny Oasis Springs. I sailed over a waterfall, kissed a llama, climbed Mt. Komorebi, been madly in love, and raised my greatest pride.... my son. My life is full of memories, and in it's twilight, I send a wish into the ocean: Do not fear the shadows surrounding you, but rather step out and shine brightly." </Text>
  <Text Key="9B42C698">"I spent the morning watching Dominique paint the harbor. When I grow up, I'd like to be just like her. She's so creative and interesting, and it's so sweet how in love she looks when Camille talks to her. I want a life like that. She told me she liked one of my paintings once, so maybe I'm on my way! - Tomi"  </Text>
  <Text Key="BD5C4C4D">"I often gaze up at the moon and wonder if there is more to life. I just want to change myself, for better or worse."</Text>
  <Text Key="675A6A8F">"We send this wish adrift while on honeymoon at Sunlit Tides. May our marriage be as blissful as life is now." Encapsulated in a heart at the bottom are the names Daniel and Mary-Sue Pleasant. </Text>
  <Text Key="469C6916">Restore</Text>
  <Text Key="BC17E5E9">View Snow Art</Text>
  <Text Key="622A24E6">Sell Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="8F4A82B4">Stop Holding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="BCD94440">Put Wedding Cake Topper in Inventory</Text>
  <Text Key="66E4586D">Eat Wedding Cake Together</Text>
  <Text Key="35F820DC">Hold Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="116D88CE">Give Speech</Text>
  <Text Key="2F9BD231">There are no nearly Sims for {0.SimFirstName} to serve tea to.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE9BA54F">There are no Sims selected for this role.</Text>
  <Text Key="8AD0B02F">Select Sim to Walk Solo</Text>
  <Text Key="68D97B45">One Sim</Text>
  <Text Key="C742BAC1">Select Flower Pal</Text>
  <Text Key="1DC6D8D0">Flower Pal</Text>
  <Text Key="65D9BAB2">Select Sim of Honor</Text>
  <Text Key="F84753EF">Sim of Honor</Text>
  <Text Key="09141116">Select Ring Bearer</Text>
  <Text Key="66ACB58B">Ring Bearer</Text>
  <Text Key="4FA93356">Select Escort</Text>
  <Text Key="B35D584B">Two Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="6A415791">Select Escortee</Text>
  <Text Key="A3557C01">Walk Down with</Text>
  <Text Key="E3B742A2">Walk Up with</Text>
  <Text Key="2EF1FD2D">{0.SimFirstName}'s partner isn't nearby.</Text>
  <Text Key="02E7CBFF">Have First Dance with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="46F4366E">Slow Dance Together with</Text>
  <Text Key="C9F88079">Slow Dance Together with</Text>
  <Text Key="D51D8456">Bow and Serve Tea to</Text>
  <Text Key="F2FF0C83">Kneel and Serve Tea to</Text>
  <Text Key="241F8652">Serve Tea to</Text>
  <Text Key="101FB0ED">Cut Cake Together</Text>
  <Text Key="72F06599">Feed Cake to {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="499F993C">Feed Cake to Spouse</Text>
  <Text Key="786209B4">Request Toast from</Text>
  <Text Key="0A76260C">(From Tossing a Wedding Bouquet)</Text>
  <Text Key="90BC7786">Wait for throw</Text>
  <Text Key="077F55AA">Slow Dance Together</Text>
  <Text Key="591FC903">(From Slow Dancing)</Text>
  <Text Key="45963975">Dance Together</Text>
  <Text Key="1D27BA26">(From Serving Tea)</Text>
  <Text Key="B6CEB316">Bow and Serve Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="2FB7FA43">Kneel and Serve Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="94329080">Receive Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="2A0CE7C2">Serve Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="11786BB7">Start Bouquet Throw</Text>
  <Text Key="49E5487D">(From Catching the Flower Bouquet at a Wedding Ceremony)</Text>
  <Text Key="11D2E59D">Throw Bouquet to</Text>
  <Text Key="48BE3830">Listen to Wedding Story</Text>
  <Text Key="33EC45CE">(From Being Dropped while Dancing)</Text>
  <Text Key="BE978159">Chat while Dancing</Text>
  <Text Key="33B1CD16">Flirt while Dancing</Text>
  <Text Key="67AD0059">Kiss while Dancing</Text>
  <Text Key="E6E84939">Let's Have Fun</Text>
  <Text Key="F5698D7F">Let's Dance</Text>
  <Text Key="E6CDD766">Let's Eat Desserts</Text>
  <Text Key="AAAEE793">Let's Eat Food</Text>
  <Text Key="4ECE572D">Let's Get Drinks</Text>
  <Text Key="D1DF724A">Let's Have Toasts</Text>
  <Text Key="D1365F8E">Let's Have Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="4BE8F77B">Complain about Wedding Party</Text>
  <Text Key="8F9DCC60">Enthuse About Party</Text>
  <Text Key="00FF1E90">Wedding Group Dance</Text>
  <Text Key="5CB3DF54">Clean Tea Set</Text>
  <Text Key="6F7707C1">Pour Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="71FFFCB8">Steep Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="64FF2209">Steep Black Dragon Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="B6DACCE1">Steep Calming Chamomile Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="D60CFD9C">Steep Earl Grey Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="0DA3CF45">Steep Healthy Green Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="BA78B860">Steep Orange Blossom Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="A47A994A">Steep Pitch Black Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="2E70AA06">Steep Run Oolong Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="DBF09F9E">Steep Cozy Apple Juice Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="6EEDD795">(From Drawing a Heart)</Text>
  <Text Key="D666FBF2">Draw Heart in Snow</Text>
  <Text Key="9B297310">Draw Heart in Sand</Text>
  <Text Key="3C12F8B9">Draw Smiley in Snow</Text>
  <Text Key="DEECEFF5">(From Drawing a Smiley)</Text>
  <Text Key="7D36D397">Draw Smiley in Sand</Text>
  <Text Key="5CCFC438">Draw Star in Snow</Text>
  <Text Key="98A20FF3">(From Drawing a Star)</Text>
  <Text Key="DB454896">Draw Star in Sand</Text>
  <Text Key="54AE80D4">Walk Down Aisle</Text>
  <Text Key="17750992">Walk Down Aisle with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="D49C36C6">Walk Up Aisle with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="ADC0588E">Walk Up Aisle</Text>
  <Text Key="4DAA99E6">Aisle Debug Buff (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="B4C894AA">Open Envelope</Text>
  <Text Key="131FFC56">Opens: 9am, Closes: 6pm</Text>
  <Text Key="DD0E98CB">Go to Town Hall</Text>
  <Text Key="FA125864">Wait for {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="3CD9AD2C">(From Window Shopping)</Text>
  <Text Key="ABDED5D9">Window Shop</Text>
  <Text Key="2A9B12D3">Cut Cake with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="F4C76A03">{0.SimFirstName}'s cake has been saved and will be available for {F0.her}{M0.his} wedding.</Text>
  <Text Key="BBD3E184">Select as Cake for Wedding Ceremony</Text>
  <Text Key="0F54BEC0">Sneak Taste</Text>
  <Text Key="67D8B6EF">Ask for Marriage Advice</Text>
  <Text Key="8399AED4">Give Toast</Text>
  <Text Key="F9088322">(From Giving a Good Toast)</Text>
  <Text Key="3CAADEA1">(From Giving a Poor Toast)</Text>
  <Text Key="D1585934">(From Hearing a Good Toast)</Text>
  <Text Key="5D0610F6">Regal Reception</Text>
  <Text Key="C5CA7D89">Double Happiness</Text>
  <Text Key="C531F605">Rosey Nuptials</Text>
  <Text Key="FA8B2772">Enchanting Mandap</Text>
  <Text Key="779B62B7">Ready to Mingle</Text>
  <Text Key="FBBB62AF">Exchange Vows</Text>
  <Text Key="94EB0729">Call Attendees to Activity</Text>
  <Text Key="C5628818">Draw</Text>
  <Text Key="99710BD6">Send Down</Text>
  <Text Key="776A82CB">Send Up</Text>
  <Text Key="F3B67015">Steep Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="E4F6439E">Black Dragon</Text>
  <Text Key="B5F6C351">Brew Black Dragon Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="3608E0F3">Orange Blossom</Text>
  <Text Key="886F240C">Brew Orange Blossom Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="4960436A">Cozy Apple Juice Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="3C0E1A15">Brew Cozy Apple Juice Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="0B2392C4">Pitch Black</Text>
  <Text Key="E9267217">Brew Pitch Black</Text>
  <Text Key="04AA91D4">Calming Chamomile</Text>
  <Text Key="A611F907">Brew Calming Chamomile</Text>
  <Text Key="F392EE32">Earl Grey, Hot</Text>
  <Text Key="AD8AEF3D">Brew Earl Grey, Hot</Text>
  <Text Key="E86F9CF4">Healthy Green</Text>
  <Text Key="7B72B527">Brew Healthy Green</Text>
  <Text Key="5E013623">Run Oolong</Text>
  <Text Key="42A7B01C">Brew Run Oolong</Text>
  <Text Key="655F3159">Craft Wedding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="1E35CC1F">Birds of Paradise Wedding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="8B20E22F">Wedding Bouquet made with Birds of Paradise</Text>
  <Text Key="C7714C77">Crocus Wedding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="83883F67">Wedding bouquet made with Crocus</Text>
  <Text Key="04E4BE50">Dahlia and Begonia Wedding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="B9A8D7E0">Wedding Bouquet made with Dahlias and Begonias</Text>
  <Text Key="780150A8">Daisies Wedding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="4D89B118">Wedding Bouquet made with Daisies</Text>
  <Text Key="1F0992C1">Lilies and Begonia Wedding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="524BCE5D">Wedding Bouquet made with Lilies and Begonias</Text>
  <Text Key="86CB1AEF">Bake Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="736BE993">Decorate Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="1081B3D4">Square Design Round Wedding Cakes</Text>
  <Text Key="7477DD59">White with Green Square Design Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="BFE0A7C6">White with Purple Square Design Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="FA1748E3">White with Rainbow Square Design Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="C7B06960">Black with White Square Design Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="1082056D">Gold with Black Square Design Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="40F4A6E9">Four-Tiered Round Cakes</Text>
  <Text Key="4BE3F324">Pink and Teal with Gold Patterning Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="7F8FE848">White with Pink Bunting Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="E825C5B5">Off-White with Grey Bunting Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="863EF49B">Orange and Purple with Gold Patterning Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="837E867E">White and Gold with Black Floral Designs Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="187F0C05">White with White Floral Designs Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="1BD3FE98">Yellow Ombre Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="880B018F">White with Pastel Pink and Purple Drip Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="E199B1E2">White with Purple Plasma Drip Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="3896A559">Galaxy Mirror Glaze Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="3CEC56EC">Pastel Sixam-inspired Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="9E9B90BD">Beachy Wedding Cakes</Text>
  <Text Key="0473B3AA">Red Ombre Beachy Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="64207B8D">Green Ombre Beachy Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="07A9B800">Purple Ombre Beachy Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="F858C403">Sand and Blue Ombre Beachy Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="5CC302E6">Silver and Gold Beachy Four-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="5749950F">Cupcake Wedding Cakes</Text>
  <Text Key="C3D45428">White and Rainbow Cupcake Display</Text>
  <Text Key="8300169F">Blue Ombre Cupcake Display</Text>
  <Text Key="70494332">White and Brown Cupcake Display</Text>
  <Text Key="FD4B5333">Expand to see a variety of Floral Wedding Cake options.</Text>
  <Text Key="BB8157D1">Floral Wedding Cakes</Text>
  <Text Key="BDB3ACAE">White with Pink Roses Two-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="451DB9C1">White with Blue Roses Two-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="167CA314">White with Green Roses Two-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="F040033F">Red with Yellow Roses Two-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="8A788852">Rainbow Ombre with White Roses Two-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="D1952E35">White Naked Cake with Brown Roses Two-Tiered Round Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="68FF50C8">White with Golden Roses Naked Two-Tiered Round Fruitcake</Text>
  <Text Key="16731493">Off-White with Golden Roses Naked Two-Tiered Round Fruitcake</Text>
  <Text Key="E2C50861">Expand this category to see more recipes.</Text>
  <Text Key="65E68E9B">Heart Wedding Cakes</Text>
  <Text Key="9271BC74">Rosy Two-Tiered Heart Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="F74B582B">Red and White Two-Tiered Heart Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="68AC5E8E">White Two-Tiered Heart Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="04F77115">Rosy and White Two-Tiered Heart Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="CF1302A8">Blue Two-Tiered Heart Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="8E3EC51F">White and Grey Two-Tiered Heart Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="01CFB773">Hexagon Wedding Cakes</Text>
  <Text Key="F572811C">Black with Gold Crisscross Pattern Three-Tiered Hexagonal Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="1F550C93">Black with Gold Tree Pattern Three-Tiered Hexagonal Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="9EF67BB6">Black with Silver Floral Pattern Three-Tiered Hexagonal Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="66283F9D">White with Gold Three-Tiered Hexagonal Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="05430C50">Pink Ombre Three-Tiered Hexagonal Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="D4E35427">Red with Gold Filigree Three-Tiered Hexagonal Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="7C7A1DF0">Pillow Wedding Cakes</Text>
  <Text Key="515FA6A5">White with Gold Piping Two-Tiered Pillow Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="47C8FC02">Red with Gold Filigree Two-Tiered Pillow Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="B736DDAF">Pink with White Hearts Two-Tiered Pillow Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="645548C4">Brown with Gold Floral Patterning Two-Tiered Pillow Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="176E5CF1">Blue with Gold Leaf Pattern Two-Tiered Pillow Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="F80298CE">Square Wedding Cakes</Text>
  <Text Key="B8C1BA87">White with White Roses Three-Tiered Square Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="F2D7C430">White with Red Roses Three-Tiered Square Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="8F19BC7D">White with Black Trim Three-Tiered Square Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="9E9BF816">White with Blue Trim Three-Tiered Square Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="1C134073">White with Colored Spots Three-Tiered Square Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="DC112C7C">White and Black with Gold Designs Three-Tiered Square Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="0A697EE9">Red with Gold Trim Three-Tiered Square Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="FD36881C">World-Famous Tartosian Fruit Tart</Text>
  <Text Key="2A31B46E">Dal Makhani</Text>
  <Text Key="22C05E9A">Gulab Jamun</Text>
  <Text Key="0E6EBC95">Mutton Biryani</Text>
  <Text Key="4FD12A4C">Roast Duck</Text>
  <Text Key="5915290E">Sweet Buns</Text>
  <Text Key="88E2353B">White and Rainbow Cupcake Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="BF8512F8">Romantic sites and scenery have long graced the seaside region of Tartosa, creating the perfect setting for love and matrimonial pursuits. It isn't uncommon for vacationers and honeymooners alike to return year after year, seeking to re-experience the intimacy of visits past. They say there's a love story in the making for everyone. Just ask Tartosa's residents, and they'll excitedly gossip about local Wedding Industry shenanigans or the area's love-laced, historical past. But even if a Sim doesn't find their soulmate here, one thing is for certain... they're fated to fall in love with the land.</Text>
  <Text Key="C6CCCF03">Tartosa</Text>
  <Text Key="04B9B452">Being a special part of the wedding is something that will be remembered forever.</Text>
  <Text Key="23362CF8">Honored Wedding Party</Text>
  <Text Key="CAE9BCA2">It's an honor to be selected a Sim of Honor for {1.SimName}'s Wedding.</Text>
  <Text Key="506B2C28">Chosen to be Sim of Honor</Text>
  <Text Key="2FB86A1E">{0.SimFirstName} is still overjoyed that {1.SimName} chose {M0.him}{F0.her} as Sim of Honor.</Text>
  <Text Key="C35ABD64">Chosen to be Sim of Honor</Text>
  <Text Key="C6AF152B">{1.SimFirstName} totally nailed the speech at {0.SimName}'s Wedding. Couldn't be happier!</Text>
  <Text Key="C40E2D6F">Gave Good Wedding Speech</Text>
  <Text Key="106A4E80">{1.SimName} asked {0.SimFirstName} to come to their Wedding, but was never properly invited! The nerve!</Text>
  <Text Key="74FCABAA">Wasn't Invited to the Wedding!</Text>
  <Text Key="70CB0495">{0.SimFirstName} is bitter about {1.SimName} not selecting {M0.him}{F0.her}. That stings!</Text>
  <Text Key="7E3E99FD">Not Selected as Sim of Honor</Text>
  <Text Key="47992D11">{0.SimFirstName} is bitter about {1.SimName} not selecting {M0.him}{F0.her}. That stings!</Text>
  <Text Key="C033B839">Not Selected as Sim of Honor</Text>
  <Text Key="8881E8ED">{0.SimFirstName} served some tea to {1.SimFirstName}, and now their friendship seems closer than ever!</Text>
  <Text Key="2CC78A85">Teatime with Friends</Text>
  <Text Key="AB935666">The first time you dance with your spouse is a truly romantic occasion!</Text>
  <Text Key="D679DEDC">Dancing Close Now and Forever</Text>
  <Text Key="1AFE4432">{0.SimFirstName} kicked {1.SimFirstName} out of a wedding event. What nerve!</Text>
  <Text Key="37DCC158">Kicked Out of Wedding Party</Text>
  <Text Key="3B691749">{1.SimName} tried to grab a piece of cake early at my wedding! UNACCEPTABLE!</Text>
  <Text Key="FDD8F201">You Ate Cake Early!</Text>
  <Text Key="59FA021C">On the best day of my life, {1.SimName} chose violence. </Text>
  <Text Key="BABF08B6">Got into a Fight at MY WEDDING!</Text>
  <Text Key="3CEC44A2">In case you didn't get the memo {1.SimName}, that was supposed to be a Wedding!</Text>
  <Text Key="F055C428">You interrupted the Wedding Ceremony!</Text>
  <Text Key="AAD91AA0">{0.SimFirstName} is angry that {1.SimName} tried to romantically upstage {M0.him}{F0.her} at {M0.his}{F0.her} Wedding. Not cool.</Text>
  <Text Key="0A81BC4A">Romantically Inappropriate at MY WEDDING!</Text>
  <Text Key="DF3505A9">Couldn't you just wait a little longer before kicking the can? This day was supposed to be about me!</Text>
  <Text Key="E5D48BE1">You Died at MY WEDDING!</Text>
  <Text Key="319F8799">Faiz</Text>
  <Text Key="89B2107C">Jaleel</Text>
  <Text Key="F85B50CE">Thebe</Text>
  <Text Key="18E6BC89">Arnessa</Text>
  <Text Key="5CB10F40">Laurent</Text>
  <Text Key="401A599F">Greta</Text>
  <Text Key="2441C364">Laurent</Text>
  <Text Key="0C81AAFB">Hector</Text>
  <Text Key="4179FA1C">Laurent</Text>
  <Text Key="74FB75A3">Hilary</Text>
  <Text Key="A79B0B10">Laurent</Text>
  <Text Key="39C7E04F">Jace</Text>
  <Text Key="79723612">Markovic</Text>
  <Text Key="7B329855">Lucia</Text>
  <Text Key="BFE67BFD">Mateo</Text>
  <Text Key="5A810830">Tomi</Text>
  <Text Key="2CC9EEE2">Soto</Text>
  <Text Key="638CD145">Camille</Text>
  <Text Key="5F365EDB">Dominique</Text>
  <Text Key="BA0A9572">Bach Party</Text>
  <Text Key="B76C1825">A wedding event must have the option to include activities.</Text>
  <Text Key="5D670AAA">(From Attending a Bach Party)</Text>
  <Text Key="821147A8">A fun outing with friends to celebrate your upcoming wedding.</Text>
  <Text Key="1778FC5D">Engagement Dinner</Text>
  <Text Key="3A3848DD">A dinner with friends and family to celebrate the new engagement!</Text>
  <Text Key="F52C326F">Family Gathering</Text>
  <Text Key="DE034C63">Family gatherings are common with any wedding, but can look very different from family to family. No matter how you celebrate, this is a time to share with loved ones. </Text>
  <Text Key="29D2D14B">Reception</Text>
  <Text Key="D7FDEABF">A wedding reception is the perfect time to gather friends and family together and celebrate your recent marriage.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B77ED95">Rehearsal Dinner</Text>
  <Text Key="C97FB6F5">In preparation for your upcoming nuptials, gather with friends and family for a dining experience!</Text>
  <Text Key="99C968C8">(From Attending Vow Renewal Ceremony)</Text>
  <Text Key="71D6D50A">Vow Renewal</Text>
  <Text Key="1D0EC1F2">Some things are worth saying twice. A chance to get together with friends and family, renew vows, and say "We still do." </Text>
  <Text Key="D9839FA7">Exchange Vows</Text>
  <Text Key="1F2A0106">Blow Bubbles</Text>
  <Text Key="95755051">Cut the Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="9FD90101">Dancing</Text>
  <Text Key="12680C8E">First Dance</Text>
  <Text Key="C4C31032">Drinks</Text>
  <Text Key="C032676D">Have Toasts</Text>
  <Text Key="51B56070">Celebration Feast</Text>
  <Text Key="94967611">Have Speeches</Text>
  <Text Key="BDDCFCF6">Spousal Kiss</Text>
  <Text Key="F94142B0">Throw Rice</Text>
  <Text Key="13CAA27A">Walk Down the Aisle</Text>
  <Text Key="2E870B59">Serve Tea</Text>
  <Text Key="9863128B">Click on a Tea Set to Steep, Pour, and Serve tea.</Text>
  <Text Key="69715E59">Want your Lot to reminisce about your destination beach holiday? Look no further! The "I Love Sand" terrain option will help you relive your wonderful memories of a fantastic voyage.</Text>
  <Text Key="FD970DDC">I Love Sand</Text>
  <Text Key="489D78CB">Sims can now be engaged in Create-A-Sim so that you can start your wedding story right away. Once both Sims are created you will be able to select Fiancé from the Create-A-Sim relationship options for any Sims Young Adult and older.</Text>
  <Text Key="20523B39">You can also get married at a City Hall! Use your phone to travel with your Fiancé Sim to the Tartosa World map. Then select any lot in the Porto Luminoso neighborhood. City Hall is located around the back of the village square along the gardens. Click on the building to Get Married. </Text>
  <Text Key="1EF043DC">To elope immediately, click on your Fiancé Sim and choose the "Elope Immediately with..." interaction. This interaction has a double-linked ring icon and can be found towards the front of the interaction menu.</Text>
  <Text Key="3EDF6D24">Both the "Elope Immediately" Sim interaction and the "Get Married" interaction on a wedding arch will allow Sims to tie-the-knot on-the-spot. You can also plan a wedding event if you want to customize your wedding experience, invite Sims, assign wedding roles, choose a location and time, or better control the flow of the wedding events. To do this, see the Tutorial section on "Wedding Event Planner." During the Wedding Ceremony Event, you can "Exchange Vows" to get married. </Text>
  <Text Key="37A87397">Once engaged, your Sims are ready to get married. Sims can 'tie the knot' a number of ways!\n• Elope Immediately with a social interaction \n• Using a Wedding Arch\n• At Tartosa's Porto Luminoso City Hall\n• During a Wedding Ceremony or on-the-spot</Text>
  <Text Key="7CD6857B">To get married using a wedding arch, go into Build Mode and search "Wedding Arch." Place down a wedding arch and return to Live Mode. Click on and interact with the wedding arch to either Plan Wedding Event or Get Married.</Text>
  <Text Key="7E49B99A">Of course, you can still do this in Live Mode through Romantic interactions with another Sim!</Text>
  <Text Key="9C127BAA">Getting Married</Text>
  <Text Key="D328A1B9">There are two Aisle types that are available in three sizes. The first has flower petals to line the pathway and the other will appear mostly invisible once you leave Build Mode. The invisible version will highlight when you hover over it and then you will be able to select it to run interactions to send Sims down the aisle.</Text>
  <Text Key="88759814">All aisles have a heart icon on one side to tell you which direction the Sims will walk towards when they walk down the aisle. The heart is where Sims will end up.</Text>
  <Text Key="CACCEBC4">Wedding Aisles allow Sims to walk down the Aisle as Flower Pals, Ring Bearers, individually or as a pair. These objects can be placed down from Build mode almost anywhere that sims can walk however the terrain underneath them will need to be flat. </Text>
  <Text Key="8BDA283D">Wedding Aisles</Text>
  <Text Key="F0B8C25B">After a Wedding Ceremony has been scheduled, you will be able to save a wedding cake for the event by selecting "Select as Cake for Wedding Ceremony" from the cake you want to save. Then the cake will be set aside until the wedding starts. Once the wedding event has started you will be able to "Place Cake" to put the cake out for the event. </Text>
  <Text Key="93F98535">Cakes can be placed almost anywhere, but to place a topper or to Cut the Cake Together the cake will have to be on a dining table. For most tables, the cake will need to be in the center, but for a larger round table it will need to be a little closer to the edge for Sims to reach it.</Text>
  <Text Key="578B9AD9">For many, Wedding Cakes are one of the most important things at a wedding. In Tartosa's Porto Luminoso, Sims are able to taste a variety of cake flavors at the patisserie stand near the village square. After the all important tasting, Sims will be able to purchase Wedding cakes through a computer, or make one themselves if they have the gourmet cooking skill.</Text>
  <Text Key="A40FFE2A">Wedding Cake</Text>
  <Text Key="E6EC8301">Once your Sims are engaged, there are a few ways to plan a wedding or wedding event. Wedding events can be planned via the Computer, Phone, or Calendar. Events planned on the Computer and Phone will happen on the current day, while scheduling an event through the Calendar will let you schedule one on the day that you select. You will also have the ability to go back and edit events after they have been scheduled, the only requirements will be that you have selected the required Sims and a time and place for the event.</Text>
  <Text Key="D7F8130A">All Wedding Events have the ability to select Activities that help customize the event to fit your Sims. Each Wedding Event has a specific selection of Activities that are appropriate for that type of event. There is no limit to the number of activities that you select. While Activities will be listed to remind you during the event, there is no downside if you decide to not run these activities while the event is active.</Text>
  <Text Key="0D48055B">In the Style Tab of the Wedding Ceremony event you will be able to enter Create-A-Sim to change the formal outfits of your Sims. Only the primary formal outfit will be selected for Wedding Ceremony event, but once the event has started you can change to any outfit you choose. You will also be able to request that Sims show up in a specific color, or clothing style under the Guest Attire section. There is also a spot to view your cake once you have selected one for your wedding.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB4E1A7C">Wedding Ceremony events have a few extra special selections available that can make your Sim's special day more unique. Your Sims can ask their friends and family to be part of their wedding as a Sim of Honor, an Officiant, a Ring Bearer, or a Flower Pal. Once Sims have been asked to be one of these special roles, you will be able to select them for this role in the Wedding Ceremony planner.</Text>
  <Text Key="6AFAB05A">Planning Wedding Events</Text>
  <Text Key="9BCCD4CF">To gather Sims for a bouquet toss, click on the bouquet and Hold Bouquet. Then select Start Bouquet Throw on the bouquet or the terrain. Once Sims are gathered select a Sim to Toss the Bouquet to. Sims may need some open space to be able to toss the bouquet.</Text>
  <Text Key="679AEF8A">Wedding Bouquets can be purchased from the Flower Cart in Tartosa's Porto Luminoso village square. Sims will receive these flowers in their inventory and can hold onto them until the wedding. These flowers can be placed in the world as a decorative object or can be held by the Sim for a bouquet toss.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC3CE522">Wedding Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="C3F2B163">My Wedding Stories</Text>
  <Text Key="01C4CB04">Sun Faded Paint</Text>
  <Text Key="156513E9">Historians say Porto Luminoso's name originated when pirates arrived at shore, attracted by the glowing tides, the promise of trade, and the invention of the fruit tart. Overtime, the village flourished, and while still famous for its fruit tarts, Porto Luminoso's real claim to fame is its self-proclaimed-title as the wedding industry's premiere destination for romance and matrimonial services.</Text>
  <Text Key="F95241CC">Porto Luminoso</Text>
  <Text Key="7B331034">A short trip up the coastline from Porto Luminoso is the loving land, known as Terra Amorosa to the locals. Whether fishing off the boardwalk, swimming at the bottom of secluded Hideaway Falls, or hiking up the hillside to visit the area's famous Lover's Tree, any Sim is bound to fall madly in love with the various charming sights and historic landmarks this lover's paradise has to offer.</Text>
  <Text Key="3095D39B">Terra Amorosa</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>