<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="39CBB8E6">Much like a royal throne, this designer changing station is the best seat in the house, thanks to its soft memory foam cushion and classy metal accents. </Text>
  <Text Key="52B05CF9">Lavish One's Changing Station</Text>
  <Text Key="8ADA8E86">This crib is an exact replica of one carved by the infamous Gunther Goth. It is made of fine oak from Pleasantview's forests, and it is just as comfortable as it is elegant.</Text>
  <Text Key="44433519">Heirloom Crib</Text>
  <Text Key="4CC6F00F">A beautiful gift from Aunt Agnes, this bassinet is guaranteed to be passed down for generations thanks to its sturdy frame and timeless appeal.</Text>
  <Text Key="51ABE1D6">Beautiful Bows Bassinet</Text>
  <Text Key="4165CC73">Is your infant ready for that big day when they transition from a crib to a bed? Look no further! This heirloom bed features all the charm and elegance of its predecessor. Aw, they grow up so fast! </Text>
  <Text Key="F12CBBA2">Heirloom Toddler Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="B933E76A">When your little one is ready for storytime, look no further than this elegant cabinet of children's books featuring beloved classics like "Goodnight, Plumbob," "Oh, the Cowplant's You'll Grow," "Make Way for Llamas," and "The Very Hungry Voidcritter."</Text>
  <Text Key="EDA609F5">Storytime Bookcase</Text>
  <Text Key="A7CA6609">These silk and velvet curtains are truly timeless and guaranteed to add a spark of color and joy to any nursery!</Text>
  <Text Key="C0107B6C">The Dreamer's Drapes</Text>
  <Text Key="2BC60B5D">This doll house features a lavish and stately home. In fact, it looks oddly familiar... don't you think?</Text>
  <Text Key="6111CC48">Little Ophelia Villa Dollhouse</Text>
  <Text Key="E95FD125">Purchased from the well-known clothing shop at 330 Main Street, proudly display this curated collection of boutique clothes for your little one in style. Who knew such a set of small garments would cost so much? No price is too high for your little angel!</Text>
  <Text Key="BB5BDCA0">Little Boutique Clothes by 330 Main</Text>
  <Text Key="198610ED">This elegant yet functional playmat features the cutest little gnome, llama, and other iconic toys made out of soft wool and cotton. It lets your little one know that they are your greatest treasure.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2B64AB8">Soft and Supple Playmat</Text>
  <Text Key="457F71C7">Don't try swinging from this chandelier! This delicate ceiling light has individually placed crystals that are sure to stun and sparkle as they light up the room. </Text>
  <Text Key="C2F5147E">Super Fragilistic Chandelier</Text>
  <Text Key="A61708B4">Mr. Gerbit is a friendly and kind llama friend that all Sims love, no matter how big or small! He'll always accompany you by being the most wholesome beacon of light in any room.</Text>
  <Text Key="30B7551B">Mr. Gerbit Table Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="2811BC83">A well-loved set of wooden blocks, rumored to be Bella Goth's favorite childhood toy.</Text>
  <Text Key="062700D2">Antique Blocks</Text>
  <Text Key="3C86CAA8">A single antique block.</Text>
  <Text Key="7AC855C7">Antique Block</Text>
  <Text Key="C63E3EE8">This plush rug is the perfect spot for your little one to play with toys or take a blissful nap. It was also the preferred napping spot for Hecuba and Menelaus, a pair of well-loved Siamese cats who lived in Old Town. </Text>
  <Text Key="40A55707">Plush Naptime Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="3BD06CE1">Like Simis Bachelor, you and your little one can be a hot air balloon aficionado! Who knows what exciting and magical places it will take you to?</Text>
  <Text Key="0C765894">Dreamland Mobile</Text>
  <Text Key="9EBBB5B0">This heirloom wagon toy has been passed down for generations. It was initially purchased from Apothecary Todd in Magic Town, who claimed it would bring joy and prosperity.</Text>
  <Text Key="4CF4745F">Wagon O' Wares</Text>
  <Text Key="445E9C97">No Sim would ever dream of leaving home without it, trust us! </Text>
  <Text Key="0A80116E">The Essential Diaper Bag</Text>
  <Text Key="72EEBC74">My oh my, these friendly creatures are all wearing outfits! They look very dapper, I must say. That possum even looks like he went to medical school!</Text>
  <Text Key="0E6327DB">Friendly Fur Friends Plush</Text>
  <Text Key="453297A2">Each milestone in your child's life is something to be celebrated. Be sure to take as many pictures as possible to celebrate every moment. Soon enough, you'll have a wall full of precious memories to look back on!</Text>
  <Text Key="A158A41D">Memorable Milestone Frames</Text>
  <Text Key="A50BD7A0">It's not so much a recreation of a circus tent as it is a nod to one. It's subtle but invokes both whimsy and elegance. Circus music sold separately. </Text>
  <Text Key="6247A1EF">The Clowntastic Canopy</Text>
  <Text Key="1FF46CA4">This sleek clothing rack proudly displays your curated infant clothing and toys. Featuring delicately carved details and elegant curves, it is undoubtedly a statement piece.</Text>
  <Text Key="E12A87EB">Lavish One's Clothing Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="F33EEC08">When you're at the Changing Station, sometimes an extra storage shelf within arm's reach is just what you need. Now, you conveniently have all your extra changing supplies ready to go!</Text>
  <Text Key="EEE2ACA7">Lavish One's Wall Shelf </Text>
  <Text Key="B09CBB5F">Providing the utmost comfort and the perfect rocking motion, read your loved one a story and rock them to sleep. Plus, it's just as functional as it is stylish!</Text>
  <Text Key="03C27906">Littlehaven Rocking Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="74F57F61">This designer nightstand is the perfect counterpart to any nursery setup. Those classic carvings and metal accents stand out and make a statement; it even has a spot to store toys!</Text>
  <Text Key="457C0814">Lavish One's Nightstand</Text>
  <Text Key="32C71A45">It's safe to say that every family has a set of toys passed down from generation to generation. That chest has the same antique wooden smell and holds the most precious childhood toys. The Heirloom Toy Box will surely bring that sentimental feeling of nostalgia. What toys will you pass on to your little one? </Text>
  <Text Key="FC99CC40">Heirloom Toy Box</Text>
  <Text Key="38A390E4">The Storybook Nursery</Text>
  <Text Key="6FFDCC91">Pleasant Views of Pleasantview </Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>