<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="64C253D3">Who needs a fancy new activity table when some imagination and a little cardboard can create something entirely new.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C45B682">Crafty Little Car Activity Table</Text>
  <Text Key="95E665FE">Bring your backyard campout to the next level with this semi-comfy fold-up bed with folding legs that keep you off of the cold hard ground.</Text>
  <Text Key="10071881">Underneath the Stars Fold-Up Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="30B754D9">Roast marshmallows and stay warm with this sturdy and safe firepit. Perfect for your backyard!</Text>
  <Text Key="44A2295C">Cozy Backyard Firepit</Text>
  <Text Key="A7185825">Why buy a dollhouse when you can just make your own? And why build a regular house when you can build a rocket house? The possibilities are endless!</Text>
  <Text Key="D240C1A0">Up, Up into the Stars Dollhouse</Text>
  <Text Key="91AA3031">Special Don't Wake the Llama Yeti Edition.</Text>
  <Text Key="D762ED04">Don't Wake the Llama Yeti Edition</Text>
  <Text Key="A83A8341">This string of lights is really low to the ground. Maybe it's for ambiance? Perhaps they're string lights for ants!</Text>
  <Text Key="A6D04074">String Lights for Ants</Text>
  <Text Key="CE705A1C">Nothing says 'backyard charm' like a jar full of fireflies. Luckily, these mini string lights from the hardware store only cost a few Simoleons, and no real fireflies were captured to create this cute outdoor lamp.</Text>
  <Text Key="35F369F3">Jar Full of Fireflies</Text>
  <Text Key="8592AC63">This lamp is sturdy enough for outdoor use and cute enough to go anywhere with your space-obsessed little one.</Text>
  <Text Key="E96E0932">Light My Way to the Moon Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="79DC0BFD">Why stay indoors to watch television when you can hang up a blanket and project the TV on it to enjoy every warm summer night.</Text>
  <Text Key="5D9C6768">Backyard TV Projector</Text>
  <Text Key="22C51FEA">Keep the wet grass from ruining your late-night backyard adventures with this waterproof lawn blanket.</Text>
  <Text Key="B3CB4B75">Outdoor Lawn Blanket</Text>
  <Text Key="70149F60">When your parent won't splurge on a new tent, some blankets and PVC do the job just fine!</Text>
  <Text Key="99804CAF">Ultimate Fantasy Blanket Fort</Text>
  <Text Key="A610E389">A pillow is a must-have for every sleepover. It's always good to bring your own with you, just in case you get a bit homesick.</Text>
  <Text Key="37587BEC">Bring Your Own Pillow</Text>
  <Text Key="799A5154">Pop-up books are loads of fun. This one is left open to the best part of the story.</Text>
  <Text Key="A5965D3B">Pop-Up Storytime</Text>
  <Text Key="C2979B3E">This sweet little gnome has a weakness for marshmallowy goodness on a warm summer's night.</Text>
  <Text Key="4ED91EC1">The Sweetest Little Gnome</Text>
  <Text Key="674BCC87">No backyard sleepover is complete without a smorgasbord of gooey, chocolatey treats!</Text>
  <Text Key="129B293E">More Smores</Text>
  <Text Key="79F14BC9">Backyard campouts need lots of surfaces. When you run out, you make do with what you can find!</Text>
  <Text Key="4CCCAF2C">Makeshift Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="228AEDF8">This chair comes in a variety of little pals in little critter form. Perfect for your little one.</Text>
  <Text Key="85F518F7">Little Pals Folding Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="0E88C7B8">These chairs were found in the back of an old abandoned shed. They may not be the most comfortable, but they get the job done!</Text>
  <Text Key="F0538EB7">Needs Paint Backyard Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="DD390DC7">TV nights under the stars require a lot of seating. When you run out, an upturned crate and cozy blanket could end up being the best seat in the house.</Text>
  <Text Key="D277287E">Makeshift Extra Seating</Text>
  <Text Key="49E0CB3B">Cozy backyard campouts are 10 times better with some sweet tunes. Play your favorites on the Kitty Tunes Radio.</Text>
  <Text Key="6E2DD69A">Kitty Tunes Radio</Text>
  <Text Key="46ED5003">The backyard can be a big scary place, even for the bravest little Sim. If you feel a little overwhelmed, Stuffie is here to be a friend.</Text>
  <Text Key="7BD66352">Bigfoot Stuffie</Text>
  <Text Key="34DA0535">Lights? A little blanket? Could this swing set get any cozier?</Text>
  <Text Key="AB22B8D0">Cozy Little Swing Set</Text>
  <Text Key="1F3CA284">This table was found in the back of an old abandoned shed. It may need a little paint, but it's perfect for a cozy backyard meal.</Text>
  <Text Key="937AFC4B">Needs Paint Dining Table</Text>
  <Text Key="F2BA44AA">Need a table in a hurry? This folding table is perfect for all of your on-the-go surface-related needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F20C435">Little Outdoor Folding Table</Text>
  <Text Key="7A75241F">This gaming table was found in the back of an old abandoned shed. It may need a little paint, but it's perfect for a game of cards or a round of Don't Wake the Llama!</Text>
  <Text Key="D3128CC6">Needs Paint Game Table</Text>
  <Text Key="C4AD68A5">Some folks say that backyard camping isn't real camping, but we all start somewhere. Get plenty of make-believe time in with the Little Camping Buddy until you're ready for the real thing.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0FA0B20">Little Camping Buddy</Text>
  <Text Key="BD8F4416">Don't Wake the Llama</Text>
  <Text Key="8EAAEA90">Replace Don't Wake the Llama</Text>
  <Text Key="8FE13A2D">Backyard Campout</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>