<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="95FAA608">Ding! {0.SimFirstName}'s efficient use of Prepped Ingredients allowed {0.SimPronounObjective} to cook extra meal servings! You can find them in {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="FDA6D4E1">(From Eating Artful Focaccia)</Text>
  <Text Key="8D32174A">(From Eating Curious Pizza)</Text>
  <Text Key="E73DE4BF">(From Eating Pleasantly-Unpleasant Waffles)</Text>
  <Text Key="FA039E30">(From Eating Heart's Desire Waffles)</Text>
  <Text Key="4222DDA3">(From Selling Poor Quality Pufferfish Nigiri)</Text>
  <Text Key="3E909EBF">(From Selling Ambrosia to a Ghost)</Text>
  <Text Key="B30D9844">(From Successful Food Sale)</Text>
  <Text Key="B66E500A">(From Selling overpriced Poor Quality food)</Text>
  <Text Key="F83BF8DB">(From Selling an Excellent Quality meal)</Text>
  <Text Key="BBF5EC28">(From Selling Food with Garlic to a Vampire)</Text>
  <Text Key="46272B57">(From Selling Vegetarian Food to a Vegetarian)</Text>
  <Text Key="9406BFAB">(From Selling Raw Meat to a Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="071977FE">(From Selling Curious Pizza to an Alien)</Text>
  <Text Key="B9C46B60">(From Selling Plasma Food to a Vampire)</Text>
  <Text Key="5C28594A">(From Selling Ice Cream or Drinks in Warm Weather)</Text>
  <Text Key="5FF79CC1">(From Selling Trash Fruit Food)</Text>
  <Text Key="C1B1B9E3">(From Selling Soup)</Text>
  <Text Key="1802F05C">(From Selling Ultimate Vampire Cure to a Vampire)</Text>
  <Text Key="F64A01E5">(From Selling Wolf-B-Gone to a Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="09905080">Chop Chopper</Text>
  <Text Key="3F30D3CB">Slicer and Dicer</Text>
  <Text Key="6FF14AC2">Flavor Fusionist</Text>
  <Text Key="49C5446D">Mixing Maestro</Text>
  <Text Key="E165A9FD">Carb Commerce</Text>
  <Text Key="EB739B2E">Nom Nom Nomad</Text>
  <Text Key="31DA6807">Hustling Hawker</Text>
  <Text Key="D2DB0E10">Street Stall Sage</Text>
  <Text Key="503710CE">(From Appliance Wiz Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="CCC3AAD2">(From Market Magnate Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="872D32EC">{0.SimFirstName} has just mastered the use of small appliances and has become a very efficient chef when it comes to using prepped ingredients in recipes!\n\nTrait Earned: Batch Cook\nSims with the Batch Cook trait are rewarded for their mastery of small appliances with extra servings of prepared meals!</Text>
  <Text Key="5393454C">This Sim knows their way around small kitchen appliances!</Text>
  <Text Key="864F12C8">Appliance Wiz</Text>
  <Text Key="E9192181">{0.SimFirstName} has just become a salesperson extraordinaire! Running a business is hard work, and they certainly have proved it!\n\nTrait Earned: Booth Boss\nIncrease the odds of items being sold during Sale Events and access a higher markup interaction!</Text>
  <Text Key="39C528B5">This Sim wants to operate the most profitable Food Stand!</Text>
  <Text Key="57FF7EB1">Market Magnate</Text>
  <Text Key="F4F34B6F">Who knew carbohydrates could be so aesthetic?</Text>
  <Text Key="CC0236B6">Carbspiration</Text>
  <Text Key="638277A6">Pascal, Vidcund, Lazlo, Tycho, and Nova all know the truth. And now, you do too.</Text>
  <Text Key="12C0E8B9">Pizza is Out There</Text>
  <Text Key="5B914E26">Cause some chaos, the way Lilith would.</Text>
  <Text Key="8610A439">That Waffle had Horns!</Text>
  <Text Key="8C93AAC2">When you're feeling Angelic, it's easy to be friendly!</Text>
  <Text Key="D2C05ABD">That Waffle was Heavenly!</Text>
  <Text Key="8849635B">That Waffle made me want to kiss kiss fall in love!</Text>
  <Text Key="64EC033A">Desirable Snack</Text>
  <Text Key="9D8AE438">Cooking is so efficient thanks to batter prepared in the Stand Mixer!</Text>
  <Text Key="496E3C37">Prepped for Success</Text>
  <Text Key="CA8C630B">Cooking is so efficient thanks to cookie dough prepared in the Stand Mixer. Now to resist stealing a few bites!</Text>
  <Text Key="E4DCF71D">Cooking is so efficient thanks to dough prepared in the Stand Mixer. No kneading necessary!</Text>
  <Text Key="85A80767">Cooking is so efficient thanks to meat prepared in the Stand Mixer!</Text>
  <Text Key="575F458B">Cooking is so efficient thanks to meat substitute prepared in the Stand Mixer!</Text>
  <Text Key="EEFFD839">Cooking is so efficient thanks to seafood prepared in the Stand Mixer!</Text>
  <Text Key="70257FE6">Cooking is so efficient thanks to veggies prepared in the Stand Mixer. No peeling necessary!</Text>
  <Text Key="85488ACB">Who would've thought {0.SimFirstName}'s cuisine could be so disruptive?</Text>
  <Text Key="F5C6674A">Agent of Chaos</Text>
  <Text Key="D365B55F">There's something strange in the neighborhood... no more! {0.SimFirstName}'s culinary skills have brought a ghost back to life.</Text>
  <Text Key="F9F84706">{0.SimFirstName}'s business? Your unfinished business!</Text>
  <Text Key="297F1E20">{0.SimFirstName}'s cool treats are the perfect way to beat the heat!</Text>
  <Text Key="87B9AD6F">Coolest Vendor on the Street</Text>
  <Text Key="BDC231E1">Welcome back to the world of the living! {0.SimFirstName}'s vampire customer will be walking on sunshine soon...</Text>
  <Text Key="6FA69794">Fang Fixer</Text>
  <Text Key="A57209C5">{0.SimFirstName}'s garlic based meal will give vampires more than bad breath...</Text>
  <Text Key="1AA082C0">Bon App the Teeth!</Text>
  <Text Key="207195F3">9/10 vampires would call {0.SimFirstName} plasmalicious!</Text>
  <Text Key="34EAE022">Fang-Tastic Deal!</Text>
  <Text Key="A1DCDE94">Presentation is everything! Junk food has nothing on {0.SimFirstName}'s trashicatessen.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E02DC7B">Live Fast, Eat Trash!</Text>
  <Text Key="75C48094">Full bellies equal full pockets! {0.SimFirstName} had a very profitable Food Sale.</Text>
  <Text Key="9484227B">Kaching!</Text>
  <Text Key="5929AC00">{0.SimFirstName}'s raw meat brings all the wolves to the yard!</Text>
  <Text Key="2474CECF">Meat the Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="4C5C715B">{0.SimFirstName}'s soup is bringing joy to the neighborhood. It's like a hug you can eat!</Text>
  <Text Key="66FBCD3A">More Soup For You!</Text>
  <Text Key="16C89756">Top shelf prices, bottom shelf quality... Oops!</Text>
  <Text Key="4676A009">Sometimes things that are expensive, are worse...</Text>
  <Text Key="4EBE9C43">{0.SimFirstName}'s meals seem to be making everyone's day!</Text>
  <Text Key="A7ED3792">Satisfied Customer</Text>
  <Text Key="BD21B4FB">{0.SimFirstName} has experienced a dough encounter of the third kind! Even aliens come from Sixam to buy {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} delicious pizza.</Text>
  <Text Key="C51C5E5A">The food is out there...</Text>
  <Text Key="6536CBD8">Give peas a chance. {0.SimFirstName}'s spreading veggie love to vegetarian customers!</Text>
  <Text Key="EC933557">Veggie Victory</Text>
  <Text Key="432C8E61">Thanks to {0.SimFirstName}'s Wolf-B-Gone, {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} werewolf customer's howling days are over.</Text>
  <Text Key="23060514">Tamed the Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="6AF2B0F2">Sauté &amp; Style</Text>
  <Text Key="DF6F7FBC">Culinary Charm</Text>
  <Text Key="7F326C04">Liminal Limestone Tile</Text>
  <Text Key="2B950FFD">Hot off the assembly line from everyone's favorite difficult-to-pronounce-furniture sales giant, the SINI seamless cabinets wil make your guests look up and exclaim, "is that built in lighting?!"</Text>
  <Text Key="9CB03368">SINI Seamless Cabinets</Text>
  <Text Key="2A735AC2">Stand strong or pull up a seat to these island counters from everyone's favorite difficult-to-pronounce-furniture sales giant. Who could resist the sleek design and paneling?</Text>
  <Text Key="0DF06ABD">SINI Seamless Island Counters</Text>
  <Text Key="06E15499">Drawers and open space for all your kitchen storage needs, the SINI Seamless Counters will make it so you never forget where you've stashed your cutting board ever again.</Text>
  <Text Key="9F5BEB1C">SINI Seamless Counters</Text>
  <Text Key="CB0C88FF">Dishwashers are amazing to have, but they're also a great waste of storage space in your kitchen. The ChowBella Compact Dishwasher is equipped with powerful jets and high-pressure nozzles to efficiently clean up all the dishes that can fit in it's highly space-optimized tub! The smaller frame makes it possible to still have storage on the side. The best of both worlds!</Text>
  <Text Key="D0E6F426">ChowBella Compact Dishwasher</Text>
  <Text Key="F6BDAF69">Lactose Free Batter</Text>
  <Text Key="75267B05">Prepped Meat Substitute</Text>
  <Text Key="639F658D">Handheld Focaccia</Text>
  <Text Key="FF615957">Batter</Text>
  <Text Key="1B3E8A1C">Cookie Dough</Text>
  <Text Key="CB1F6F9E">Dough</Text>
  <Text Key="BC34D64B">Prepped Seafood</Text>
  <Text Key="855199C0">Prepped Meat</Text>
  <Text Key="24DD24E1">Prepped Veggies</Text>
  <Text Key="974FE460">Pizza Caliente</Text>
  <Text Key="EDE9BCE5">Curious Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="17BD26F4">Artful Focaccia</Text>
  <Text Key="E03ED4B5">Herb Focaccia</Text>
  <Text Key="7C263172">Sfincione</Text>
  <Text Key="AA933D22">Garden Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="06BB3A03">Pizza Margherita</Text>
  <Text Key="1B6DE7AC">Pizza Marinara</Text>
  <Text Key="05148148">Pineapple Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="47DC36EB">Pizza Quattro Stagioni</Text>
  <Text Key="977F91A8">Seafood Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="052DA20B">Apple Bacon Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="934AC21D">Banana Split Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="9AB7DA48">Berry Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="A716BEBF">Cured Fish Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="06FBAB32">Mushroom Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="97109406">Pumpkin Spice Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="8C70D2B9">Saffron Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="CAAC4639">Pleasantly-Unpleasant Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="EE69BAA2">Heart's Desire Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="BC832B8F">Pizza Caliente Slice</Text>
  <Text Key="A64AE8D4">Curious Pizza Slice</Text>
  <Text Key="A76DD0CB">Artful Focaccia</Text>
  <Text Key="9BEEBAE6">Herb Focaccia</Text>
  <Text Key="D9E0447B">Sfincione</Text>
  <Text Key="37FB4FC5">Garden Pizza Slice</Text>
  <Text Key="0C536AF4">Pizza Margherita Slice</Text>
  <Text Key="77D2EE9F">Pizza Marinara Slice</Text>
  <Text Key="736B59A5">Pineapple Pizza Slice</Text>
  <Text Key="CD3D9882">Pizza Quattro Stagioni Slice</Text>
  <Text Key="A1F2A4A9">Seafood Pizza Slice</Text>
  <Text Key="49C5391C">Apple Bacon Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="919B069D">Berry Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="A043B8CC">Chicken &amp; Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="78D2AF9E">Cured Fish Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="CE121C75">Mushroom Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="A018D95D">Plain Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="DBB5CB19">Pumpkin Spice Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="DEA0816C">Saffron Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="25F6E802">Pleasantly-Unpleasant Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="00797D2B">Heart's Desire Waffle</Text>
  <Text Key="8DBB877E">Technology does not stop at your TV or smartphone, kitchen appliances are just as impressive! The ChowBella Sleek Fridge features a wide range of modern day cooling solutions to safely store ingredients that can't wait to be turned into something absolutely delicious! It also looks really good, and that's probably why you bought it isn't it?</Text>
  <Text Key="ECB1C501">ChowBella Sleek Fridge</Text>
  <Text Key="1D50FA17">What if there was a way to optimize a ceiling light? The SINI Hanging Shelf is the answer to that question! With a spacious double-decker shelf featuring a bright LED light, you will have easy access to your most used tools and ingredients in a stylish storage solution.</Text>
  <Text Key="B045B1EE">SINI Hanging Shelf - Short</Text>
  <Text Key="AFA373C2">Wow, those are some high ceilings! The SINI Hanging Shelf offers a modern open shelving and lighting solution for all types of homes. Create a functional space out of unreachable spaces and brighten it up as well! What more could you ask? Decorate your kitchen in style with SINI!</Text>
  <Text Key="EC2365BD">SINI Hanging Shelf - Medium</Text>
  <Text Key="5801668D">Okay, now THOSE are some high ceilings. But don't worry, we've got you covered too! The SINI Hanging Shelf is a stylish storage and lighting solution to a tall walls house's storage problems. Get the most out of your kitchen space and make it bright and cozy while you're at it, with SINI!</Text>
  <Text Key="FD349AD8">SINI Hanging Shelf - Long</Text>
  <Text Key="EA5C9313">These empty plates stand proudly as blank canvases, poised and polished to perfection. Their ceramic catches the light with gusto, flashing wistful glints toward inspired onlookers, practically &lt;i&gt;daring&lt;/i&gt; them to create masterful culinary creations upon their surfaces. And to think, their malleable destinies could be in your hands!</Text>
  <Text Key="11DB6DC2">Plates of Infinite Potential</Text>
  <Text Key="0FD2F835">Toss it around and try not to drop it. This is just some pizza dough.</Text>
  <Text Key="DEC521D0">Pizza Dough</Text>
  <Text Key="56B4A8AE">Is that the aroma of fresh baked pizza cooking on an open flame? The ChowBella Portable Pizza Oven is the perfect addition to your kitchen or outdoor grilling space! Fire it up and treat yourself to a delicious slice or two.</Text>
  <Text Key="DFE27C51">ChowBella Portable Pizza Oven</Text>
  <Text Key="1933DAC1">Nothing says love like a homemade meal, especially if that meal was made by your grandma! In this handy cookbook, Nonna Caterine has captured all of her favorite recipes. With this culinary treasure trove in your kitchen, the answer to the eternal question "What's for dinner?" will always be at your fingertips!</Text>
  <Text Key="8225AEF4">Nonna's Cookbook</Text>
  <Text Key="5DA5A03E">Crafting the perfect pizza is not for the faint of heart, looks are as important as taste! Yes, that also means your preparation station. Immerse yourself in the right vibe with fresh ingredients from Monte Vista and create the perfect disk of doughy deliciousness!</Text>
  <Text Key="CE2A1DC1">Aesthetically Messy Pizza Station</Text>
  <Text Key="FB4B0B16">Make your friends green with envy at this chic knife block. Slash through your ingredients with ease and feel like the King of the kitchen.</Text>
  <Text Key="3FED1FC9">Tom Berry Knife Block</Text>
  <Text Key="D9F87048">Whether you're feeling sporty, scary or posh; this rack suits all tastes. It's what all the best chefs want, what they really, really want.</Text>
  <Text Key="7E7224E7">Spice of Life</Text>
  <Text Key="2A866A2E">Made of the freshest raspberries from the hills of Henford-On-Bagley, this jam and clotted cream combo is a royal winner! These condiments pair perfectly with all your baked goods. Just don't let Agnes catch you spreading the cream on before the jam!</Text>
  <Text Key="48A108D1">Clotted Cream and Jam</Text>
  <Text Key="3936200C">Cooking is a science, and as such it needs precise measurements. The days of eye-balling are finally over, with the ChowBella Food Scale! It includes countless units of measures and the possibility to do unit conversion calculations on the spot! The smart display allows you to record, rename and access an archive of past measurements, jotting down numbers is a thing of the past!</Text>
  <Text Key="0B8607C3">ChowBella Food Scale</Text>
  <Text Key="ACD766D3">Every mother-in-law's kitchen has one, and the time has come for you to have one too. With a recommended placement above your kitchen sink, drying your hand washed dishes has never been easier! Special dish cloths, cutting boards, cheese graters and more all have a home on the SINI Dish Drying Rack.</Text>
  <Text Key="7E427F82">SINI Dish Drying Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="0F1078A9">The SINI Double Shelf is a simple, yet highly functional piece of furniture. The lighting in the back gives your kitchen a modern wash of brightness, while maintaining an inviting and cozy look. Store your most used spices or those everyday kitchen utensils on its spacious shelves, or maybe both!</Text>
  <Text Key="7202DE8C">SINI Double Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="DDACFE98">Washing the dishes has never been easier, with the SINI Chef's Sink! It features a soap pump on the side of its modern, detachable high-pressure spray nozzle tap. The drying rack on the side makes it possible to complete your washing up in one single spot, no more water drips all over the kitchen!</Text>
  <Text Key="B1F7A717">SINI Chef's Sink</Text>
  <Text Key="8193F1A1">Goodbye elbow grease and mixing spoons, hello automatic cooking bliss! Prep for success and make cooking more efficient with this set it and forget it Stand Mixer.\n\nMake Prepped Ingredients such as batter and cookie dough, which can be used to cook other recipes faster than normal. Prepped Ingredients also reduce cooking cost and help increase food quality.</Text>
  <Text Key="408C1854">ChowBella Stand Mixer</Text>
  <Text Key="C3CB9639">The inviting smell of a freshly cooked dinner can make or break the mood! Get rid of those invasive odors with the ChowBella Stove Hood. With advanced filters technology, it will eliminate even aftermath of baking an Pleasantly-Unpleasant Waffle... why do people eat those anyway?!</Text>
  <Text Key="37368C3C">ChowBella Stove Hood</Text>
  <Text Key="A8079D2B">The ChowBella Sleek Stove features a modern induction hob and a high-speed heating oven that doesn't compromise on design. The induction technology makes it possible to cook without dispersing heat in the room and, in combination with the ChowBella patented oven seal, the Sleek Stove will not affect the temperature of your kitchen! Make sure to try asking its voice assistant software to set a timer for you! There's no need to yell at it, that will hurt its feelings.</Text>
  <Text Key="476CC72A">ChowBella Sleek Stove</Text>
  <Text Key="4207DD5B">The people are hungry... and with your very own food stand, YOU can feed them. Stock it, Mark Up your prices, and sell any meal your heart desires to the people on the streets or from the comfort of your home. Take it with you when you travel and feed the world!</Text>
  <Text Key="3B0A513A">Anywhere Any Fare Food Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="5DB23DDF">Sweet or savory, enjoy your waffles for breakfast, lunch, or dinner. Eat your heart out!</Text>
  <Text Key="B7CE7886">ChowBella Heart Waffle Maker</Text>
  <Text Key="509D5946">Food Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="CF494344">View Lesson</Text>
  <Text Key="E24AC7DA">Wow, is that a &lt;b&gt;ChowBella Stand Mixer&lt;/b&gt;? You’ll be whipping up tasty treats in no time with that impressive piece of culinary machinery!\n\nDo you want to learn more about cooking with the &lt;b&gt;Stand Mixer&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Prepped Ingredients&lt;/b&gt;?</Text>
  <Text Key="3F616BCC">Congrats on buying the &lt;b&gt;Anywhere Any Fare Food Stand&lt;/b&gt;! You can now start your entrepreneurship journey and sell food and other goods around the world.\n\nDo you want to learn more about selling items with the &lt;b&gt;Food Stand&lt;/b&gt;?</Text>
  <Text Key="D0F89723">Prepped Ingredient</Text>
  <Text Key="B0C318EC">There are no available slots on the counters.</Text>
  <Text Key="A729B2C6">There are no small appliances in {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="1E400849">Place Appliance</Text>
  <Text Key="3770BD2A">Nothing is stocked on the table.</Text>
  <Text Key="6BCF4C19">{1.SimFirstName} just used Convince to Buy! {1.SimPronounSubjective} must wait to try again.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0B19F59">Convince to Buy</Text>
  <Text Key="8467BCFA">Serve Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="53F7E0F2">Collect Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="28BBDB3E">Cook</Text>
  <Text Key="4387ADDD">Speedy Bake</Text>
  <Text Key="378AAC0B">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished installing the Pizza Oven upgrade.</Text>
  <Text Key="FEC57E60">You will never need to scrape burnt cheese from this Pizza Oven again!</Text>
  <Text Key="EDF697AA">Add Unbreakable</Text>
  <Text Key="70C68541">The Pizza Oven will become unbreakable.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF5C22F6">Continue Upgrading Speedy Bake</Text>
  <Text Key="DCD1F6D9">Continue Upgrading Unbreakable</Text>
  <Text Key="C5D15AC4">Turn up the heat to bake your pizza and focaccia faster.</Text>
  <Text Key="C2C1D618">Speedy Bake</Text>
  <Text Key="7989C7F3">Unbreakable</Text>
  <Text Key="44859815">Brand your Food Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="79725CFD">Business Details</Text>
  <Text Key="06B5DF7E">Change Business Details...</Text>
  <Text Key="D2EE3404">Disable AutoStock</Text>
  <Text Key="1D5C8F62">Enable AutoStock</Text>
  <Text Key="2308F751">Start Food Sale</Text>
  <Text Key="CBA327B3">Select Small Appliance From {0.SimFirstName}'s Inventory</Text>
  <Text Key="8A9B4530">Convince To Buy</Text>
  <Text Key="5DEF935C">Collect Prepped Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="6E330C6F">Prep Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="090C7E19">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished installing the Stand Mixer upgrade.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE3D3748">Speedy Mix</Text>
  <Text Key="990AA6EB">Full speed ahead, mix your Prepped Ingredients faster.</Text>
  <Text Key="7C32FD0D">Squeaky sparkling clean, the Stand Mixer will clean itself.</Text>
  <Text Key="32DBC22E">The Stand Mixer will become unbreakable.</Text>
  <Text Key="30FBC357">Continue Upgrading Speedy Mix</Text>
  <Text Key="5BB89C19">Full speed ahead, mix your Prepped Ingredients faster.</Text>
  <Text Key="3B8340E1">Speedy Mix</Text>
  <Text Key="125141B5">Squeaky sparkling clean, the Stand Mixer will clean itself.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF213A0E">This Stand Mixer is super durable and can process the toughest of ingredients without breaking.</Text>
  <Text Key="35F014C2">Serve Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="918CFFC6">Collect Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="E71794C1">Cook</Text>
  <Text Key="99BF324E">Speedy Bake</Text>
  <Text Key="A364D8F8">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished installing the Waffle Maker upgrade.</Text>
  <Text Key="A51368D5">Continue Upgrading Speedy Bake</Text>
  <Text Key="20098A3F">Extra hot maker, extra fast waffles.</Text>
  <Text Key="828AADCB">Speedy Bake</Text>
  <Text Key="849800E3">You will never need to scrub burnt batter from this Waffle Maker again!</Text>
  <Text Key="11E89A74">The Waffle Maker will become unbreakable.</Text>
  <Text Key="A3F6316D">Danish Coffee Kitchen</Text>
  <Text Key="445EDBBA">EuroFusion Food Experience</Text>
  <Text Key="5131B00B">Collect Prepped Ingredients {1.Number} times while Inspired</Text>
  <Text Key="B3D1A12C">Click on the Stand Mixer and select Prep Ingredients. Then click on the Stand Mixer and select Collect Prepped Ingredients while Inspired.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2AEF6F4">Collect {1.Number} Prepped Ingredients that were made using Fresh Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="398F74F1">Click on a Stand Mixer and select Prep Ingredients while the Use Fresh Ingredients checkbox is ticked in the recipe menu. Then click on the Stand Mixer and select Collect Prepped Ingredients.</Text>
  <Text Key="BE4A7650">Own {1.Number} small kitchen {S1.appliance}{P1.appliances}</Text>
  <Text Key="FE6881CD">Small appliances can be found on the Kitchen category in Buy Mode.</Text>
  <Text Key="166BDD77">Experience Sped Up Cooking {1.Number} times</Text>
  <Text Key="AA0632F8">Click on the Fridge or the Oven and select any recipe while the Use Prepped Ingredients box is checked.</Text>
  <Text Key="9D138F81">Collect {1.Number} excellent quality Prepped Ingredient</Text>
  <Text Key="3BDA1E06">Click on the Stand Mixer, select Prep Ingredients, and select a recipe from the list. Hover the cursor over the food to check its quality! Sims with high Skill are more likely to create higher quality items.</Text>
  <Text Key="33B1F34E">Cook {1.Number} times while listening to music</Text>
  <Text Key="A3D7DCA7">Click on a Stereo and select Listen to Music. Then, click on any appliance and select Cook.</Text>
  <Text Key="5E35F20F">Cook {1.Number} Pizzas or Waffles at a single Goaled Social Event after reaching Silver</Text>
  <Text Key="0B049450">Click on the phone and select Plan Event under the Social category. While at the event, once Silver has been achieved, Cook Pizza or Waffles at the event.</Text>
  <Text Key="CEACF03E">Make Pleasantly-Unpleasant Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="8E6E6137">Grow a Trash Fruit and use it as an ingredient when making Pleasantly-Unpleasant Waffles.</Text>
  <Text Key="88FE2831">Cook meals using 6 unique Prepped Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="4C822016">Use 6 different types of Prepped Ingredients when cooking food.</Text>
  <Text Key="2CEAB378">Make a Prepped Ingredient using a Stand Mixer with at least one Upgrade</Text>
  <Text Key="B181BCD5">Click on the Stand Mixer and select Upgrade. Apply Upgrades to the appliance by increasing the Handiness skill. Then make Prepped Ingredients.</Text>
  <Text Key="C17994CC">Run a Food Sale from a residential lot</Text>
  <Text Key="B9242C29">Click on a Food Stand once it is stocked with food and select Start Food Sale.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D39B863">Sell {1.Number} excellent Pizzas or Waffles during a Food Sale</Text>
  <Text Key="675C6044">Stock a Food Stand with Pizzas or Waffles, then select Start Food Sale and successfully make {1.Number} sales.</Text>
  <Text Key="42E71857">Run Food Sales from {1.Number} different lots</Text>
  <Text Key="934C7E98">Travel to a different lot, place the Food Stand, and start a Food Sale. Do this {1.Number} times.</Text>
  <Text Key="752BBE30">Convince customers to buy something {1.Number} times during a Food Sale</Text>
  <Text Key="5CB5E86D">During a Food Sale, click on any customer and select the Convince to Buy social interaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="877B9E3E">Earn {1.Money} during a single Food Sale</Text>
  <Text Key="85681B37">Run a Food Sale and focus on selling high value meals, until reaching {1.Money}.</Text>
  <Text Key="41CCD631">Tend a Food Stand for more than {1.Number} hours</Text>
  <Text Key="437BDA16">Click on a Food Stand while a Food Sale is active and select Tend.</Text>
  <Text Key="E5B96178">Sell one meal for §300</Text>
  <Text Key="A87B76D5">During a Food Sale, sell a meal worth §300 or more.</Text>
  <Text Key="55E23D81">Sell a poor quality item for §100</Text>
  <Text Key="32D3D806">Craft any item with a low-skilled or uncomfortable Sim to obtain a low quality item. Stock it at any Food Stand and sell it for a high price, selecting any of the markup interactions available.</Text>
  <Text Key="EC80A14E">Resurrect a Ghost by selling Ambrosia</Text>
  <Text Key="9AD196A7">Reach level 10 in Gourmet Cooking and Homestyle Cooking and gather the ingredients required to cook Ambrosia: Death Flower, Angelfish and Potion of Youth. Click on any fridge or stove and select Cook. Then choose Ambrosia from the recipe list.</Text>
  <Text Key="1704A00F">Earn {1.Money} by completing Food Sales</Text>
  <Text Key="01FE4E50">Run Food Sales until {0.SimFirstName} has earned {1.Money} in sales.</Text>
  <Text Key="0861A27D">Artful Focaccia</Text>
  <Text Key="7CBF97CE">Make Artful Focaccia</Text>
  <Text Key="6BEAD511">The Sims who say “don’t play with your food” obviously never made focaccia art! This culinary masterpiece is sure to inspire anyone who eats it.\n\nVegetarian-Safe, Lactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="793CBC10">Herb Focaccia</Text>
  <Text Key="BF1AC9BB">Make Herb Focaccia</Text>
  <Text Key="212128A0">Focaccia is a flat leavened bread from Italy, often made with olive oil and topped with herbs such as rosemary. It’s eaten as a side dish, sandwich bread, or as a pizza base.\n\nThe word focaccia dates back to the 14th century. It is derived from the Latin &lt;i&gt;panis focacius&lt;/i&gt;, meaning “hearth bread”, but the bread itself may originate from the Etruscans, thus predating the Roman Empire.\n\nVegetarian-Safe, Lactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="88C679E1">Sfincione</Text>
  <Text Key="51AB004A">Make Sfincione</Text>
  <Text Key="B1C8BCBD">&lt;i&gt;Sfincione&lt;/i&gt; is a Sicilian pizza with a thick crust, usually topped with herbs, onions, tomato sauce, strong cheese, and anchovies (but this recipe is 100% vegetarian!), although the traditional ingredients vary from region to region.\n\nThis scrumptious dish was brought to the United States by the first Sicilian immigrants. The American version, simply known as Sicilian Pizza, is usually squared and has a thicker crust. The famous Detroit-Style pizza was also developed from a Sicilian recipe.\n\nVegetarian-Safe</Text>
  <Text Key="89777433">The &lt;i&gt;Pizza Diavola&lt;/i&gt; (“deviled pizza” in Italian) is topped with chili peppers and slices of spicy sausage. No wonder this hot treat is more commonly known as Pizza Caliente among the inhabitants of the Sims universe!</Text>
  <Text Key="4E9462A9">Make Canadian Bacon Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="84B13F5E">Make Cheese Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="1C1BF4D8">Curious Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="86DCF043">Make Curious Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="533399A8">Ever since Lazlo Curious had the ingenious idea to put extraterrestrial fruit on a pizza, this unique dish has become a Strangetown delicacy.\n\nA single slice will focus your brainwaves, and has been known to attract &lt;i&gt;unexpected&lt;/i&gt; visitors…\n\nVegetarian-Safe, Lactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="BD444869">Garden Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="37051652">Make Garden Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="3575E7C5">Pretty much every vegetable tastes better on a pizza! Prepare this dish with whatever is in season from your garden—although we wholeheartedly recommend roasted slices of aubergine, inspired by &lt;i&gt;Pizza Alle Melanzane&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Pizza Alla Parmigiana&lt;/i&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0FF9759">Kebab Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="CEC09122">Make Kebab Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="2F78FA56">Pizza Margherita</Text>
  <Text Key="EDF0D449">Make Pizza Margherita</Text>
  <Text Key="1EEFC19A">The &lt;i&gt;Pizza Margherita&lt;/i&gt; was invented in 1889 by Raffaele Esposito (known as the father of modern pizza), in honor of Queen Margherita of Savoia. The basil, mozzarella, and tomato reminded her of the Italian flag, and the dish became her personal favorite. \n\nThanks to this royal seal of approval, pizza soon went from “poor people’s food” to a delicacy enjoyed by all!\n\nVegetarian-Safe</Text>
  <Text Key="1EE5F1DB">Pizza Marinara</Text>
  <Text Key="94EB3054">Make Pizza Marinara</Text>
  <Text Key="1A4F3343">It is said the &lt;i&gt;Pizza Marinara&lt;/i&gt; was introduced in 1735 by Neapolitan sailors, making it the first tomato-based pizza. It is made with ingredients that preserve well during long journeys at sea; olive oil, tomatoes, basil, oregano, and garlic.\n\nThe ingredients may seem simple, but the delicious combination of earthy and pungent flavors is sure to leave a lasting impression!\n\nVegetarian-Safe, Lactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="3060893D">Make Pepperoni Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="0FDB32B8">Pineapple Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="F4DEDE23">Make Pineapple Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="7A2B3456">Pizza Quattro Stagioni</Text>
  <Text Key="D2B51E49">Make Pizza Quattro Stagioni</Text>
  <Text Key="E9A36B9A">&lt;i&gt;Pizza Quattro Stagioni&lt;/i&gt; (“four seasons pizza” in Italian) is prepared with four sections of different toppings, each representing a season of the year.\n\nTraditionally, it is made with artichokes (spring), tomatoes and basil (summer), mushrooms (autumn), and prosciutto or olives (winter).</Text>
  <Text Key="4987F5DF">The inspiration for this dish is &lt;i&gt;Pizza Tonno e Cipolle&lt;/i&gt;, an Italian pizza topped with tomato, mozzarella, tuna, red onion, and olive oil.\n\nYou can make this recipe with any kind of fish you have available, but if you’ve caught yourself a nice tuna, we suggest you give it a try!</Text>
  <Text Key="AE1DE944">Sweet Corn Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="0B608C97">Make Sweet Corn Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="71AB884E">Seafood Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="9B018721">Make Seafood Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="C4CBA13B">Pizza Caliente</Text>
  <Text Key="444EB5B4">Make Pizza Caliente</Text>
  <Text Key="A9EA1789">Tikka Masala Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="581937F2">Make Tikka Masala Pizza</Text>
  <Text Key="664421F1">{0.TimespanShort} until ready!</Text>
  <Text Key="28A47830">Pleasantly-Unpleasant Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="862CECDB">Make Pleasantly-Unpleasant Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="3F7E1380">Strawberry sweetness and trash fruit pungency is the most delicious combination known to Sim kind! It’s also the most disgusting thing you’ve ever tasted. Curiously, the experience changes from bite to bite. Will it fill you with pure bliss or burning rage? There’s only one way to find out!\n\nVegetarian-Safe</Text>
  <Text Key="6C96B69B">Apple Bacon Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="490DA514">Make Apple Bacon Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="1BB194F2">Banana Split Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="237BB9FD">Make Banana Split Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="E4A1F5BB">Berry Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="40F77E34">Make Berry Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="65015C63">Berry jam and whipped cream is the most common waffle topping in the Nordics. Raspberry, strawberry, and European blueberry (also known as bilberry) are popular jam choices.\n\nThe heart shaped waffle originates from the 19th century, when circular waffle irons became popular to fit the holes of the new cast iron stoves.\n\nVegetarian-Safe</Text>
  <Text Key="E9794596">Chicken and Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="F7635189">Make Chicken and Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="E60C47DA">Crispy fried chicken and golden waffles, a match made in heaven! This soul food version of an old Pennsylvania Dutch recipe, especially popular in the Southern United States, is best enjoyed with some butter and a generous dollop of syrup.</Text>
  <Text Key="14F1D850">Cured Fish Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="07C7A1FB">Make Cured Fish Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="C87C61E0">Cured fish is a delicacy in many Nordic countries. Originally, fish was cured with salt or sugar to make it last longer. These days, the method is mainly used to produce the traditional flavors. Salmon, flounder, cod, and herring are popular choices, often flavored with dill.\n\nWhile cured fish is usually eaten with boiled potatoes for Easter, Midsummer, and Christmas, why not try something new and put it on your waffles?</Text>
  <Text Key="3FF9B56B">Mushroom Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="F18FD744">Make Mushroom Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="AB085C33">The Nordic countries have an old tradition of foraging for berries and mushrooms in the wilds, in many places protected by laws known as &lt;i&gt;Allemansrätten&lt;/i&gt;.\n\nThe chanterelle mushroom, also known as “the gold of the forest”, is a beloved delicacy, and the lingonberry is a common side dish to venison and meatballs. In this recipe, we combine the two for the perfect umami and tart fusion!\n\nVegetarian-Safe</Text>
  <Text Key="B0E589AB">Plain Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="3DBE7384">Make Plain Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="57534A97">Pumpkin Spice Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="F9A4C0B8">Make Pumpkin Spice Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="AA3848AE">Saffron Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="09229181">Make Saffron Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="A8639D32">In Swedish cuisine, saffron is traditionally used in desserts, such as &lt;i&gt;lussekatt&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;saffranspannkaka&lt;/i&gt;. Putting saffron in your waffle batter is a modern way to enjoy this yellow delicacy!\n\nIn this recipe, it’s served with a healthy dollop of cloudberry jam from the Nordic wetlands.\n\nVegetarian-Safe</Text>
  <Text Key="9859F9E1">Heart's Desire Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="DF0A804A">Make Heart's Desire Waffles</Text>
  <Text Key="E0303CBD">Who can resist a perfect slice of Heart's Desire Waffles? And who can resist the waffle eater? This delectable dish is sure to put anyone in a flirty mood!\n\nVegetarian-Safe</Text>
  <Text Key="1E5C047F">Lactose Free Batter</Text>
  <Text Key="18AA05D9">Prepped Meat Substitute</Text>
  <Text Key="8ACA83A2">Make Prepped Meat Substitute</Text>
  <Text Key="82627FFE">Batter</Text>
  <Text Key="18E839B1">Make Batter</Text>
  <Text Key="C2CF7414">Make Lactose Free Batter</Text>
  <Text Key="E5312F7B">Cookie Dough</Text>
  <Text Key="56743FF4">Make Cookie Dough</Text>
  <Text Key="BB1313F9">Dough</Text>
  <Text Key="BE779FC2">Make Dough</Text>
  <Text Key="B23B1F9D">Prepped Meat</Text>
  <Text Key="53D251EE">Make Prepped Meat</Text>
  <Text Key="FB38A8FD">Prepped Seafood</Text>
  <Text Key="35C9E24E">Make Prepped Seafood</Text>
  <Text Key="C4D65B88">Prepped Veggies</Text>
  <Text Key="2D029C13">Make Prepped Veggies</Text>
  <Text Key="1BD5B456">Speeds up cake recipes. Can also be used when making waffles!\n\nVegetarian-Safe</Text>
  <Text Key="00CD7277">Speeds up the cooking of lactose free cake recipes.\n\nVegetarian-Safe, Lactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="97EBD28F">Speeds up the cooking of cookie recipes.\n\nVegetarian-Safe, Lactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="813DFCE9">Speeds up the cooking of dough based recipes. Can also be used when making pizza and focaccia!\n\nVegetarian-Safe, Lactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="72677965">Speeds up the cooking of meat based recipes.\n\nLactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="CE59EC81">Speeds up the cooking of meat substitute based recipes.\n\nVegetarian-Safe, Lactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="D6107C1D">Speeds up the cooking of seafood based recipes.\n\nLactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="2AF3918C">Speeds up the cooking of veggie based recipes.\n\nVegetarian-Safe, Lactose Free</Text>
  <Text Key="219E33B6">Sims with this trait get duplicates of any recipe they cook with Prepped Ingredients.</Text>
  <Text Key="C03F8201">Batch Cook</Text>
  <Text Key="88D3B692">Sims with this trait can set higher markup prices and are more successful at Convincing Customers to Buy while using Food Stands and Sales Tables.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE103C04">Food Sale Complete</Text>
  <Text Key="890D0C89">{0.String} made {1.Money}\n</Text>
  <Text Key="02B5050B">Food sales {0.Money}\n</Text>
  <Text Key="FFD50620">{0.Number} x {1.String} - {2.Money}</Text>
  <Text Key="036511CA">Food Sale</Text>
  <Text Key="B70C8EA1">Batch Cook</Text>
  <Text Key="0D7CA23F">Batch Cook</Text>
  <Text Key="AD44B07B">(From Completing the Appliance Wiz Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="9D87D0E6">Booth Boss</Text>
  <Text Key="F7E5836E">Booth Boss</Text>
  <Text Key="404B1219">Booth Bosses can set set higher markups and are more successful at Convincing Customers to Buy while using Food Stands and Sales Tables.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA04861C">(From Completing the Market Magnate Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="16D6481C">Home Chef Hustle</Text>
  <Text Key="4FDD5072">Stand Mixer &amp; Prepped Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="40DC430A">Some recipes that use a Prepped Ingredient will &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;take less time&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; if that ingredient is used. For example, if your Sim makes a cake with premade Batter, they can skip the entire batter mixing step and simply pour the premade batter into a baking pan directly!\n\nYou can identify these recipes by their &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;background&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;tooltip&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. If the Prepped Ingredient is available, the background will be blue. If it’s unavailable, the background and tooltip will be grayed out and the normal recipe will be used.</Text>
  <Text Key="1C625541">You might notice that Prepped Ingredients will &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;replace&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; some or all Fresh Ingredients in certain recipes when the setting is activated. As Prepped Ingredients are cheap to make, and have a chance of being even higher quality than any Fresh Ingredients used to make it, this version of the recipe is better in terms of cost and dish Quality.\n\nYou can uncheck the Prepped Ingredients checkbox if you’d prefer to cook a recipe with Fresh Ingredients instead.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC7C8B7F">It’s time to cook with Prepped Ingredients! You can find recipes that use Prepped Ingredients from your &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;fridge&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;stove&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, as well as some other appliances such as the &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Pizza Oven&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Waffle Maker&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.\n\nRun a cooking interaction that opens the &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;recipe menu&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, such as Cook on the fridge, and make sure the &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Prepped Ingredients&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; checkbox is enabled. Optional Prepped Ingredients will then appear in the ingredients list.\n\nYour Sim must have that Prepped Ingredient in the fridge or their Inventory to use it in the recipe.</Text>
  <Text Key="72D7A9F6">The &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Stand Mixer&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; is the crown jewel of any chef’s kitchen, be they hobbyist or professional!\n\nSims can use it to make &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Prepped Ingredients&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, a new type of ingredient that makes cooking faster and cheaper. It also helps to improve the Quality of a dish.\n\nYou can find the Stand Mixer in the &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Kitchen Appliances&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; category in Build Mode.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="F35C6E03">To make Prepped Ingredients, use the &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Prep Ingredients&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; interaction on the Stand Mixer.\n\nYou can choose to use &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Fresh Ingredients&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; in the Stand Mixer to reduce the cost and possibly increase the Quality of the Prepped Ingredients that are created, which may then further boost the quality of any recipes prepared using those Prepped Ingredients.\n\nWhile the Stand Mixer is processing, your Sim is free to do other things. Let it work its magic and simply &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Collect Prepped Ingredients&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; once it’s done. Five Prepped Ingredients are produced each time.</Text>
  <Text Key="A88FEADE">Take your business on the road by bringing the Food Stand, appliances, and wares in your Sim’s &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;inventory&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; when they travel.\n\nPick up the Food Stand by selecting &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Put in Inventory&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, find your new location, and select &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Place In World&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; on the table in the inventory. You can also &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;drag&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; the table in and out of your Sim’s inventory while it’s on a lot.\n\nIf the Food Stand has wares or appliances on it, your Sim needs to &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Clear Table&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; before they can pick it up.</Text>
  <Text Key="477C64AA">To prepare a sale, &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;drag&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; food or other items to the Food Stand or its inventory. When you’re ready, choose &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Start Food Sale&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, and customers will flock to your table!\n\nYour Sim will automatically &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;stock&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; the table when the sale starts, and keep restocking it over time as things get sold. You can select Disable AutoStock to stock manually instead.\n\nIf your Sim has to take a break, they can continue selling by selecting &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Tend Table&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.\n\nThe Street Food Sale will end when the timer runs out.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="8E2F7117">To place a &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;small appliance&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; on the Food Stand, you can either purchase or move it in Build Mode, drag it onto the table in Live Mode, or select &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Place Appliance&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to place it from your Sim’s Inventory.\n\nMost small appliances allow your Sim to cook while they’re still tending the table. How efficient!</Text>
  <Text Key="62C454B9">Bring your home chef hustle dreams to life with the &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Food Stand&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;!\n\nUse it to &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;sell&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; food and other items from the comfort of your Sim's home, or put it in your &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;inventory&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; and bring their booming business around the world.\n\nThe handy dandy side tables allow you to cook with &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;small appliances&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; on the go!\n</Text>
  <Text Key="A7CAF3F8">Increasing the &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Mark Up&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; will earn you more Simoleons per sale, but it will also make customers less likely to buy something.\n\nYour Sim can attempt to &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Give Sales Pitch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to make a customer more interested in your wares.\n\nSelect &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Convince to Buy&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to try and sell a specific item to a customer! Convince them to buy your most expensive dish, or something... &lt;i&gt;special&lt;/i&gt; if your Sim is feeling mischievous.\n\nImproving your Sim’s &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Charisma&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; skill and completing the &lt;b&gt;&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;Market Magnate&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; aspiration will make them better at selling items, Give Sales Pitch, and Convince To Buy.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E29EE31">Food Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="AA029036">Hydraulic Harmony Mosaic</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>