<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="FA5AA8D8">This multipurpose mirror mixes the three things you need most in the morning: light to look good, a mirror to help you do it, and a tray for your makeup.</Text>
  <Text Key="360E3C57">Shine On Shine Off</Text>
  <Text Key="24AA2DB0">This handy dandy memo pad will keep your thoughts and ideas organized. Now you just have to remember to write things down.</Text>
  <Text Key="B4065C5F">Write It Down Memo Pad</Text>
  <Text Key="C0881E0E">The Pro-Tector is the ultimate in professional grade storage bins. Its sturdy design and special locking mechanism protect your precious memories from anything that will try to harm them...</Text>
  <Text Key="65CDC331">The Pro-Tector</Text>
  <Text Key="E0CBB253">The perfect kit for you and your chess mate... check mate!</Text>
  <Text Key="3FEE8A02">Once a Pawn a Time Chess Kit</Text>
  <Text Key="260C5F9D">Gym in a Box is the all in one gym solution that'll help you rebound from your last relationship. So lawyer up, hit the Gym in a Box, and delete Social Bunny. Welcome to step #2 of the rest of your life.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF3F5988">Gym in a Box</Text>
  <Text Key="EE8AC80F">Behold! Your very own box of boxes, letters, and random items. Maybe you'll organize these one day, but that's a problem for the future.</Text>
  <Text Key="877FE9D6">Procrastinator's Box of Stuff</Text>
  <Text Key="89FDE4AD">These kicks are guaranteed to be fresh, or your money back.</Text>
  <Text Key="1784B978">Kicks Are For Kids</Text>
  <Text Key="E487B93A">A wireless drawing tablet and mug, accompanied by a pair of art books and pens. With this assortment of objects you can finally begin your lifelong dream of filling the internet with increasingly cute cat drawings. After doing so you might ask yourself, "But was there more to life?". You'll find the answer is "no". You've reached the apex, well done. </Text>
  <Text Key="C168F7E5">A Slightly Creative Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="EC95972C">The yoga mat only comes out for show binging stretch sessions. Sometimes the kettlebell makes it to your desk for breaks between the meetings. Either way, it's the smallest intentions that make the most impact, and this aestheticly active pair reminds you of that daily.</Text>
  <Text Key="1DC74663">Beacon of Intention Active Set</Text>
  <Text Key="0711F86D">Your Simoleons are waiting in the eight sided arena. Bankruptcy will tap out while you watch your savings grow. Are you ready to get EXTREME?</Text>
  <Text Key="071E6938">Coinoctagon</Text>
  <Text Key="3920E8DC">In an effort to raise awareness about the issue of plastic pollution in the oceans, we bring you The Thirsty Thermos. It was made from plastic salvaged from an ocean garbage patch and now serves as a reminder of this absurd tragedy. It has found a second purpose in life, and now adeptly contains the very water which it once floated in.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6E496B3">The Thirsty Thermos</Text>
  <Text Key="241F9F5A">This cap was worn by doctors, astronauts, celebrities, and more. It's guaranteed to bring fame and fortune to all that wear it! Don't believe it? Well, suit yourself!</Text>
  <Text Key="FC2B0585">Cap of Lucky Ambition</Text>
  <Text Key="943CB61E">An extra pair for when you lose track of the ones already on your face. Now, where did I put those? I could have sworn they were right there a moment ago...</Text>
  <Text Key="E6785121">Spare Specs</Text>
  <Text Key="83BC24D8">Leave your enemies in the dark with the headset that illuminates your intention to win.</Text>
  <Text Key="D041F057">Aural Ambrosia Headset</Text>
  <Text Key="4E58F6A4">Whoever said "You can't buy happiness" doesn't know about this amazing jewelry stand. It's just what you've always desired - a beautiful stand with enough space to display your jewelry collection and make your friends jealous.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D3E05EB">The Adoringly Adorned Jewelry Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="EC60D944">Whether you've actually read these issues or not, magazines are always a great way to fill up your space.</Text>
  <Text Key="748D230B">Mega Magazine Stack</Text>
  <Text Key="659344FF">Get the look of your dreams! Keep all your makeup in one place with this beautiful organizer. You'll never have to worry about losing your favorite blush again.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF066826">Subtle Serve Makeup Kit</Text>
  <Text Key="F1D13D8D">A single mug that says you are so rich and privileged you don't need to buy mugs in bulk.</Text>
  <Text Key="671E6FD8">Mug Solo</Text>
  <Text Key="BD36AEE5">They're not your average mugs: they're better. Or at least one is, and the other two are also good. Limit 1 per customer.</Text>
  <Text Key="70DB2460">Mug Trio</Text>
  <Text Key="516FA1AD">This all-in-one notebook is your perfect desk companion for all your thoughts, ideas, and to-dos. </Text>
  <Text Key="60C36078">Write It Down Notebook</Text>
  <Text Key="AF9EF062">Your phone &amp; keys are the bare necessities of modern survival. Just don't forget where you placed them! Now, where did I put my keys?</Text>
  <Text Key="71DC0ADD">Phone &amp; Keys</Text>
  <Text Key="3B08A1A7">A Snack Pack 2 Go is filled to the brim with gourmet, sweet and savory snacks that would appeal to an adult on the go. These small bites are perfect for date nights and long flights (but not necessarily together).</Text>
  <Text Key="80204EDE">Snack Pack 2 Go</Text>
  <Text Key="BBFD409C">Don't you hate getting dressed when you can't find your glasses or watch? That's why we have a spot for both and room to store them. Owning the Invincible Frame Tray is like having an eye doctor and watchmaker on call.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA405573">Invincible Frame Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="D25D8469">A special watch to spare the time.</Text>
  <Text Key="6017AB4C">Antique Spare Watch</Text>
  <Text Key="2C14022C">A very nice box. A box for my trinkets! What's going on? It's Trinketville!</Text>
  <Text Key="12909763">Trinketville</Text>
  <Text Key="E2CB4D80">We think you should be able to carry more than one thing at a time, so we've created the Lug Trio. One canvas, one leather, and one nylon bag are perfect for all occasions and places. No matter what you're carrying, they won't weigh you down!</Text>
  <Text Key="5BDCFB4F">Lug Trio</Text>
  <Text Key="17B15BA8">Gone fishing? This wall art is a sure catch and makes a perfect addition to your home. Decorate your walls with a beautiful fish carving and framed photos of your best catches. A perfect gift for anyone who likes to spend their weekends on the water.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA7138C7">Sealine Memories</Text>
  <Text Key="1935AAFE">Tired of having your flat brimmed hats and basketballs laying around? The Ball 'N Cap is a wall-mounted display built to hold your favorite ball and hat! It's perfect for a sports room, man cave, or just for the avid athletic enthusiast.</Text>
  <Text Key="35D7D781">Ball 'N Cap Display</Text>
  <Text Key="E1800F5E">Sturdy and functional, the Hooked on Storage wall organizer works for you! The built-in hooks make finding what you’re looking for a breeze.</Text>
  <Text Key="98633861">Hooked on Storage</Text>
  <Text Key="ADC42ACC">A great gift for any audiophile, Boom Blocks transforms your workspace into a mini concert hall. Designers have thought of everything; there's space for your books, your pens, and--most importantly--two miniature speakers that make listening to music fun again!</Text>
  <Text Key="269EAB83">Boom Blocks</Text>
  <Text Key="38F9E96E">Kinda Unkept Study</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>