<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="C97ACDE6">In a world where imagination can take you anywhere, the possibilities are endless. This wall decal is here to help make bath and potty time fun and imaginative.</Text>
  <Text Key="80F78BF9">BeanStalk Bathroom Decals</Text>
  <Text Key="B0C4765C">What is better than a small flame, creating a relaxing and warm atmosphere? This candle has a clean, modern look to it, perfect for any home. Light up and relax with the gentle fragrance of essential oils, made from naturally derived materials. It's like going to a spa with no appointments!</Text>
  <Text Key="9696C733">ScentsibleSim Scented Candle</Text>
  <Text Key="36DE2F0F">Nobody likes feeling afraid of the dark. That's why the Blissful NiteLight is a must-have for kids and adults alike. This plug in provides a soft glow that keeps you safe, reduces your energy costs, and makes it easy to see. No more stumbling in the dark in the middle of the night!</Text>
  <Text Key="AB7F6ED6">Blissful NiteLight</Text>
  <Text Key="B3B16D6D">Would you like to enjoy the moment when taking a break in your bathroom? Do you have cold feet? Not with this mat! Made of soft cotton, this mat has a plush, warm and comfortable design to keep you comfortable while on the toilet.</Text>
  <Text Key="7688B838">Toilet Mat by FootCushion</Text>
  <Text Key="4B73F593">Dry off your feet after a relaxing shower or bath with this home essential. This mat keeps you safe in the bathroom and it's made of highly absorbent materials that dries quickly to prevent slips and falls.</Text>
  <Text Key="74870D42">Bath Mat by FootCushion</Text>
  <Text Key="D2771606">The Privy Plunger is a monument to all the people who prefer a proper plunging for their plugged privy, over the flow of an over-flowing flowing over-filled bowl.</Text>
  <Text Key="3ABB3399">Privy Plunger</Text>
  <Text Key="E4C15D39">This bath tray makes it easy to have all your daily bathroom essentials in one place. Make lotions, soap, and other items easier to grab in the morning by displaying them on this elegant and decorative bath tray.</Text>
  <Text Key="3CCF313C">Set-It and Forget-It Bathroom Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="26BAE007">Now this is what we call sleek style! This three drawer organizer makes it easy to organize your bathroom counter with and keep everything within arm's reach. The three deep drawers separate toiletries, cleaning supplies, medicines and cosmetics into neat compartments for easy access.</Text>
  <Text Key="76AD0BBE">PLASTIK Three-Drawer Organizer</Text>
  <Text Key="593A29A9">This box may be a hot mess, but it's a teen’s go-to for all their accessories. It’s got all the right compartments for jewelry, bracelets, and even has room at the bottom for hair ties and rubber bands. Somehow, there’s always something new to find when you open one of its drawers.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A3F218C">PLASTIK Teen Organizrz</Text>
  <Text Key="A8BAE864">If your bath contains just water, you are missing out on a whole new world of bathing luxury! These bath fragrances are the perfect way to enjoy the spa experience at home, relax and unwind after a stressful day. This jar has many scents to choose from and come in a variety of colors to match your mood or decor.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA64FCAB">SaltBathe Fragrance Jar</Text>
  <Text Key="2D7AD198">EVERY skincare Simfluencer has been talking about Glowy Dew's newest 3 Step Collection. Guaranteed to not only deliver the glossiest skin ever recorded in the history of Simkind, but also make every houseguest jealous while noticing its very deliberate position on the bathroom sink - a declaration that yes, you &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; in fact way trendier (and considerably more moist) than them.</Text>
  <Text Key="4842B017">Glowy Dew's Skincare Essentials</Text>
  <Text Key="D44ED6D0">You can’t leave the house without combing your hair. It's a given. Whether you're fighting daily bedhead or trying to tame your curls, these combs will help bring order to your hair while giving you an excuse to smell like sandalwood.</Text>
  <Text Key="FA3738FF">Assorted Combs by HairLabs </Text>
  <Text Key="A627EA1D">The world's first smart razor with a built-in AI system that learns and adapts to your beard preferences. With 5-directional blades, dual precision heads, and an integrated microchip that senses beard density, and an optimized facial mapping system, this razor promises the closest shave of your life.</Text>
  <Text Key="73EEF108">AI Luxe Electric Razor</Text>
  <Text Key="52E70A04">The corded hair dryer is the perfect option for those looking for speed, healthy, and a quick drying time. This hairdryer is so quick and easy to use, you'll think you've never had to use it.</Text>
  <Text Key="0AF69ACB">Micro Lightning Dryer by Easy Hair</Text>
  <Text Key="DC43D78E">Let your skin soak up the luxury of this rejuvenating collection. Carefully made to restore vitality and a youthful appearance, it's your own little Potion of Youth. Who needs satisfaction points?</Text>
  <Text Key="7BB8B7B1">Pointedly Luxurious Lotions Routine</Text>
  <Text Key="8564FF13">The best lotions are the ones that you don't even need to think about. That's why we created Single. Used. Lotion. Just rub it on, and you're good to go. No greasy after-feel, no worries about whether or not your kids will get it on their clothes—and it smells like a dream! It's the perfect lotion for people who don't like lotions.</Text>
  <Text Key="2D70F1C2">Single. Used. Lotion.</Text>
  <Text Key="46C552BB">It's soap! A big bar with suds, it gets me clean! I can't imagine a more beautiful thing.</Text>
  <Text Key="71FDD51A">It's Soap</Text>
  <Text Key="7E446150">Nothing makes a statement quite like the Resolute Hand Soap. Its simplistic design, modern finish, and elegant accents all say, "I'm filled with brand name soap." Your Sims will surely enjoy the luxury of washing their hands when in the company of this beauty.</Text>
  <Text Key="4154D07F">Resolute Hand Soap</Text>
  <Text Key="57BAEBB6">Creating a welcoming bathing environment has never been easier. You'll never ever have to worry about running out of towels and having to streak to the bedroom ever again! Each set includes a bar of handmade llama milk soap that leaves skin soft and supple. </Text>
  <Text Key="8B41E2E9">SimSpa Towel Set</Text>
  <Text Key="8DCB6542">Yes, your teeth are the window to your soul, but sometimes we'd like them to be dressed appropriately for company. This glass cup is part of a full set that comes complete with a dentures replica and bedside table.</Text>
  <Text Key="46AD823D">Glass Cup and Accessories</Text>
  <Text Key="C2C22AF0">For the more conservative Sim, you can never go wrong with a manual toothbrush and toothpaste. Now updated with modern color schemes.</Text>
  <Text Key="744DAE9F">Ole' Faithful Toothbrush Set</Text>
  <Text Key="D0791924">Experience the power of the NEWave Toothbrush with a built-in stand and rinse cup. This toothbrush is recommended by the top SimCity dentists thanks to its built-in timer, power settings, and wireless charging. Your teeth will be so clean and bright, you won't want to stop smiling!</Text>
  <Text Key="8F27E56B">NEWave Toothbrush Set</Text>
  <Text Key="B5D32DBD">Fight bad breath and start your day off fresh with LlamaFairy's Tooth Lacquer, now with a brand new formula proven to both brighten teeth and fight cavities. It's the same reliable brand your grandparent's used, but with all the benefits of modern science!</Text>
  <Text Key="64662728">LlamaFairy's Tooth Lacquer</Text>
  <Text Key="5E4A7154">There comes a time in life where one questions an object's worth. This is that moment. Will this poor tube be forgotten on the counter, pushed aside into the garbage, or lovingly cared for until the bitter end?</Text>
  <Text Key="9E6CBD3B">Dearly Departed Tooth Lacquer</Text>
  <Text Key="A2C21D1F">On a wall, it's considered hygienic, but on a surface, most view it as currency. In fact, there was a time not long ago when Sims considered this material invaluable beyond all others. Show off your wealth in a unique way! Stock up on this commodity, show it off to your friends, and see what all the rave is about. </Text>
  <Text Key="3C4627C6">Lone Paper</Text>
  <Text Key="78FC4A02">Today's world of modern skincare and beauty products makes it impossible to find all the space you need for your daily bathing and pampering. Look no further than the ShowerTime Caddy for all your organization needs. You'll find everything you need to rinse, wash, repeat, and more!</Text>
  <Text Key="F98CCDFD">ShowerTime Caddy</Text>
  <Text Key="911C22B3">Click it up. Click it down. Now do that ten times fast. Now do it when someone's using the room. Now do it and go AhwhoooOOOOoooo!</Text>
  <Text Key="E0F898E2">Clickity Light Switch</Text>
  <Text Key="6568BF4F">Everyone's seen one, but has anyone actually used one and how does it work? Now's your chance to find out with the Rocket Light Switch &amp; Dimmer! This reliable and modern switch comes equipped with a neon night light to help with visibility, in case you forgot where your light switch is. Of course, you could also utilize the sleek and modern flush design for a contemporary finish.</Text>
  <Text Key="A2214E16">Rocket Light Switch &amp; Dimmer</Text>
  <Text Key="0289696A">Step into your own home spa with the SimSpa Luxury Towel Bar. Indulge in the crisp, clean display of these luxurious plush cotton towels after a bath or shower, smell the fresh towel scent, close your eyes, and sink into your moment of bliss.</Text>
  <Text Key="534AEFF5">SimSpa Luxury Towel Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="8A5315A4">Give your bathroom a truly lived-in and shamelessly messy look that portrays a sense of bold disarray, with a verbose tone of disregard. Sims with these towels like to show that they live on the edge.</Text>
  <Text Key="778432EB">Left to Dry Towel Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="EDE749E4">No Sim can live without this everyday necessity. Place this item in your bathroom and rest assured that no Sim will ever find themselves lacking, even if it is placed the "wrong" way. </Text>
  <Text Key="04F1692B">THE Toilet Paper Roll</Text>
  <Text Key="245AF4CB">Simple and Clean</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>