<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="8A0CB2C3">This shabby bookshelf reminds me of the days when I used to study in my dorm room. It makes me realize that the best books can’t be purchased. They all may be old and worn, but each book holds more than just the text on the page. They hold precious memories of days gone by. </Text>
  <Text Key="4656B312">Unstable Shelves</Text>
  <Text Key="1861CF61">Sometimes, no matter how hard you try, your house will always show wear and tear. To some, it's a nuisance and to others it's a talking point. Will you hide the signs of disrepair, or show them off with pride? The choice is yours!</Text>
  <Text Key="346FF814">Weary Wall Decal</Text>
  <Text Key="3D505F3A">This lamp has what today’s light fixtures simply can’t provide: vintage patina, quality materials, and timeless design. That flickering may be a nuisance, you know, but what if it’s someone sending messages from the other side? Maybe you shouldn't part with it just yet…</Text>
  <Text Key="87F609E5">Brass Floor Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="69455F6F">Feeling a little tense? Lighten up! It’s that not so modern mod-lamp for the folks who just can't get enough of a bygone era. Why get a functional lamp when you could have this non-functional art piece? And who doesn't love art that makes you… feel? </Text>
  <Text Key="527432B6">The Not-So-Mod Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="23FD8CA8">Tucked away in a basement, forgotten picture frames wait for someone to bring them out again. An old large mirror, passed down through a family line, waits to be seen once more. These treasures sit in storage, waiting for their time to shine.</Text>
  <Text Key="028CFBC7">Forgotten Frames</Text>
  <Text Key="7BB3A693">This mirror stands the test of time... graceful, ambitious, bold, and flawless. This standing mirror is a head-turner, to say the least. Starting from humble beginnings and crafted to stand the test of time, you'll gaze into this mirror and reflect on the many memories and ask, where did they go?</Text>
  <Text Key="F7255042">The Graceful Ambition Standing Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="7797CBB3">&lt;i&gt;Excerpt from &lt;b&gt;An Elder Sim's Perspective&lt;/b&gt; by O. Specter&lt;/i&gt;:
"Nearing the end of their life, every Sim falls for the bittersweet temptation of nostalgia, the dreamy allure of old photos in painted frames. We look to the past with a certainty we simply cannot hold for the present, seeking comfort in stories we already know the endings of. The things that left us awestruck and full of wonder then, leave us tired and longing for familiarity now. While it might be easy to dwell on what was, or what could have been, never forget that this mode of living we've been given is a gift."</Text>
  <Text Key="071943E2">Strange Reminiscence Framed Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="4AE0D908">Old chairs have all kinds of stories to tell. Often discarded, they usually find themselves in need of a new purpose. These chairs have been waiting for you to come along and get some use out of them. They're not quite ready for sitting, so maybe place something on top for now? </Text>
  <Text Key="405AE3A7">Unmatched Chairs</Text>
  <Text Key="30FA83B8">Having once spruced up a bare corner and enlivened many decks, this artificial plant is now a handy dust collector for generations to come. Requiring much less tending than other plants, it stands the test of time for Sims who may want a bit of green without having too much work involved.</Text>
  <Text Key="7C4402B7">Uncle Bob's Dusty Rubber Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="7BDE9045">These stains have been here a while... quite a while, almost as if each one has a unique story to tell. What do you think they're saying?</Text>
  <Text Key="063A4E40">Unbeatable Stains</Text>
  <Text Key="0E870C73">A classic for a reason. The Moving Buddy is a hand-me-down that has seen it all and been through so many moves. Where will it take you next?</Text>
  <Text Key="704C7BA2">The Moving Buddy</Text>
  <Text Key="BF03C27E">It’s been over 20 years, yet this old Vibromatic will still have you feelin’ flirty as you recall the good old days when you were livin’ large. It has a lot of history and it shows. Nonetheless, there’s still some motion in the ocean and maybe the vibration engine could even work again one day. This unique piece captures such a special place in our hearts that we can't quite part with it.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA0F8601">Disassembled Heart Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="0BDE50FE">A well-traveled trunk, replete with tales of mystery and intrigue, awaits to be rediscovered. This curious object was once used by an unknown passenger on a long journey across the sea.</Text>
  <Text Key="E404E981">The Traveler's Trunk</Text>
  <Text Key="A9D7438F">Collect family treasures and stow away one-of-a-kind keepsakes with the Shabby Cardboard. Dusty and worn, these cardboard boxes are an invitation to investigate the memories held within.</Text>
  <Text Key="BE5D8456">Shabby Cardboard Box</Text>
  <Text Key="ED44FB26">The Sim that packed this box? We all know what they were thinking. "Oh, I can't get rid of my 9th grade algebra notes! What if I'm faced with a linear equation one day and there's nowhere else for me to turn?" Of course, that notebook has sat unopened since that moment. Cradled by a pair of old, worn out jeans they swear will fit them again one day. Hugged by a scarf that happens to be their least favorite color, that they vaguely remember buying because they needed to "expand their wardrobe horizons." </Text>
  <Text Key="51921B39">Big Box of Irreplaceably Replaceable Things</Text>
  <Text Key="7545B939">Fun for all ages! Almost all the pieces are included for you to enjoy either a game of &lt;i&gt;Scrobble&lt;/i&gt; or &lt;i&gt;Syndicate&lt;/i&gt;. Instructions no longer included.</Text>
  <Text Key="2335853C">The Fun of Yesteryear</Text>
  <Text Key="74BF399F">These must be some form of ancient technology. While the outer square sleeves vary in color and appear to be merely used for protection and identification purposes, they all contain mostly black-colored plates. However, these plates have a hole in the middle, which is why we conclude that they're probably not meant to hold your grilled cheese. There's still much to unveil but we believe that the engraved spiral texture on these plates was used to convey some sort of signal—but a signal to whom and what kind of signal? That remains to be uncovered...</Text>
  <Text Key="6761D546">Records of the Past</Text>
  <Text Key="0C040B00">This telephone was once the pinnacle of a teenager's life. Now replaced by the convenience of smartphones, new generations of Sims will never know the struggles of having to remember other Sim's numbers by memory, the awkwardness of asking your crush's parents if they are available to talk, or the frustration of being kicked off the internet because your Mom "accidentally" picked up the phone.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0E7BBCF">Relic of Good Times</Text>
  <Text Key="667A19B0">When you need a little pick-me-up, take a moment to look back at all you've accomplished! You were bowling royalty, even if only for the night, and your hotdog eating skills were unmatched. In some cases, you didn't get first, but at least your participation earned you a medal or two. Dust these relics off and get lost reminiscing about the good old days.</Text>
  <Text Key="D25A605F">Mementos of Glory</Text>
  <Text Key="01BAA901">Dusty trinkets that hold strange sentimental value. They're creepy but also cute... kinda.</Text>
  <Text Key="BEB41034">Dusty Trinkets</Text>
  <Text Key="B16BE883">Without a doubt, an old recliner is far better than a new one! This chair has been perfectly broken into and the leather is soft and supple. It's been the best seat in the house many times, and will be for many more years to come.</Text>
  <Text Key="0485C4D2">The Best Seat In The House</Text>
  <Text Key="CC7D0E79">This couch has been passed down from your grandparents’ days. It’s a well-loved piece, with plenty of stories to go along with the ruthless wear and tear. At this point in its life, it holds too much sentimental value to simply throw away. You can't buy memories after all!</Text>
  <Text Key="2562607C">Grandma's Couch</Text>
  <Text Key="91032D97">An old piece of furniture you've been keeping out of sight for a while. It may be shabby, but it's still functional nonetheless.</Text>
  <Text Key="3176F46E">Candid Coffee Table</Text>
  <Text Key="5214B59D">The Retroplex TV Console is truly a heirloom to be cherished...even though its beyond repair. Perhaps it can be repurposed into something new because this piece is just too cool to throw out! </Text>
  <Text Key="D31C7B88">Retroplex TV Console</Text>
  <Text Key="E50BAC33">A unique piece of history, this vintage and square TV is a reminder that there was once a time before flat screens. It may not work too well anymore, but why not make a statement?</Text>
  <Text Key="5295FD62">SquareTube</Text>
  <Text Key="05C94323">Basement Hideaway </Text>
  <Text Key="7BA2B27C">Dated Drywall</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>