<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="37DCE937">(From Watching a Movie)</Text>
  <Text Key="02895E5C">But... wait... why... ugh! How could they mess up a movie so badly in my favorite genre?</Text>
  <Text Key="0F80FF33">Big Screen Let Down</Text>
  <Text Key="09782600">You could call that movie the sleeper hit of the year. Emphasis on "sleeper".</Text>
  <Text Key="F9431CCF">Boring Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="54251CA4">{0.SimFirstName} can list all the movie's mistakes, plot holes, and bad dialog in less than ten minutes.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC7D97EB">Cinema Sin</Text>
  <Text Key="680E1E4B">An instant classic! Surely that flick will be in contention for awards season this year.</Text>
  <Text Key="BF13C9CA">Genre Staple</Text>
  <Text Key="4EFB1076">That movie was... interesting. Worth a watch, at least this once.</Text>
  <Text Key="5644C6A9">Interesting Flick</Text>
  <Text Key="EEB50C58">Bravo! How fortuitous that we bear witness to this pinnacle of the medium!</Text>
  <Text Key="37610ED7">Silver Screen Masterpiece</Text>
  <Text Key="85E357D7">Watch Movies</Text>
  <Text Key="EFC89858">Watch Movies</Text>
  <Text Key="4650196E">Don't Watch Movies</Text>
  <Text Key="0B911BC5">Artsy-Fancy Flair</Text>
  <Text Key="1F35704E">Rhapsodist's Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="EC0573CC">Offbeat Charm</Text>
  <Text Key="4E5AE13D">Point Breaker</Text>
  <Text Key="A457A268">Laid-Back Mastery</Text>
  <Text Key="AD602CC4">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 4, Episode 3\n100 East Northbank Boulevard, Champs Les Sims\n\nAh Paris... Stephen and Checo quibble over "City of Lights" vs "City of Love" as their preferred nickname, but the argument is ultimately inconsequential. Any picker knows that Paris has been picked clean for years now. Instead the two drive into the French countryside until reaching the town of Champs Les Sims. While sipping coffee at The Catania Café, Stephen spots a woman with striking blue eyes who introduces herself as Aimée. As the pleasant chitchat turns to business, she mentions her husband André's collection of fine cloth that he keeps in immaculate condition. With their interest piqued, the pair travel to the Lefebvre's home, where Checo is immediately impressed at the elegant embroidery, noting how the level of skill on display can only be found in the old country. Checo strikes a deal for a bundle of cloth, perfect for curtains without any alterations.\n\nPicked = §45\nProfit = §70</Text>
  <Text Key="9BDBC58B">Triomphant Textiles - Left</Text>
  <Text Key="81768DAB">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 4, Episode 3\n100 East Northbank Boulevard, Champs Les Sims\n\nAh Paris... Stephen and Checo quibble over "City of Lights" vs "City of Love" as their preferred nickname, but the argument is ultimately inconsequential. Any picker knows that Paris has been picked clean for years now. Instead the two drive into the French countryside until reaching the town of Champs Les Sims. While sipping coffee at The Catania Café, Stephen spots a woman with striking blue eyes who introduces herself as Aimée. As the pleasant chitchat turns to business, she mentions her husband André's collection of fine cloth that he keeps in immaculate condition. With their interest piqued, the pair travel to the Lefebvre's home, where Checo is immediately impressed at the elegant embroidery, noting how the level of skill on display can only be found in the old country. Checo strikes a deal for a bundle of cloth, perfect for curtains without any alterations.\n\nPicked = §45\nProfit = §70</Text>
  <Text Key="74CDB0AA">Triomphant Textiles - Right</Text>
  <Text Key="9EEA0C98">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 8, Episode 7\n323 Knott Drive, Moonlight Falls\n\nStephen and Checo head to Varg's Tavern in Moonlight Falls - a local hotspot that's renown for attracting some of the city's more colorful characters. Shortly after arriving they notice something odd; there's a gentleman who's not only entertaining patrons with his guitar, but he's also buying rounds for the entire bar! Chatting with the mixologist reveals that the man is Rainflower Ivy, a local entertainer who recently came into a large inheritance. Intrigued, Stephen approaches him, and finds out that Rainflower is planning a large renovation to his estate, and would be more than happy to sell fixtures of his home instead of sending them to the trash heap. As the two browse the Ivy home, they're drawn to a pair of hand painted doors that represent the same ethos Rainflower stands for - peace and harmony with mother Earth. Stephen assures Rainflower that the doors will find a new home, and continue to be used for years to come.\n\nPicked = §25\nProfit = §25</Text>
  <Text Key="EF657117">Green Flower Power - Double</Text>
  <Text Key="D8566A7C">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 8, Episode 7\n323 Knott Drive, Moonlight Falls\n\nStephen and Checo head to Varg's Tavern in Moonlight Falls - a local hotspot that's renown for attracting some of the city's more colorful characters. Shortly after arriving they notice something odd; there's a gentleman who's not only entertaining patrons with his guitar, but he's also buying rounds for the entire bar! Chatting with the mixologist reveals that the man is Rainflower Ivy, a local entertainer who recently came into a large inheritance. Intrigued, Stephen approaches him, and finds out that Rainflower is planning a large renovation to his estate, and would be more than happy to sell fixtures of his home instead of sending them to the trash heap. As the two browse the Ivy home, they're drawn to a pair of hand painted doors that represent the same ethos Rainflower stands for - peace and harmony with mother Earth. Stephen assures Rainflower that the doors will find a new home, and continue to be used for years to come.\n\nPicked = §25\nProfit = §25</Text>
  <Text Key="D13CF6D3">Green Flower Power - Single</Text>
  <Text Key="F02ACD3E">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 9, Episode 2\n153 Herschel's Pond Road, Twinbrook\n\nFresh off a successful pick, Stephen and Checo return to the mouth of the Simislaus Creek to visit their old friend Buddy Bailey. The past seven years have been kind to Buddy, having found great success after his appearance on Plumbob Pickers in season 2. In fact, he's moved into the former Knack mansion - it seems Pattina's 15 minutes of fame quickly came and went, and she left town after her family left her. It should come as no surprise that love fades quickly when someone who can't stand art marries an artist who suddenly can't find success. After catching up with Buddy, the two take a drive around the outskirts of town with an eye for picking. They come across the Bayless family shack (affectionately known as Marsh Mansion); with odds and ends strewn about the front yard. Suddenly Checo spots it... an original Pattina Knack armoire! What a coincidence! "I ain't never done liked that sideways dresser. It came from 'dem rich folk parts," said Skeet, right before shaking Checo's hand.\n\nPicked = §150\nProfit = §625</Text>
  <Text Key="986814C1">Profit &amp; 'Postrophes</Text>
  <Text Key="DEA97725">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 4, Episode 2\nThe Papyrus House, Al Simhara\n\nPicking and tomb raiding... Stephen and Checo discover they aren't so different after all while exploring the sand-bleached dunes of Al Simhara. The two stroll through the local marketplace, where they come across a stall run by Farouk Rashid, who happens to be selling Egyptian antiquities! He tells a tall tale of an ancient tomb he discovered underneath his home when excavating for a basement addition. As Farouk is terrified at the possibility of encountering a mummy, he invites the pair to explore the tomb on their own, and he'll offer a bargain on any treasures they extract. Farouk's fears aren't unfounded, as they turn a corner in the darkness only to encounter a gaping bandaged maw, and the sounds of decayed sinew stretching and snapping into place as the mummy stumbles towards them. Terrified, they run from the tomb, but not before yanking an old star-shaped fixture from the ceiling that was intended to guide Al Simharians on their journey to the beyond.\n\nPicked = §5\nProfit = §110</Text>
  <Text Key="FD9BEEA0">Stars Over Simhara</Text>
  <Text Key="ED8AADF1">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 5, Episode 9\n1 Mithrilen Manor, Dragon Valley\n\nNo matter where Stephen and Checo go in Dragon Valley, they keep hearing one name spoken - be it in hushed tones or on the tip of sharp tongues - Mithrilen! Determined to learn more, they pay a visit to the Mithrilen family home where they meet Fintan. He's clearly a man with many thoughts on many matters, but primarily he stands for two things. One, he believes he's the rightful mayor of the town by birthright, and that the O'Connell family should be driven from the land. Two, he... HATES... dragons! Fintan proudly shows a trio of dragon eggs he pilfered from a wurm's lair, which he carefully cracked to make an omlette (or as he describes it - "a feast for the ages"). Afterwards, he preserved the dragon egg shells and turned them into iridescent hanging lanterns, which Stephen immediately decided he must have.\n\nPicked = §100\nProfit = §35</Text>
  <Text Key="2B2926C4">Cantankerous Cackleberries</Text>
  <Text Key="61EC389A">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 4, Episode 1\n73 South Shang Simla Hills, Shang Simla\n\nA new season for a new year! Stephen and Checo kick off the season with a bang, as they enjoy fireworks underneath the skies of Shang Simla. While strolling through the Forbidden City they meet Maya Wang, a free spirited artist who draws inspiration from the nature that surrounds her. Maya invites the duo to her family's home, where she prepares a traditional egg roll recipe for them. Stephen connects with Maya over a shared love of arts and crafts, and she shows him the paper lanterns that she's handmade using a technique passed down from her grandmother. Stephen insists on purchasing a variety of the laterns for his own private collection, not even bothering to haggle over prices.\n\nPicked = §615\nProfit = NOT FOR SALE</Text>
  <Text Key="D00532C5">Lilacs &amp; Lanterns</Text>
  <Text Key="54128F09">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 5, Episode 8\n68 Velkominn Road, Aurora Skies\n\nStephen and Checo make a stop in chilly Aurora Skies. There they encounter Jackie and Felicia, two lovely ladies who have an uncanny amount of fine jewelry and art that they seem more than willing to part with. Stephen breaks the ice to get the deals flowing by paying full price for a hand-crafted candelabra (and also because the heater at the "Hostility-Free Hostel" is broken, and they sure as plum need a way to stay warm). Upon attempting to leave the country, the pair get stopped at the border by customs officers - their entire haul is identified as stolen goods! Not only are their posessions confiscated, but Stephen and Checo are forced to endure a night in jail - a very cold night mind you. They're freed the next day when their story checks out, but in the meantime Jackie and Felicia seem to have vanished.\n\nPicked = §170\nProfit = -§170; CONFISCATED</Text>
  <Text Key="9CEEA66C">Of Fire And Ice</Text>
  <Text Key="3A81CB5A">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 2, Episode 3\n1787 Bayshore Highway, Bridgeport\n\nStephen and Checo rarely visit cities, but they're too intrigued by the prospect of picking a vampire's property to resist. In Bridgeport they meet Morrigan Hemlock, a pale lady with an eclectic taste for the old world. She's initially hesitant to sell, but agrees to part with a Romani mirror in her collection once Checo points out that it isn't something she'll need for, oh say... the rest of eternity. The morning after, Stephen panics upon discovering bite marks on his neck! The source is soon traced back to a rampant bed bug infestation in their hotel though, and the two quickly leave Bridgeport in their rearview mirror.\n\nPicked = §175\nProfit = §60</Text>
  <Text Key="8321C985">Reflection of a Vampire</Text>
  <Text Key="DD63B63E">When you hear "Projectotron" you think of quality. You think of consistency. You think of a best in class product that's stood the test of time. Well... throw that second thought out the window! Introducing the Projectotron Outdoor Movie Screen, an exciting new product in our 2016 lineup. No, this isn't 4K resolution - please stop asking. It's the same dependable picture you've come to expect from Projectotron over the past ten years, but now with outdoor mounting bracket and speakers to match!\n\nProjectotron Incorporated not responsible for public broadcasts of copyrighted content intended for private use in a home broadcast. Any public showings of such content without express written consent is prohibited.</Text>
  <Text Key="3FBC7FC1">Projectotron Outdoor Movie Screen</Text>
  <Text Key="C30C9065">"4K resolution" is a fancy gimmick. When you buy a Projectotron, you know you're buying quality. Our projectors don't rely on new-fangled new technology, we stand behind our decade old designs - why do you think we haven't changed them? Consistency, reliability, stability. These are more than words, they're a company ethos. This is technology you can trust, and a product you can rely on... Projectotron. The industry standard.</Text>
  <Text Key="D22C10E0">Projectotron Indoor Movie Screen</Text>
  <Text Key="E75A1194">Rumor has it that MorcuCorp is smuggling national treasures out of Egypt, including the famous pink Diamond of D'nile. Can James Pond infiltrate their headquarters and return this natural treasure to its rightful place in Al Simhara?</Text>
  <Text Key="857E057B">Diamonds Are For Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="405C4E81">Too many cooks in the kitchen doesn't even begin to describe the situation the Khlumzee Sisters find themselves in. This is one fancy dinner that's gone to the dogs... literally!</Text>
  <Text Key="7E5508B4">The Khlumzee Sisters</Text>
  <Text Key="CF921602">The terrific two-o duo return in SuperKids: Cortex Catastrophe. After years in exile, their arch nemesis Mind Ove'Matter executes his plan to bring about the end of existance! Can the SuperKids save humanity yet again?</Text>
  <Text Key="C58C71FD">SuperKids: Cortex Catastrophe</Text>
  <Text Key="98C7A94F">Five college friends refuse to heed the local's warnings as they venture to a remote campsite deep in the woods for a weekend of debauchery. Shaka-bra? More like shaka-buried!</Text>
  <Text Key="B555EC16">Moonlight Massacre III
</Text>
  <Text Key="254514D1">Romance simmers when using Simder, the hot new app for heated hookups. Can Grace find love before her passion burns out?</Text>
  <Text Key="17F71C24">Simder</Text>
  <Text Key="749011CB">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 2, Episode 7\n19 Poker Flats Drive, Twinbrook\n\nJokes of Stephen and Checo being "good ole' boys" pass back and forth as the pair cross the Simisouri state line on their way to Twinbrook. They've already received a lead on a budding artist named Buddy, and make a beeline to his home. One thing is immediately apparent as they step inside - Buddy is on the cusp of breaking out. His art speaks to the soul and the culture of the South, deftly weaving stories and emotions together on canvas. They learn of his hardships... he labors daily at city hall polishing the podiums for the town's politicians, just in the hopes of rubbing two simoleons together to scrape by each week. This is it, this is his chance! An appearance on Plumbob Pickers will elevate him to stardom! ...suddenly his roommate Gala shouts from the other room... "You know he's a couch potato, right?" Undeterred, Stephen buys a clustered arrangement of his paintings, knowing their value will be through the roof soon enough!\n\nPicked = §145\nProfit = §280</Text>
  <Text Key="7E284C4A">Songs of Simisouri - Bottom Arrangement</Text>
  <Text Key="03FE5B62">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 2, Episode 7\n19 Poker Flats Drive, Twinbrook\n\nJokes of Stephen and Checo being "good ole' boys" pass back and forth as the pair cross the Simisouri state line on their way to Twinbrook. They've already received a lead on a budding artist named Buddy, and make a beeline to his home. One thing is immediately apparent as they step inside - Buddy is on the cusp of breaking out. His art speaks to the soul and the culture of the South, deftly weaving stories and emotions together on canvas. They learn of his hardships... he labors daily at city hall polishing the podiums for the town's politicians, just in the hopes of rubbing two simoleons together to scrape by each week. This is it, this is his chance! An appearance on Plumbob Pickers will elevate him to stardom! ...suddenly his roommate Gala shouts from the other room... "You know he's a couch potato, right?" Undeterred, Stephen buys a clustered arrangement of his paintings, knowing their value will be through the roof soon enough!\n\nPicked = §120\nProfit = §215</Text>
  <Text Key="1D785BDD">Songs of Simisouri - Top Arrangement</Text>
  <Text Key="350F2FB2">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 6, Episode 5\n125 Lakeside Drive, Lucky Palms\n\nStephen and Checo arrive in Lucky Palms and make the town's famous wishing well their first stop. Checo immediately wished for wealth, while Stephen shared a personal moment and wished for a child. The two soon meet Lola Lancaster, a former showgirl who's earned quite the reputation around town after being spotted with multiple high rollers. She happens to possess an intricately detailed planter, plucked from the lobby of the Desert Knights casino before it was torn down to make way for the Lucky Simoleon. In the spirit of the town, the two agree to a coin toss to settle the final purchase price for this unique piece of old Lucky Palms. The episode concludes with a surprise call from Stephen's wife Wanda - she's pregnant!\n\nPicked = §160\nProfit = §145</Text>
  <Text Key="E717724D">Lucky Leads, Planted Palms</Text>
  <Text Key="9A2C93B6">Plumbob Pickers: Celebrity Edition\nSeason 7, Episode 3\n57 Dockside Road, Bridgeport\n\nSeason 3 saw Stephen and Checo swearing off Bridgeport forever, but an opportunity to pick from the cast of Little Celebrity proves to be irresistible! Checo has a fun evening at The Brightmore club with Katelyn Missoni and her BFF Sugar Bijou. Of course the afterparty ends up back at the Little Celebrity set, where Checo notices a vase that was seen in the music video for the seminal lyrical hit of the aughts, "Drop a Nickle for a Dime" by Sugar's bae Tom. A deal is quickly struck.\n\nPicked = §195\nProfit = §65
</Text>
  <Text Key="19165AE9">Fast Money, Fast Flora</Text>
  <Text Key="F0FBA25F">You've tried the chill, now enjoy the thrill... of the Kane family's newest innovation! To celebrate the company's 21st anniversary they're looking to the past. What better inspiration than Papa Charlie's sugarcane popcorn? This is popcorn just the way Dad used to make it, air popped with a sprinkle of sugar to give it that irresistible crunch. From the Kane family to yours, it's the treat you'll love to heat.</Text>
  <Text Key="130C7E06">Sugar Kane Popcorn Popper</Text>
  <Text Key="80EA54A9">Plumbob Pickers: High Seas\nSeason 3, Episode 10\n1 Camino del Ray, Isla Paradiso\n\nStephen and Checo travel to a slice of paradise, where they meet the Ichtaca family - local ambassadors of culture, whose lineage traces back to island royalty. Checo is immediately drawn to a vibrant rug that dates back hundreds of years. Guillermo shares ancient stories of a successful hunt, and the following festivities during which the rug was woven. After a terse negotiation, Carolina agrees to sell the rug in an attempt to promote cultural diffusion.\n\nPicked = §200\nProfit = §45</Text>
  <Text Key="4971B28C">Sha(g)ka Bra</Text>
  <Text Key="DA4B9AB2">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 1, Episode 1\n19441 Bob-o-Link Drive, Appaloosa Plains\n\nThis reality series follows Stephen Tinker and "Checo" Ramirez around the world in search of valuables hidden in homes, storage centers, and private collections. In the series premier, they meet Kanoa Parrot, an eccentric transplant from Hawaii. An adorable teapot with island origins quickly catches Stephen's eye and a deal is made. The exchange ends controversially however, when Jazlyn returns home to find her husband sold the family heirloom out from under her.\n\nPicked = §75\nProfit = §300</Text>
  <Text Key="04BAC34D">Tea and Tears</Text>
  <Text Key="0F4317BA">Plumbob Pickers: Celebrity Edition\nSeason 7, Episode 1\n177 Foothill Drive, Starlight Shores\n\nSeason 7 kicks off with Stephen and Checo picking from familiar faces - and who better to start with than world renowned magician Steve Cupp? Normally one who prefers solitude, Steve cautiously welcomes the duo into one of his hidden storage facilities - a veritable treasure trove of magician's props from his sellout shows. Stephen is immediately drawn to an elaborate tapestry that was used to conceal Steve as he performed one of his most dangerous tricks within the infamous Box of Danger.\n\nPicked = §650\nProfit = §210</Text>
  <Text Key="CE87CB65">Drape of Danger</Text>
  <Text Key="1D4C681A">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 1, Episode 4\n180 Bounty Drive, Riverview\n\nWhile driving to a pick in a neighboring state, Stephen and Checo pass through the rustic town of Riverview and take the opportunity to make cold calls. This leads them to the McDermott family, simple folk who live off the land by growing their own food and catching fish from the Simomon River. This family seems content with only having the essentials of life, but that's when Stephen spots it... a genuine Ferdinand original. Being one of the few names that carries weight beyond Riverview's borders, Stephen knew he couldn't let the opportunity to own an authentic piece from Hank Ferdinand slip away. Ginny, the matron of the family, is sharp as a whip and has a firm grip on the family wallet. She squeezes Stephen for top dollar before allowing this special piece to leave the home.\n\nPicked = §180\nProfit = §40</Text>
  <Text Key="23A7A945">Pick a Peck of Pennies</Text>
  <Text Key="ADF11451">Plumbob Pickers: The Lost Episodes\nSeason 10, Episode 5: Part 1\n125 Poffald Place, Midnight Hollow\n\nStephen and Checo drive along a foggy highway, when they suddenly encounter an exit ramp that doesn't appear on their map. Intrigued, the two decide to alter their route. They soon arrive in the town of Midnight Hollow, an inexplicable destination with residents as intriguing as the surreal surroundings. One man radiates style as he strolls down the street; it's none other than Phineas Bledsoe, the town's self-made socialite. Ever the showman, Phineas agrees to show the two around his home. The interior is an explosion of color, causing Stephen to instinctively shield his eyes after growing accustomed to the drab landscaping. A set of dining room chairs is of particular interest, and Phineas shares how he fashioned them from leftover cloth used in his latest clothing line. When Stephen inquires about the matching dining table, Phineas turns cold and asks the pair to leave. In a last ditch effort, Checo offers near market value for the seats. After a pause, Phineas snatches the simoleons and ushers the pair out the door.\n\nPicked = §125\nProfit = §30</Text>
  <Text Key="CB1402A4">Vexing Dining - Rounded</Text>
  <Text Key="BA779E1A">Plumbob Pickers: The Lost Episodes\nSeason 10, Episode 5: Part 1\n125 Poffald Place, Midnight Hollow\n\nStephen and Checo drive along a foggy highway, when they suddenly encounter an exit ramp that doesn't appear on their map. Intrigued, the two decide to alter their route. They soon arrive in the town of Midnight Hollow, an inexplicable destination with residents as intriguing as the surreal surroundings. One man radiates style as he strolls down the street; it's none other than Phineas Bledsoe, the town's self-made socialite. Ever the showman, Phineas agrees to show the two around his home. The interior is an explosion of color, causing Stephen to instinctively shield his eyes after growing accustomed to the drab landscaping. A set of dining room chairs is of particular interest, and Phineas shares how he fashioned them from leftover cloth used in his latest clothing line. When Stephen inquires about the matching dining table, Phineas turns cold and asks the pair to leave. In a last ditch effort, Checo offers near market value for the seats. After a pause, Phineas snatches the simoleons and ushers the pair out the door.\n\nPicked = §125\nProfit = §5</Text>
  <Text Key="71B76B45">Vexing Dining - Squared</Text>
  <Text Key="92316FB8">Plumbob Pickers: The Lost Episodes\nSeason 10, Episode 11\n33 Prosperity Street, Roaring Heights\n\nStephen and Checo pay a special visit to the Roaring Heights police station. Notorious criminal Donia Spinelli is there in her own holding cell, apart from the other riff-raff. News of her arrest made national headlines, and the pair mused that this may be the perfect opportunity for a pick. Upon her arrest all of Donia's assets were frozen, and she's been struggling to pay her legal team. Stephen meets with the police chief and cites the little known National Picker Profiteering Act of 1928 in a bid to exercise picker-client privilege for a private meeting. During their discussion, Donia lists disposable assets currently held under her consigliere. Chief among them is a set of furniture intended to adorn a speakeasy. It was meant to launch her bid to rule over Roaring Heights's illicit nightlife, but those plans have to be shelved for the time being. Knowing he's bidding from a position of power, Stephen lowballs Donia on purchasing the the club's seating.\n\nPicked = §50\nProfit = §140</Text>
  <Text Key="3E1D06B7">Grandma's Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="CD597957">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 12, Episode 1\nEP-XI Imports Gallery, 361 Proclivity Promenade, Oasis Landing\n\nSeason 12 kicks off with Stephen and Checo traveling through time to the futuristic world of Oasis Landing. As they make their way towards the fantastical architecture that encapsulates the center of town, they find themselves crossing through Legacy Park. Checo is drawn to one statue in particular, and upon reading the name on the plaque he drops to his knees with tears streaming down his face. It's his daughter Tessa, sculpted in perpetuity in recognition of her compassionate work as a philanthropist. The plaque details the entrepreneurial empire she founded, only to pass its daily operations down to her own children, thus fulfilling Checo's dreams. She then dedicated herself (and her vast fortunes) to helping others in need. Stephen slips away to give Checo a moment alone, and discovers that all chairs in the future have been replaced with things called "poofs", which he promptly purchases to see if he can set a trend back in their own timeline. Meanwhile in Legacy Park, another statue begins to shimmer, soften, and morph...\n\nPicked = §4,500\nProfit = §592 (Adjusted For Inflation)</Text>
  <Text Key="3305882E">A Poof in Time</Text>
  <Text Key="3A41AC12">Plumbob Pickers: High Seas\nSeason 3, Episode 11\n10 Azure Avenue, Sunlit Tides\n\nAfter acquiring a houseboat's worth of goods from Isla Paradiso, Stephen and Checo motor over to the shores of Sunlit Tides for more picking in paradise. They hear of Eleanor Waterson, a woman who's in the sunset of her life and is amidst preparation for her own estate sale. As she shows the two around her property, she shares short anecdotes of her favorite possessions. Her cheeks flush when the trio reach a colorful loveseat as she recalls a torrid romance with her late husband Hal. Checo's initial offer of §600 reflected the quality of craftsmanship and cultural island heritage seen in the woven wood. Eleanor's reminiscence of a weekend of woohoo on that very seat drops Checo's offer to §400, as he quickly realizes it'll need to be re-upholstered.\n\nPicked = §400\nProfit = §345</Text>
  <Text Key="F32F992D">Island Loving</Text>
  <Text Key="FB216032">Plumbob Pickers: The Lost Episodes\nSeason 10, Episode 11\n33 Prosperity Street, Roaring Heights\n\nStephen and Checo pay a special visit to the Roaring Heights police station. Notorious criminal Donia Spinelli is there in her own holding cell, apart from the other riff-raff. News of her arrest made national headlines, and the pair mused that this may be the perfect opportunity for a pick. Upon her arrest all of Donia's assets were frozen, and she's been struggling to pay her legal team. Stephen meets with the police chief and cites the little known National Picker Profiteering Act of 1928 in a bid to exercise picker-client privilege for a private meeting. During their discussion, Donia lists disposable assets currently held under her consigliere. Chief among them is a set of furniture intended to adorn a speakeasy. It was meant to launch her bid to rule over Roaring Heights's illicit nightlife, but those plans have to be shelved for the time being. Knowing he's bidding from a position of power, Stephen lowballs Donia on purchasing the the club's seating.\n\nPicked = §100\nProfit = §770</Text>
  <Text Key="767E1BCD">The Long Stretch</Text>
  <Text Key="4118528A">Plumbob Pickers\nSeason 5, Episode 7\n729 Bella Vista Drive, Monte Vista\n\nStephen and Checo continue their international tour with a stop in the ancient city of Monte Vista. In a town packed with treasure, they seize upon an opportunity to strike a deal with Nicoletta Lombardi. Nicoletta happens to be the last of a royal line, but it turns out that the Lombardi name doesn't carry much weight these days. She's spent every last simoleon trying to restore her family's reputation, putting Checo in a position to make an offer she can't refuse. The two haggle over a 19th century table, infamous for being the first item in the city to feature a mirrored surface.\n\nPicked = §125\nProfit = §95</Text>
  <Text Key="E4B65095">Reflections of the Past</Text>
  <Text Key="6BCF6A88">Plumbob Pickers: The Lost Episodes\nSeason 10, Episode 5: Part 2\n80 True Terrace, Midnight Hollow\n\nStephen and Checo visit the Lonely Literary Café to reflect on their strange encounter with Phineas. It's there that they meet Kara Carter, who's off in a corner attempting to subtly stifle her sniffles. Stephen inquires if she's alright, and in an apparent flood of relief to encounter a non-judgmental stranger, she tells the tale of her troubles. "Midnight Hollow can be such an oppressive place." she says, "The same faces, the same people... everyone talks, nothing stays private!" As it happens, she'd had a recent tryst with none other than Phineas Bledsoe! It seems that word spread amongst the townfolk when Phineas commissioned a special dining room set as a gift to her, causing a sudden split in their whirlwind romance. It was a beautiful gesture to Kara, being a five-star chef meant that food was the first love in her life... but now, she can barely serve a meal without being reminded of what happened. She offers Stephen the table that completes the set with the previously purchased chairs, relieved to rid it from her life so she can move forward.\n\nPicked = §200\nProfit = §335</Text>
  <Text Key="2D36E027">Run Run Runnerway</Text>
  <Text Key="F9725F72">Plumbob Pickers: High Seas\nSeason 3, Episode 8\n1 Camino del Ray, Isla Paradiso\n\nStephen and Checo set sail across the Simuyan Sea to reach Barnacle Bay - an island first settled by pirates. Local tradition dictates that visitors walk the plank and swim back to shore while wearing pirate boots to get a glimpse of the struggles of life in the olden days. An odd custom, and one that's faded in popularity in recent years, but the pair are happy to oblige if it'll keep an old timer like Willy McKellar happy. Willy is the town's former lighthouse keeper, and he's rumored to have quite the stash of antiquities. When the two come knocking with simoleons in hand, he reluctantly allows them inside. One item that immediately catches Stephen's eye is a painted folding table with an attention to detail simply not seen in modern carpentry. Willy speaks of how the table washed up on shore after a smuggler's ship capsized some seventy odd years ago. It just so happened to be the impetus that pushed the town to build the lighthouse. Recognizing an opportunity to own a piece of the region's history, Stephen quickly strikes a deal.\n\nPicked = §170\nProfit = §40</Text>
  <Text Key="38A8B80D">Smuggler's Paradise</Text>
  <Text Key="4EC066AC">Chat About Actors</Text>
  <Text Key="F07549FD">Ask Question About Movie's Plot</Text>
  <Text Key="07CB64E1">Complain About Actor</Text>
  <Text Key="5367173E">Complain About Director</Text>
  <Text Key="CBA8EF6A">Declare Favorite Movie Genre: Action</Text>
  <Text Key="48362422">Declare Favorite Movie Genre: Comedy</Text>
  <Text Key="48362421">Declare Favorite Movie Genre: Family</Text>
  <Text Key="48362420">Declare Favorite Movie Genre: Horror</Text>
  <Text Key="48362427">Declare Favorite Movie Genre: Romance</Text>
  <Text Key="CABA5E4D">Declare Favorite Movie Genre</Text>
  <Text Key="1F90591B">Listen to {1.SimFirstName}'s Declaration</Text>
  <Text Key="0011B3D0">Discuss Horror Scene</Text>
  <Text Key="6D96D967">Discuss Heartwarming Scene</Text>
  <Text Key="52350A0B">Quote Movie Scene</Text>
  <Text Key="6925EF6B">Recount Funniest Scene</Text>
  <Text Key="20BEF6A8">Discuss Action Scene</Text>
  <Text Key="8161AB92">Discuss Scene</Text>
  <Text Key="A2BA4133">Enthuse About Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="2811D691">Spread Fake Spoilers</Text>
  <Text Key="8FD6C8AA">A better projection means increased fun when watching movies!</Text>
  <Text Key="552D4616">Improved Projection</Text>
  <Text Key="27835DA9">Continue Upgrading Better Projection</Text>
  <Text Key="8C6197E3">Watch College Cram</Text>
  <Text Key="0FC64874">Watch Diamonds Are For Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="56B7DE02">Watch Lost Dog's Journey Home</Text>
  <Text Key="74E8427C">Watch Moonlight Massacre III</Text>
  <Text Key="35D4279C">Watch Roaring Vice</Text>
  <Text Key="451FB834">Watch Sims of the Dead</Text>
  <Text Key="1F4F0963">Watch SuperKids: Cortex Catastrophe</Text>
  <Text Key="4B08E16E">Watch The Adventures of Spaceship Simulation</Text>
  <Text Key="16D61511">Watch The Khlumzee Sisters</Text>
  <Text Key="335B40B4">Watch Simder</Text>
  <Text Key="326FF201">Watch Movie With</Text>
  <Text Key="32047717">Watch College Cram With</Text>
  <Text Key="A0EDE8A8">Watch Diamonds Are For Sims With</Text>
  <Text Key="904B755E">Watch Lost Dog's Journey Home With</Text>
  <Text Key="69610C58">Watch Moonlight Massacre III With</Text>
  <Text Key="3D573E98">Watch Roaring Vice With</Text>
  <Text Key="5D7F1748">Watch Sims of the Dead With</Text>
  <Text Key="C48A543F">Watch SuperKids: Cortex Catastrophe With</Text>
  <Text Key="C3CDB6CA">Watch The Adventures of Spaceship Simulation With</Text>
  <Text Key="7D171CB5">Watch The Khlumzee Sisters With</Text>
  <Text Key="FAB4CB40">Watch Simder With</Text>
  <Text Key="7BF28145">Unlock all popcorn recipes by reaching level 7 in the Cooking Skill.</Text>
  <Text Key="8BD65354">Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="DD1B6846">Empty Popper</Text>
  <Text Key="4D4BFF26">Grab Serving</Text>
  <Text Key="4570DEAC">Grab Serving</Text>
  <Text Key="E7A10180">Cannot cook popcorn while power is delinquent.</Text>
  <Text Key="2201D468">Cook Buttered Popcorn</Text>
  <Text Key="A67CBEDC">Cook {2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="9914BCE1">React to Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="9C4321F1">Shush</Text>
  <Text Key="EAD00D79">Cuddle While Watching Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="7D8AFDD6">Wait To Watch</Text>
  <Text Key="1748322A">Watch Current Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="4804E733">(From Watching a Boring Movie)</Text>
  <Text Key="69445648">Eclectic Dinette</Text>
  <Text Key="C4BC31F8">Boho Urbane Living</Text>
  <Text Key="2CE48826">Chic Flicks Houseplex</Text>
  <Text Key="BC0F1188">Watch an Action Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="96A40EB7">Diamonds Are For Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="56D50BA9">The Adventures of Spaceship Simulation</Text>
  <Text Key="CC67A7BF">Watch a Comedy Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="C75DB1BE">College Cram</Text>
  <Text Key="69785F3B">The Khlumzee Sisters</Text>
  <Text Key="6DBE7EC2">Watch a Family Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="ACC7AC7F">Lost Dog's Journey Home</Text>
  <Text Key="26016554">SuperKids: Cortex Catastrophe</Text>
  <Text Key="95C4C5A6">Watch a Horror Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="78D0B23D">Moonlight Massacre III</Text>
  <Text Key="2CC97CAD">Sims of the Dead</Text>
  <Text Key="CBDE06BD">Watch a Romance Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="78ED0716">Roaring Vice</Text>
  <Text Key="3C2C34E8">Simder</Text>
  <Text Key="C1E90278">Watch Movie With</Text>
  <Text Key="98CCD50F">Watch Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="233D6A5F">Grab Popcorn</Text>
  <Text Key="0D801362">Buy Popcorn Popper</Text>
  <Text Key="805C7C3A">Purchase a Popcorn Popper from Build Mode. Look for it in Kitchen Appliances.</Text>
  <Text Key="6CD8A5D2">Eat Popcorn</Text>
  <Text Key="8ADDC5AA">Use the Popcorn Popper to cook and then eat popcorn.</Text>
  <Text Key="D844B790">Watch a Movie</Text>
  <Text Key="54CE5B58">Click on a TV or Movie Screen and select a movie in the Watch Movie category.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C0D1DDE">{0.SimFirstName} has declared action movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches an action flick, {M0.he}{F0.she} is more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="98FF613A">{0.SimFirstName} has declared action movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches an action flick, {M0.he}{F0.she} is more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="F1FE41BE">{0.SimFirstName} has declared comedy movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches a comedy flick, {M0.he}{F0.she}'s more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="53716FED">{0.SimFirstName} has declared comedy movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches a comedy flick, {M0.he}{F0.she}'s more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="8BC70B03">{0.SimFirstName} has declared family movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches a family flick, {M0.he}{F0.she}'s more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="61074D48">{0.SimFirstName} has declared family movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches a family flick, {M0.he}{F0.she}'s more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="D8A1E295">{0.SimFirstName} has declared horror movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches a horror flick, {M0.he}{F0.she} is more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="1D0C751D">{0.SimFirstName} has declared horror movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches a horror flick, {M0.he}{F0.she} is more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="85311F72">{0.SimFirstName} has declared romance movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches a romance flick, {M0.he}{F0.she}'s more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E97E2AA">{0.SimFirstName} has declared romance movies to be {M0.his}{F0.her} favorite genre! Whenever {M0.he}{F0.she} watches a romance flick, {M0.he}{F0.she}'s more likely to enjoy the movie.</Text>
  <Text Key="842534F0">Favorite Movie Genre: Action</Text>
  <Text Key="71E3C47B">Favorite Movie Genre: Comedy</Text>
  <Text Key="6016B6BA">Favorite Movie Genre: Family</Text>
  <Text Key="7E2242BA">Favorite Movie Genre: Horror</Text>
  <Text Key="B152AC07">Favorite Movie Genre: Romance</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>