<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="45F1E969">Kiss the Cook</Text>
  <Text Key="50E09C0A">Backyard Allure</Text>
  <Text Key="54D12320">Ready to Mingle</Text>
  <Text Key="8D882AA7">Pop’s Secret Recipe</Text>
  <Text Key="03A4DB49">Patio Men</Text>
  <Text Key="F8D3FF5D">Backyard Chillaxing Trunks</Text>
  <Text Key="F50E6468">Originally entitled the Noisy Neighbor Slatted Fence, this refurbished version is just as effective at stating the product's intended purpose… keeping all bad neighbors out; no ifs, ands, or buts. If there's a neighbor you wish to bid adieu, put the Nosy Neighbor Fence to work for you.</Text>
  <Text Key="0489CF87">Nosy Neighbor Slatted Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="DE48FF08">What, were you expecting a rhinestone covered bar? No, this is where the suburban cowboy makes his stand. Rugged granite feels like home on the range, while elegant drink mixes tie you to the vibe of the city. With the Slabstone Cowboy Bar you're right in the middle, right here in suburbia.</Text>
  <Text Key="4DAE75A7">Slabstone Cowboy Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="CB662136">Welcome to the aughts. Take a (small) step back in time to deck out your backyard with these elegant island counter pieces. Some may try and convince you that quartz is the wave of the future, but these granite tops will always be de rigueur.</Text>
  <Text Key="A5AA8B69">Islands By The Aughts</Text>
  <Text Key="55125E6F">Welcome to the aughts. When choosing outdoor countertops, your priority should always be looks first, and durability second. Thankfully, a decade of design backs these granite counters, so buy with confidence!</Text>
  <Text Key="E3FCFFB6">Counters By The Aughts</Text>
  <Text Key="DC913B5C">Does separation truly make the heart grow fonder? Having regrets about installing the Nosy Neighbor Slatted Fence is perfectly normal. Resist temptation to start anew; add the Nosy Neighbor Gate to allow passage through.</Text>
  <Text Key="8A680633">Nosy Neighbor Gate</Text>
  <Text Key="F9FCDADE">Designed by veteran grill masters, the GrillZone doesn't just grill...it perfects. Enjoy immaculately charred veggies and meats on this state of the art cooking masterpiece. </Text>
  <Text Key="7840C2E1">GrillZone by GrillMania</Text>
  <Text Key="6881045F">This elegant hot tub was originally commissioned by the Center of Center Spa, and engineered by the fine scientists at FutureSim Labs. An unfortunate miscalculation resulted in a hot tub that was decidedly left of center, but this happy accident led to a promising scientific breakthrough in the field of time travel.</Text>
  <Text Key="827B0406">Left of Center Hot Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="758AB804">Mr. Prometheus Pringo loved the warmth of the sun on his skin. The feeling of steam creeping up to his chin. The knowledge that with time, the heat would prune his epidermis. That's why he loved hot tubs and devoted his millions to making a hot tub affordable to the every man or woman. Join Mr. Pringo metaphorically (unless you're the one with his body -- call us!) in this luxurious hot tub for all!</Text>
  <Text Key="B49644CB">Pringo's Heater Hot Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="C71D8221">This luminous light piece is looking for a king and queen to protect! Spruce up your party pad with this sheik floor light.</Text>
  <Text Key="D3FAE1D4">Immacu-light Knight</Text>
  <Text Key="06A7E1E6">A normal chess board has eight pawns on each side. Does this mean you should have eight of these at your next swanky party? You tell me.</Text>
  <Text Key="C50A87F9">Immacu-light Pawn</Text>
  <Text Key="E4324D30">This stylish floor light also doubles as a divider in case you want to break up that open space in your luxurious pad. Coincidentally, it's also shaped like the number 0.</Text>
  <Text Key="26BDA2DF">The Zero</Text>
  <Text Key="C8A1AB71">It's a little metal house for a candle! Isn't that adorable? Or maybe it's a cage, which is slightly less adorable. How you interpret this sleek table light is up to you.</Text>
  <Text Key="26FAA744">Candle's Crib</Text>
  <Text Key="639F1FFF">Bob is a green, chlorophyll, oxygen making tree. We don’t know what kind of tree. Management handed us this tree, said to sell it, and describe it to folks like you. We're not sure on the specifics. What do we look like, a botanicalist? </Text>
  <Text Key="D21D0926">Bob Tree</Text>
  <Text Key="A4D58069">A vase, No! Please, go kindly discipline yourself for thinking such foul thoughts. Good, that’s better. Now, we can continue. This, my uncultured reader, is a Vaaas! The perfectly crafted vessel with which to house the life of your precious oxygenating organism. Vaaas, because a vase is never ok.</Text>
  <Text Key="64C6DF4C">The Vaaas</Text>
  <Text Key="6246BAC7">You know Sgt. Peepers as the maker of quality surveillance equipment, all weather rain apparel, and now, all purpose privacy hedges. This All Purpose Privacy Hedge has been hand crafted to require little to no care, place easily, and is sure to keep your private moments private.</Text>
  <Text Key="84E69F7E">Sgt. Peepers All Purpose Privacy Hedge</Text>
  <Text Key="93E0D268">Sometimes the large size just doesn’t fit your needs, and that’s ok, Sgt. Peepers isn’t judging you. And they have created precisely what you need to meet your special needs with the All Purpose Privacy Hedge, junior edition.</Text>
  <Text Key="29F9B987">Sgt. Peepers All Purpose Privacy Hedge Junior</Text>
  <Text Key="95D2A403">Have you ever wondered about space, distance, the emptiness of it all? Have you ever talked with a child about it? Have you ever been to prison with a turkey? It’s all just so cyclical. Turkeys, space, emptiness, our children, and we’re all just lost in the center of it.</Text>
  <Text Key="EB1E1F52">Space Turkey</Text>
  <Text Key="28CE297D">When Kopernicus observed the stars, he was wowed by their luminescent presence, but utterly frustrated by their placement in the far heavens. Though he was never able to discover a solution, we at MetaLife have done so -- Floor Stars! Now, you can bring the heavens beneath your feet.</Text>
  <Text Key="11D547E8">Floor Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="A5938542">At MetaLife, we recognize that many attribute water with a well balanced, healthy life. Also, circles? Life is cyclical, and when paired with water, we have a fountain that pulses with H2O and all the vibes your water bill can handle.</Text>
  <Text Key="BD4BE23D">Vibe Gate Fountain</Text>
  <Text Key="50D92AF1">Can you see those tong, ta tong tong tongs? Whether you're grilling, thinking about grilling, or telling others you might be grilling, you can point out your luxurious, stainless steel Rack 'o Tongs!</Text>
  <Text Key="43E20DC4">Rack 'o Tongs</Text>
  <Text Key="CA02082A">Whether it's hickory honey, or Carolina mustard, or vinegar smoked, or honey with a hint of southern spice, or tongue scorching rib marinade, or just a dabble of tangy steak sauce, or even a smidge of ketchup with a kick, Sauce the Pig's Spread has the sauce that'll make your tongue jump out of your face and slap your momma!</Text>
  <Text Key="18FDB6B5">Sauce the Pig's Spread</Text>
  <Text Key="1EF86473">Life is a constantly evolving string of adjoining intersections. Sometimes you're coming, others you're going, and always, the world around you is moving. We at MetaLifa hope you take a moment to consider the depth of that statement, and think about buying Das Mesh.</Text>
  <Text Key="8FB103A2">Das Mesh</Text>
  <Text Key="37F5002C">Hillbillies and country folk may think they've cornered the market on stacks of logs about the home, but they ain't seen nothin'! Excuse us. Eh hem. The Log Roll starts from the humblest of beginnings (the woods, yech), but culiminates in a chic piece of haute coture that's sure to bring the best of the woods to your decor. </Text>
  <Text Key="41C73163">Log Roll</Text>
  <Text Key="EC69E87F">Many customers have complained that their posterior vents too much heat for most chairs. Therefore, to meet expectations, we've added vent slats to every stool. Burn off excess heat from those hot buns when sitting with The Slatted Perch!</Text>
  <Text Key="3A99FAA6">The Slatted Perch</Text>
  <Text Key="78E3A8AE">When an overheating behind gets in the way of a good meal, nobody wins. Well, now we've removed that issue from the rest of your life! Purchase the Slatted Perch - Dinner Edition, for all your seated food consumption tuccus heating needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="013F7C51">The Slatted Perch - Dinner Edition</Text>
  <Text Key="C3DF0648">Every backyard and porch deserves top notch snazz and pizzazz…Wickish Pizzazz that is! When earthen tones and boring patterns bring you down, toss in the double ZZ with a wicker shine to get back on track.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D1606E7">Wickish Pizzazz</Text>
  <Text Key="6F2D0997">Woah! This backyard ain't settling for 2 Zs. It ain't settling for 4 Zs. No, this Wickish party needs, nay, DEMANDS 3 Zs. The Grande Wickish Pizzzazzz - for when you need more wicker than you can stomach.</Text>
  <Text Key="FCD5C86E">Grande Wickish Pizzzazzz</Text>
  <Text Key="114385BE">Back in the days of yore, back when empires were toppled based on the predominance of wicker in one's patio, the first (and last) Wickish Ottoman Emperor proudly displayed this stylish, beautifully patterned piece of furniture with the same name in the patio.</Text>
  <Text Key="378BD641">Wickish Ottoman Emperor</Text>
  <Text Key="9C9F5C04">First, there was a wonderful Wicker chair. Totally reasonable. Then, our designers said no! There must be a loveseat. Woah! Put a Grande on that and add another Z. But then, someone clearly hallucinating shouted "there must be a sofa!" Therefore, the Super Grande.</Text>
  <Text Key="FFAAF0CB">Super Grande Wickish Pizzzazzz</Text>
  <Text Key="8F4E8FDA">This wall-mounted stereo is intended for use at community venues. Chillaxin' to the max on a deck'd out patio has never sounded so good! And that's great news, because these backyard jams never stop rolling.</Text>
  <Text Key="B2CBEF05">Venue Wall Speaker: Backyard</Text>
  <Text Key="0BF57619">It's easy to ignore the refined patio setting in favor of gaudi tables or garrish potted plants. Pah! Here at MetaLife, we think everything can and should be top tier. Let's table this discussion. Purchase the Patio Chic Table today.</Text>
  <Text Key="5193979C">Patio Chic Table</Text>
  <Text Key="EB3AF01C">Yarr! When pirates be missing thar ships an' they want a right good meal (and perhaps a cup o grog!), they rip apart thar ship and eat on thar patio on the Eat the Plank! Table. Or, if you don't buy this marketing nonsense, it's a perfectly fine patio table.</Text>
  <Text Key="C0034BF3">Eat the Plank! Table</Text>
  <Text Key="1AAE404F">Sometimes you want to go out back (or front,  if that's where your patio is) and eat under an Umbrella. Perhaps one with stripes? Bold stylish colors? Eh? Yeah, that's what we have for you. Take this umbrella or don't. Actually, please take it! We're sorry.</Text>
  <Text Key="CA480116">Passive Aggressive Umbrella Table</Text>
  <Text Key="4B69FC57">Listen to Backyard</Text>
  <Text Key="1A0FAA0C">Backyard Confine</Text>
  <Text Key="656A3593">Backyard</Text>
  <Text Key="737D85A4">Buy a Hot Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="B937A8B4">Purchase a Hot Tub from Build Mode. Look for it in Outdoor Activities</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>