<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="FB822982">(From Eating Wolfsbane)</Text>
  <Text Key="20F8725E">Now that I'm done, want to hang out?</Text>
  <Text Key="63F05BCB">Werewolf Mentorship Unlocked!</Text>
  <Text Key="B2CB4772">{0.SimFirstName} can now offer enhanced guidance to other Werewolves.</Text>
  <Text Key="BF41CECD">(From Being Mentored by a Veteran Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="20C15A4F">{0.SimFirstName} scared {1.SimFirstName} so bad {M1.he}{F1.she} dropped {M1.his}{F1.her} wallet! Nice!</Text>
  <Text Key="ABAB663C">(From Being Screamed at by a Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="3CEE93DF">Lunar Epiphany Unlocked!</Text>
  <Text Key="528BCBBB">{0.SimFirstName} can now start to decipher the strange markings found in the margins of Werewolf books. What new knowledge is out there waiting to be discovered?</Text>
  <Text Key="37770A2A">(From Marking Territory Near Other Sims)</Text>
  <Text Key="E9C51FAB">{0.SimFirstName} learned how to calm other Werewolves on the brink of rampage. </Text>
  <Text Key="B7B8474F">Pacify Unlocked!</Text>
  <Text Key="09FD711F">(From Smelling Someone With a Very Special Scent)</Text>
  <Text Key="408473DA">Werewolf Diplomacy Unlocked!</Text>
  <Text Key="47FBBE85">{0.SimFirstName} successfully convinced someone that Werewolves aren't so bad after all.</Text>
  <Text Key="836D37E7">Werewolf Menace Unlocked!</Text>
  <Text Key="E3A7C096">Wow, {0.SimFirstName} was a real bully! {F0.She}{M0.He} has learned to revel in scaring other Sims and no longer feels guilty about it. </Text>
  <Text Key="45D243F5">{0.SimFirstName} has grown into a full-fledged Werewolf! {M0.He}{F0.She} has gained a Temperament and now has to maintain Fury! {M0.He}{F0.She} can also now seek out a pack, learn abilities, and partake in Werewolf life. </Text>
  <Text Key="434780DC">(From Winning a Fight With a Sibling)</Text>
  <Text Key="BC7084BB">{0.SimFirstName} has had enough of {F0.her}{M0.his} life as a werewolf and has decided to seek a cure!</Text>
  <Text Key="3EFFBBA7">{0.SimFirstName} has also gained the Werewolf Ally trait due to {F0.her}{M0.his} past experience as a Werewolf!</Text>
  <Text Key="34888004">A pack would only hold {F0.her}{M0.him} back! {0.SimFirstName} has decided to become a Lone Wolf.</Text>
  <Text Key="0D0DB9FA">Calm, cool, and collective! {0.SimFirstName} has chosen to pursue membership with the Moonwood Collective.</Text>
  <Text Key="8900E193">{F0.She}{M0.He} don't give a fang 'bout {F0.her}{M0.his} reputation! {0.SimFirstName} has chosen to pursue membership with the Wildfangs.</Text>
  <Text Key="3E2F447B">(From Drinking Werewolf Plasma)</Text>
  <Text Key="2EA16401">Has {0.SimFirstName} found {M0.his}{F0.her} Fated Werewolf Mate? Every Werewolf has one true love destined by the moon.</Text>
  <Text Key="E9205654">(From Fighting Rival Pack)</Text>
  <Text Key="511ED5A4">{0.SimName} has made it through the Full Moon! What a harrowing experience! Hopefully {F0.she}{M0.he} learned a thing or two about being a Werewolf. </Text>
  <Text Key="6056B637">{0.SimFirstName} has returned with some fresh meat {M0.he}{F0.she}... &lt;i&gt;found&lt;/i&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="A7B44463">(From Going on a Hunt)</Text>
  <Text Key="56762313">Like the description on the back of the book suggested, {0.SimFirstName} is definitely being challenged about {M0.his}{F0.her} preconceived notions on Werewolves. And who knew Werewolves and dogs were so close? From now on, {M0.he}{F0.she} isn't going to be quite so afraid of Werewolves when they're just doing their thing.</Text>
  <Text Key="75E60FEC">There might be more to discover if {0.SimFirstName} gives this book another read...</Text>
  <Text Key="D6A175BD">\n&lt;i&gt;{0.SimFirstName} learned how to make the Wolf-B-Gone cure.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="0E23B70F">&lt;i&gt;This particular entry appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nJohn and Maria are interested in a cure. Not for themselves, they'll be quick to tell you, but for others who might not wish this curse upon themselves or their loved ones. We've been researching as a group and theorize that a mixture of Wolfsbane and Moonpetal might do the trick. The problem is the rarity of Moonpetal makes experimentation slow and failure discouraging.\n\nI'll admit only here, dear unknown reader, I have considered taking the cure. It would allow me more time with Avelina. And yet! We would lose access to our bond, for she is my fated mate. What would become of that connection were I to transform back and never be beast again? There must be another way.</Text>
  <Text Key="B917B39F">&lt;i&gt;This particular page appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nBeing a Werewolf isn't for everyone. If you're at your wit's end, and the only transformation you want is one back into a non-Were-Sim, you can always seek out the cure. Many Werewolves over the years have speculated that a combination of Wolfsbane and something touched by the original magic that caused the first transformations might do the trick. Perhaps the elusive Moonpetal flower?</Text>
  <Text Key="F276BCE1">&lt;i&gt;This particular page appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nNon-Werewolf Sims seeking occults and answers have visited the town for decades, and even more come looking for a "cure" to the Werewolf curse. Moonwood Mill might, in fact, be the singular location one of the cure ingredients may be acquired: Moonpetal. When mixed with Wolfsbane the effects are quite potent and have been known to remove the curse upon consumption.</Text>
  <Text Key="7B7B587F">&lt;i&gt;This particular article appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;b&gt;Your Cure.&lt;/b&gt;\n\nReal talk: It's not easy being a Werewolf. While some learn to love their inner wolf, others detest that inevitable lack of control. Thankfully, there are a lot of helpful options available if you're dreading your next transformation.\n\nThere's a wide array of abilities a Werewolf can master over time: Lunar Resistance, Transformation Mastery, Somber Howl, and even the Will to Resist. All of these can help with your fury control and help with timing your transformations. Plus, it never hurts to have a friend with Werewolf Empathy.\n\nIf you still find yourself wanting to live a non-were-life, then there are more options available. The original Mooncasters developed a cure using a mixture of Wolfsbane and Moonpetal - though the latter can only be acquired in Moonwood Mill during a Full Moon. </Text>
  <Text Key="57261973">\n&lt;i&gt;{0.SimFirstName} learned how to make Grilled Luna Fish.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="1844B089">&lt;i&gt;This particular entry appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nToday, Avelina and I discovered that some of the fish in Moonwood's lake had been changed by the overload - the very same one that caused our transformations. She was so proud to name the new species: the Luna Fish. We celebrated with a fish roast. I do believe some sort of magical energy still persists within them. I felt energized, with my body feeling younger than it has for quite some time as I moved throughout the town. Remarkable, truly.</Text>
  <Text Key="6CCF43F9">&lt;i&gt;This particular page appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nWerewolves love to brawl. If you're commonly seen as the runt of the pack, try snacking on some Grilled Luna Fish before a workout. It's guaranteed to boost your fitness regimen and keep you energized longer.</Text>
  <Text Key="9B06A845">&lt;i&gt;This particular page appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nRecords show that the Luna fish originated from the crescent lake beneath Moonwood Mill's overlook, also known as the howling point.\n\nThe fish itself is infused with moon energy, hence its name. This magical species of fish was created in a Spellcasting overload during an untamed mooncasting ritual.\n\nThose who eat the Luna Fish attain some of this fish's raw energy. It's said to increase athleticism and sate your needs. </Text>
  <Text Key="D5903D62">&lt;i&gt;This particular article appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;b&gt;Grilled Luna Fish Recipe: Make it tonight!&lt;/b&gt;\n\nThis savory dish will give you the athletic rush you need to keep up with your pack! Plus, who doesn't require a little self-care to ensure their needs are met?\n\nIngredients:\n• 1 Luna Fish - That's it!\n\nInstructions:\n• Toast that delicious Luna fish over the open flame. Serve among friends, and make it a night with the pack!</Text>
  <Text Key="141097C1">\n&lt;i&gt;{0.SimFirstName} learned how to make Moonpetal Punch.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="FA35ABBE">&lt;i&gt;This particular entry appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nI've been grasping at new methods to aid in retaining control of these transformations. They have kept me away from Avelina too often, leaving her alone day after day while I rampage in the wilds. Without me there, I know that she gets easily distracted by her work. One of my more recent attempts involved mixing the Moonpetal flower into a hot drink. Though the effects on my fury were negligible, I did find that it helped ease my moodiness to some extent. I must keep searching.</Text>
  <Text Key="A86599C5">&lt;i&gt;This particular page appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nBeing a Werewolf can be very emotionally taxing. A great solution: Moonpetal Punch! Made from the rare Moonpetal flower, Moonpetal Punch can lessen negative emotions and bring you some peace.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C2A17B8">&lt;i&gt;This particular page appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nAs it turns out, Moonwood Mill is the only location in which to find Moonpetal. This species of flora was created in a Spellcasting overload during an untamed mooncasting ritual. Evidence of similar plant cultivation has not been reported elsewhere around the world to this day. When ground to a powder and mixed with liquid, it is said to ease a Sim's humors and improve the mood. </Text>
  <Text Key="2F7419D6">&lt;i&gt;This particular article appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;b&gt;So, is feeling emotional normal?&lt;/b&gt;\n\nLet's be real: It's &lt;i&gt;completely&lt;/i&gt; normal for a Werewolf to burst into an uncontrollable lycanthrope-induced rage every time the full moon rises! In fact, Werewolves are acutely emotional creatures. It's the moon magic!\n\nIt won't stop transformations, but experts recommend that if you need a reprieve from your mood you try a Moonpetal-infused drink. </Text>
  <Text Key="EC0CA9B1">&lt;i&gt;This particular page appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nThose who have explored the tunnels beneath Moonwood Mill whisper of a magical chamber that depicts the town's secret past. A reward awaits those who sing the moon's song. Many have tried to find such a place and returned disappointed. </Text>
  <Text Key="34A206BC">\n&lt;i&gt;{0.SimFirstName} learned a secret about the mysterious room in the Moonwood Mill tunnel system. {M0.He}{F0.She} should go check out the local tunnels for answers.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="5A0A914E">&lt;i&gt;This particular entry appears to have a shimmering enchantment overtop that {0.SimFirstName} is able to read through.&lt;/i&gt;\n\nAt the end of the Century Conflict, the remaining Werewolves scattered throughout the world. The Volkovs remained in Moonwood Mill. On one of my visits, I discovered a chamber below ground that tells the Werewolf origin story. John and Maria Volkov must have asked a Spellcaster to come and infuse it with moon magic. Whoever sings the moon's song as a show of respect will be rewarded. Sentimental to the last.</Text>
  <Text Key="B37943C5">(From Having a Moon Dream)</Text>
  <Text Key="AE1C92FD">(From Drinking Moonpetal Punch)</Text>
  <Text Key="1C2CF9A2">(From Being a Small Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="42112A74">Transformation Mastery Unlocked!</Text>
  <Text Key="3C39C8C9">{0.SimFirstName} has learned how to transform at will!</Text>
  <Text Key="263E835D">(From a First Time Transformation)</Text>
  <Text Key="6A8F92DE">(From Recovering After a Werewolf Rampage)</Text>
  <Text Key="3CAE54B9">(From Werewolf Temperaments)</Text>
  <Text Key="3B69E897">(From an Excessive Amount of Fury)</Text>
  <Text Key="2E4980E8">(From Going to Work)</Text>
  <Text Key="8A1A4EF2">(From the Carnivore Temperament)</Text>
  <Text Key="5E2DC322">Um, no thank you. I don't want to be a Werewolf right now, but I might change my mind if I knew you better.</Text>
  <Text Key="195B2921">I would love to be a Werewolf! Thanks for asking. Can you please turn me?</Text>
  <Text Key="C026986D">I was hesitant at first, but I think I'm ready to be a Werewolf! Let's do this.</Text>
  <Text Key="B5519C01">(From Disgusting Drink)</Text>
  <Text Key="73529991">(From Being Bitten by a Werewolf) </Text>
  <Text Key="88C361D7">Ouch! {0.SimFirstName} got bitten and contracted Werebies. Is this the first step towards becoming a Werewolf?  Best ask around Moonwood Mill to see if anyone knows how to cure it before it gets worse! </Text>
  <Text Key="878064FC">{0.SimFirstName} has been cured of Werebies! Try to be more careful next time or things might get a little hairy...</Text>
  <Text Key="B0960173">(From Successfully Treating Werebies) </Text>
  <Text Key="F3CE0837">(From Taking Wolf-B-Gone)</Text>
  <Text Key="D43AD50D">Relations between the Moonwood Collective and Wildfangs have become neutral, neither alliance nor feud.\nWhich way will they swing next? Only time will tell...</Text>
  <Text Key="C1D9DF68">Hooray! An alliance has formed between the Moonwood Collective and Wildfangs!</Text>
  <Text Key="7B84F8D2">Uh oh... a feud has started between the Moonwood Collective and the Wildfangs!</Text>
  <Text Key="1146694D">Fine, I'll admit that sometimes it can be a bit &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; when one of my packmates goes on a couch-devouring and computer smashing spree in the local library. I get it, ok? Not something you'd expect to see every day unless you lived it. We can't help it, though! It's just part of this crazy life we lead.\n\nBut I gotta say, something kinda surprisingly tasty about certain kinds of wood...</Text>
  <Text Key="0B0CBB10">You didn't hear it from me, {0.SimFirstName}, but I heard both packs have pretty sweet perks at each rank. Picture this: delicious snacks, delivered to you weekly. And that's just part of the entry-level reward for Omega ranks. Dude, are you kidding me? Ugh... I need to at least look into joining one.</Text>
  <Text Key="3B5BA89A">Pack drama? Not really my style. The way I see it, BOTH sides have issues. All that sanctimonious chatter at the Collective...and those Wildfangs always have to be the main character don't they?</Text>
  <Text Key="1DA615F0">Oh, I'm not in a pack... for now. I'm not sure which one is more my speed. I mean, it's either I put in all that effort to control my Werewolf powers, or I confront the world as a proud, unapologetic Werewolf. Either way, it's challenging to succeed. I'm not sure if I'm cut out for that yet. </Text>
  <Text Key="08AC3DFD">Yeah, I know about the Moonwood Mill packs. Can't really say it's my scene, but they play important roles. The Moonwood Collective set the standard for improving the public image of us Werewolves, and the Wildfangs... well, at least they spread the word about us. Hard to imagine what the Werewolf world would look like today without them.</Text>
  <Text Key="C977F1C5">Me? Join a pack? Nah, not right now. I'm good on my own. I don't need some Alpha know-it-all telling me how to live my life, wagging their claw at me if I lose my temper, or don't workout enough, or whatever they all do.\n\nI gotta admit though... every time I've visited Moonwood Mill, those pack members do look pretty cool, all leaned up against their hangouts like that... I'd consider joining just for that.</Text>
  <Text Key="3B4F2637">Ahh, it sounds so fun, right? Moving to Moonwood Mill, joining the Wildfangs, working out together, exploring the world! Maybe one day I'll pack up, head over, and figure out how to join them... once I figure out how to impress them, obviously.</Text>
  <Text Key="A6FA0CB7">Don't you dare let The Moonwood Collective make you feel guilty for going on a rampage around town, {0.SimFirstName}. That's just the moon's gift to you, really. It's &lt;i&gt;efficiency&lt;/i&gt;. Think of all the places you can gallop off to and see with all that Fury channeling through you! The possibilities are endless, why would we try to limit them?</Text>
  <Text Key="A26C0755">You might not know this, but it takes a whole heck of a lot of self-control for a Werewolf to make sure they're respecting the space and comfort of others, especially on certain nights when the moon's allure is just too strong. Admittedly, there are those among us that are... &lt;i&gt;not quite as diligent&lt;/i&gt; when it comes to exercising restraint.\n\nAnd yes, I'm talking about the Wildfangs. Obviously.</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE1BB03">Hopefully your experiences with Werewolves have been positive overall, {0.SimFirstName}, especially the members of my pack. I'd hate to hear that someone in the Collective was being a nuisance. It goes against our pack beliefs.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C34B11B">I run a tight ship, {0.SimFirstName}. When someone is a member of The Moonwood Collective, it should be obvious to &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; Sim, from their actions and how they carry themselves.\n\nThe Wildfangs might have the edge on us when it comes to reach, but they can't match our deep understanding of Werewolf nature and history. Our track record as good citizens of Moonwood Mill speaks for itself.</Text>
  <Text Key="3A59E837">{0.SimFirstName}'s Leadership is Under Scrutiny! Everyone knows {F0.she}{M0.he} hasn’t been the best representative lately, failing to set a good example of the pack's values. The pack is starting to question if {F0.she}{M0.he} &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; deserves to be in charge.\n\n{0.SimFirstName} must resolve all current warnings on pack values if {F0.she}{M0.he} wants to secure {F0.her}{M0.his} position as leader. Check the Werewolf Packs Panel for more information on which pack values {F0.she}{M0.he} needs to address.</Text>
  <Text Key="4CCE63CF">{0.SimFirstName} is on Pack Probation! It's become clear to the leader that warnings alone aren’t enough to keep {F0.her}{M0.him} in line with the pack’s values.\n\n{0.SimFirstName} must resolve all current value warnings if {F0.she}{M0.he} wants to avoid further discipline. Check the Werewolf Packs Panel to see which pack values {F0.she}{M0.he} needs to address. </Text>
  <Text Key="8F10C11D">{1.SimName} has requested that {0.SimFirstName} report to for {F1.her}{M1.him} for disciplinary action. It's best not to keep {F1.her}{M1.him} waiting.</Text>
  <Text Key="37BE921D">Have you checked in with {1.SimFirstName} yet? I heard there’s something you two have to talk about.</Text>
  <Text Key="20390766">Hey, {0.SimFirstName}. You should probably check in with {1.SimFirstName}... I think it’s something important.</Text>
  <Text Key="DF25D69C">We need to talk, {0.SimFirstName}. Report to me when you have a moment.</Text>
  <Text Key="7042CBB2">While you’re here, I need to discuss something with you. Not as your friend, but as your leader. Please report to me when you’re ready.</Text>
  <Text Key="3B27A3EC">The pack has noticed that {0.SimFirstName} hasn't been adequately demonstrating &lt;b&gt;Diplomacy&lt;/b&gt;. If this behavior continues, or {F0.she}{M0.he} receives additional warnings for other pack values, {0.SimFirstName} will be put on Pack Probation.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips for practicing &lt;b&gt;Diplomacy&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="D4182BB9">Moonwood Collective: Notice</Text>
  <Text Key="2710855E">Despite {F0.her}{M0.his} position, {0.SimFirstName} hasn’t demonstrated enough &lt;b&gt;Diplomacy&lt;/b&gt; lately. If this behavior continues, {F0.her}{M0.his} leadership may come under scrutiny.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips for practicing &lt;b&gt;Diplomacy&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="EB85A589">The pack has noticed that {0.SimFirstName} hasn't been adequately fulfilling the &lt;b&gt;Expand and Explore&lt;/b&gt; value. If this behavior continues, or {F0.she}{M0.he} receives additional warnings for other pack values, {0.SimFirstName} will be put on Pack Probation.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips to effectively &lt;b&gt;Expand and Explore&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="329CEAAF">Wildfangs: Notice</Text>
  <Text Key="A921D781">Despite {F0.her}{M0.his} position, {0.SimFirstName} hasn’t been adequately fulfilling the &lt;b&gt;Expand and Explore&lt;/b&gt; value lately. If this behavior continues, {F0.her}{M0.his} leadership may come under scrutiny.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips to effectively &lt;b&gt;Expand and Explore&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="5DC90118">The pack has noticed that {0.SimFirstName} hasn't been adequately demonstrating &lt;b&gt;Pack Participation&lt;/b&gt;. If this behavior continues, or {F0.she}{M0.he} receives additional warnings for other pack values, {0.SimFirstName} will be put on Pack Probation.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips for maintaining &lt;b&gt;Pack Participation&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="449C3B20">Despite {F0.her}{M0.his} position, {0.SimFirstName} hasn’t maintained enough &lt;b&gt;Pack Participation&lt;/b&gt; lately. If this behavior continues, {F0.her}{M0.his} leadership may come under scrutiny.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips for maintaining &lt;b&gt;Pack Participation&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="931A005B">The pack has noticed that {0.SimFirstName} hasn't been adequately demonstrating &lt;b&gt;Self-Improvement&lt;/b&gt;. If this behavior continues, or {F0.she}{M0.he} receives additional warnings for other pack values, {0.SimFirstName} will be put on Pack Probation.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips for working towards &lt;b&gt;Self-Improvement&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="839EF7BD">Despite {F0.her}{M0.his} position, {0.SimFirstName} hasn’t been demonstrating enough &lt;b&gt;Self-Improvement&lt;/b&gt; lately. If this behavior continues, {F0.her}{M0.his} leadership may come under scrutiny.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips for working towards &lt;b&gt;Self-Improvement&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="F0CAFEFA">The pack has noticed that {0.SimFirstName} hasn't been adequately demonstrating &lt;b&gt;Self-Sufficiency&lt;/b&gt;. If this behavior continues, or {F0.she}{M0.he} receives additional warnings for other pack values, {0.SimFirstName} will be put on Pack Probation.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips for maintaining &lt;b&gt;Self-Sufficiency&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="2BD4097B">Despite {F0.her}{M0.his} position, {0.SimFirstName} hasn’t maintained enough &lt;b&gt;Self-Sufficiency&lt;/b&gt; lately. If this behavior continues, {F0.her}{M0.his} leadership may come under scrutiny.\n\nThe Werewolf Packs panel contains helpful tips for maintaining &lt;b&gt;Self-Sufficiency&lt;/b&gt;, which can point {0.SimFirstName} in the right direction!</Text>
  <Text Key="81A6E495">Pack Leader</Text>
  <Text Key="5E462F3B">The Pack Leader is the only Alpha-rank in their pack. Wielding the power to command, discipline, and remove pack members, they are expected to set the standard for upholding their pack's values.</Text>
  <Text Key="61772CB0">The Moonwood Collective is a dignified group of Werewolves, whose mission embodies the union of lycanthropy and philanthropy.\n\nMembers are expected to be tactful, prudent, and diplomatic. They seek to make meaningful connections with &lt;b&gt;all&lt;/b&gt; Sims. This includes mastering Fury control to become more approachable and friendly to non-Werewolves.</Text>
  <Text Key="958A9F3E">The Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="D566DB26">\nPack leadership is currently in transition.</Text>
  <Text Key="E79FE191">The Wildfangs are a scrappy, free-spirited group of Werewolves. They believe the Werewolf lifestyle is the ultimate gift, and they're going to make the most of it.\n\nThe world is The Wildfangs' playground. While exploring the vast world to expand the pack's influence, members are also expected to commit to ongoing self-improvement, aiming to become the best Werewolf possible.</Text>
  <Text Key="E6032D83">The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="7E9D1885">Sounds great! I'm in.</Text>
  <Text Key="E6ACFCB4">Nevermind...</Text>
  <Text Key="09018A7F">Hmm? You know where to find us if you change your mind...</Text>
  <Text Key="6CFD894E">Before we continue, keep in mind what we stand for at the Moonwood Collective. First, each and every one of us must foster a good community within the pack, and help out the group. Second, we must serve as effective ambassadors of Werewolves to all, representing our kind with dignity. And third, we're all expected to provide for the pack as an investment in its future, which includes growing our own food (and avoiding munching on couches in public!)</Text>
  <Text Key="2F19937D">Before you join, remember that the Wildfangs stand for embracing &lt;b&gt;all&lt;/b&gt; aspects of Werewolf life. We value three things the most. First, no lazy packmates! You'll actually have to contribute to the pack and help out. Second, stay on that grind. You've gotta &lt;i&gt;work&lt;/i&gt; to improve yourself as a Werewolf. And third, we don't keep our talents limited to Moonwood Mill. You'll need to get out there, expand your horizons, and maximize our impact everywhere!</Text>
  <Text Key="B69A7475">{0.SimFirstName}, I understand your decision, but I wish you gave us a heads up before taking the cure. You can't be the Moonwood Collective's leader as you are now. I'll spread the word that you've stepped down...</Text>
  <Text Key="07394EEF">Wait a sec. You... you're not a Werewolf anymore? That's not something you should just spring on the pack, {0.SimFirstName}. I think I speak for everyone when I say you have to step down. The Wildfangs will figure ourselves out from here.</Text>
  <Text Key="7769DB8C">I see. Would you mind telling me why you want to leave?</Text>
  <Text Key="7AFDE84E">Pack life just isn't for me.</Text>
  <Text Key="A95BE32A">...</Text>
  <Text Key="690BF4F5">This pack sucks and you stink!</Text>
  <Text Key="23FC0396">I'm going to take the cure.</Text>
  <Text Key="85829585">I changed my mind! I don't want to leave.</Text>
  <Text Key="D925F3BB">Nice! {0.SimFirstName} just received the following packmate gift from {1.SimFirstName}:\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="F7089076">I think it's time you met your match, {0.SimFirstName}. I challenge you for the rank of Alpha! May the best Werewolf win.</Text>
  <Text Key="E451E1FD">(From Pack Demotion)</Text>
  <Text Key="6197A806">(From Pack Promotion)</Text>
  <Text Key="E55CD557">With the way {0.SimFirstName} has been acting, {F0.she}{M0.he} is starting to betray the Moonwood Collective's trust! If {F0.she}{M0.he} continues this behavior, {0.SimFirstName} could lose {F0.her}{M0.his} status as a Friend of the Moonwood Collective.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F6690EA">With the way {0.SimFirstName} has been acting, {F0.she}{M0.he} is starting to betray the Wildfangs' trust! If {F0.she}{M0.he} continues this behavior, {0.SimFirstName} could lose {F0.her}{M0.his} status as a Friend of the Wildfangs.</Text>
  <Text Key="0851CEFE">(From Upholding Pack Values)</Text>
  <Text Key="2BB9C8CE">(From Being Disciplined)</Text>
  <Text Key="285B83F4">(From Becoming an Apex Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="A66CB355">{0.SimFirstName} found something in the Underground!\n\nItems Received: \n{1.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="2FB21BBD">(From Exploring the Underground)</Text>
  <Text Key="FCE2E2D5">The Grimtooth Bar stocks a lot of meat. You can imagine why... </Text>
  <Text Key="EA6C0068">Why move to Moonwood Mill? I'm not sure if you can tell but I've been obsessed with Werewolves ever since I was a kid, and I figured out that there were Werewolves actually living here!</Text>
  <Text Key="4C26D411">When I was a kid I had ridiculously long hair. As a teen, I really went wild experimenting with it. I've had perms, highlights, lowlights...  I got really good at dying hair. Sometimes I try and talk the Werewolves in town into letting me dye their fur. It's a very different texture, but I've become an expert at the art. Honestly, the hard part is getting them to stay still...</Text>
  <Text Key="43639132">I &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; WE'RE Living Magazine! I've been reading it since I was a teen. I figured out who its audience &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; was, and that kickstarted my journey to Moonwood Mill!</Text>
  <Text Key="76F78144">My favorite book genre is romance and my favorite books are always about Werewolves, so obviously, my two favorite books are "The Wolf Next Door" and "Packs and Prejudice." And between you and me... &lt;i&gt;I've met the author&lt;/i&gt;!</Text>
  <Text Key="22ED656E">It's not that I've always wanted to run a bar, per se. But opening the Grimtooth Bar felt like a great way for me to be part of this town, get close with the locals, and still keep some distance from the hairier nature of it all. After my run-in with Greg, it seemed like a good compromise.</Text>
  <Text Key="6E097125">Take my advice, stay away from Greg. He isn't like the other Werewolves around here. He's dangerous. They put those signs up for a reason. The other Werewolves don't even like him. </Text>
  <Text Key="DD2419CF">I don't know how Jacob is a Vegetarian and a Werewolf. It's an odd mixture.</Text>
  <Text Key="56984805">Going on that midnight walk in the woods with Lou started off romantic, but when we saw Greg's warning signs I wanted to turn back. Of course, he &lt;i&gt;just had&lt;/i&gt; to show off instead. It didn't turn out great for either one of us. I still don't like thinking about that night.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA4BC98A">Sometimes I wonder if I turned into a Werewolf if I'd have a fated mate... I certainly think it'd be romantic!</Text>
  <Text Key="419C11C9">After I got bit, I contracted Werebies and I knew I didn't have long before I turned. Kristopher knew I wasn't ready and directed me towards a remedy. It wasn't too hard to concoct, and I now have some on hand at the bar at all times. I want to help others who find themselves in a similar state.</Text>
  <Text Key="A1C3A509">I wouldn't want to go back to my life before Moonwood Mill. It was too... &lt;i&gt;normal&lt;/i&gt;. I've spent my entire life dreaming about Werewolves and the occult. To go back would be turning my back on a dream.</Text>
  <Text Key="12F91B58">I know the remedy for Werebies, but I don't know the cure for lycanthropy. There's a difference. Kristopher taught me that Werebies is much easier to undo. I've heard hints that a cure is out there and it uses the rare Moonpetal flower plus other secret ingredients. I bet someone wrote it down in a book somewhere. </Text>
  <Text Key="375095C7">I consider becoming a Werewolf all the time. Cursed by magic, a creature of the night, a fated mate. It's all incredibly romantic! But then I think about Greg and how terrifying his lack of control was...</Text>
  <Text Key="C479FBF1">I feel mostly safe in Moonwood Mill, but the full moon can be an intense time. Most Werewolves around here seek to control their abilities in one way or another, but Kristopher told me that the moon is even more powerful than he is.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C0D4118">The locals say Moonpetal is a magical flower that first bloomed from a surge of moon magic. Whether that's true or not, it does only bloom during the Full Moon. If you want to harvest it, you better find it now. </Text>
  <Text Key="018F5B8F">Strange things happen in Moonwood Mill during a full moon. It's one of the best times to explore. It's also somewhat dangerous to be out and about. </Text>
  <Text Key="2458913A">If you moongaze before heading to bed, they say the moon will grant you a special dream. </Text>
  <Text Key="08180882">Catching a Luna Fish is rare. If you do, however, there are some great benefits from grilling it up and eating it. You'll gain moon-infused natural energy, and you'll increase your athletic prowess tenfold.</Text>
  <Text Key="B2CD052A">You can't see as far into space with a small telescope. To really see the galaxy, you'll need a larger one. Some of the best Moon Prints come from the big, fancy telescopes. </Text>
  <Text Key="9954E281">Locals know the tunnels beneath Moonwood Mill as "the Underground." It's been called that for as long as anyone can remember. </Text>
  <Text Key="D8A6E3C7">The rare Luna Fish is only found in Lake Lunvik. I hear it's even more active during a full moon. If you want to catch it, you'd better fish now!</Text>
  <Text Key="0DEBC493">They say that during a New, First Quarter, Full, or Third Quarter Moon you'll become better at fishing. Fishing is such a superstitious hobby!</Text>
  <Text Key="D41662E3">Does anyone really know what the moon is made of? It &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; be cheese! Why are we discounting cheese?</Text>
  <Text Key="FB8312F6">Anyone can moonbathe, but the effects are particularly potent for those who have the magical moon curse in their veins. </Text>
  <Text Key="B38027B4">I always love how the night sky seems brighter during the full moon. It's romantic, really. </Text>
  <Text Key="25F4F732">I'm not sure how the lunar statue in Moonwood Mill stays in sync with the moon. Maybe it's magic, or maybe someone is much more mechanically savvy than I am!</Text>
  <Text Key="1CCB1D26">It's always the darkest out during the New Moon. I can't count how many times in the past I've stubbed my toe on something in the dark. </Text>
  <Text Key="F7EBA75A">Greg is dangerous, but he's particularly dangerous during a full moon. I'd stay away tonight if I were you. </Text>
  <Text Key="20CFA9B1">I feel like I grow as a Werewolf during the Full Moon. Everything I do makes me a better Werewolf for some reason.</Text>
  <Text Key="DBCFB701">A werewolf never forgets a first kiss under the full moon. It's a singularly magical and romantic moment.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0AFB9BE">As a Werewolf, the Waxing Gibbous Moon phase is always interesting. You can inherently tell the full moon is coming, and that surge makes it so that you're a much better fighter. I love sparring during the Waxing Gibbous.</Text>
  <Text Key="AD88ECB2">If you get bitten by a Werewolf, you can always acquire the remedy and stop the infection before you turn. They sell it over at the bar. It happens more than you'd think. </Text>
  <Text Key="F0A9DF1F">The makeup of Werewolf blood in the child of two Werewolf parents can fluctuate. Sometimes a child's lunar connections are stronger than another werewolf child's. They'll be more naturally gifted as a Werewolf, but that doesn't mean others can't attain the same level of skill. Other times, a child's werewolf affinity might be seem to be missing entirely.</Text>
  <Text Key="7C722005">Werewolves don't have their first transformation until their teenage years. It's an exciting but painful experience. </Text>
  <Text Key="FB39A192">Every Werewolf knows that their fury builds faster during a Full Moon. Some Werewolves have learned to control that, but it isn't an easy ability to master. </Text>
  <Text Key="BE5462FC">Fury for a Werewolf feels different depending on how much it's built up...it's always there in the back of your mind, but sometimes it can become the only thing you can think about. </Text>
  <Text Key="5E5FFC17">I always feel the most handy during the Waning Gibbous moon. Come to think of it, most Werewolves are particularly handy during that phase. Huh.</Text>
  <Text Key="62F69DE4">Not every Werewolf is cut out to be an Alpha. You have to be a good representative of your pack's values. And you have to be able to challenge the current Alpha—which is never an easy feat. Rank won't matter at that point, just your ability to win the challenge.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE2EA4DA">Howling is the moon's song. Dogs know this. In fact, the first spellcasters learned this magic from their canine familiars.</Text>
  <Text Key="7F8BFBF5">Your personality as a Sim affects your temperament as a Werewolf. We're like anyone else... just a little more extreme. That's not always a bad thing!</Text>
  <Text Key="DC3AEF46">Between Spellcasters, Werewolves, and Vampires, Spellcasters are the eldest group. Vampires and Werewolves originated from them.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB946DB0">PowerSip MIDNIGHT is a great way to build your fury if you're wanting to transform.</Text>
  <Text Key="C5ACA819">During the First and Third Quarter Moon phases, I feel like my relationships always really improve or go downhill much more quickly. I've only noticed that happening for Werewolves, though. I wonder if there's something to it?</Text>
  <Text Key="DBBF23F2">It can be pretty scary for a non-were Sim to see a Werewolf transform. It can really affect our relationship with them.</Text>
  <Text Key="7FD1D711">Werewolves are physical creatures—even our young. A Werewolf toddler may not have a beast form, but they always excel when learning new motor skills. </Text>
  <Text Key="E6470A99">All Werewolves gain some special abilities that they normally wouldn't have during the Full Moon.</Text>
  <Text Key="DF8F2B29">They say there might be a cure, but if there is... I imagine it will be difficult to create. You'd probably need to do some investigation to learn the right combination of ingredients. </Text>
  <Text Key="9D75E3D2">The moon doesn't just affect Werewolves. During a full moon, Mermaids can stay out of the water longer, Vampires gain power slower, and Spellcasters are more successful with their spells.</Text>
  <Text Key="94B42609">The tunnels under Moonwood are difficult to navigate in the dark. Then again, there are more than a few residents here that can see better in the dark than most...</Text>
  <Text Key="FFE5A496">The original Werewolves were Spellcasters, known as Mooncasters. After the first transformation, they lost their ability to cast anything. All of that magical affinity was directed internally, and that's how it remains to this day.</Text>
  <Text Key="18F32750">The lunar phases affect Werewolves differently. Sometimes these effects are good and sometimes they're a little hard to deal with. Some werewolves have even managed to develop a resistance to lunar magic. Those lucky dogs!</Text>
  <Text Key="69D2C210">It's always funny to watch a non-Werewolf Sim eat raw meat. Delicious if you're a Werewolf. Otherwise...</Text>
  <Text Key="638CC190">Not all Werewolves have a fated mate, but having one can be a powerful thing. You'll discover the connection when you really get to know someone, or when there's a bit of romance between the two of you. That doesn't mean you have to end up together, however. Who doesn't want to defy fate from time to time? </Text>
  <Text Key="689A50B6">A long time ago, before there were Werewolves, a group of Spellcasters frequented this area. They liked to use the howling point at night to call upon powerful untamed moon magic.</Text>
  <Text Key="BCCC3DB9">Once you find your fated mate, you're fated forever, and you'll only have the one. To embrace or deny fate is a rather impactful decision.</Text>
  <Text Key="788B46E5">As a werewolf, I don't always want to sleep at night, but if I manage to get some sleep during a New Moon, I come out feeling so well rested. It's really nice.</Text>
  <Text Key="38F7B87A">The best time to work out for a Werewolf is during the Waxing Crescent Moon. I'm not sure why, but that's always when I get my best workouts.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4280ED9">I'm not sure why, but as a Werewolf, I always feel much more logical during the Waning Crescent Moon. Plus, I can get through books so much faster.</Text>
  <Text Key="7E2D85D0">There are two main ways to become a Werewolf... be born one or be turned into one through a bite. Some Sims receive the latter involuntarily, but you can always ask a Werewolf if you're close enough and they might agree. The first Werewolves came about through a magical explosion, but that ritual was lost generations ago—and I believe it required a lot of special circumstances. </Text>
  <Text Key="39305C1C">Moonbathing during the Full Moon is a unique experience for us Werewolves.</Text>
  <Text Key="218AB317">Alphas who don't properly adhere to their pack's values are more likely to be challenged for the position. And if you're not the Alpha, if you don't follow the pack's values, you're more likely to be demoted!</Text>
  <Text Key="B0EACD6E">You think toddlers are difficult? Have you ever met a Werewolf toddler? Their poor toys! They always develop motor skills quickly, but it can be a challenge to potty train them. </Text>
  <Text Key="1741F44D">A lot of recipes for helpful Werewolf concoctions use Moonpetal in them and the only place to harvest it is on top of the tall rock. Though it won't really help to clamber up there unless there's a full moon in the sky.</Text>
  <Text Key="47A740C0">Kristopher looks just like his mother. Reminds me of the old days. I hate it. </Text>
  <Text Key="5D476D65">I hated the noise from the old mill. After they shut down, I tore it apart and dragged it into the tunnels where it can be forgotten. Now it can't be rebuilt!</Text>
  <Text Key="3E2861FC">Some say I'm mean. They say I'm gruff. A menace. You know what's mean? Gruff? What's really menacing? Life. Get used to it. </Text>
  <Text Key="A6634C39">I don't like going up to the howling point with how many other wolves frequent it, but that's where it &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; started. Where the magical explosion happened. Curious? Well, too bad.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBDCBFC9">I put up those signs for a reason. You'd think Sims would learn to read them. </Text>
  <Text Key="8C11C3D9">Not sure what happened to my diary. And honestly, I don't care. It's not like I write anymore. </Text>
  <Text Key="BC61B934">How old am I? I grew up in Old San Myshuno, back when the streets were filled with horses and carriages. Yeah, that's how old. </Text>
  <Text Key="77BF429E">Vlad is perhaps the cleverest Vampire I've ever met. Don't mistake my compliment for admiration, though. He's a monster. </Text>
  <Text Key="4AA3F96D">I'm always watching.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC113C58">I hate a lot of things, but the thing I hate more than anything else is a Vampire. </Text>
  <Text Key="44E53E23">I had a dog familiar named Brutus. Back when I was a spellcaster. Don't look so surprised... when I transformed, we lost our bond, and he grew old and died just like any other pet. Everything we love dies.</Text>
  <Text Key="9F43DA07">I won't say her name... but I was married once. When she died, I had no use for my weaker form anymore, no reason to be anything other than a beast.</Text>
  <Text Key="52B6DFA5">During the Century Conflict, we captured Vlad and took him down into the tunnels. We figured we'd use him as leverage, end the conflict. But even in his youth, he was already too powerful. We couldn't hold him and he escaped. </Text>
  <Text Key="C0DEFBE0">I was a spellcaster hundreds of years ago, a master of the Untamed school. I stood atop that mountain, back when this area was simply called Moonwood, and with a group of other powerful spellcasters, we channeled the most powerful Moon Infusion spell that has ever been cast. The results were explosive... but effective. The Moonlight infused both us and the land around us. Why do you think the Moonpetal only grows atop that mountain? Where do you think the Luna Fish comes from? We made them. &lt;i&gt;I made them.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="B074E9F9">My family used to be in the textiles industry. My... mother was... Don't have much use for textiles nowadays. </Text>
  <Text Key="E193BFCE">Rory will always be special to me. Even if we're in different packs, she's my sister. We've always been close, ever since dad found me and took me in. </Text>
  <Text Key="21CC3968">I really respect my dad. He's brought a lot of lost people together, and he's taught us how to live better, safer lives. I don't know who or what I'd be today if it wasn't for him. Hopefully I wouldn't be like Greg.</Text>
  <Text Key="7EB5B5C3">I don't think I ever want to leave Moonwood. I like the small town feel, the fact that everyone is really close-knit here, plus I've found my pack. If I did move anywhere though, I'd be interested in seeing Evergreen Harbor. That's where I'm from.</Text>
  <Text Key="93050C64">Yeah, I guess it is a little strange to be a vegetarian Werewolf. You don't find many of us. Oh well, it's who I am! Rory gets it. She'd always drool over the steaks when she was grilling, but then toss on a big mushroom for me.</Text>
  <Text Key="B1CEADBA">Lily's story is so sad. I can't imagine losing Rory or dad to someone like Vlad.</Text>
  <Text Key="C995405F">I know a lot of people are angry with Greg, or afraid of him, but I just feel sorry for the guy. I heard he had a fated mate that he lost. That has to be tough. </Text>
  <Text Key="BD376A88">Ever since I was little, dad has taught me to control my emotions. I'm grateful I haven't had to learn the hard way. </Text>
  <Text Key="AC58C415">Dad says that when he found me, I was being hunted by a Vampire. Pretty scary stuff. I'm too young to remember a lot, but one thing I do remember is the smell. I can usually smell when one's nearby. </Text>
  <Text Key="0E4E6816">A lot of people think I'll take over the Moonwood Collective as the Alpha some day. I hope that some day isn't too close. I could do it, but why would I when dad's still around? He's such a great leader. </Text>
  <Text Key="2F49C4AD">Dad has always taught me that non-were Sims are to be protected. I don't blame them for being afraid of us, given the history and the Vampire propaganda. I hope that some day they'll see us for who we really are as an occult though. </Text>
  <Text Key="DE88F117">Throughout my childhood, dad was my pack leader. Sims always ask me if that was weird. He didn't treat me any differently than any other member. We all follow the pack values. I'm just like everybody else. At least, that's how I see myself.</Text>
  <Text Key="339D3B8B">I was born in Evergreen Harbor. I don't remember much because I was pretty young when I left. Dad says that maybe I forgot what happened for a reason. I remember that there was a fire... and that afterwards, I was lost in the woods for a long time.</Text>
  <Text Key="4BE7BCCF">I didn't grow up with someone my age around. Still, I've always thought the concept of fated mates was really romantic. Imagine, another Werewolf fated to be only with you.</Text>
  <Text Key="63F9F980">I don't think I'd want to take a cure even if someone offered it to me. I'm part of a pack, and that means a lot to me. Don't take family for granted.</Text>
  <Text Key="6E257BA0">I don't like to dwell on it, but I do have flashes of memories from when I was lost in the woods. I knew so little back then, so a loose Vampire and Werewolf was the stuff of nightmares. Sometimes, I wonder about the Werewolf that bit me. Did they just lose control? Were they scared? I'd like to meet them and let them know that I'm happy now.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA165C5C">When you lose control, you lose yourself. Something else takes over and you don't know what might happen. Every Werewolf is different, but pay attention to the way that your specific temperaments feed the beast inside and try to keep yourself level.</Text>
  <Text Key="42C3ACA6">Rory had a rough time of it before I adopted her. Even if we don't always get along these days, I'm lucky to have had the opportunity to be her father.</Text>
  <Text Key="303840FF">I actually met Wolfgang here in Moonwood Mill. I believe he first came here to get away from the bustle of the city, to unwind. He discovered a lot more than he expected, I imagine. Ha!</Text>
  <Text Key="EE07E228">I want to live a lifestyle that's symbiotic with nature, a self-sustainable sort of livelihood. The plants we nourish in turn provide us nourishment and the moon ties our world to others through its energy. Some call it magic. All Sims feel it, though some may not understand it. In Moonwood Mill, we connect with the night sky. On the Isle of Volpe in the Bramblewood, they connect with the animals — at least they did centuries ago. These natural wells of power are easy to find if you know where to look. </Text>
  <Text Key="5ECFE596">I used to work at the Moonwood Mill before the town dried up. Please don't ask how old that makes me! After it was torn down, all of the old equipment disappeared. I know where it is... but I have no idea how it got there.</Text>
  <Text Key="E0BE2A42">I've never had a fated mate. My parents were fated to each other, which is lucky, because they were already married when they became Werewolves. I can't imagine how it would have felt if they'd been fated to be with others.</Text>
  <Text Key="212F044B">It's been a long time, but I once met the sages of the Magic Realm. My parents had some old connections there, friends from before they turned. It was interesting to see a glimpse of the life my parents led before the Century Conflict. I wonder if I might have enjoyed being a Spellcaster, but I know that leading the Moonwood Collective is my calling.</Text>
  <Text Key="16E4AD05">The secret passages beneath the town were built back during the Century Conflict to hide powerful relics from the Vampires and to get around unnoticed. Today, they're also an easy way to get from one end of town to the other.</Text>
  <Text Key="4BEC28CD">I think it's unfortunate we don't have more non-were Sims around. My parents dreamed of building a truly special, hybrid community here in Moonwood Mill. It...hasn't been that way since I was much younger. </Text>
  <Text Key="76CDF128">I've had arguments with Rory around our differing philosophies. Part of me is happy if she's happy, but part of me is afraid the Wildfang way is dangerous. I don't want an entire pack to turn out like Greg and lead others down that path...</Text>
  <Text Key="BF3C6B12">My father and mother fought in the Century Conflict alongside Greg - or Greggorius, as he was known. He's one of the oldest Werewolves alive that I'm aware of. Maybe &lt;i&gt;the&lt;/i&gt; oldest. He must be so lonely, but he nearly ruined what my parents tried to build here. They'd invited a lot of non-werewolves to the area and were building a special community when Greg returned and... well, you can see what it's become.</Text>
  <Text Key="97FC8D2D">My parents, grandparents, and great-grandparents were all talented spellcasters who fought during the Century Conflict. Me? I was born a werewolf — my parents were some of the original Mooncasters. I've always been proud of that fact. </Text>
  <Text Key="C02039F4">My parents rejected immortality, and it was a difficult decision for me. I don't plan to be immortal forever. I just need to ensure someone else is ready to lead the pack before I go. The Moonwood Collective has an important past, and I know it'll have an important role to play in the future as well. </Text>
  <Text Key="6F0A5321">I've certainly had some run-ins with Vampires. The closest was when I met Jacob. Because my parents knew about Vlad, I've always been able to avoid him pretty easily. </Text>
  <Text Key="383370FA">When I found Jacob, he was practically a pup. I'd heard there was a feral werewolf in those woods, and I wanted to help. Turns out, there was also a Vampire there. Thankfully, I got to Jacob before either of them could. When I found the other wolf, he wasn't interested in coming back to Moonwood Mill with me. A pack didn't interest him. Some Werewolves like being the lone wolf. </Text>
  <Text Key="3E163045">I remember when my cousin, Lilith, first told me she'd met a fascinating man named Vlad. After that, she started spending a lot of time "training" with him. I thought she meant they were workout buddies. It wasn't until later that I found out she'd been lured to the dark arts. </Text>
  <Text Key="096A51E0">It was very kind of Kristopher to take me in. I was lost for many, many years before coming to Moonwood Mill. He's been my family. As real a family as the one I lost...</Text>
  <Text Key="D83B0579">When I was a child, I was very close with my cousins, Caleb and Lilith Vatore. Our mothers were sisters, and we spent most of our childhoods together. Lilith always had a dark side, but Caleb was a gentle soul. </Text>
  <Text Key="249911E4">Jacob has always made Kristopher so proud. He was in danger when Kristopher found him, you know? </Text>
  <Text Key="6C87EBB4">They say Greg is as old as Vlad. I don't know as much about his past, but I believe that being around on his own for that long will taint anyone's senses.</Text>
  <Text Key="C289447E">The statue in the middle of Forgotten Hollow is supposed to depict a Straud ancestor. It's almost believable, because it looks so much friendlier than Vlad does... but I know the truth. It's been Vlad haunting that town all along.</Text>
  <Text Key="C9639B21">I wasn't in the Century Conflict between the Vampires and the Spellcasters. I'm not nearly that old. Not even Kristopher was around for that, but I believe his parents were. </Text>
  <Text Key="B1C7CEFE">After I was bitten by a Werewolf in the tunnels beneath Forgotten Hollow, I was lost for years. I spent so much of it as a beast, transformed and unable to remember much. Learning how to control my fury really turned my life around. For that, I'll always be grateful to Kristopher.</Text>
  <Text Key="02BDA183">I was older by the time I met Kristopher and learned to control my powers. That's why I'm elderly and he isn't, despite him being my senior. I struggled to determine if I should pursue immortality or not. After thinking about it, the answer was clear. I have unfinished business with my cousins. Perhaps once that's settled, I can rest.</Text>
  <Text Key="4333F459">Of all of the Werewolves here, I'm probably the one who's most familiar with Vampires, given my history. I'm sure Kristopher has heard plenty of stories from his parents, though.</Text>
  <Text Key="F7B67DAD">I heard about that fateful date Lou and Celene went on. What a silly man. Everyone knows Greg is dangerous. To provoke him was just fool-hardy. It must have been traumatizing for poor Celene. No wonder she took the remedy.</Text>
  <Text Key="4642C965">After I was turned into a Werewolf, things with my cousins, Lilith and Caleb, were never the same again. I'd already felt they were changing under Vlad's influence too quickly, but after my own transformation, there was something natural that pushed us apart. More than anything, I want to rekindle the relationship we had as children. </Text>
  <Text Key="0B655618">Not all Werewolves feel this way, but I don't enjoy the Full Moon. I spent too much of my life out of control. When the full moon rises, it reminds me of those times. Truthfully, I'd be cured if I could, but I'm not sure that I'd ever see Caleb or Lilith again if I did. I'm too old without my abilities to keep me alive. </Text>
  <Text Key="EF0ED7A0">We were young when my cousins Caleb and Lilith were turned into vampires. Lilith was turned by Vlad, and Caleb by Miss Hell. Vlad came for me as well, but I hid in the underground tunnels—which is how my own transformation, of a different nature, came about. I stayed there, half feral, and I tried to make it work with my cousins when they visited. After I discovered Moonwood Mill and my pack, I learned that they'd officially moved to Forgotten Hollow. It's upsetting. </Text>
  <Text Key="682EB283">I spent much of my youth feral in the tunnels beneath Forgotten Hollow where I was bitten by a Werewolf. After I arrived in Moonwood Mill, Kristopher told me that Forgotten Hollow was once under Werewolf control — back before Vlad moved in. He arrived with a mob and manipulated them into driving the Werewolves out. They, of course, didn't know he was a Vampire. They even put up a statue in his honor! Then, they all disappeared, one by one...</Text>
  <Text Key="79D95679">When I ran into that rabid Werewolf in the tunnels beneath Forgotten Hollow, I remember saying to him, "My, what big ears you have!" and then, "My, what big teeth!" At first, it almost looked like my grandma, but I knew that couldn't be the case.</Text>
  <Text Key="3E8AABE7">Kristopher's a pretty cool Werewolf to have taken in everyone he has. Of course, he didn't take me in... so he kind of missed taking in the coolest wolf, but hey, he does an adequate job. </Text>
  <Text Key="069B1BDD">I love me some PowerSip MIDNIGHT! I'm glad they're always fighting the legal battles to make their next big flavor. Who wouldn't want to taste "midnight"? Seriously, they must have some spellcaster brewers making the stuff. How else do you harness the essence of night? </Text>
  <Text Key="838A936D">So I've snatched a few things over the years. A future cube, a few paintings, some children's toys—which I &lt;i&gt;donated&lt;/i&gt;, so don't look at me like that! The best thing I ever took was a piano. Don't ask me how I did it. That's a secret. </Text>
  <Text Key="A2815530">How did I end up in Moonwood Mill? Well, I stole a few things I probably shouldn't have, and I was on the run. I figured nobody would find me way out here in the middle of the wilderness. Guess I was right. </Text>
  <Text Key="02BAEC8C">Who doesn't want to be an immortal wolf? I hear you need to be pretty powerful to pull it off. Don't worry, I'll get there soon.</Text>
  <Text Key="603EA6B4">Not sure how I feel about the concept of fated mates. Like, ONE Werewolf? FOREVER?? That's a lot of commitment. </Text>
  <Text Key="7DE6A0BF">So I asked Celene out on a date, yeah. We were going for a walk over that bridge, when I heard a helpless kid or something crying for help. I'm a pretty nice guy, so I was like, "Hey Celene, we gotta go help the kid." We braved going past those signs and all that, and we ran into Greg. Well, I had to try and protect Celene. She was pretty scared! So I ran up to him and suggested Greg leave us alone. No taunting or anything, just a stern suggestion. He didn't take kindly to that, and well... here we are. That's the &lt;i&gt;truth&lt;/i&gt; of it all!</Text>
  <Text Key="C8C352A1">I'm not sure I like the idea of Vampires. I guess most Werewolves don't... Spellcasters on the other hand? They sound pretty cool. I'd get together with one.</Text>
  <Text Key="E3B747CC">Greg is kind of a problem. We all know it. I don't know why he came here in the first place if he doesn't want to join a pack and live like the rest of us. </Text>
  <Text Key="71DFEE8D">The Moonwood Collective isn't really my scene. They're too into nature. Have you seen them leaning on that old tree? No fire anywhere? BORING.</Text>
  <Text Key="66C5CBFA">Rory was a lone Alpha until I joined her pack. It just felt right to me. We're a good fit as a pack and I like how she encourages me to explore being a Werewolf.</Text>
  <Text Key="065CCC06">Who knows if I'd take a cure or not. I mean, right now? No. My pack is pretty cool. I'm still figuring out everything I can do. Why would I want to give that up? </Text>
  <Text Key="DE6A6A43">Yeah, okay, I'll admit that I feel kind of bad about what happened to Celene. I know she was pretty traumatized by it all. She, well... we were both pretty scared. I don't know, I don't think I want to talk about it, even with you.</Text>
  <Text Key="23A72DAF">When you're the new wolf on the block, you'll notice that you certainly have less control than the others. Give it time, it gets better.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE7D8512">I'm always getting asked why I didn't take the antidote after our encounter, like Celene did. Well, I figured I was strong enough to ride it out. It was just a small bite! I guess I was wrong... </Text>
  <Text Key="6A559168">Just because I'm all about embracing the inner beast doesn't mean I'm opposed to someone seeking a cure. Be true to you. That's what's important. Just don't try to make me take it!</Text>
  <Text Key="1320D511">If I wasn't a Werewolf, I think I'd want to be a Mermaid. Surprised? Eh, don't be. They also have a connection to the moon, you know? With the tides and all that. Did you know mermaids can stay out of the water longer during a Full Moon?</Text>
  <Text Key="4785A5B8">The Moonwood Collective fears their own natural state. It's like they've built a fire that they only let smolder. Why not stoke that thing and have some fun? Just keep it contained to the fire pit, you know? </Text>
  <Text Key="DE11FB16">We may not be in the same pack anymore, but I love my little brother, Jacob. Always have, always will. And I think the Moonwood Collective suits him well. It just didn't work for me. </Text>
  <Text Key="44C02D5A">What are the Wildfangs about? All right, think of fury like the ocean. The Moonwood Collective wants to avoid it. Greg is drowning in it. The Wilfangs want to go for a swim. Sure, it's not 100% safe, but can you imagine living your whole life by the water and never taking a dip? </Text>
  <Text Key="262EA527">Even as a kid, I had a strong sense of individuality. Yeah, Kristopher is my dad, but I've always been Rory Oaklow, you know? I'm not going to change my name for some elder Werewolf. Jacob wanted to. That's his decision, and I support that.</Text>
  <Text Key="8F911374">Sure, normies are great, but they're not my pack, and they can never be. That's fine. You're close with the people you connect with, you run with the ones you trust, you know? </Text>
  <Text Key="254F00AD">What would I do if I ever met Vlad Straud? I'd fight him, of course. He needs to know who the top dog around here is. And it's not going to be some ancient, evil Vampire.</Text>
  <Text Key="C0E1AF28">I've never had a fated mate before. And even if fate decided to put me on the list, I don't really subscribe to that being the end-all-factor in who I end up with. I decide my fate.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA7CF7E8">Other occults come here from time to time. Before coming here, I'd never met a Spellcaster! I was always around normie Sims, born and raised in a standard normie family. It's strange to think about now. I wouldn't want to go back to that. </Text>
  <Text Key="1EBBB690">When I became leader of a pack, I realized I was going to have to open myself to learning about what it means to be a leader each day. There's always a lot of pressure to care for the well-being of those who follow me, but I want to do right by the pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="4DCF1D53">I learned the secrets to immortality early. Most werewolves don't, but I was able to by truly embracing who I am inside. I don't hide, and because of that, I'm more in tune with my inner wolf.</Text>
  <Text Key="3EA46DC6">The original Werewolves didn't deny their inner beasts. They embraced the moon and its magic, and they used it for good, keeping the Vampires from taking over. I don't think the Moonwood Collective would even be strong enough today to take on the Vampires if they started another conflict. The Wildfangs would be.</Text>
  <Text Key="89E376AA">I don't talk much about my past. I was bit by a dog that'd somehow contracted lycanthropy. It doesn't usually happen, so it must have been a freak accident. I was with my family at the vet in Brindleton Bay—that's where I grew up. The day after my first transformation, my parents kicked me out. They didn't know how to handle the new me. Kristopher took me in. We don't agree on a lot of things these days, but I'll always remember his kindness.</Text>
  <Text Key="8EEBB135">Kristopher thinks that if I keep heading down the path I'm on, I'll turn out like Greg. He can't be serious. I'm nothing like Greg. I'm in control. I just don't shy away from the fury inside me. I use it. Sure, it's a difficult balancing act, but I'm killing it.</Text>
  <Text Key="BB1B8BA7">I made it to the ocean once. I always thought it would be romantic to throw a message in a bottle into the sea, so I wrote one. Something sappy about looking up at the moon and wondering if I could change for the better. I wonder if anyone ever read it.</Text>
  <Text Key="F9AA7F95">I met Kristopher when I came here to unwind. I was tired of the - pardon the pun - dog-eat-dog hustle of the city, and we became fast friends. He started talking to me about certain harmful stereotypes, how so many others see Werewolves — enough that I was intrigued.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2339C6F">I'm not the only person around here who grew up in San Myshuno, but I am the only person who came over within the last few decades. The city life wasn't for me. I wanted something more close-knit. A pack, if you will. </Text>
  <Text Key="0A1ED61A">Here in Moonwood Mill, we make do with what we have around. Turning an old factory into a library, for example. We've got a lot of ingenuity.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F8DA4DE">Oh, I love books. Histories are my favorite, though I've never felt quite talented enough to write one. No, I stick to my fiction, though I always write with the intention to teach. </Text>
  <Text Key="4BD0E321">Kristopher believes that when you are in control of your emotions, you are the truest version of yourself. It allows you to act in a way that best represents your personal ideals and motives. It was this philosophy that piqued my interest in the Werewolf lifestyle. I would never had made the change if it wasn't for him. </Text>
  <Text Key="8F883A81">If I could go back to how things were before I arrived, would I? No. I have a family now. They're my pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="820EE2EA">Now that we're closer, I'll let you in on a secret: I am Vulfgang Mulder, the author. Not many know. I want to live the quiet life, and I don't want to draw attention to Moonwood Mill, so I keep my real identity secret. </Text>
  <Text Key="B39067C8">Greg is a living fixture of history, a reminder of darker times, and a warning for those who forget the value of control. He long ago gave into his rage and lost himself in it. It's a sad tale. </Text>
  <Text Key="0BF07DEC">My favorite moon phase is the Waning Crescent. For Werewolves, it bestows the gift of logic. I find I can read books far faster than during any other moon phase. I can't think of a better way of spending the night! </Text>
  <Text Key="85528E02">The Wildfangs are young. The pack hasn't been around nearly as long as the Moonwood Collective, nor is it as rooted in history. The Moonwood Collective goes back to the very first Werewolves. The Wildfangs should learn from history's valuable lessons — lest they go down a dangerous path.</Text>
  <Text Key="A1FEEC49">I find the entire, forgotten origins and the ongoing plight of the Werewolf fascinating. I wanted to be an advocate for them, to reorient their image in society, and so I asked Kristopher to change me. I couldn't write on something so intimate unless I truly experienced it myself. </Text>
  <Text Key="260A5DC6">After losing the war, the Vampires launched "Operation High Fang" with the intent of using propaganda to turn general sentiment against Werewolves. My books do the opposite. They encourage readers to view Werewolves in a new, more favorable light - one that I feel is more authentic to who we are as an occult.</Text>
  <Text Key="44ACFD04">Did you know that the very first Werewolves were Spellcasters? It's true. There were many ways Spellcasters attempted to fight back against the Vampires, and Werewolves were the most successful attempt. It's fascinating stuff if you can find ways to read up on it!</Text>
  <Text Key="00AE5598">Reading Werewolf-themed books is one of the best ways to learn the secrets of the Werewolves. You'll discover quite a lot, especially if you have the ability to read between the lines...</Text>
  <Text Key="3DA55D43">{0.SimFirstName} learned how to make {1.String}!</Text>
  <Text Key="EF37A3F3">Tunnel Path Discovered</Text>
  <Text Key="7227E10F">{0.SimFirstName} can now use the underground tunnels to travel directly between the sparring grounds portal potties and old bunker exit above ground.</Text>
  <Text Key="0B21A815">{0.SimFirstName} can now use the underground tunnels to travel directly between the sparring grounds portal potties and the sewer grate.</Text>
  <Text Key="7608223E">{0.SimFirstName} can now use the underground tunnels to travel directly between the old above ground bunker and the sewer grate.</Text>
  <Text Key="0BC0FDFA">&lt;b&gt;Do not trespass in areas marked by signs!&lt;/b&gt;
Got bit? Suspect you might be infected? Stop by the local bar. Moonwood Mill bartenders carry a remedy on hand. Don't forget to: Get extra rest, wash the infected area in a shower, and cleanse your bowel system. Taking a run on the treadmill has also been known to help sweat it out. </Text>
  <Text Key="3593B9F4">Werebies Advisory</Text>
  <Text Key="8780B59E">(From Being in Moonwood Mill)</Text>
  <Text Key="3A7351D9">(From Devouring an Object)</Text>
  <Text Key="5D4114BE">It wasn't the first time Peter and his friends had explored the town's nearby tunnels and caves. It felt like they would find something new every time they ventured into the mysterious depths, and this time was no different...</Text>
  <Text Key="C13A52FB">Peter Barker had always loved full moons, but this one felt different. There was a thrilling pulse of energy that grew stronger and stronger as the day ended and the night began.</Text>
  <Text Key="79378D00">He'd made it through his first full moon! It was mostly a blur and Peter hadn't felt in control through most of the night, but he also remembered how exciting it was to run wild in the night with his friends under the loving gaze of the moon.</Text>
  <Text Key="EFA76AB3">Traveling was fun, but Peter knew where he belonged. His home was with his pack of friends, with those he loved most. He just wondered if they would think that he'd forgotten them or, worse yet, that they had forgotten him!</Text>
  <Text Key="78875437">It was a surprise party for him! Peter hadn't seen it coming. It was good to be around so many friends, and to share memories of past times under the homemade "Welcome Home, Peter!" banner. There was even a cake! Before he was able to control his excitement, and to the dismay of those around him, he dove towards it head-first!</Text>
  <Text Key="0036D58B">Living in the big city this past year had been fun, but for Peter Barker, it never really felt like home. Home was the mysterious foggy forest with its big swaying trees. He longed to return to those familiar leafy guardians and the moon's embrace, casting its lunar effect upon all who witnessed it.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CC72ABC">Jumping out of the lake, Peter didn't even bother taking the towel Luna reached out to hand him. After a couple vigorous shakes, he was super dry! Luna giggled and Peter noticed that he'd sent water flying everywhere, much to the disapproval of some nearby Sims in the "splash zone."</Text>
  <Text Key="964938CB">Peter Barker was excited. Summer was here and camp started in a few days. He looked forward to huddling around the campfire, roasting marshmallows, and telling scary stories. And boy did he have a doozy of a story! He'd recently heard of a dangerous howling man that lived in the nearby forest and captured careless were-children, his cold glowing eyes watching for anyone foolish enough to get too close!</Text>
  <Text Key="B4D3C0AD">Peter was normally unlucky when he would dig and scavenge around, but this time was different. He'd managed to dig up something that looked ancient and mysterious, but he had no clue what it was. It would take some deciphering to reveal all of its secrets.</Text>
  <Text Key="9AE6E330">3...2...1...BLAST OFF! The roar of the engines filled the classroom as everyone watched the rocket start its ascent on the small TV. "And," Peter's teacher continued, "if you win this essay contest, you could be present at the next rocket launch!"</Text>
  <Text Key="EB448735">The door to the rocket was just... open. Inviting. Almost calling to him. Peter hesitated. He shouldn't, should he? But then again, this rocket was headed for the moon, establishing a new lunar colony, and didn't Werewolves deserve to be a part of history? What would life for a Werewolf be like on the moon? Would they always be in beast form?</Text>
  <Text Key="8FCF0AAF">The hotel room, though small, seemed extra fancy to Peter, who stared at the launch pad out the window. When he could finally fall asleep, he dreamed of being the first Werewolf spaceship captain. He grinned to himself, imagining new adventures for him and a big furry companion who only communicated in strange alien growls and grunts.</Text>
  <Text Key="207C4205">Peter dreamt again that night. It was the same dream he always had. All around him was a wilderness that led to a crescent shaped lake with a large mountain overhead. A wolf howled from atop the mountain, and then he woke up. That's how it always went.</Text>
  <Text Key="E3299972">Peter sniffed the air around him. It smelled like wet dog, comforting and familiar. He looked around, spotting an old friend, and a wide smile spread across his face. "Luna!" </Text>
  <Text Key="140FBA32">As the moon came into view, Peter smiled. It was as if he were greeting a friend. What magical adventures they'd had together! </Text>
  <Text Key="51726289">Peter lifted his head towards the moon and, with the shadowed figures around him, let out an exuberant pack howl. He was officially one of them.</Text>
  <Text Key="C1FCCB9F">Both of Peter's parents had been Werewolves. He knew that made his family different, but he couldn't imagine life any other way!</Text>
  <Text Key="DAAC5BB7">Before the mill was established, the area was simply known as Moonwood. The name was coined by locals, who believed the surrounding forest was imbued with lunar energy. </Text>
  <Text Key="039266E7">In the early days of Moonwood Mill, the town's mill-working founders formed an organization known as the Moonwood Collective. This organization encouraged the community to pursue self-sustainability, diplomatic communication, and communal contribution as key values. They saw a brighter future for Moonwood Mill on the horizon. </Text>
  <Text Key="91C74277">Moonwood Mill flourished with the arrival of its factories and mill. Many Sims traveled to this remote town from San Myshuno, eager to escape the urban hustle and bustle. The vast wilderness surrounding the town's center promised an easier lifestyle more in tune with nature. </Text>
  <Text Key="48D8179D">Original settlers to the area were refugees, seeking an end to the conflict that had been plaguing them. They sought a connection with nature and the moon. They came upon what's commonly called Moonwood's "Howling Point" today, and the breathtaking night views and the crescent-shaped lake beneath both seemed good omens of their pursuits.</Text>
  <Text Key="50F6DDDF">There seem to be entire passages along the pages written in an indecipherable language. The only thing {0.SimFirstName} can make out are some symbols that look like the moon.</Text>
  <Text Key="AAF95A45">For years, Moonwood Mill was known as the Lumberjack capital of the world. It played host to the world's largest annual lumberjack competition. Prizes were awarded for: Most Plaid Shirt, Beard Density, Syrup Chugging, and Shouting "Timber" Loudly.</Text>
  <Text Key="CA5FD1D3">An extensive tunnel network runs below Moonwood Mill. There are various entrance points around town, though even the locals find it difficult to navigate. Many speculate these tunnels were originally created during a regional time of strife, though records of such an event are lost to time. Perhaps the dark tunnels themselves might contain clues?</Text>
  <Text Key="E059E5F4">&lt;b&gt;5 Things You Need to Know Before Your First Transformation&lt;/b&gt;\n\n&lt;b&gt;1.&lt;/b&gt; You're not going to remember it. Maybe that's for the best! But for fun, try re-tracing your steps to find out what mischief you got into!\n\n&lt;b&gt;2.&lt;/b&gt; You might have a frog in your throat the next day. Rampaging Werewolves do &lt;i&gt;a lot&lt;/i&gt; of howling. Awooo!\n\n&lt;b&gt;3.&lt;/b&gt; You're probably going to tear your clothes! Let's face it: Werewolves have hulking frames! It's easy to rip your clothes or lose them altogether the first time you transform. \n\n&lt;b&gt;4.&lt;/b&gt; You might make an enemy or two. It's not always easy for non-Werewolves to understand your transformations. They might be scared or angry that you transformed right in front of them. Catch a flick together and rebuild that friendship.\n\n&lt;b&gt;5.&lt;/b&gt; It gets better! Werewolves naturally learn to control their powers over time and every Werewolf grows and learns with each transformation. Your first one might get a little messy, but in time you might even find you like transforming and be able to do it when and were you want to.\n\nStay safe out there!</Text>
  <Text Key="26C6969B">&lt;b&gt;World's Top Howling Spots&lt;/b&gt;\n\n&lt;i&gt;Pictured on this issue's cover&lt;/i&gt;\n\nEvery Werewolf needs a local howling spot. In this issue we're covering the worlds top locales to go "awooo!" \n\n&lt;b&gt;1.&lt;/b&gt; Moonwood Mill - Our top pick! Where better to howl than where it all began? There's always a little magic in the air at this spot.\n\n&lt;b&gt;2.&lt;/b&gt; Mt. Komorebi - It takes work to reach the top of Mt. Komorebi, but few spots put you closer to the moon at night.\n\n&lt;b&gt;3.&lt;/b&gt; Del Sol Valley - Head on up to The Pinnacles at night. The city below is as dazzling as the night sky above. You'll find yourself star struck! \n\n&lt;b&gt;4.&lt;/b&gt; San Myshuno - Gather the pack at any rooftop skyscraper and feel the city's buzz. Howling has never been so electrifying!\n\n&lt;b&gt;5.&lt;/b&gt; The Magic Realm - Spellcasters and Werewolves share a history and the Magic Realm is unlike any other. Enjoy a bit of anti-Vampire comradery and howl outside the realm's fabric tear.</Text>
  <Text Key="8F08C552">&lt;b&gt;What's the Deal with Catching Werebies&lt;/b&gt;\n\nIt's easier than you'd think to get bit. You'll know you have werebies when you feel the fury! Here are today's top 5 hottest tips on how you can say goodbye to a case of the howls!\n\n&lt;b&gt;1.&lt;/b&gt; Go for a run on the treadmill. Sweat it out!\n\n&lt;b&gt;2.&lt;/b&gt; Run to the bathroom and...drain that fury!\n\n&lt;b&gt;3.&lt;/b&gt; Shower and let the steam wash it away!\n\n&lt;b&gt;4.&lt;/b&gt; Get plenty of rest. That's actually good advice all the time.\n\n&lt;b&gt;5.&lt;/b&gt; If you're in the area, the bartenders in Moonwood Mill always carry a locally-sourced remedy on-hand, which they're happy to hand them out to those in need!</Text>
  <Text Key="0B86A200">♥&lt;b&gt;What's Your Perfect Pack?&lt;/b&gt;♥\n\n\nMy friends describe me as...\n○ Self-Sufficient    ○ Rebellious\n\nFull Moons Make Me Feel... \n○ Controlled    ○ Ready to Rock &amp; Roll\n\nMy Must-Have Accessory is... \n○ A Leaf in My Hair    ○ My Spiked Collar\n\nI Hope My Fated-Mate will be a... \n○ Nature Enthusiast    ○ Rock Star</Text>
  <Text Key="E2C60619">&lt;b&gt;Dear Wolfy: slobbering fated-mate&lt;/b&gt;\n\nDear Wolfy: A few months ago I turned sixteen. I hosted a big party with all of the other local wolves hoping to meet my fated mate. It didn't happen. The next day at school, I saw (let's call him) Drooly. We both made wolf eyes at each other and we both knew. I remember thinking the goopy puddle on the top of his desk was gross, but now I find it charming! What is happening to me? -  Future Mrs. Drooly</Text>
  <Text Key="F23E723C">&lt;b&gt;Next Issue Sneak Peak: Best. Collars. Ever.&lt;/b&gt;\n\n• 16 Designer Collars That Are Better Than Your Dog's\n• Eco-Friendly Collars for the Nature-Loving Werewolf\n• Collars Brands That Make Your Neck Look Buff</Text>
  <Text Key="5D28A93F">&lt;b&gt;Help! My Inner-Wolf is Dormant!&lt;/b&gt;\n\nHey, let's face it: Werewolves who discover their inner wolf is dormant can feel left out. They aren't fully like non-Were Sims, nor do they quite fit in with the pack. But being in-between doesn't have to be a bad thing! In fact, many Dormant Wolves learn to enjoy their unique vantage in society. \n\nFor those with lycan blood who want more wolf and less Sim, though, legend has it that there is a way! Visit scenic Moonwood Mills, the place where it all began. Lake Lunvik is rich with magical lunar energy and a dip during the full moon will have you howling with joy!</Text>
  <Text Key="CE180635">Removing gum from your Werewolf fur can be quite the sticky situation! First and foremost, remember to be gentle. You might be a rambunctious beast, but that doesn't mean you don't have tender skin! </Text>
  <Text Key="C6D0D948">Some Werewolves think that they want to have a go at life alone, but it's often not the easiest path. Wolves naturally find pack behavior satisfying, and packs offer support in ways you may not have even considered! From managing fury to sharing resources, it'd be a shame to miss out on it all. They're also a great place to find a Fated Mate, that once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.</Text>
  <Text Key="A5268C3B">When you feel that rage coming on and don't want to destroy the house again, consider one saving grace: door locks. Just go lock the door. Even a Werewolf can't break through those things!</Text>
  <Text Key="4F10965D">If, by chance, you are bitten by a Werewolf, use the following guidelines on how to act:\n\n1. Take a moment to reflect. Do you feel angrier than usual? If so, you might be infected. \n2. Make sure you get plenty of rest. Sleeping can help you regain your health. \n3. Take a shower or use the toilet. Both can wash out the infection. \n4. Take a run on the treadmill! Sometimes you can sweat out the infection. </Text>
  <Text Key="3A87CA2F">Each Werewolf has temperaments as unique as themselves. To retain control, a Werewolf must look inward and discover what makes them feel angry. Only then can they lessen their rage-induced transformations.</Text>
  <Text Key="8D1619ED">If you're having trouble sleeping, you're not alone. Most Werewolves struggle to rest well when the moon is looming overhead. Make sure that during the New Moon, you're getting as much rest as possible. 99% of Werewolves report that they feel more rested after sleeping during the New Moon lunar phase. </Text>
  <Text Key="EDB8F87D">Turning on a date can be catastrophic, especially if it's your &lt;i&gt;first&lt;/i&gt; date! Our recommendation? Go for a run! Rampage to your heart's content... in the other direction. You might not have complete control, but even rampaging Werewolves consider a nice, long run a good time. Give into that instinct, and you're sure to find yourself far away from your (likely terrified) date.</Text>
  <Text Key="A1E26AAD">Today, I broke a few doors during a rampage, and somehow even destroyed Avelina's telescope. Once I'd transformed back to myself, I could see how distraught she was. I took the wood from a broken door and repaired the telescope's leg. I am no woodworker, but my dear told me she liked it better this way. I am often reminded what a lovely woman she is. I am so fortunate.</Text>
  <Text Key="8E244769">After the Vampire uprising, every one of us Spellcasters grew increasingly desperate. One group tried to create a spell that could simultaneously “cure” every Vampire in existence. A single spell to end the conflict. Of course, they were blinded by hubris and hurried by desperation. The spell was too powerful for the group to handle. It caused a massive fracture in the fabric of the Realm itself.</Text>
  <Text Key="608C630E">I've always known that Avelina's heart belongs to the night's sky. I've known it since the day we met in Glimmerbrook. I wooed her with the poetry of the stars and the moon. How ironic to think of those days now, with what we've become, our very forms entwined with the moon itself. Perhaps fate knew, even if we did not, that we were destined to be together. There must be something magical about fate. It does seem to bind all things.</Text>
  <Text Key="139C2BC5">Brutus is growing older. Before my transformation, when I was like any other Spellcaster, he was my familiar. Though that particular connection is now lost, we still share a kinship in the moon itself, in our sharp fangs, our fighting prowess. In a way, he has become my brother and I am already weary of how it will feel to watch him slow down.</Text>
  <Text Key="4D7C5554">Avelina has forgotten to care for herself yet again while I was rampaging. How long was I gone? I can't even recall. That telescope will be her undoing! She becomes so transfixed by its mysteries and neglects everything else, herself included. I must hasten my efforts to control these transformations. My beloved wife needs me here with her.</Text>
  <Text Key="9B798E42">I write today with a heavy heart. My closest confidant and most daring friend Yina Kia has left this planet. It was a Cow Plant, those blasted abominations of the Moo Casters! In certain hands, magic can do beautiful things. In others, it can create some of the galaxy's greatest monsters. Cow Plants, Vampires, and perhaps...some would say us. Do Werewolves belong on that list? I know John and Maria would adamantly disagree.</Text>
  <Text Key="CDC1215D">All along this page are magical moon glyphs. With {M0.his}{F0.her} Lunar Epiphany, {0.SimFirstName} is able to read about a group of Spellcasters who communed with their dog familiars to learn about the untapped magical potential found in moonlight. They declared themselves Mooncasters and experimented with unstable transformation magic from the Untamed School.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0D7CA2B">Glowing, magical moon glyphs along the edge of this page detail a hundred-year conflict called "Operation Eternal Flame." Beset by their own thirst and an innate distrust, the first Vampires hunted Spellcasters, raiding their small communities to drink their magical plasma. This was how Vampires first developed a small degree of magic within themselves. It eventually led to them being capable of turning Sims into what they themselves now were.</Text>
  <Text Key="66DA7A6D">The magical moon symbols around the page glow faintly, and {0.SimFirstName} is able to decipher them with {M0.his}{F0.her} Lunar Epiphany. They tell the tale of Spellcasters long ago who explored the limits of their power. They experimented by creating duplicates of themselves, but quickly became frustrated that these duplicates required sustenance to survive. In an effort to be efficient, they fed them potions... they created monsters.</Text>
  <Text Key="EE291E7F">Magical moon glyphs line the outside of this page, and {0.SimFirstName} is able to use {M0.his}{F0.her} Lunar Ephiphany to understand them. It seems that towards the end of Operation Eternal Flame, the near-extinct Spellcasters grew desperate and struggled with a variety of magic types to try and turn the tide of their conflict with the Vampires. Some sought a cure for Vampirism, though the spell proved too powerful and caused a tear in the very fabric of the Magic Realm itself. </Text>
  <Text Key="FCC09AE3">Glowing moon symbols around the edges of this page tell a dark story that {0.SimFirstName} is only able to decipher with {M0.his}{F0.her} Lunar Ephiphany. It's a tale of betrayal, of duplication spells gone wrong. After an overloaded spell turned a mutated group of Spellcaster mimics permanent, they turned on their creators and sank their fangs into them. They feasted on these Spellcasters and their magical plasma, which enhanced their strength, despite never sating their thirst.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C8D9F99">A howl echoed through the alleys. In a second, Dolf was down on all fours and gave chase - the moon his sole companion, gleaming off his fangs, giving speed to his legs. Like a snake, the alleys seemed to coil and cross over one another until his head felt as hazy as the local nightclub Dolf would retreat to when it all got to be too much. Suddenly, there was a dumpster in front of him, something atop it glinting in the moonlight. For some unknown reason, Detective Dolf felt drawn to it. He edged closer until he came upon the shattered mirror, reflecting back a man he did not know. Himself.</Text>
  <Text Key="76C2BF93">Detective Dolf was always a mystery to those closest to him - and at times, even to himself. Perhaps that's why he was so drawn by those unsolvable mysteries, why he always felt like a lone wolf hunting for answers. But he had yet to solve the greatest mystery of all: &lt;i&gt;who was he?&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="65E032E4">There seem to be entire passages of this written in an indecipherable language. The only thing {0.SimFirstName} can make out are some symbols that look like the moon.</Text>
  <Text Key="092F73A8">Every time the hunt grew difficult, Dolf's dark past propelled him forward. It was a past he didn't like to mention, a past that reached forward and cast its shadow on his present and future. A shadow that turned into a wall that kept everyone else out, turning him into the lone wolf detective he was, looking for answers only he could find.</Text>
  <Text Key="84D718BA">The pack was abuzz with anticipation. The new wolf in town was intent on challenging the Alpha. Were he to win...what would that mean for her? For...&lt;i&gt;them&lt;/i&gt;?</Text>
  <Text Key="F3D2717B">Ginger couldn't help but stare out her kitchen window. He was outside again, mowing the lawn (like he did every day at exactly 3:04 pm)...shirtless. It was especially hot today and the sweat beaded on his neck and shoulders, each bead slowly rolling down his body, tracing the contours of each muscle. Her throat felt dry and the wolf inside her stirred, begging her to go out and meet him.</Text>
  <Text Key="CDB12704">As the handshake ended, Ginger felt her inner wolf cry out. There was a connection between the two of them, one that both terrified and excited her. Had he felt it as well? His steely expression led her to believe that he had not, that she was no different from any other new neighbor he had felt obligated to meet. The thought weighed heavier in her heart than she'd anticipated...</Text>
  <Text Key="89425BE9">The new moon always led to one friend or another proposing a lazy gathering in the woods. As they snacked and slumbered, their friendship flourished. It was on these days that Boris liked to invite the group to go hunting for mushrooms rather than for meat. </Text>
  <Text Key="CA14B406">Amidst the forest was a known Vampire's lair. Though most of the group dared not creep any closer, Mingan was already halfway through the trees. Little mushrooms spilled out of her basket along the way, marking her ascent with a haphazard trail.</Text>
  <Text Key="AC050D4D">The group of four had always been inseparable, even if Mingan was a Vampire. They'd sworn that together they would find a cure for her - no matter the cost. She would one day be part of the pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="9B8228F3">"Don't keep howling so, Mitsy! Have a little compassion on my nerves. You'll cause me to transform, and then I'll tear them to pieces." \n“Mitsy has no discretion in her howls,” said her father; “she times them ill.” \n“I do not howl for my own amusement,” replied Mitsy fretfully.</Text>
  <Text Key="5CDF57F7">Lizo spoke well, but he didn't only speak of love, and he was not more eloquent on the subject of their fated-bond than of his pride. His sense of her inferiority—of its being a degradation—to his pack's obligations...</Text>
  <Text Key="41798B48">It is a truth universally acknowledged, that an Alpha Werewolf in possession of a good pack, must be in want of a Fated Mate.</Text>
  <Text Key="BAF1FA81">The magical moon symbols along the page are easily deciphered by {0.SimFirstName}'s Lunar Epiphany, and {M0.he}{F0.she} sees the text reaching out to those like {M0.him}{F0.her}. "The Moonwood Collective is here to help those in need, to teach control, for the betterment of Werewolves around the world. Any who come to Moonwood Mill have a pack waiting for them."</Text>
  <Text Key="E644EBC2">Magical moon symbols glow around the edge of the page from {0.SimFirstName}'s Lunar Epiphany, offering an explanation on Operation High Fang. After the end of Operation Eternal Flame, a group of Vampires came out of hiding to start the initiative. Through a successful propaganda campaign, they branded Vampires as refined and classy, boasting of what they offer through their historical knowledge and charismatic ways. At the same time, they smeared Werewolves as dirty and dangerous monsters, lacking in control. The results were catastrophic for the new Werewolf communities who were still maturing as an occult.</Text>
  <Text Key="A23641DD">The magical moon symbols along the edge of the page seem to glow, and the real author of this book is revealed to {0.SimFirstName} through a Lunar Epiphany. Vulfgang Mulder is truly Wolfgang Wilder of Moonwood Mill. </Text>
  <Text Key="CE9DD2F5">A Lunar Epiphany comes over {0.SimFirstName} as {M0.he}{F0.she} stares at the moon scribbles at the bottom of the page. These books were written in an attempt to undo the damage caused by Operation High Fang, a Vampire-led propaganda initiative.</Text>
  <Text Key="17EEB650">{0.SimFirstName}'s gaze slides from the writing in the book to the magical moon glyphs around the edge of the page. The symbols speak of control, of freeing yourself from the bindings of rage, so that you might live in harmony with your inner wolf.</Text>
  <Text Key="17F0B8E1">{0.SimFirstName} found something while scavenging! \n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="6E023211">Finding a Cure</Text>
  <Text Key="8E6E7361">Lunar Attunement</Text>
  <Text Key="25A778E7">Solo Hunt</Text>
  <Text Key="23D75027">Community Canine</Text>
  <Text Key="12A2E25C">Going Wild Worldwide</Text>
  <Text Key="2352141D">Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="E693C705">Fangs for the memories, even if they weren't so great!\n{0.SimFirstName} has successfully cured {F0.her}{M0.his} lycanthropy. Now that Fury is no longer knocking on {F0.her}{M0.his} door, where will life take {F0.her}{M0.him}?</Text>
  <Text Key="45657F41">This Sim seeks a cure for lycanthropy to live {M0.his}{F0.her} life as a non-werewolf Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2051695">Cure Seeker</Text>
  <Text Key="04EDCBE5">{0.SimFirstName} has successfully unleashed {M0.his}{F0.her} inner beast and basked in the moonlight! The time has come to decide whether {M0.he}{F0.she} wants to join a pack, carve {M0.his}{F0.her} own path as a lone wolf, or return to life as a normal Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="80CC32E1">This Sim wants to unleash {M0.his}{F0.her} inner beast and become a werewolf!</Text>
  <Text Key="AE2B07B5">Werewolf Initiate</Text>
  <Text Key="ACB1F87B">Who's afraid of the big bad wolf? Not {0.SimFirstName}, {F0.she}{M0.he} IS the big bad wolf! \n{0.SimFirstName} has completed the journey to become the most independent and fearsome werewolf in Moonwood Mill. What will {F0.she}{M0.he} accomplish next?</Text>
  <Text Key="B86ECA93">This Sim wants to become the strongest and most feared werewolf, all on {M0.his}{F0.her} own!</Text>
  <Text Key="D16C6F8F">Lone Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="39C1F42B">{F0.She's}{M0.He's} style, {F0.she's}{M0.he's} grace, {F0.she's}{M0.he's} The Moonwood Collective's ace!  \n{0.SimFirstName} has risen the ranks and become the best ambassador the Collective has to offer. What path will {F0.she}{M0.he} walk next?</Text>
  <Text Key="EE7C9703">This Sim wants to join The Moonwood Collective and become a friendly werewolf ambassador to all!</Text>
  <Text Key="15CB295F">Emissary of the Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="A2A97F9C">Whoa! {0.SimFirstName} is like, totally radical, dude!\n{0.SimFirstName} has risen the ranks and proved to the world that the Wildfangs are here to stay. What adventure will {F0.she}{M0.he} conquer next?</Text>
  <Text Key="A0829BFC">This Sim wants to join the Wildfangs and unapologetically take on the world as a Werewolf!</Text>
  <Text Key="C0784F58">Wildfang Renegade</Text>
  <Text Key="D6D0810C">(From Sniffing Out a Hidden Trove)</Text>
  <Text Key="72D7863A">(From Being Near Another Sim's Marked Territory)</Text>
  <Text Key="809A3B12">(From Scaring Other Sims)</Text>
  <Text Key="45937708">(From Being Near a Transformed Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="97A59AA6">(From Something Nearby)</Text>
  <Text Key="4EAEF65C">(From Nighttime Howling Point)</Text>
  <Text Key="2CE675D8">Alpha Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="539D5467">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Win most fights and challenges against other werewolves.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThose fledgling pups are beneath you now. As a natural Alpha, enjoy quicker pack advancement, the ease of taking leadership of a pack, and better results when fighting other werewolves. And if you run into Greg, give him a taste of his own medicine. </Text>
  <Text Key="56535364">Curse Bearer</Text>
  <Text Key="4432941B">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Turn other Sims into Werewolves via a cursed bite.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nBearer of the Curse. Seek others, grant them the gift. Seek the moon, embrace its light. </Text>
  <Text Key="37985465">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Read the ancient werewolf writings.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nEureka! {0.SimFirstName} can comprehend the lost secrets of the moon! This is an important step towards understanding the history and nature of werewolves, and can lead to learning how to cure this ailment for good.\n\n&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Unlocked by reading werewolf-related literature.&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="45C7F2D9">Lunar Epiphany</Text>
  <Text Key="3F52E21E">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Read the ancient werewolf writings.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nEureka! {0.SimFirstName} can comprehend the lost secrets of the moon! This is an important step towards understanding the history and nature of werewolves, and can lead to learning how to cure this ailment for good.</Text>
  <Text Key="5E8689C9">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Transform into beast mode at will!&lt;/font&gt;\n\nStaying contained and away from others while rampaging will grant {0.SimFirstName} a brief moment of clarity. This insight will help {M0.him}{F0.her} master the art of transformation, granting the ability to call upon the beast form at any time while still retaining a semblance of humanity. Be warned! Even with this newfound mastery, {0.SimFirstName} will still be susceptible to the ever encroaching Fury boiling within.\n\n&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Unlocked by preventing your werewolf from scaring any Sims during a Fury-induced rampage.&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="E09B190D">Transformation Mastery</Text>
  <Text Key="B84D19FA">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Transform into beast mode at will!&lt;/font&gt;\n\nStaying contained and away from others while rampaging will grant {0.SimFirstName} a brief moment of clarity. This insight will help {M0.him}{F0.her} master the art of transformation, granting the ability to call upon the beast form at any time while still retaining a semblance of humanity. Be warned! Even with this newfound mastery, {0.SimFirstName} will still be susceptible to the ever encroaching Fury boiling within.</Text>
  <Text Key="C38F8CD4">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Use diplomacy to win over werewolf allies.&lt;/font&gt;\n\n{0.SimFirstName} now has the social tools to convince others that werewolves are still &lt;i&gt;somewhat&lt;/i&gt; human. Use {M0.his}{F0.her} new Werewolf Diplomacy skills to bestow the "Werewolf Ally" Trait on Sims, changing their outlook on werewolves forever.\n\n&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Successfully Ask for Werewolf Sympathy on a non-werewolf Sim.&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="9264FFA8">Werewolf Diplomacy</Text>
  <Text Key="BC708017">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Use diplomacy to win over werewolf allies.&lt;/font&gt;\n\n{0.SimFirstName} now has the social tools to convince others that werewolves are still &lt;i&gt;somewhat&lt;/i&gt; human. Use {M0.his}{F0.her} new Werewolf Diplomacy skills to bestow the "Werewolf Ally" Trait on Sims, changing their outlook on werewolves forever.</Text>
  <Text Key="9D700CB6">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Help pacify other werewolves.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nAfter spending enough time around other werewolves, {0.SimFirstName} has learned a thing or two about their behavior. Sometimes, a werewolf just needs another werewolf to hear them out. With Pacify, {M0.he}{F0.she} can now remove all Fury from another werewolf and even prevent them from rampaging. There, there, it's going to be okay.\n\n&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Unlocked by reaching Delta rank in a wolf pack.&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="EAC25182">Werewolf Empathy</Text>
  <Text Key="AAFBDE2D">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Help pacify other werewolves.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nAfter spending enough time around other werewolves, {0.SimFirstName} has learned a thing or two about their behavior. Sometimes, a werewolf just needs another werewolf to hear them out. With Pacify, {M0.he}{F0.she} can now remove all Fury from another werewolf and even prevent them from rampaging. There, there, it's going to be okay.</Text>
  <Text Key="93076855">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Enjoy scaring Sims and feel no guilt about it.&lt;/font&gt;\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has given in to the beast within and now has a thirst for chaos. Scaring others will now make {M0.him}{F0.her} feel playful! Sure, it's not nice to antagonize someone who is already terrified, but {0.SimFirstName} left nice on the side of the road a long time ago.\n\n&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Unlocked by running Ferocious Intimidation, Turn into Werewolf or Vicious Howl on a Sim who is already frightened, while below maximum Fury.&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="DD15AA29">Werewolf Menace</Text>
  <Text Key="74F49D8E">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Enjoy scaring Sims and feel no guilt about it.&lt;/font&gt;\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has given in to the beast within and now has a thirst for chaos. Scaring others will now make {M0.him}{F0.her} feel playful! Sure, it's not nice to antagonize someone who is already terrified, but {0.SimFirstName} left nice on the side of the road a long time ago.</Text>
  <Text Key="EAAD5BB5">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Teach other werewolves with skill and grace.&lt;/font&gt;\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has been around the block, and has a wealth of insight on all things werewolf. Werewolves under {M0.his}{F0.her} guidance will receive bonus rank, mood, and relationship gains when being mentored, taught to howl, or having werewolf experiences shared with them. \n\n&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Unlocked by running Practice Howling, Share Werewolf Experiences, or Pack Mentor as a Veteran werewolf on a Good Friend werewolf.&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="24927B09">Werewolf Mentorship</Text>
  <Text Key="DDF7F16E">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Teach other werewolves with skill and grace.&lt;/font&gt;\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has been around the block, and has a wealth of insight on all things werewolf. Werewolves under {M0.his}{F0.her} guidance will receive bonus rank, mood, and relationship gains when being mentored, taught to howl, or having werewolf experiences shared with them.</Text>
  <Text Key="75C43F10">Voracious Hunger</Text>
  <Text Key="E90C9E5F">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Devour objects to satisfy hunger.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nFeeling hungry? With this ability {0.SimFirstName} will be able to eat &lt;i&gt;almost&lt;/i&gt; anything. That new couch? Dinner. That priceless heirloom? Delicious. Is this a good idea? Who's to say. Will curiosity get the better of {M0.him}{F0.her}? Undoubtedly.</Text>
  <Text Key="FFE7602E">Enhanced Smell</Text>
  <Text Key="DA493481">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Sniff out information and treasure.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nWith a new heightened ability to smell, {0.SimFirstName} can put {M0.his}{F0.her} nose to the ground and smell emotions on other Sims, sniff out treasure buried in the backyard, or detect nearby occult Sims. Some things smell better than others, so get out there and sniff!</Text>
  <Text Key="EB3F4582">Ferocity</Text>
  <Text Key="6354122D">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Intimidate other Sims for fun and profit!&lt;/font&gt;\n\nUnlocking the ability to use Ferocious Intimidation on others, {0.SimFirstName} can now bear {M0.his}{F0.her} fangs and send Sims fleeing in terror! With any luck, they'll drop their wallet too. If being a bit beastly is wrong, {0.SimFirstName} doesn't want to be right.</Text>
  <Text Key="608BBBF3">Hunter</Text>
  <Text Key="02FD50D4">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Learn to hunt for food.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nWe all want our food to be fresh, but Werewolves want it &lt;i&gt;fresher&lt;/i&gt;. Wherever {M0.he}{F0.she} is, {0.SimFirstName} will be able to Hunt for Food out in nature's buffet and grab a bite - and some meat for later - whenever hunger strikes!</Text>
  <Text Key="46B6E8A6">Requires the Hunter Ability to be unlocked</Text>
  <Text Key="398B5622">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Lead a group hunt.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nEverything is better with friends, especially combing the wilderness for tasty treats. The Lead Hunting Party interaction lets {0.SimFirstName} bring others - even non-werewolf friends and family! - along on a hunt. Since teamwork makes the dream work, {0.SimFirstName} will gain additional goodies too.\n\n&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Requires the Hunter Perk to be unlocked&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="6BFD1E7E">Hunting Party</Text>
  <Text Key="967BB731">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Lead a group hunt.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nEverything is better with friends, especially combing the wilderness for tasty treats. The Lead Hunting Party interaction lets {0.SimFirstName} bring others - even non-werewolf friends and family! - along on a hunt. Since teamwork makes the dream work, {0.SimFirstName} will gain additional goodies too.</Text>
  <Text Key="CDCD9F1D">Requires the Natural Healing Ability to be unlocked</Text>
  <Text Key="3C517DD2">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Live forever!&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThe gift is finally realized; As long as the moon remains, so shall you. \n\n&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Requires the Natural Healing Ability to be unlocked&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="FB35F28E">Immortal Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="B6B06261">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Live forever!&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThe gift is finally realized; As long as the moon remains, so shall you. </Text>
  <Text Key="198603ED">Legacy of the Lycan</Text>
  <Text Key="5F15D65A">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Turn Ability Points into Satisfaction Points.&lt;/font&gt;\n\n{0.SimFirstName}'s journey as a werewolf knows no ends! As {M0.he}{F0.she} continues to rank up, {M0.he}{F0.she} can turn that extra werewolf knowledge into 250 Satisfaction Points.\n\n&lt;i&gt;This ability may be taken multiple times.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="68DC9FF2">Lunar Blessing</Text>
  <Text Key="C38EC4BD">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Extend benefits from the lunar cycle.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThe moon impacts Werewolves daily, from learning speed and quality of sleep to how everyone interacts together. Let the lunar gifts affect {0.SimFirstName} all day long with this Lunar Blessing.</Text>
  <Text Key="CFE9686F">Lunar Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="A2BA5688">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Howl under the moonlight to transform temperaments!&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThe most forbidden howl. Release what little remains of {0.SimFirstName}'s humanity and succumb to the moon's glow. Be warned, {F0.she}{M0.he} may never be the same again!</Text>
  <Text Key="1DCD100E">Lunar Resistance</Text>
  <Text Key="44FBD7E1">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Protect against the moon's harmful effects.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nWhile a full moon is a glorious sight to many, it sparks dread for some werewolves. With Lunar Resistance, a werewolf will no longer feel its influence on their psyche, letting them explore the night unhindered.</Text>
  <Text Key="A380C84A">Natural Healing</Text>
  <Text Key="A422E975">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Recover from injuries more quickly!&lt;/font&gt;\n\n{0.SimFirstName} already feels anything but normal, but with a bit of effort and focus, the strength of the werewolf blood in {M0.his}{F0.her} body can be harnessed to recover from various fights, injuries, and all physical maladies much more quickly.</Text>
  <Text Key="E68C251F">Nightvision</Text>
  <Text Key="17DC3318">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Explore more with enhanced eyesight.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nExploring the underground tunnels beneath Moonwood Mill can sometimes lead down to a dark dead end. With this ability, {0.SimFirstName} will be able to conquer them by seeing things {M0.he}{F0.she} may have otherwise missed, as well as spend less time hunting for prey at night.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E66CBC0">Pack Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="8C57BE6F">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Howl to the pack to fulfill social needs.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nUse this new Pack Howl to communicate over great distances with other canine-minded creatures. Is there any sweeter sound than howls on the wind? Ditch the cell phone for the social dopamine drip, return to wolf. </Text>
  <Text Key="CA3F360B">Personal Grooming</Text>
  <Text Key="DCDA3F0C">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Lick away the dirt!&lt;/font&gt;\n\nIs {0.SimFirstName} feeling dirty? Just have {M0.him}{F0.her} lick {M0.himself}{F0.herself} clean. Why re-invent the wheel when the answer was inside us all along. Social appropriateness of using Groom Self may vary.</Text>
  <Text Key="9627E48B">Primal Instincts</Text>
  <Text Key="A83F558C">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Tap into your instincts for a quick confidence boost.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nWho needs all these unnecessary emotions? Being a werewolf who can Activate Primal Instincts means channeling the beast within to focus the mind on what's important: being a confident werewolf who can keep other more negative moods at bay.</Text>
  <Text Key="ECC06911">Scavenger</Text>
  <Text Key="FB914E16">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Dig up lost treasures and artifacts.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThere is a wealth of lost artifacts right beneath {0.SimFirstName}'s feet. With the ability to Scavenge Ground, {M0.he'll}{F0.she'll} be able to pull treasures right out of the earth with {M0.his}{F0.her} bare hands. Who cares what the neighbors think?</Text>
  <Text Key="81B2A0A1">Somber Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="F3932446">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Learn a howl that reduces fury.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nBeing a werewolf is hard, and sometimes {0.SimFirstName} has just gotta speak {M0.his}{F0.her} truth. {M0.He'll}{F0.She'll} be able to release a Somber Howl from time to time to calm down and reduce {M0.his}{F0.her} Fury.</Text>
  <Text Key="77947FA7">Super Speed</Text>
  <Text Key="D5DB2700">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Run at super speed!&lt;/font&gt;\n\nPut those werewolf muscles to good use and zoom everywhere! {0.SimFirstName} can now choose to Enable Super Speed at any moment. Run after the mailman! Run into the woods! The possibilities are endless.</Text>
  <Text Key="2CE7A61A">Territory Marking</Text>
  <Text Key="2B7B90A5">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Leave a mark in the world and relieve bladder need.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nBe free. Enjoy the relief of being able to Mark Territory anywhere and at any time. The world is your canvas.</Text>
  <Text Key="8D82D71D">The Will to Resist</Text>
  <Text Key="A408E72A">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Regain control while rampaging. &lt;/font&gt;\n\nWith some added mental fortitude, a large dollop of willpower, and a few breathing exercises, {0.SimFirstName} can now attempt to Regain Control after losing it and entering a rampage. If successful, {0.SimFirstName} will immediately stop rampaging.</Text>
  <Text Key="DB77DF28">Requires the Scavenger Ability to be unlocked</Text>
  <Text Key="7838C90E">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Quickly travel around the world by digging tunnels.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nBore through the earth with a handy Tunnel Here! Perfect for wanting to make a grand entrance or needing to make a quick escape. {0.SimFirstName} will make it look effortless!\n\n&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Requires the Scavenger Ability to be unlocked&lt;/font&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="D5FF82EA">Tunneler</Text>
  <Text Key="562CD615">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Quickly travel around the world by digging tunnels.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nBore through the earth with a handy Tunnel Here! Perfect for wanting to make a grand entrance or needing to make a quick escape. {0.SimFirstName} will make it look effortless!</Text>
  <Text Key="BA363F6D">Vicious Howl </Text>
  <Text Key="A36E49DA">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Let loose a terrifying howl.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nMaster the Vicious Howl, a scream that strikes fear in the hearts of all. Incredibly satisfying and fun - at least for {0.SimFirstName}, though maybe not so much for other Sims who might be nearby?</Text>
  <Text Key="E52CCD08">Wolf Nap</Text>
  <Text Key="376AA177">&lt;font color = '#1e81e6'&gt;Sleep anywhere on the ground using the Wolf Nap Ability.&lt;/font&gt;\n\nIt's time you learned that beds are just suggestions. Now {0.SimFirstName} can curl up into a ball and sleep anywhere!</Text>
  <Text Key="F9A22BA8">Ahhh... moonlit serenity is floating around {0.SimFirstName} like a delicate silk scarf.</Text>
  <Text Key="9CCAA8C7">Moonpetal Calm</Text>
  <Text Key="D170B1BE">Whoa... ok. {0.SimFirstName} is feeling a little &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; glowy and serene. But maybe it's not such a bad thing? Everything is... still. </Text>
  <Text Key="6BF39A41">Moonpetal Stillness</Text>
  <Text Key="41A669BC">Power-Sip MIDNIGHT, flavored with the &lt;i&gt;essence&lt;/i&gt; of night. Wondering how we managed to bottle the very concept of time itself? The truth is that &lt;i&gt;it doesn't matter&lt;/i&gt;. Nothing matters. All that matters is the SIP. And the POWER!! &lt;i&gt;POWER-SIP!!&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="56B63113">MIDNIGHT!! SIPPING!!</Text>
  <Text Key="072D7C71">{0.SimFirstName} is over the moon right now, packed to the gills with energy!</Text>
  <Text Key="74834A44">Power of the Luna Fish</Text>
  <Text Key="BC6B2E0A">Why did {0.SimFirstName} eat Wolfsbane? The warning is literally in the name!</Text>
  <Text Key="8E190B15">Wolf's Bane</Text>
  <Text Key="40BA4E36">{0.SimFirstName} is feeling well-rested after sleeping during the New Moon. It'll be difficult for {M0.him}{F0.her} to stay in a bad mood today!</Text>
  <Text Key="B1258269">Lunar Peace</Text>
  <Text Key="AE54495C">(From Sleeping during the New Moon)</Text>
  <Text Key="68F5501D">Ruh-roh, {0.SimFirstName} can feel the pull of the Full Moon. Ahh-wooooooo!  </Text>
  <Text Key="4BEE4308">Call of the Moon</Text>
  <Text Key="9C9B2459">Thanks to {0.SimFirstName}'s Lunar Resistance, {M0.he}{F0.she} can block out most of negative influence of a full moon, but {M0.he}{F0.she] still feels its sting. </Text>
  <Text Key="9D3D7FDC">The Moon's Gaze</Text>
  <Text Key="3F09AB83">The full moon is quickly approaching, and {0.SimFirstName} knows what that means...</Text>
  <Text Key="665D9DD2">Full Moon Imminent!</Text>
  <Text Key="E6464BD9">The full moon is quickly approaching, but {0.SimFirstName} knows {M0.he}{F0.she} is resistant to its magical effects. Silly moon.</Text>
  <Text Key="315F5E5C">Full Moon Imminent</Text>
  <Text Key="3A53CE7B">{0.SimFirstName} dreamed that the moon was on its side and {M0.he}{F0.she} was running back and forth atop it as it tilted! What a rolly moon!</Text>
  <Text Key="96DC72DA">Waxing Crescent Moon Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="C0E36351">{0.SimFirstName} had a dream {M0.he}{F0.she} was playing hide and seek with the moon. It really is a nice moon.</Text>
  <Text Key="E76BBFA4">First Quarter Moon Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="6D291809">{0.SimFirstName} had a dream that the moon was small and kept eating cheese until it was a waxing gibbous. How funny!</Text>
  <Text Key="4829F16C">Waxing Gibbous Moon Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="390C076D">{0.SimFirstName} had a dream and the moon was red. It made {0.SimFirstName} very angry!</Text>
  <Text Key="2E816638">Full Moon Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="3EC12931">{0.SimFirstName} had a dream that {M0.he}{F0.she} was a magician and turned an egg into the moon!</Text>
  <Text Key="40D48804">Waning Gibbous Moon Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="13CC19FA">{0.SimFirstName} had a dream the moon was a cookie and Princess Cordelia took it and split it in half to share with {M0.him}{F0.her}. </Text>
  <Text Key="E1C13AA5">Third Quarter Moon Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="0E3D0FD3">{0.SimFirstName} had a dream that {M0.he}{F0.she} had to fit the crescent moon into a box with various-shaped holes on top. Thankfully, the crescent goes inside the... circle.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D012A82">Waning Crescent Moon Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="49FDBDE3">{0.SimFirstName} had a dream that {M0.he}{F0.she} put the moon in {M0.his}{F0.her} pocket, but the pocket had a hole and the moon got lost, and {M0.he}{F0.she} couldn't find it, because it wasn't glowy!</Text>
  <Text Key="571785B2">New Moon Dream</Text>
  <Text Key="E35EFF95">Famished Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="3CFAF654">Beastly Hunger</Text>
  <Text Key="B67E0CCD">Directly ingesting the Moonpetal flower is not recommended in most cases.</Text>
  <Text Key="AEC16B18">Foul Flora</Text>
  <Text Key="124ACA57">Spending time together can definitely draw you closer when it's with your Lycan Bond! </Text>
  <Text Key="B3C6AB2E">Friends Fur-Ever</Text>
  <Text Key="59ED58E1">Let’s raise the woof! {0.SimFirstName} is having a great time with their Lycan Bond. </Text>
  <Text Key="84215C94">Howlin' Good Time</Text>
  <Text Key="459E0A03">{0.SimFirstName} always feels a bit of magic when {M0.he}{F0.she} remembers that special first kiss under the full moon. </Text>
  <Text Key="5DB77152">Moonkissed</Text>
  <Text Key="EDFC0FC4">{0.SimFirstName} is as happy as a full moon when {M0.he}{F0.she} remembers that delightful first kiss under it...</Text>
  <Text Key="D413FE8B">Lunar Puppy Love</Text>
  <Text Key="5F9B79C7">{0.SimFirstName} feels horribly guilty about scaring loved ones. It's not easy being a beast at times.</Text>
  <Text Key="70FAAC7E">Big Sad Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="38575494">NO MORE!</Text>
  <Text Key="EC5C5E7B">WORK IS THE POOP</Text>
  <Text Key="FF5261EA">{0.SimFirstName} has the sudden urge to pick a fight with someone. </Text>
  <Text Key="EA0B7175">Overwhelming Aggression!</Text>
  <Text Key="39D91478">{0.SimFirstName} has a deep craving for fresh meat.</Text>
  <Text Key="DD41C477">I Need REAL Meat!</Text>
  <Text Key="3B6F193F">Flashing lights! So pretty! </Text>
  <Text Key="AE85DD66">Screen Time!</Text>
  <Text Key="0E233B25">Ugh! How do these other Werewolves outrank me? What do they have that I don't?</Text>
  <Text Key="8495FAA0">Bottom of the Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="CE31905D">Nobody knows what I'm going through as a Werewolf... Sometimes I feel like I don't belong anywhere.</Text>
  <Text Key="D5034B48">Nobody Understands Me!</Text>
  <Text Key="E1DBFFDC">Love is in the air and {0.SimName} is feeling a little frisky. Time to test out those pick-up lines!</Text>
  <Text Key="472C2BB3">Better Find Somebody to Love</Text>
  <Text Key="0406C820">BASK IN MY RADIANCE.</Text>
  <Text Key="D28C8B6F">I'M. SO. CLEAN.</Text>
  <Text Key="C3703000">EVERY MOMENT IS TORTURE UNTIL I'M CLEAN AGAIN.</Text>
  <Text Key="44B91ACF">MUST. BE. CLEAN.</Text>
  <Text Key="740F5A25">{0.SimFirstName} wants to curl up and sleep for hours. {F0.She}{M0.He} gets a little cranky otherwise...</Text>
  <Text Key="A61227A0">Need to Hibernate!</Text>
  <Text Key="BA9C701D">My sleep schedule is all wrong! Night time is wolf time!</Text>
  <Text Key="3BF9A308">Daytime is for Sleeping!</Text>
  <Text Key="81FA80DF">What is this &lt;i&gt;feeling&lt;/i&gt;? You're all supposed to like me! Start liking me already!</Text>
  <Text Key="109DD186">Narcissist's Nightmare</Text>
  <Text Key="95E7AA75">Ouch, that fight was lost with a whimper. {0.SimName} better run off to lick {F0.her}{M0.his} wounds.</Text>
  <Text Key="979CF310">Wounded Pride</Text>
  <Text Key="B41C1CD2">{0.SimFirstName} needs to get outside! Right now!</Text>
  <Text Key="46AB91ED">The Walls are Closing In!</Text>
  <Text Key="5CBA2189">MY EARSSSSS!</Text>
  <Text Key="EFF3D5EC">LOUD NOISES!</Text>
  <Text Key="0826C1FE">The beast hungers! {0.SimFirstName} needs food NOW!</Text>
  <Text Key="36E16C81">Sudden Craving!</Text>
  <Text Key="D600F7F4">{0.SimName}'s survival instincts have kicked in, and the adrenaline is flowing. </Text>
  <Text Key="7226025B">Fight or Flight!</Text>
  <Text Key="192FD91F">{0.SimFirstName} has a sudden desire to pee &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; wants others to know this space belongs to {F0.her}{M0.him}!</Text>
  <Text Key="676C092B">{0.SimFirstName} has to pee &lt;i&gt;and &lt;/i&gt; wants others to know this space belongs to {F0.her}{M0.him}. Multi-tasking!</Text>
  <Text Key="A9564B2A">Gotta Mark Something!</Text>
  <Text Key="F99303B9">See that? That's mine! No touchy!</Text>
  <Text Key="264E5CBC">Territory Marked!</Text>
  <Text Key="B855D823">Nobody talk to me until I dry myself off...</Text>
  <Text Key="338E69F2">I'm Wet and I Hate It</Text>
  <Text Key="BC2C1735">This sensation is horrible! How do Sims &lt;i&gt;enjoy&lt;/i&gt; this?</Text>
  <Text Key="DA5A6201">THINKING HARD. HEAD HURT.</Text>
  <Text Key="FEE3EB34">OW! MY HEAD!</Text>
  <Text Key="10782E09">Deep down inside, am I truly a monster?</Text>
  <Text Key="FD9F536C">Transformation Guilt</Text>
  <Text Key="4564B976">Everything feels so much harder as a Werewolf. Will I ever adjust to this beastly life?</Text>
  <Text Key="2CCF71A9">What Have I Become?</Text>
  <Text Key="4E44FC77">Rampaging just doesn't have the same zing as it used to now that {0.SimFirstName} can just hang out in Beast form. </Text>
  <Text Key="AD8A79CE">Well, That was Weird</Text>
  <Text Key="AAB70C99">I can smell something wonderful! I need to dig! </Text>
  <Text Key="F0FF931C">Nearby Treasure!</Text>
  <Text Key="167F454C">I can't help it sometimes! These things just happen! YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND!</Text>
  <Text Key="80F7F303">Don't Look at Me!</Text>
  <Text Key="41D95F48">Delicious! The way nature intended! With fresh meat in {0.SimFirstName}'s stomach, the pangs of hunger are temporarily gone!</Text>
  <Text Key="FB13C1E7">Fresh Meat!</Text>
  <Text Key="4DFF372C">{0.SimFirstName} is feeling great! Hunting comes as naturally as breathing for Werewolves! </Text>
  <Text Key="74922663">Hunter's Stride</Text>
  <Text Key="895BDE3A">It was all a blur... Where did this food even come from? Why on earth did I agree to do this?</Text>
  <Text Key="50F256E5">The Horrors I've Seen</Text>
  <Text Key="7899D128">{0.SimFirstName} was rattled to the core! </Text>
  <Text Key="618DA147">Ferociously Intimidated!</Text>
  <Text Key="D17E38EC">Being near the markings of another Werewolf is like nails on a chalk board. Indescribable, and immensely unpleasant. </Text>
  <Text Key="B48FB923">Nearby Marked Territory</Text>
  <Text Key="3FFEF63A">Something smells... weird. </Text>
  <Text Key="34C01EE5">What &lt;i&gt;Is&lt;/i&gt; That Smell?</Text>
  <Text Key="721B0C1A">Those unnecessary feeling of uneasiness and stress are gone! Maybe those howling wolf shirts were onto something, because this feels great!</Text>
  <Text Key="36CA5545">Primal Instinct</Text>
  <Text Key="611C5CF9">Although {0.SimFirstName} feels a little calmer, {M0.he}{F0.she} can't help but feel a little sad after that howl. </Text>
  <Text Key="DE0A03FC">Big Sad Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="1E28F8C8">Ugh, is there a walking corpse nearby? </Text>
  <Text Key="BCB45667">Smells Like Vampire</Text>
  <Text Key="7CAD284F">Somehow that hit the spot! Not bad!</Text>
  <Text Key="2AC03916">Surprisingly Tasty!</Text>
  <Text Key="5F803A1E">What is that &lt;i&gt;smell&lt;/i&gt;?! It smells incredible! Have Sims always smelled this good? {0.SimFirstName} is absolutely entranced by this wonderful aroma.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F239D21">Tantalizing Aroma</Text>
  <Text Key="9D79E912">9 out of 10 Dentists agree that eating random objects is a really bad idea.</Text>
  <Text Key="BFF9C02D">Toothache</Text>
  <Text Key="38F8F382">Could a brighter future between Sim and Werewolf be possible?</Text>
  <Text Key="B187927D">Werewolf Diplomacy!</Text>
  <Text Key="750EDF0C">No matter how you slice it, a Werewolf is a Werewolf. There will always be a lingering unease. </Text>
  <Text Key="A3E614C3">Werewolf Distrust</Text>
  <Text Key="7897E2A0">{0.SimFirstName} has a great Werewolf teacher! It's all so clear now! With proper guidance, {F0.she}{M0.he} now temporarily gains increased Werewolf Experience!</Text>
  <Text Key="BC87D2EF">Werewolf Guidance</Text>
  <Text Key="1383346F">Someday, {0.SimFirstName} hopes to be half the Werewolf {M0.his}{F0.her} teacher is!</Text>
  <Text Key="4783B953">Oh, you little rascal! {0.SimFirstName} is reveling in the delight of terrorizing others. While in this giddy state, {M0.his}{F0.her} Fun gains are doubled too! </Text>
  <Text Key="DAB9EF02">Werewolf Menace</Text>
  <Text Key="A4A65438">Undoubtedly it was delicious, but at the cost of {0.SimFirstName}'s humanity. </Text>
  <Text Key="30058C37">What Have I Done?</Text>
  <Text Key="45A9EEE1">{0.SimFirstName} is near other like-minded kin.</Text>
  <Text Key="04673E94">The Wolves Among Us</Text>
  <Text Key="E3DABA49">{0.SimFirstName} has asserted dominance in the sibling hierarchy.</Text>
  <Text Key="D8F8B2AC">Alpha of the House</Text>
  <Text Key="78857C74">Welcome to legendary status. </Text>
  <Text Key="99EB67DB">Legendary Apex</Text>
  <Text Key="E464FA5B">Growing up is weird enough as it is, but now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;?</Text>
  <Text Key="186D183A">Beastly Growth Spurt</Text>
  <Text Key="2BC08DBF">Absolutely disgusting! Like drinking from a dog bowl! Who thought this was a good idea?</Text>
  <Text Key="E73F12E6">Disgusting Dog Water!</Text>
  <Text Key="9C62DE35">(From Flirting With Someone Other Than Your Fated Mate)</Text>
  <Text Key="F6163BB2">Sigh... why did {0.SimFirstName} even think it was a good idea to try fighting a Werewolf?</Text>
  <Text Key="E926D64D">Beaten by the Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="F743F916">THIS ADRENALINE RUSH! {0.SimFirstName} never could have imagined {F0.she}{M0.he} would beat a Werewolf in a fight!</Text>
  <Text Key="AF0889C9">Bettered the Beast!</Text>
  <Text Key="E7AFBAEF">Rough and tumble, but with none of the trouble! {0.SimFirstName}'s feeling pretty good about {F0.her}{M0.his} fighting skills after a friendly spar with a fellow Werewolf.</Text>
  <Text Key="C2856D36">Super Sparring</Text>
  <Text Key="607F0C0D">Yikes! How could {0.SimFirstName} lose to that stinky mongrel?</Text>
  <Text Key="FBA99358">A Fistful of Fur</Text>
  <Text Key="FDB04817">That stinky little pup thought it could beat {0.SimFirstName}? Bah! It's vampires that own the night, obviously!</Text>
  <Text Key="11063BEE">Plasma Power!</Text>
  <Text Key="83748470">HA! Honestly, did they really think {0.SimFirstName} would lose?</Text>
  <Text Key="4C1A831F">Puny Sim!</Text>
  <Text Key="2A5AB2BB">Take that, plasma-drinker! The night belongs to us!</Text>
  <Text Key="8BFFF51A">Winner Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="D18A5B6F">Losing to a puny normal Sim? {0.SimFirstName} is never going to live this one down... </Text>
  <Text Key="A4FA66B6">What the Wolf?</Text>
  <Text Key="49BA4E78">What an embarrassment to Werewolves everywhere! How could {0.SimFirstName} lose to that plasma-drinking weirdo?</Text>
  <Text Key="F2CC5277">Vampiric Victor?</Text>
  <Text Key="7DD223AC">I wanna hug it!</Text>
  <Text Key="D6A643E3">Fluffy Puppy!</Text>
  <Text Key="21A6688D">{0.SimFirstName} is losing {M0.his}{F0.her} grip on humanity, and will soon give into the beast within. Make sure to keep {0.SimFirstName} a safe distance away from anyone. You wouldn't want anything bad to happen, &lt;i&gt;right&lt;/i&gt;?</Text>
  <Text Key="2BB000D8">The Beast Beckons</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE027E6">That pack was {0.SimFirstName}'s home... what is {F0.she}{M0.he} going to do now?</Text>
  <Text Key="F19479F9">Hopelessly Pack-less</Text>
  <Text Key="E8BB9D8C">Although not quite yet a full fledged Werewolf, {0.SimFirstName} still feels the agonizing influence of the Moon. </Text>
  <Text Key="045B0843">Moon Madness</Text>
  <Text Key="295197D0">You can never be too careful around Werewolves, especially transformed ones!</Text>
  <Text Key="1E91ABFF">Beastly Presence</Text>
  <Text Key="B934D342">{0.SimFirstName} isn't just bellyaching, it really hurts!</Text>
  <Text Key="70326C3D">New Fang Pain</Text>
  <Text Key="C3DD7D24">Something feels indescribably wrong about all of this. Can {0.SimFirstName} defy Fate?</Text>
  <Text Key="5A9FD16B">Not Meant to Be</Text>
  <Text Key="20E6CEFA">RAMPAGE!</Text>
  <Text Key="81B08376">{0.SimFirstName}'s fury is unleashed! Werewolves who are rampaging are on a merciless warpath, and have little control of themselves. The path that all Werewolves walk is certainly cruel.</Text>
  <Text Key="349653DB">{0.SimFirstName}'s fury is unleashed! Werewolves who are rampaging are on a merciless warpath, and have little control of themselves. The path that all Werewolves walk is certainly cruel.</Text>
  <Text Key="C0732631">My memory is a little foggy, but I'm pretty sure whatever I just did, I regret.</Text>
  <Text Key="B85FEF04">I'd Rather Not Talk About It</Text>
  <Text Key="B661BAB1">YOU DONUT!!! DID YOU EVEN TASTE THIS?!\n\nGET! OUT! OF! MY! KITCHEN!</Text>
  <Text Key="AF268484">IT'S RAAAAWWWWWWW</Text>
  <Text Key="0503CE85">A Werewolf has lost control and is on the loose!</Text>
  <Text Key="C5FFAC80">WEREWOLF!!</Text>
  <Text Key="7FC68F73">{0.SimFirstName} is feeling a little strain on {F0.her}{M0.his} vocal chords. Better give it a rest for a little while. </Text>
  <Text Key="F3DD94A2">Sore Throat!</Text>
  <Text Key="7B74D629">{0.SimFirstName} will never quite get used to this newfound strength. For Werewolves, sometimes even mundane tasks become a challenge.</Text>
  <Text Key="337E7F0C">Stronger than I Thought</Text>
  <Text Key="017E9F19">Maybe someday society will accept us...</Text>
  <Text Key="9464C29C">Sympathy Denied</Text>
  <Text Key="7B68EB68">{0.SimFirstName} has mastered the ability to stay comfortably in {M0.his}{F0.her} beastly form. In this form, Werewolf Experience and Skill gains are increased, but Fury gains are increased as well. </Text>
  <Text Key="6FB4B487">Transformation Mastery</Text>
  <Text Key="885F0FF6">Did you see that?! Werewolves are so cool! I wanna be a Werewolf when I grow up too!</Text>
  <Text Key="4E09AD29">Werewolves are AWESOME!</Text>
  <Text Key="A557D649">What just happened to me? Where did I run off to? I have so many questions. Is this what being a Werewolf is like?! </Text>
  <Text Key="CB6D46AC">What Happened?! Where am I?!</Text>
  <Text Key="705617E5">And I'd do it again, too!</Text>
  <Text Key="C01B0F60">I Woohoo'd a Werewolf!</Text>
  <Text Key="786C1729">That never gets more pleasant...</Text>
  <Text Key="4C8E720C">Worst. Headache. Imaginable. </Text>
  <Text Key="BB180AD0">So long and thanks for all the beef! </Text>
  <Text Key="5A2494FF">Curse Free!</Text>
  <Text Key="B921D365">{0.SimFirstName} is feeling much better. That was a close call!</Text>
  <Text Key="6CD269E0">Werebies Free!</Text>
  <Text Key="236C734E">What was that big hairy monster?! {0.SimFirstName} was just attacked and has a painful bite to prove it! </Text>
  <Text Key="39A8D871">Bit out of the Blue!</Text>
  <Text Key="72967297">{0.SimFirstName} seems to be getting hungry much faster than usual. {F0.She}{M0.He}'s absolutely famished!</Text>
  <Text Key="D6D3B36E">Insatiable Hunger</Text>
  <Text Key="CC8539C0">{0.SimFirstName} is ravenous! Something is definitely happening… could {F0.she}{M0.he} be turning into a Werewolf?!</Text>
  <Text Key="D07BC68F">Ravenous Hunger</Text>
  <Text Key="DFA00696">Does this look infected to you? </Text>
  <Text Key="3A7C3A49">Painful Bite</Text>
  <Text Key="0089D083">{0.SimFirstName} is excited to become a Werewolf. It's only a matter of time before {F0.she}{M0.he} will be able to bare those teeth and claws!</Text>
  <Text Key="142AFCD2">There's a New Wolf in Town</Text>
  <Text Key="083D39D8">{0.SimFirstName} is feeling irate after that brush with Werewolves. {F0.She}{M0.He} feels a bit strange... is {F0.she}{M0.he} coming down with something? </Text>
  <Text Key="C05F1F57">Werebies</Text>
  <Text Key="D2633CAF">Something is definitely up with {0.SimFirstName}! Maybe the locals know more about this mysterious illness?</Text>
  <Text Key="2BDA12F6">Advanced Werebies </Text>
  <Text Key="7EB9003C">What was that big hairy monster?! {0.SimFirstName} just witnessed a Werewolf attack!</Text>
  <Text Key="2E452C93">Did That Just Happen?!</Text>
  <Text Key="45FFAE07">(From Nearby Allied Pack Member)</Text>
  <Text Key="69290FA5">And wolf for all! Seeing allies from the other pack around town really creates a sense of community.</Text>
  <Text Key="347E5020">All for Wolf! </Text>
  <Text Key="31728DD9">(From Nearby Rival Pack Member)</Text>
  <Text Key="1D3CC5EF">Argh, it's like they're EVERYWHERE! Can't that other pack just keep to their own side of town?</Text>
  <Text Key="F0F89E36">Feuding!</Text>
  <Text Key="4F596105">{0.SimFirstName} isn't actually a bad pack member, is {F0.she}{M0.he}? </Text>
  <Text Key="32AEDC00">Bad Pack Member?</Text>
  <Text Key="29D3F739">Well, that was sufficiently awkward and unpleasant. Time to be a better pack member so this doesn't happen again!</Text>
  <Text Key="366FDF3C">Disciplined!</Text>
  <Text Key="67C5D2F5">B-but I was happy in my old rank! How could my pack leader do this to me?</Text>
  <Text Key="B6360490">Demoted? Really?</Text>
  <Text Key="FF40F2CE">In order to maintain {F0.her}{M0.his} spot in the pack, {0.SimFirstName} needs to resolve all current warnings on pack values. Check the Werewolf Packs panel for more information on which pack values {0.SimFirstName} needs to address.</Text>
  <Text Key="D4D73EF1">Pack Probation!</Text>
  <Text Key="C1D3FB41">With doubts surrounding {F0.her}{M0.his} leadership ability, {0.SimFirstName} must work to secure {F0.her}{M0.his} position as leader. Check the Packs panel for more information on which pack values {F0.she}{M0.he} needs to address. </Text>
  <Text Key="92F32874">Leadership Under Scrutiny!</Text>
  <Text Key="D3FED392">Word is that the leader wants to see {0.SimFirstName}. {F0.She}{M0.He} should report in as soon as possible.</Text>
  <Text Key="F6E777AD">Report to Pack Leader</Text>
  <Text Key="CCBD77D9">Report to Leader of the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="93CDC5B4">Report to Leader of the Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="6D903F1E">{0.SimFirstName} currently has a warning for failing to uphold one of {F0.her}{M0.his} pack's values. Check the packs panel to see which pack value {0.SimFirstName} needs to address. </Text>
  <Text Key="73DA9C21">Pack Warning!</Text>
  <Text Key="0EDC0D7B">Sheesh, {0.SimFirstName} can't believe the nerve of the other pack's leader! How are they &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; confident when their pack is &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; lame? </Text>
  <Text Key="1332FFDA">The AUDACITY!</Text>
  <Text Key="71BEC424">Well, that went better than expected. It's pretty obvious which Alpha is better, if we're being honest... it's {0.SimFirstName}!</Text>
  <Text Key="3422F66B">The Alpha's Alpha</Text>
  <Text Key="99E60FEE">Aw, man! {0.SimFirstName} can't believe {F0.she}{M0.he} lost to someone from the other pack. How is {F0.she}{M0.he} ever going to show {F0.her}{M0.his} face at the pack hangout again?</Text>
  <Text Key="536E0B91">Let Down the Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="1606DFAE">Well, well, well! Check out {0.SimFirstName} the hotshot pack leader!</Text>
  <Text Key="BC057151">New Alpha in Town</Text>
  <Text Key="04FE3220">Take that! What a win for {0.SimFirstName}'s pack!</Text>
  <Text Key="5222A96F">Pride of the Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="4373EE91">Woooo yeah! Look who's fired up and ready to take on a new pack rank!</Text>
  <Text Key="7D7A46E4">Promoted!</Text>
  <Text Key="C037AD8C">Awoooo-d you look at that! {0.SimFirstName}'s howling with delight knowing {F0.she's}{M0.he's} upholding {F0.her}{M0.his} pack's values. </Text>
  <Text Key="9EF23843">Model Packmate</Text>
  <Text Key="ED0BBC4E">It doesn't take exceptional olfactory prowess to sense that there's a dangerous scent on the wind...</Text>
  <Text Key="3AA26371">A Dangerous Scent</Text>
  <Text Key="FD7AAA9E">{0.SimFirstName} has that distinct creepy feeling that someone... or &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; was watching {M0.him}{F0.her}.</Text>
  <Text Key="454F06A1">Something's Watching</Text>
  <Text Key="6EE7A895">{0.SimFirstName} is feeling physically chaotic after being bitten by Greg. </Text>
  <Text Key="B79370B0">Greg's Gift</Text>
  <Text Key="94E624ED">Miles and miles of wilderness but this point stands above it all. {0.SimFirstName} has never felt so close to the night sky.</Text>
  <Text Key="04F246B8">Close to the Stars</Text>
  <Text Key="5CA355FD">There's something mysterious and magical about swimming in Lake Lunvik under the full moon.</Text>
  <Text Key="6FDC2568">Alluring Lunar Lake</Text>
  <Text Key="CD62FDC5">{0.SimFirstName}'s enhanced senses can tell... there are wolves about. The magical kind. </Text>
  <Text Key="11F91EC0">Wolf Eyes Everywhere</Text>
  <Text Key="5ABF65BD">The moon has bestowed powers of concentration. Now {0.SimFirstName}'s concentration is impervious to everything!</Text>
  <Text Key="C8854F28">Anti-Spaced</Text>
  <Text Key="D7945FDC">When looking for inspiration, look no further than the stars... or, more specifically, &lt;i&gt;the moon&lt;/i&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="A8274BB3">Celestial Refresh</Text>
  <Text Key="8F41DE08">{0.SimFirstName} is positive that love is in orbit tonight!</Text>
  <Text Key="C534E2A7">Frisky Moon</Text>
  <Text Key="D7469AC4">There's something about basking in the light of a half a moon that makes {0.SimFirstName} happy.</Text>
  <Text Key="8E47AF8B">Lunar Glee</Text>
  <Text Key="D49DEE81">If the moon "says" {0.SimFirstName} can do it... {0.SimFirstName} can do it!</Text>
  <Text Key="C627E8B4">Lunar Reassurance</Text>
  <Text Key="CBC5E422">Bathing in the moonlight might be relaxing for most Sims, but the full moon's light is quite potent for a Werewolf!</Text>
  <Text Key="28FFE19D">Moody Moon</Text>
  <Text Key="9529651F">It's funny how a floating space rock can bring out {0.SimFirstName}'s inner child.</Text>
  <Text Key="6EC97FC6">Space Rock Amusement</Text>
  <Text Key="8157E5C6">If only {0.SimFirstName} could find a way to relax the night before a full moon!</Text>
  <Text Key="0718C059">Space Rock Stress</Text>
  <Text Key="21E655BE">Bathing beneath the moon's light can lift spirits just as much as barking at it does! </Text>
  <Text Key="835B4641">Wolfshine</Text>
  <Text Key="B0485ACF">Cheek Tufts</Text>
  <Text Key="B5E33982">Chin Tufts</Text>
  <Text Key="85DF84FF">Faces</Text>
  <Text Key="F6D0FEAF">Noses</Text>
  <Text Key="F1DE0CE5">I hide!</Text>
  <Text Key="F8BA0B1E">I hike!</Text>
  <Text Key="92F506C3">I howl!</Text>
  <Text Key="6B63C6E4">I want to be rich and mysterious.</Text>
  <Text Key="34E5C507">Turn me into a beast, a terror of the night, a moonlit monster.</Text>
  <Text Key="8DD4A5E2">I'd like natural ease, with flip curls and perfumed magazines.</Text>
  <Text Key="009AF7A4">When the full moon rises...</Text>
  <Text Key="72F781C7">It's makeover time! Have a seat and tell me what you want.</Text>
  <Text Key="67BC4367">It's tough! It's metal! It's a zig-zag ceiling rail!</Text>
  <Text Key="E584139E">Zig Zag Factory Ceiling Rail</Text>
  <Text Key="9DFD5D3B">The Moonwood Collective is a dignified group of community-minded Werewolves, whose mission embodies the union of lycanthropy and philanthropy. </Text>
  <Text Key="4AC76057">The Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="DE4DB212">The Wildfangs are a scrappy, free-spirited group of Werewolves. They believe the Werewolf lifestyle is the ultimate gift, and they're going to make the most of it.</Text>
  <Text Key="79E0174A">The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="6147BFB6">&lt;b&gt;Be a good representative for all Werewolves!&lt;/b&gt;\nBe friendly and welcoming towards non-Werewolves while in Beast Form, have friendly discussions about Werewolves, exercise Werewolf Empathy, Diplomacy, and the Will to Resist, and maybe even bridge the gap and get through to Greg. \n\n&lt;b&gt;Don't feed into the negative stereotypes of Werewolves!&lt;/b&gt;\nAvoid being mean to non-Werewolf Sims while in Beast Form. That includes picking fights with them or scaring them with your Ferocity or Vicious Howling.</Text>
  <Text Key="9651198E">Diplomacy</Text>
  <Text Key="48AE2AD3">Expand and Explore</Text>
  <Text Key="060CD548">&lt;b&gt;Make the world your playground and expand the reach of the pack!&lt;/b&gt;\nExplore the Moonwood Mill Underground, travel to remote or hard-to-reach locales, Mark your Territory, and meet non-Werewolf Sims that have something... different about them. </Text>
  <Text Key="0BBCBE36">Pack Participation </Text>
  <Text Key="AF28E2BC">&lt;b&gt;Contribute to the pack and help out packmates!&lt;/b&gt;\nMaintain good relationships with your packmates, give plenty of Packmate Gifts, and contribute to pack resources at the hangout.</Text>
  <Text Key="B5B933EA">Self-Improvement</Text>
  <Text Key="7233011D">&lt;b&gt;Improve yourself! Redefine what it means to be a strong Werewolf all-around!&lt;/b&gt;\nGet fit and Spar with packmates, level up to higher tiers of Werewolf, read Werewolf books from around Moonwood Mill, unlock your Dormant Abilities, and maybe even Provoke Greg for the ultimate challenging fight.</Text>
  <Text Key="27FCC232">Self-Sufficiency</Text>
  <Text Key="C2FC83A5">&lt;b&gt;Provide for yourself, and the future of the pack!&lt;/b&gt;\nAcquire your own food through fishing, gardening, or Werewolf Hunting, and cook some excellent meals. Contribute some of the harvests or finished food to the pack resources. \n\n&lt;b&gt;Avoid public displays of beastly gluttony!&lt;/b&gt;\nWe understand it can be difficult, but try &lt;b&gt;not&lt;/b&gt; to Devour things in sight of non-Werewolves.</Text>
  <Text Key="1839A75A">Moonbathing</Text>
  <Text Key="5D5697D9">Moonbathe</Text>
  <Text Key="FDA00189">Don't Moonbathe</Text>
  <Text Key="D8D63F34">When you run a lumber mill, columns like this are easy to come by. It's just a square piece of cut lumber.</Text>
  <Text Key="526A309B">Basic Lumber Column</Text>
  <Text Key="B1EA3FC2">This old column is pretty rusty, but don't worry—it's the toughest column out there. It can hold anything. It's so tough... all of the other columns are jealous. </Text>
  <Text Key="DA6609BD">"The Toughest" Factory Column</Text>
  <Text Key="D56DA4E2">You... you made me a Werewolf, remember? Well, I'd really like to join your pack!</Text>
  <Text Key="25186976">Of course, welcome!</Text>
  <Text Key="210208DB">What? No way!</Text>
  <Text Key="3FB3252E">Hello? Who is this? Why are you texting me these weird memes?</Text>
  <Text Key="27574552">&lt;i&gt; [Unintelligible Screeching Noises] &lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="667A4A2A">&lt;b&gt;I WILL EAT YOUR SOFA&lt;/b&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="8D8964B3">Hey pack member! Need help with repairs?</Text>
  <Text Key="5BF1D328">Wolfy Explorer</Text>
  <Text Key="6C605228">Precious Pup</Text>
  <Text Key="A9CD0C8E">Autumn Coffee Date</Text>
  <Text Key="2D79449C">Collectively Cozy</Text>
  <Text Key="CC77DA17">Ripped Rebel</Text>
  <Text Key="36CE7B4F">Fanged and Wild</Text>
  <Text Key="BC1526BD">Not-So-Fresh Duds</Text>
  <Text Key="A1D3A141">Lunar Snooze</Text>
  <Text Key="AEE56BB7">Collectively Cozy</Text>
  <Text Key="5B1F0BC0">Not-So-Fresh Duds</Text>
  <Text Key="2A2E1ED0">Patched Punk</Text>
  <Text Key="058E958B">Fanged and Wild</Text>
  <Text Key="B141175E">Woodsy and Wolfy</Text>
  <Text Key="A6B7C092">This fence is made out of wood planks. It's simple. It works. Enough said.</Text>
  <Text Key="CFF4AEAD">Woodsy Plank Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="565E5365">This industrial fencing is a little rusted, but it's also very sturdy! Also very bright! It's a cool fence, okay. </Text>
  <Text Key="2EDFE9E0">Old Factory Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="CCD0D6D1">This fence screams "Hey! No, you aren't allowed inside. You can look, you can try to climb, but you're going to have a lot of regrets." So really it just wants you to stay out. </Text>
  <Text Key="49EAC224">"Keep Out" Chain-Linked Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="1C12B280">This old tile floor has certainly seen better days. It's falling apart. It's broken, but you know what? It's still here. That makes it rough and tumble!</Text>
  <Text Key="1BDC1A4F">Rough and Tumble Tile</Text>
  <Text Key="67439D8F">When Celene decided to open a bar in Moonwood Mill, the Moonwood Collective and Wildfangs were glad to help. Together, the Werewolves scavenged the surrounding factories and underground tunnels, bringing in enough material for Celene to fashion her bar. Today, it is still a reminder of what the Grimtooth Bar represents to her—a place where all are welcome and can come together, despite their differences. </Text>
  <Text Key="8A5F7256">Scrap Heap Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="45704594">You wouldn't let the newest and littlest member of your pack sleep on some second rate sack of splinters, would you? NO WAY! You'd pick the solid, tried-and-true option. And let me tell you, this bassinet is so antique that it's gotta be top notch if people have kept it around &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; long, right? No? Well who cares! It's cute as heck. </Text>
  <Text Key="1FC2617B">Precocious Pup's Plush Palace</Text>
  <Text Key="7D3B947A">You wouldn't let the newest and littlest member of your pack sleep on some second rate sack of splinters, would you? NO WAY! You'd pick the solid, tried-and-true option. And let me tell you, this bassinet is so antique that it's gotta be top notch if people have kept it around &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; long, right? No? Well who cares! It's cute as heck. </Text>
  <Text Key="9549A225">Precocious Pup's Plush Palace</Text>
  <Text Key="851C3F62">Reach the apex of your orbit on this cozy lofted bunk bed! This reliable ol' hunk of wood is sturdier than ever, so there's only a very small chance of it becoming a Perigee Loft!\nSleeping on it will have you feeling as delighted as your 9th grade science teacher would if you actually remembered the definitions of apogee and perigee!</Text>
  <Text Key="A9E4C7DD">Pups &amp; Up Apogee Loft</Text>
  <Text Key="D8B5F3A4">"Well, it'll have to do for now," Greggorius said with a sigh, covering the makeshift "bed" with the old Lunvik's Loom linens he found in the closet. It was the best he could do, considering he'd devoured the only bed in his research cabin last night and woke up on the floor. \n"Perhaps less Fury next time..." he muttered. He could already imagine the sight of his beloved Avelina eagerly waiting for him return, standing in the front doorway, clutching her folio of notes on the moon. </Text>
  <Text Key="B8DA6CEB">Hasty Replacement Palette Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="3160B361">Sleep sweet dreams under the stars and moon in this adorable, itsy-bitsy, patchwork toddler bed. </Text>
  <Text Key="90AF6414">Starry Night Toddler Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="87900537">Honestly, I wouldn't inhale the fumes. It's probably not safe. </Text>
  <Text Key="9A2E058E">Junk-Filled Bonfire</Text>
  <Text Key="3123A391">By: Maria Volkov\n\nThough few Sims have heard of the small town of Moonwood Mill, this book is recognized as the world's go-to source of information on the topic. Naysayers argue that its accounting of history isn't entirely accurate—though these individuals also cite curses, an occult conflict, and other magical elements as the true root of Moonwood Mill's origins. </Text>
  <Text Key="56A155E4">A History of Moonwood Mill</Text>
  <Text Key="B560D51E">From what to do when you accidently turn while on a date to removing sticky gum from a furry tail, this book will guide you through life as werewolf!</Text>
  <Text Key="641C7E21">An Insider’s Guide to Being a Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="F3CAD749">Wait, who is Greggorius Lunvik? Why is his diary just laying around Moonwood?</Text>
  <Text Key="54A479AC">The Diary of Greggorius Lunvik</Text>
  <Text Key="5083206C">By: Vulfgang Mulder\n\nA page-turning mystery about a lone Werewolf on the hunt for answers.</Text>
  <Text Key="C212D7A3">The Werewolf Who Came in From the Cold</Text>
  <Text Key="CC4CA4B9">By: Vulfgang Mulder\n\nThings heat up fast for Ginger when she meets the mysterious Werewolf next door. It's not long before she feels the moon's pull...</Text>
  <Text Key="4E576FBC">The Wolf Next Door</Text>
  <Text Key="30042F0E">By: Vulfgang Mulder\n\nAs the lunar phase changes, so too does the lives of a group of fanged friends. The real question is, will their friendship last forever?</Text>
  <Text Key="26B32631">Fanged Friends Forever</Text>
  <Text Key="965DC503">By: Vulfgang Mulder\n\nLizo Barknet is perfectly happy running his pack as Alpha leader - his rules, no questions asked. That is until arrogant and haughty Ms. Darcie comes to town. Sparks and fur fly in this delightful comedy as these two young lovers delicately navigate Werewolf society and pack expectations.</Text>
  <Text Key="08E3B252">Packs &amp; Prejudice</Text>
  <Text Key="53048994">By: Bruno Finol\n\nKurt is a veteran Werewolf, battle-hardened from years of fending off the vampire threat. Now restless in an era of peace, he seeks to forge a new path for himself. His journey for redemption and fulfillment begins in the most unlikely of places - a vampire daycare. As the daycare's newest teacher, will he finally find what he was looking for? Or will he fizzle out as a glorified chew toy for extra feisty teething toddlers?</Text>
  <Text Key="F903ED7B">The Good Boy</Text>
  <Text Key="6109359A">Perfect for the Warriors of Write among us, with a penchant for collecting one too many written works and curious from their adventures. These shelves come in a variety of colors for any preferred glamour- one brings shadow, one brings light, some are even two-toned! Having one of these in your house will have you RIDING HOOOOOOME as soon as possible just to see it again.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDE199C5">Racked Teak-a Greatshelves</Text>
  <Text Key="E3757333">Back in the day, this bookcase didn't hold books. It held tools and the odd logging manuscript. What's a logging manuscript you ask? Well, you certainly aren't getting an answer out of me! </Text>
  <Text Key="CE4AA262">Industrial Bookcase</Text>
  <Text Key="795898E9">bookDisplay_GP12GENsecret Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="6B5BC0CC">bookDisplay_GP12GENsecret Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="DCB745D6">bookDisplay_GP12GENsecret_set2 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="412E6389">bookDisplay_GP12GENsecret_set2 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="381F8EE1">bookDisplay_GP12GENsecret_set3 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="E8961E94">bookDisplay_GP12GENsecret_set3 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="8C075458">bookDisplay_GP12GENvulfgangMulder Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="10B566D7">bookDisplay_GP12GENvulfgangMulder Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="5FC4C691">bookDisplay_GP12GENvulfgangMulder_set2 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="13654EE4">bookDisplay_GP12GENvulfgangMulder_set2 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="321F9B86">bookDisplay_GP12GENvulfgangMulder_set3 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="E6FACC19">bookDisplay_GP12GENvulfgangMulder_set3 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="5ABE6A7B">bookDisplay_GP12GENvulfgangMulder_set4 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="CFA186DA">bookDisplay_GP12GENvulfgangMulder_set4 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="FAB52000">bookDisplay_GP12RWnovel Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="6894EACF">bookDisplay_GP12RWnovel Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="38BB3603">bookDisplayThin_GP12GENpeterBarker Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="D7EF3552">bookDisplayThin_GP12GENpeterBarker Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="F2CCE4A0">bookDisplayThin_GP12GENpeterBarker_set2 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="F7B338EF">bookDisplayThin_GP12GENpeterBarker_set2 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="A986AA4B">bookDisplayThin_GP12GENpeterBarker_set3 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="ECBFADCA">bookDisplayThin_GP12GENpeterBarker_set3 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="EFB80216">bookDisplayThin_GP12GENpeterBarker_set4 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="56E454C9">bookDisplayThin_GP12GENpeterBarker_set4 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="812DEF4D">bookDisplayThin_GP12GENwereMagazine Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="91CE8A98">WE’RE Living Magazine</Text>
  <Text Key="1E0C15CD">Every Werewolf's one stop shop for all the saucy, scandalous news howling through the Werewolf world! Who bit half their neighborhood during their most epic rampage last week? Who's trying to woo all of their packmates' Fated Mates? And who faked enjoying the flavor of raw meat for years just to fit in? Find out here!</Text>
  <Text Key="64CB3618">BARK Magazine</Text>
  <Text Key="D00756BB">By: A. Wolfe\n\nBook 1 in the Peter Barker series.\nJoin Peter Barker as he takes a wild lunar adventure, making new friends and discovering the mysteries of the night.</Text>
  <Text Key="5F5CA11A">Peter Barker’s First Moon</Text>
  <Text Key="9924AC58">By: A. Wolfe\n\nBook 2 in the Peter Barker series. \nThings take a mischievous turn as Peter Barker returns home. Follow along as he finds out what it's all about!</Text>
  <Text Key="EE5DEED7">Peter Barker’s Homecoming Hijinks</Text>
  <Text Key="B2403CC3">By: A. Wolfe\n\nBook 3 in the Peter Barker series.\nSchool's out and summer is on! For Peter Barker and his friends, that means getting ready for Camp Moonwood. But it doesn't take long for things to take an unexpected turn...</Text>
  <Text Key="A8A73112">Peter Barker’s Camping Conundrum</Text>
  <Text Key="85A46ACE">By: A. Wolfe\n\nBook 4 in the Peter Barker series.\nPeter Barker is where?! Things are going to get a bit hairy in this new astronomical adventure for sure.</Text>
  <Text Key="F93826F1">Peter Barker…in Space!</Text>
  <Text Key="B988F045">Get the low down on all things Werewolf! Guts 'n glory: who's sparring with who? Top 100 most beautiful howling spots. Learning to love the beast within. 29 meaty recipes worth trying!</Text>
  <Text Key="786B6E40">WE’RE Living Magazine</Text>
  <Text Key="8C00A62B">Every Werewolf's one stop shop for all the saucy, scandalous news howling through the Werewolf world! Who bit half their neighborhood during their most epic rampage last week? Who's trying to woo all of their packmates' Fated Mates? And who faked enjoying the flavor of raw meat for years just to fit in? Find out here!</Text>
  <Text Key="60C7922A">BARK Magazine</Text>
  <Text Key="99BD8F36">Unlock by joining the Wildfangs.</Text>
  <Text Key="961ADADD">Unlock by joining the Wildfangs.</Text>
  <Text Key="2A949A2C">This stuff may be pretty nasty, but it sure beats having Werebies!</Text>
  <Text Key="C47EDF63">Werebies Remedy</Text>
  <Text Key="F3ACF221">There once was a group of spellcasters,\nWho feared their vampiric attackers,\nIn the moonlight they swore, to bear weakness no more\nSo they bore fangs and fur thereafter.</Text>
  <Text Key="88AE31D4">Moonlit Fable Wall Clock</Text>
  <Text Key="8D8C371C">Unlock by reaching rank Alpha in The Moonwood Collective.</Text>
  <Text Key="297F8CCF">A fanged fish blessed by the power of the moonlit waters of Moonwood Mill.</Text>
  <Text Key="5A493E96">Luna Fish</Text>
  <Text Key="91F8F7D1">A fanged fish blessed by the power of the moonlit waters of Moonwood Mill.</Text>
  <Text Key="68F75524">Luna Fish</Text>
  <Text Key="29121CF1">A fanged fish blessed by the power of the moonlit waters of Moonwood Mill.</Text>
  <Text Key="8CF643C4">Mounted Luna Fish</Text>
  <Text Key="B9C5D061">Just scavenged up a little piece of local history? Fished a priceless relic out of a glowing magic moon lake? Well you're in luck! This is &lt;i&gt;the&lt;/i&gt; spot for your little wolf-y tchotchkes.\n\nAs your collection grows, you'll notice that certain relics seem to fit extra well in certain spots. Perhaps, they have a larger story to tell... it may come to you in an epiphany!</Text>
  <Text Key="B1AA2B14">Moonwood Relic Display</Text>
  <Text Key="5FF82E96">An old skull relic with strange text on it, masked by a lunar encryption. </Text>
  <Text Key="583C3249">Tamed Cowplant Skull</Text>
  <Text Key="85DE84A4">An old jawbone with strange text engraved upon it, masked by lunar encryption. </Text>
  <Text Key="521D4FEB">Tamed Cowplant Jawbone</Text>
  <Text Key="CCBBAB91">An old painted tablet, with strange writing engraved on the back of it, masked by lunar encryption.</Text>
  <Text Key="985AEDE4">Myshupotamian Tablet: Wise Wolfman</Text>
  <Text Key="0927F0E4">An old painted tablet, with strange writing engraved on the back of it, masked by lunar encryption.</Text>
  <Text Key="F7B4AE2B">Myshupotamian Tablet: Cowplant Taming</Text>
  <Text Key="3069B39C">A carved wooden figurine of a spellcaster's wolf familiar, with the name "Brutus" engraved at its base, along with some other writings masked by a lunar encryption.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0E53E73">Canine Familiar Figurine: "Brutus"</Text>
  <Text Key="09D33A29">A carved wooden figurine of a spellcaster's wolf familiar, with the name "Renga" engraved at its base, along with some other writings masked by a lunar encryption.</Text>
  <Text Key="0AC46B0C">Canine Familiar Figurine: "Renga"</Text>
  <Text Key="8A5E7E7E">A carved wooden figurine of a spellcaster's wolf familiar, with the name "Verity" engraved at its base, along with some other writings masked by a lunar encryption.</Text>
  <Text Key="1A6AFA01">Canine Familiar Figurine: "Verity"</Text>
  <Text Key="C73E9BB3">A carved wooden figurine of a spellcaster's wolf familiar, with the name "Gibby" engraved at its base, along with some other writings masked by a lunar encryption.</Text>
  <Text Key="18B4B3E2">Canine Familiar Figurine: "Gibby"</Text>
  <Text Key="22F365AE">This painted pot shard is engraved with strange text, masked by a lunar encryption. </Text>
  <Text Key="93F82351">Mooncaster Pot Shard: "Learning"</Text>
  <Text Key="6B4EBAC7">This painted pot shard is engraved with strange text, masked by a lunar encryption.</Text>
  <Text Key="C17E9F7E">Mooncaster Pot Shard: "Turning"</Text>
  <Text Key="4BD1A18C">This painted pot shard seems to have a deeper meaning hidden within its brushstrokes, masked by a lunar encryption. </Text>
  <Text Key="EEF5D443">Mooncaster Pot Shard: "Planting"</Text>
  <Text Key="DE0CFA25">This painted pot lid is engraved with strange text, masked by a lunar encryption. </Text>
  <Text Key="CA5907A0">Mooncaster Pot Lid</Text>
  <Text Key="3CB6EBA6">This old factory shutter used to keep out the light so that the factory was nice and dark and moody. Just how old, creepy factories like. </Text>
  <Text Key="EB8C04B9">Old Factory Shutter</Text>
  <Text Key="1887C985">When you have a window that you want to cover up, and you don't have curtains, but you do have a tarp... I feel like the solution is clear...</Text>
  <Text Key="89C4AD80">Left Tarp Curtain</Text>
  <Text Key="CFDC8390">When you have a window, and you think that curtains are obnoxiously fancy, but tarps are really useful and cool... I feel like the solution is clear...</Text>
  <Text Key="7A92ADBF">Right Tarp Curtain</Text>
  <Text Key="23430459">Embody the ethos of your true werewolf identity and let the world know you have a bone to pick with authority by proudly displaying this poster. You're not a sellout! You're authentic, you're &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt;. </Text>
  <Text Key="D6EF1FDC">Fury-Fueled Nonconformity Poster</Text>
  <Text Key="34F8E2A4">Unlock by reaching rank Delta in The Wildfangs.</Text>
  <Text Key="20032254">Promotional materials from some of the most popular films featuring iconic Werewolf film stars Sam Quill and Lea Embrie, both born and raised in Moonwood Mill back in the day! Even though they took their talents to Starlight Boulevard those many years back, their films garnered cult followings among the residents of their hometown. At this point though, most people haven't &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; seen their movies. They just put the posters up because they like the aesthetic. And you know what? That's valid. </Text>
  <Text Key="FA26003B">Werewolf Noir Film Poster</Text>
  <Text Key="3D953AEE">Behold this selection of wall destruction! There is a scratch mark, an array of scratch marks, swervey scratch marks, vertically-serious scratch marks, places where wallpaper has been torn off, places where wallpaper is &lt;i&gt;actively&lt;/i&gt; being torn off, squiggly cracks, and cracks that look like a hockey player just checked the wall! What a collection! What character!</Text>
  <Text Key="986D9C91">Collection of Wall Destruction</Text>
  <Text Key="A5494AA2">If you're looking for adorable, trendy, lunar-themed wall stickers... we've got your walls covered! See the sketchy moon, Bucky the Wolf Pup, a starry sky howl, two owls (one excited and one cautiously optimistic), woodsy moon trees, the lunar mountains of fog, a lunar moth named Luna, and a lunar moth named Paul. </Text>
  <Text Key="EA684D1D">Lunar Wall Stickers Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="3CA405D3">Stereotypes and suburban homes? Heck no. You're not a clone, you're not a statistic. You're a WEREWOLF, so declare it to the world!</Text>
  <Text Key="5E782C82">Lupine Subculture Anti-Mural v.12 by Barksy</Text>
  <Text Key="57D9BD78">Just because this is an old secretary desk, doesn't mean you have to be a secretary to use it. You could be anyone! It doesn't mind. </Text>
  <Text Key="98E16F77">Worn Secretary Desk</Text>
  <Text Key="DD32C47A">This object is half desk, half door. However, you can't walk through it like a door, but you can sit at it like a desk, making it 74.67% desk and only 12.3% door. You do the math. </Text>
  <Text Key="A4283225">Door Desk</Text>
  <Text Key="4719A306">This door is rusted, battered, and it's missing a handle, but it's still standing! Would you really want a normal door that hasn't been tested? This old factory door is tried and true. Plus, it comes as an array of bold fun colors!</Text>
  <Text Key="44134A99">Tested by Time Industrial Door</Text>
  <Text Key="1039B9EE">Wolf Graffiti Industrial Door</Text>
  <Text Key="1EC74BC2">This door is too heavy for a &lt;i&gt;normal&lt;/i&gt; Sim. That's why the werewolves have marked it... with graffiti, of course!</Text>
  <Text Key="294A43D0">Back in the day, they wanted the old Moonwood Mill factory to have a cheery touch, so they painted the doors brightly. They were proud of their doors. These were bold doors that would stand the test of time. </Text>
  <Text Key="0983EFFF">Bold Industrial Door</Text>
  <Text Key="B70C0C83">At its core, this archway is strong, but on the outside... it's brittle. See it crumble and yet see it stand against all that weight. </Text>
  <Text Key="2664F0D2">Brittle Brick Archway</Text>
  <Text Key="3626EE4C">This door is made out of wood that is pretty woodsy. Look at it. There's no denying that fact!</Text>
  <Text Key="72DC9E03">Woodsy Wood Wooden Door</Text>
  <Text Key="C6D2AE48">They might say you've got a lot of junk in that trunk, but that's not junk... it's clothing. So they can stop saying that. </Text>
  <Text Key="F0D07EE7">Clothing Storage Chests</Text>
  <Text Key="5B1A5B97">Here at Power-Sip, we always strive for the impossible. Weaker beverage companies often tell us, "You can't make that a flavor!" or "Our lawyers are awaiting a response." Cowards. Introducing 'Power-Sip MIDNIGHT', flavored with the &lt;i&gt;essence&lt;/i&gt; of night. You might be wondering how we managed to bottle the very concept of time itself, but the truth is that &lt;i&gt;it doesn't matter&lt;/i&gt;. Nothing matters. All that matters is the Sip. And the Power. &lt;i&gt;Power-Sip&lt;/i&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="68191E6E">Power-Sip MIDNIGHT</Text>
  <Text Key="27B60B09">A drink that will instantly remove the Werewolf curse from a Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="1E485A6C">Wolf-B-Gone</Text>
  <Text Key="7CA64548">A delicious, calming juice infused with Moonpetal blooms.</Text>
  <Text Key="93F993E7">Moonpetal Punch</Text>
  <Text Key="C86EEC9B">Jerky Bites</Text>
  <Text Key="D189379C">Wolfitos</Text>
  <Text Key="DCD8C03A">Raw Fish</Text>
  <Text Key="6D2A3D73">Jerky Bites</Text>
  <Text Key="B6D3CB10">Cold Cuts</Text>
  <Text Key="C1163A58">Steak Tartare</Text>
  <Text Key="F487F094">Wolfitos</Text>
  <Text Key="84D48561">Moonpetal</Text>
  <Text Key="2CF54770">Raw Meat</Text>
  <Text Key="439D94FA">Grilled Luna Fish</Text>
  <Text Key="2934A606">Mushroom Steak</Text>
  <Text Key="D6B22648">Blue Steak</Text>
  <Text Key="B36B844F">Steak Tartare</Text>
  <Text Key="DD095264">Cold Cuts</Text>
  <Text Key="463322B1">Grilled Luna Fish</Text>
  <Text Key="AD2C0A87">Mushroom Steak</Text>
  <Text Key="A829BC31">Blue Steak</Text>
  <Text Key="580A90D5">Raw Meat</Text>
  <Text Key="CF1EAF6C">Steak Tartare</Text>
  <Text Key="A6A2B79C">Maria Volkov always wanted a small garden for the community of Moonwood Mill. It'd encourage self-sustainability and bring everyone together. In an effort to make his mother's dreams come true, Kristopher created these garden planters by hand for her, a gift for the mother he dearly loved. </Text>
  <Text Key="35790A73">Kristopher's Planter</Text>
  <Text Key="FF6BBBEB">This gate says, "Hey! I might let you go inside, but only if I'm unlocked. Otherwise, you're going to have to make some life decisions about how you like barbed wire." </Text>
  <Text Key="74562DEA">"Maybe You Can Go In" Chain-Linked Gate</Text>
  <Text Key="71274DDC">hiddenPortalPortaPotty_GP12GEN Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="68F0B5B3">Portal Potties</Text>
  <Text Key="3BDEAB4C">hiddenPortalTunnel_GP12GENbunkerDoors Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="780D4503">Old Bunker</Text>
  <Text Key="7FEC81C9">hiddenPortalTunnel_GP12GENmountainEntrance Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="DC4C712C">Cave Opening</Text>
  <Text Key="304E118F">hiddenPortalTunnel_GP12GENmountainCave Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="5ECC8E56">Cave Opening</Text>
  <Text Key="A1594E2F">hiddenPortalTunnel_GP12GENsewerGate Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="0D348F76">Sewer Grate</Text>
  <Text Key="BD4D54E9">It's so dark inside... it seems to lead to a secret tunnel network. Is that howling? </Text>
  <Text Key="8E6534CC">Moonwood Mill Tunnel Entrance</Text>
  <Text Key="4AB22458">jig_2x4_duoSocial_tugOfWar Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="781CD6D7">jig_2x4_duoSocial_tugOfWar Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="BC9E2E0E">jig_4x7_duoSimWerewolfFight Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="3712F331">jig_4x7_duoSimWerewolfFight Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="CA96DF59">jig_4x7_duoWerewolfFight Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="A35DC0DC">jig_4x7_duoWerewolfFight Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="DF283F0A">This old factory lighting fixture might be worn, but it's also bold. Just look at the array of colors it comes in! If you didn't know any better... you might think it was designer. </Text>
  <Text Key="D2F16E15">Worn Factory Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="C42478C1">Hi, I'm Patchy the Lamp, and I'm here to brighten your day! How can I help? I can light things, and I can swivel, and I can swivel and light things! Plus I'm a lamp! Hi!</Text>
  <Text Key="E43928F4">Patchy the Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="3E65A6F2">Say goodnight to the moon as it sweetly guards over your dreams and protects you from nightmares. </Text>
  <Text Key="95E8F68D">Night Night Moon Moon Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="BCB04C6C">Legend has it that the delicate glass used to make these lamps can only be crafted under a full moon, much like the flower they are modeled after. </Text>
  <Text Key="3A7A9BA3">Graceful Moonpetal Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="2D30A3CC">lunarStatue_GP12GEN Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="8418C683">Moonwood Mill's Lunar Statue</Text>
  <Text Key="7383CA29">Long ago, a group of spellcasters caused an overload while practicing a powerful, moon-infused, untamed spell. The resulting explosion imbued the surrounding area with lunar energy. Because of this, the wood from trees surrounding Lake Lunvik are eagerly sought after by the spellcasting community. This wand was one of the first ever crafted. </Text>
  <Text Key="C4D11B0C">Moonwood Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="CC6937E0">Miss Hell used to live a normal life. Before Vlad. Before that fateful night... \n\nMarybell Smith had beautiful, blunted teeth. As a child, they'd been rather crooked, and her parents paid a fortune for braces. Ever grateful and enamoured by their perfection, she'd taken diligent care of them ever since. It was a nightly ritual for her to floss, brush, and gargle. She didn't even see Vlad in the mirror as he crept up behind her. That night, everything changed. \n\nAfter transforming into a creature of the night, Marybell felt with her tongue that her teeth were no longer quite so perfectly blunt. She rushed to a mirror to cast her gaze once more upon the visage of her smile. To her horror, she could not see herself. Enraged and scared, she threw a fist into the mirror, shattering it! Even if she couldn't see herself she knew the truth... Forever more was she fanged! Forever more was she... Miss Hell.</Text>
  <Text Key="83D1AE2F">Seven Years Unlucky Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="EFB7F588">Forget rock stars! The future of rock lies in the power of the moon! As its name would suggest, Rockmeister created the Syzygy 7000 with alignment in mind. Its handcrafted strings are expertly aligned to produce unprecedented howls and growls. And every note will bring your psyche into alignment with a celestial body (100% scientifically proven, by the way).</Text>
  <Text Key="D8E49127">Rockmeister Syzygy 7000 Guitar</Text>
  <Text Key="000D715F">Unlock by reaching rank Alpha in The Wildfangs.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E16F9E2">Celene stared at the masterpiece on the wall, tilting her head to make out the shredded artwork beneath. It wasn't the strokes beneath that fascinated her, but rather the content of the painting. What about this painting triggered the beast within to attack?</Text>
  <Text Key="F3AAEF5D">Clawed Masterpiece</Text>
  <Text Key="1B525C8F">A few years ago, these art prints popped up around town. Supposedly they were released by the Moonwood Mill Historical Society, a mysterious organization quite literally no one in town has heard of, in celebration of Moonwood Mill's 200th anniversary. What's strange is that the list of members is comprised of names no one can quite place. And where did they produce such a large quantity of these?\n\nWell, regardless of all that, they're really quite cute!</Text>
  <Text Key="89817F56">Moonwood Mill Historical Society's Bicentennial Celebration Prints</Text>
  <Text Key="9A31D42F">Sure, Werewolves can learn to care for their needs in the wild... it doesn't mean they don't love using a party bush from time to time. </Text>
  <Text Key="CD2B4176">Wolf Party Bush</Text>
  <Text Key="B6209227">A rare flower that only blooms under the full moon, originating from Moonwood Mill. </Text>
  <Text Key="602C385E">Moonpetal</Text>
  <Text Key="77020D7E">But who cut the barrel in half? And how did they cut it in half so perfectly? They are a genius—an artist! For now, this barrel—imbued with spring plants—shall brighten the lives of the Sims around them for all time!</Text>
  <Text Key="16927701">Sunshine Barrel Planter</Text>
  <Text Key="42A6A948">Anything can be a planter. It just needs to be capable of holding dirt! As an example, look at this array of planters! I named one Gladus, one Edith, one Dorris, and one Earl. Oh... and over there... the basket is Bruno. But we don't talk about that one. </Text>
  <Text Key="DC857FE7">The Planters Five</Text>
  <Text Key="67152504">It's a slab of wood! No, a drawer! Wait... it's &lt;i&gt;planter drawer&lt;/i&gt;! </Text>
  <Text Key="865FFBCB">Planter Drawer</Text>
  <Text Key="8164BF3F">This mailbox is woodsy and quaint—all the way from its little rusted roof down to its bending branch base. </Text>
  <Text Key="6B09EF66">Woodsy Mailbox</Text>
  <Text Key="66454516">You never know when a vampire might attack! If you want to be in tip-top athletic, fighting shape (but you don't have access to high-end athletic machinery) this is the punching bag for you! </Text>
  <Text Key="1972ADC9">Beat'em-Up Beat-Up Punching Bag</Text>
  <Text Key="BC5ACAD6">Behold this selection of floor destruction! It's scratch after scratch after mighty scratch (with some scratch-like cracks and splats too!) Yet another ravishing collection of somewhat terrifying accents for your somewhat terrifying rooms! I am already very scared of them!</Text>
  <Text Key="F747E289">Collection of Floor Destruction 1: Scratches</Text>
  <Text Key="E5A5BD3C">Behold this OTHER selection of floor destruction! It's crack after crack after crinkly crack! What went smack on this floor to make so cracked? Who knows! Who cares! Because it's yet another ravishing collection of somewhat terrifying accents for your somewhat terrifying rooms! I am now even more scared of them!</Text>
  <Text Key="B704D393">Collection of Floor Destruction 2: Cracks</Text>
  <Text Key="DD592198">Now THIS is one of the official flagship rugs Pernilla Lunvik sold to make a name for herself! Unlike the prototypes, it is pristinely preserved, no Werewolf toddler damage to be found. You can enjoy the intricate patterns and expert weaves, as immaculate as the day they were made. Just keep in mind that if anyone marks their territory on this one, Pernilla's spirit is &lt;b&gt;very sternly&lt;/b&gt; frowning at them from beyond the veil. </Text>
  <Text Key="6DECA017">Lunvik's Loom Flagship Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="A850057C">Hand-woven by Pernilla Lunvik herself, this iconic rug would eventually become the backbone of the Lunvik's Loom textile empire. Well, the &lt;i&gt;official&lt;/i&gt; versions, at least. You see, Pernilla wanted to ensure that no amount of wear and tear would cause this rug to fully unravel, so she stress tested them by setting her rambunctious toddler Greggorius loose on each one. And boy, did he do a number on them...</Text>
  <Text Key="B730D7D3">Lunvik's Loom Flagship Rug (Prototype)</Text>
  <Text Key="0DB99900">This old fan is rusted, but it still works, and honestly... it's really cool! Haha. Get it? Cool.</Text>
  <Text Key="7D5705CF">Rusted Factory Fan</Text>
  <Text Key="A54BC8D8">Back in the day, this bus was pretty cool. It's even cooler these days! Slip in a bar and you've got yourself a really cool bar hangout. </Text>
  <Text Key="7BD79C57">Boss Bus Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="1F6AF778">A sign to hopefully warn any unknowing passersby about the dangers of Greg.</Text>
  <Text Key="E67BFD77">Warning Sign: Greg</Text>
  <Text Key="B5A92E8C">&lt;i&gt;Excerpt from a speech of the final meeting of the Convocation of Marshmallows by President Y. Ellowpeep.&lt;/i&gt;\n"My fellow gentlemallows, we face yet another Calamity on our horizon. For alas, the Giant Devourers will undoubtedly begin consuming us by the dozen. Why, you might ask? It is the work of THIS, this hunk of stylish metal, perfect for holding logs just the right size for fires. Think of the charring blazes they'll continue to conjure for us! The shards of firelight glimmering across their ghastly, hungry smiles! The senseless barbarity of it all... and here we remain, sundered by this metal yoke. Because of it, no longer shall we fly as carefree confections. No... henceforth, we shall walk."</Text>
  <Text Key="F7DCEB43">Seventh Confectioner's Calamity Firewood Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="4E919C71">Here lies a pile of factory rubble. See the gears, see the ruin, and marvel at the past!</Text>
  <Text Key="EF35AA44">Factory Rubble</Text>
  <Text Key="3301AC47">World's Most (In)Accurate Sundial</Text>
  <Text Key="D2C77F7F">Unlock by reaching rank Beta in The Wildfangs.</Text>
  <Text Key="34436414">This sundial will (usually) tell you the correct time. You can (ideally) use it when the sun is shining from (only certain spots in) the sky! And it will give you a (somewhat) accurate read of the time with its (sloppy) hand-crafted, resourceful construction! Because modern technology is (actually not) overrated! Who needs clocks (most people), anyways? </Text>
  <Text Key="C81059F0">The gnome wolf stands alone in the garden—for who else can understand him?  </Text>
  <Text Key="17330B9F">The Gnome Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="7C4944CC">This booklet is so full of scattered notes and loose-leaf pages, it threatens to explode with paper at any moment. One excerpt sticking out of the side reads as follows:\n&lt;i&gt;Year 1, Week 6, Day 2\nLunar Phase: Waxing Gibbous\nGreggorius arrived back at our cabin tonight after a week of solo study... very, very tense. Each time I peer at the moon through my telescope, I feel it too. Like the glow itself is irritating to look at, and be under. Perhaps an effect of the current phase?\nNearly full moon... will probably wait to replace the door to the kitchen, considering what happened last time. Nothing stops a hungry Werewolf, apparently.&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="650ED983">Lunar Expert's Folio</Text>
  <Text Key="C35F5EBC">Oh, so you &lt;i&gt;didn't&lt;/i&gt; expect me to notice that little perfectly-placed stack of antique books and stationery things. Because your home just always looks like some kind of interior decorating magazine spread? Wow, look at you! &lt;i&gt;Very&lt;/i&gt; cool.\n\nBitter? Me? Absolutely not. I'm just singing your praises, like you seem to expect people to do with your cute little book piles! I'M NOT JEALOUS OR ANYTHING.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF350013">Surreptitiously Studious Stationery Pile</Text>
  <Text Key="DC32EE5B">Unlock by reaching rank Beta in The Moonwood Collective.</Text>
  <Text Key="9A3D9B2D">This antique metal piece has a delicately engraved plate attached to its base, which reads:\n\n&lt;i&gt;"As powerful emissaries of the moon, we have a duty to serve not just those with fur and fangs, but &lt;b&gt;all&lt;/b&gt; who bask in the night's gentle light. We are Sims first and foremost, not beasts. We must exercise control over our duality and foster a more inclusive community."\n- Maria Volkov, Founding Leader of The Moonwood Collective &amp; Original Mooncaster&lt;/i&gt; </Text>
  <Text Key="80D114F8">Mooncaster Memento</Text>
  <Text Key="B9CA4C00">Unlock by reaching rank Delta in The Moonwood Collective.</Text>
  <Text Key="451D5A16">A rare flower that only blooms under the full moon, originating from Moonwood Mill.</Text>
  <Text Key="8AE4DCC9">Moonpetal</Text>
  <Text Key="5F4BE99C">This terrarium is looking pretty sus-piciously cute! Look how tiny it is! Definitely is not the impostor. Just... don't set it down near any vents. </Text>
  <Text Key="E86A0073">The "Tiny Fungus Among Us" Terrarium</Text>
  <Text Key="91AAB6D6">Welcome, beloved child of the stars, to your new life as the owner of this harmonically balanced and rhythmically aligned masterpiece. The crystals... well, they're tuned to reach frequencies that will put you in alignment with your best energy. I mean, wow! Just look at your aura! Even just thinking about this piece has you looking more celestially attuned than you've ever been before. Fate is dictating that neither you nor your body's energy aqueducts will regret this purchase.</Text>
  <Text Key="781BE689">Lunar Vibes Wall Hanging</Text>
  <Text Key="D7CBBD70">The old trailer used by The Wildfangs as their main pack hangout spot. </Text>
  <Text Key="1AD8DE1F">The Wildfangs Hangout Trailer</Text>
  <Text Key="8FA0D1DB">The tall tree used by the Moonwood Collective as the their main hangout. </Text>
  <Text Key="D20206BA">The Moonwood Collective Hangout Tree</Text>
  <Text Key="C9B07765">This community sign sure does contain a lot of helpful information about Moonwood Mill.</Text>
  <Text Key="673515E0">Moonwood Mill Community Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="E8BF650C">Now, this one I got right! I had my copy of &lt;i&gt;Building Stable Chairs&lt;/i&gt; handy when I built it. Just... um... try not to scooch around too much. I wouldn't tempt fate with that sanding job, the splinters are- WAIT! Be careful which part you sit on, that one nail looks a bit... Oh, and just sit still. If you lean too far in any direction it'll... You know what? Just don't sit on it.</Text>
  <Text Key="ACE4C6C3">Totally Stable Dining Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="E7010CD7">This chair might be old. It might be patched and torn. And there might still be sticky residue from spilled drinks of old in its old dilapidated cup holders... But it sure is cushy!</Text>
  <Text Key="C758EAAE">Cushy Leather Chair (with Cupholders!)</Text>
  <Text Key="A10E5E3C">During what most call the "Golden Age" of Starlight Boulevard, Pernilla Lunvik had the opportunity to design freestanding theater chairs featuring her signature Lunvelvet upholstery. Confident in her design, she had thousands of them made prior to presenting her design proposal - only to lose the opportunity to BlandCo. She never sold them officially (out of shame) but this initial batch still circulates the antiques trade to this day.</Text>
  <Text Key="8BEAE693">Lunvik's Loom Lunvelvet Theater-esque Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="D425392E">Field Notes, Entry #1886: How miraculous! I was dragging my tired feet through the woods, and happened upon a few large, circular rubber objects that were the perfect size to stack on their sides, add an old rag and a few stitches, and voila! A chair for me to finally rest upon. Oddly enough, it would appear these rubber objects are able to fit on some sort of... large metal machinery? Just a working theory of course. </Text>
  <Text Key="F85645D1">Tired No More Seat</Text>
  <Text Key="1766A1BC">This natural log loveseat will make you want to &lt;i&gt;Sit! Stay!&lt;/i&gt; The distinctly lycan lichen is perfect for a cozy "fetch sticks and chill" sesh. And you're in luck. Any werewolf* can put this &lt;b&gt;anywhere&lt;/b&gt;, wolf! As long as it fits, of course.\n*Non-werewolves can do this too, ok? Just... go along with it.</Text>
  <Text Key="0D115913">"I'm Lycan You" Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="7AA2D906">Some Sims would have given up on this couch. They might have thrown it out when it got its first hole. Or its second. Or eighth. But whoever owned it before... they weren't quitters! You can see how loved this couch was. Now you can love it too!</Text>
  <Text Key="2ADD0C99">Patched-Up Old Couch</Text>
  <Text Key="603A5CF3">Look, before you say anything, I KNOW I messed up one of the legs... Don't look at me like that! I'd like to see you use a band saw accurately while sneezing! \n*sigh* If only I could find my copy of &lt;i&gt;Building Stable Tables&lt;/i&gt;, I've looked everywhere for it.</Text>
  <Text Key="A88C8522">Totally Stable Dining Table</Text>
  <Text Key="03CE4A43">This was the preferred telescope model used by the late Avelina Lunvik during her iconic studies of space. Her discoveries surrounding the effects of the lunar cycle on Fury were crucial to her husband Greggorius' breakthroughs on harnessing werewolf power. Fun fact: it was with this telescope that she discovered the existence of the planet Sixam, using her heightened werewolf senses to identify its far off glimmer as a life-supporting planet. We've even included the makeshift tripod leg she fashioned! Where'd the plank come from? Well, Greggorius was pretty hungry one night during a full moon, and the door to the kitchen was in his way...</Text>
  <Text Key="6510E192">Avelina's Trusty Telescope</Text>
  <Text Key="AB24D3CE">Here may a Werewolf finally find respite from their inner fury. </Text>
  <Text Key="9FCB11F1">Werewolf Tombstone</Text>
  <Text Key="08FF2E52">This toy is totally harmless. Not in ANY way related to a wolf. It's 100% not secretly a wolf in disguise. It really isn't, it's just a normal ol' sheep. Nothing to see here, folks. </Text>
  <Text Key="0C3D0E6D">Sheep in Sheep's Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="C1148EE1">Look at this goofy little guy. He's just a lil dude. A tiny friend. He's just kinda there, doing his best. And he promises that despite his name, he won't chomp anyone. Quite the opposite, actually. His sturdy rope limbs are perfect for tantrum-prone teething tots, reinforced specifically for mini Werewolf fangs. </Text>
  <Text Key="D7651E94">Fenry Chompsalot Jr. </Text>
  <Text Key="FCF0083E">No longer does this oil drum hold oil. It's been promoted! Now it holds trash! Take that, oil!</Text>
  <Text Key="65ACD5C1">Oil Drum Trashcan</Text>
  <Text Key="FE56144E">Here may a Werewolf finally find respite from their inner fury. </Text>
  <Text Key="A341EB71">Werewolf Urn</Text>
  <Text Key="0B3FDD96">Here may a Werewolf finally find respite from their inner fury. </Text>
  <Text Key="10D60F49">Werewolf Urn</Text>
  <Text Key="45C695CC">This frame is made out of woodsy planks of woods. When slotted into a building, you can look through them, so that makes it a window!</Text>
  <Text Key="F5B3FC83">Wood Slab Window</Text>
  <Text Key="67C40D53">Who knocked out the frames and glass in this window? Was it you? It better not have been you! </Text>
  <Text Key="B922AB02">Brittle Brick Frame</Text>
  <Text Key="E859457C">Old windows like this really don't have the best insulation, even if glass really is a pretty impressive material when it comes to insulation. </Text>
  <Text Key="CA8897D3">Old Factory Window (Small)</Text>
  <Text Key="9A71E929">Old windows like this really don't have the best insulation, even if glass really is a pretty impressive material when it comes to insulation. </Text>
  <Text Key="F5B3480C">Old Factory Window (Large)</Text>
  <Text Key="16379B98">There are many things in life that correlate to being cool. One of those things is being super buff. Just the other day Maura was telling me, "Hey, that Rory sure is super buff and super cool! Look at her leaning toughly on that building over there!" If you want people to say that about you... you should get this exercise machine. Be the beast you know is inside! </Text>
  <Text Key="576AEE17">Get Buff Workout Machine</Text>
  <Text Key="C069F8FC">In a town split by ideals, the newly established Grimtooth Bar is Celene's vision for the future - a friendly, neutral locale where all Sims - Werewolf or not - can gather and mingle.\n\nThough the scrapped-together venue may be a recent addition, the "secret" bunker out back isn't. The hairier inhabitants of Moonwood Mill have long considered it a local haven from curious eyes, and perhaps something more...</Text>
  <Text Key="14631DC3">Grimtooth Bar &amp; Bunker</Text>
  <Text Key="2B2BE96C">This inviting plot just off the Moonwood River and across from the local library is the perfect lot for any Sim looking to settle down in a small town. Inhale the fresh scent of woodland pine under the full moon, and pay no mind to the creatures lurking about and the incessant howling coming from every direction. (On second thought, maybe this would be a great commercial venue for the denizens who already live here!)</Text>
  <Text Key="DD20B073">Prowler's Patch</Text>
  <Text Key="E46C1AB5">Moonwood Mill's community has repurposed an old logging factory into their very own local library. Its open and airy structure make it the perfect location to curl up with a book or catch a view of the night sky, and out back, the Wildfangs have dragged old workout equipment into the former loading dock for a handy make-shift gym. </Text>
  <Text Key="1A434D72">The Moonwood Mill Library</Text>
  <Text Key="E6AB177B">Nestled on the outskirts of Lake Lunvik, Kristopher Volkov created a home for himself and those in need. He's made room for all who have joined him over the years, with the homey garden and shed out back ensuring those who live here can live a self-sustainable lifestyle in peaceful solitude.</Text>
  <Text Key="0FF96008">The Collective Cabin</Text>
  <Text Key="AB78C9B2">Kristopher Volkov has been around longer than most can remember. He founded and leads the Moonwood Collective, and is eager to take in any werewolf feeling displaced or lost.\n\nLily joined the household long ago, a lonely wanderer who had lost her closest friends to the vampires. After her came Rory, then Jacob. Though Rory's relationship with her adoptive father has soured, Jacob and Kristopher's connection has flourished. Both bear the same calm yet intense soul, and everyone in Moonwood Mill knows Kristopher intends for Jacob to be the heir to his pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="370D204D">Volkov</Text>
  <Text Key="227162A3">This little home may not seem like much, but for the Sim who's looking for some solitude and fresh air, living here can be quite... transformative.</Text>
  <Text Key="210E5450">New Moon Shack</Text>
  <Text Key="F365D78A">Shortly after Lou's arrival in Moonwood Mill, he tried to impress his date Celene by taunting the town's notoriously feral werewolf, Greg. His poor decision led to painful consequences for both him and Celene, but while she sought a remedy, Lou figured he could just ride this one out...which didn't turn out as anticipated. Will this master of mischief learn to love his new inner wolf or will he try and find a way out of the mess he's found himself in?</Text>
  <Text Key="5EADCF95">Howell</Text>
  <Text Key="BE087BC7">Ever since she was a little girl, Celene has been fascinated by romanticized tales of lycanthropy. However, she got more than she bargained for while on a midnight date in the woods. Thankfully, she discovered an antidote which prevented her transformation. She's more cautious now, but her position as the local barkeep gives her a front row view to the wondrous world of werewolves without the risk of injury.</Text>
  <Text Key="334E127E">López</Text>
  <Text Key="4061BA52">Most of Moonwood Mill knows Rory as the leader of the Wildfangs, but she first arrived as a confused young werewolf under the care of Kristopher Volkov. He tried to counsel control and to nurture her like one of his garden flowers, but the two grew apart as Rory grew up. His ideals and values stifled her inner wolf until Rory chose to listen to the beast inside her and moved out to form her own pack. Nowadays, Rory may seem like she has it all figured out, but deep down, she's still discovering how to be the leader she always wished Kristopher could have been.</Text>
  <Text Key="8386F26D">Oaklow</Text>
  <Text Key="80C613C8">Wolfgang has lived in Moonwood Mill for decades, where he's been documenting the history of werewolves and trying to give them a brighter future. A famous author who specializes in werewolf "fiction," his books have introduced the idea of the “friendly neighborhood werewolf” into popular culture. Because he uses a pen name, nobody realizes he himself is actually the very thing he champions.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA3AB767">Wilder</Text>
  <Text Key="F376349B">Try to Sweat Werebies Out </Text>
  <Text Key="DD3DCFDC">Decipher Engraving</Text>
  <Text Key="D45195CA">Drink Vile Concoction</Text>
  <Text Key="CBD4761F">{0.SimFirstName} is the Pack Leader, so {F0.she}{M0.he} can't drink this.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B00D8D1">{0.SimFirstName} can't use this while transformed!</Text>
  <Text Key="B8B3A24F">Drink Wolf-B-Gone </Text>
  <Text Key="612E87A2">The Moonpetal doesn't seem to be blooming right now. Come back when conditions are right to harvest.</Text>
  <Text Key="154B6177">The Moonpetal was harvested recently and will need to bloom again before another harvest.</Text>
  <Text Key="A1A44046">Harvest</Text>
  <Text Key="B9F343BB">Beat Greg Buff (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="810ECED4">Get useful werewolf items (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="5BC7EB3C">Join Pack A (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="F95DB907">Join Pack B (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="5536326B">Leave Pack A (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="EA6F0D20">Leave Pack B (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="025153DA">Make Friend of Pack A (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="8E3FE0B9">Make Friend of Pack B (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="A354D71B">Make Pack Leader (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="04EEA03A">End Alliance/Feud (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="AE432D64">Set Pack Rank 1 (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="BD8BF04F">Set Pack Rank 2 (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="9CDB84B6">Set Pack Rank 3 (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="5F4B1E61">Start Pack Alliance (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="17D0689E">Start Pack Feud (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="7DF96B8B">Pack Value: Max All (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="58922D05">Pack Value: Min All (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="A9FF8710">Force Bloom (debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="6B95F32A">Unlock All Moonwood Portals (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="FBEDC02A">Unlock GP12 Recipes (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="6063587B">Learn Sculpture Secret (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="530B19DC">Lock All Moonwood Portals (Debug)</Text>
  <Text Key="88BEBA42">Enable Fury Effect</Text>
  <Text Key="F4A47424">Disable Fury Effect</Text>
  <Text Key="5F89D5B3">Focus Camera on the Moonwood Collective Hangout</Text>
  <Text Key="138E4D30">Focus Camera on the Wildfangs Hangout</Text>
  <Text Key="4C9D0E45">The Pack Leader is currently somewhere else. </Text>
  <Text Key="3DB59455">Focus Camera on Pack Leader</Text>
  <Text Key="2A79787B">Sorry, but I don't want to talk about this with &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="76FC72B9">Ask about Moonwood Mill</Text>
  <Text Key="FA83AA54">Supernatural Smackdown</Text>
  <Text Key="428FB926">Fight {1.SimFirstName}!</Text>
  <Text Key="14783281">Werewolf Brawl!</Text>
  <Text Key="8E019EB9">Sniff and Introduce</Text>
  <Text Key="EC0DE05D">Spread Beastly Rumors</Text>
  <Text Key="E5935C0F">Insult Feeble Nature</Text>
  <Text Key="591E8F7F">{1.SimFirstName} has not yet achieved Transformation Mastery.</Text>
  <Text Key="CC1F1AB9">Transformation Mastery is required to do this.</Text>
  <Text Key="305678D2">Werewolf Spar</Text>
  <Text Key="75D9927D">Werewolf Spar at the Sparring Grounds</Text>
  <Text Key="47681042">{1.SimFirstName} needs to have Transformation Mastery to do this.</Text>
  <Text Key="52992D00">{0.SimFirstName} needs to rest {F0.her}{M0.his} fangs after {F0.her}{M0.his} recent Tug of War.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE834729">Werewolf Spar with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="94C5BDD8">{0.SimFirstName} has recently been Pack Mentored.</Text>
  <Text Key="D4E633FA">Offer Pack Mentorship</Text>
  <Text Key="B162A4C3">Between you and me, the Moonwood Collective is a bit stuffy for my tastes. They're all sunshine and daisies with everyone, going to all that trouble just to avoid scaring non-Werewolves... ugh. That's why I'm a proud Wildfang! I'm a &lt;i&gt;Werewolf&lt;/i&gt;, not some goody two-shoes camp counselor. </Text>
  <Text Key="440BCE7B">Moonwood Mill's got some cool stuff going on. Sure, I get that we're talking about organized groups of supernaturally strong Sims, and I should probably be intimidated. But even as a non-Werewolf I can admit they're pretty awesome. Probably isn't &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; bad having all those Werewolves around.</Text>
  <Text Key="55709AE8">Our main goal is to spread the good word about Werewolves, building a more positive public perception. Ideally, we live up to this standard not just through what we say, but through our actions as well.</Text>
  <Text Key="C6F656FE">Packs are great way to get involved in the Werewolf community. The Moonwood Collective is like a second home for me. I appreciate how we value being kind and welcoming to all Sims, Werewolf or not!\n\nOh, the Wildfangs? Well, uh... they sure are a pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="1717EE6B">&lt;i&gt;Some&lt;/i&gt; Werewolves see themselves as inherently better than other Sims. They wield their Fury like a weapon against the world. I've never really felt that way, and I'm glad my fellow Moonwood Collective members feel the same. We're working towards a better tomorrow for &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; citizens of Moonwood Mill.</Text>
  <Text Key="9653207A">The two packs are a core aspect of Moonwood Mill's culture and layout. The Moonwood Collective dominates one side of the river, Wildfangs have the other. They're usually clustered around their respective pack hangout spots, but they'll also roam around town butting heads here and there.</Text>
  <Text Key="DF00B470">As leader of The Moonwood Collective, I make sure my members are working towards a better tomorrow for Werewolves and non-Werewolves alike. That's the spirit this pack was founded on, and I have no intention of letting it be forgotten.</Text>
  <Text Key="5504C63F">Well, it's not based on first-hand experience obviously, but I've heard being a member of packs has its benefits. Seems like if you keep following the rules they set, the benefits get sweeter and sweeter. I saw a Wildfang walking around with the coolest looking guitar I'd ever seen the other day... I guess that one must've been pretty high ranked.</Text>
  <Text Key="FAA9601E">There's too much fun out there for us Werewolves to spend a single minute feeling sorry for ourselves, {0.SimFirstName}! The Wildfangs have helped me improve myself. They've taught me to embrace my identity as a Werewolf. I'm never going to &lt;i&gt;apologize&lt;/i&gt; for who, what, or where I am!</Text>
  <Text Key="904B8E26">There's a lot of folks who wouldn't be where they are today if it wasn't for the Moonwood Collective. Packs should be working to benefit the community, not just themselves. We aren't &lt;i&gt;wild&lt;/i&gt; animals, after all.</Text>
  <Text Key="03760349">Remember, {0.SimFirstName}, being a Werewolf isn't some big hokey sentimental burden. It's a gift! Sure, you gotta be willing to put in the work, but that doesn't make it any less of a gift. Just better yourself and get out there into the world.\nI'd never let a single member of the Wildfangs get away with being some sad sack know-it-all. Each and every member has to have fight in 'em.</Text>
  <Text Key="E678C9E1">"Oh ho ho, pardon me while I twiddle my mustache and think of more ways to be the most boring Werewolf in the history of werewolves. Maybe talk synergy with some townspeople tomorrow! Oh, how quaint-"\nHA! Whew, sorry, can't keep a straight face tryin' to act like the Dweebwood Collective. I mean, come on! It's just too easy. Trust me, I'll never lead the Wildfangs to become some "singing circle friendship force" or whatever. We're here to &lt;i&gt;dominate&lt;/i&gt; the Werewolf world. </Text>
  <Text Key="C0F212CA">Get this, {0.SimFirstName}. Two rival packs with completely opposite ways of life... slapped together in one tiny town. And they're all Werewolves. Mark my words, that Moonwood Mill is a ticking timebomb. You couldn't pay me enough Simoleons to move somewhere like that!</Text>
  <Text Key="6E0B8D95">Listen, {0.SimFirstName}. I joined The Wildfangs because I love being a Werewolf. I'm not planning to turn my back on this lifestyle. They don't pick sides over there in the Moonwood Collective, everyone is on their own special "Werewolf Journey" or whatever. I'd rather go on a REAL journey to somewhere cool!</Text>
  <Text Key="61F37D3E">If you find yourself in need while wandering around Moonwood Mill, the folks in the Collective are plenty helpful. Even though I'm not a Werewolf, they've always welcomed me. The Wildfangs, on the other hand... well, they're more focused on helping themselves.</Text>
  <Text Key="5614CEE8">Oh, so somehow it's MY fault that some Wildfangs showed up just to "mark their territory" right outside MY front door last week! It took &lt;b&gt;ages&lt;/b&gt; to get the smell out. Why couldn't it have just been one of those nice Moonwood Collective folks that come by to chat sometimes? </Text>
  <Text Key="B4F1814D">Think about it this way, {0.SimFirstName}. Imagine you're given the best gift ever. Stronger, faster, more durable than any other Sim you know. Fury bubbling around in your noggin. Would you run away from it like a coward? NO, you'd embrace it! You'd OWN it! Get wild, show the world what you can do!\n\nThat's the Wildfang way.</Text>
  <Text Key="6411553B">Sure, the Wildfangs deserve respect just like the rest of us. I'm sure they think all their posturing and brash statements make them seem cool... but all it really does is generate more fear of werewolves. I'd assume you wouldn't want your non-Werewolf neighbor recoiling at the very sight of you, right {0.SimFirstName}? That's why I chose to become the leader of The Moonwood Collective. Because I believe our goals pave the best path forward for us Werewolves to live comfortably. </Text>
  <Text Key="E700CC2D">Packs? How about instead you just pack it up and leave.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CF362B5">Ask about Werewolf Packs</Text>
  <Text Key="CCB81410">Ask About Being a Delta Rank</Text>
  <Text Key="3A9E2584">Ask About Being an Omega Rank</Text>
  <Text Key="D5FE1450">Ask About Being an Alpha Rank</Text>
  <Text Key="007F8D7E">Ask About Being a Beta Rank</Text>
  <Text Key="869A62A2">Ask About Pack Rank</Text>
  <Text Key="05A307E0">{0.SimFirstName} has recently received Pack Mentorship.</Text>
  <Text Key="DD21BD80">Ask for Pack Mentorship</Text>
  <Text Key="06DC1911">Complain about the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="D705BED2">Complain about The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="D9481C82">Declare the Moonwood Collective as the Superior Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="FBB5C841">Declare Wildfangs as the Superior Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="78091469">(From Higher-Ranked Packmate Discipline)</Text>
  <Text Key="6ABB51C5">{1.SimFirstName} has recently been disciplined. </Text>
  <Text Key="8341613E">Discipline Packmate</Text>
  <Text Key="A8065B2F">Discuss the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="EA261F44">Discuss The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="D1F19C40">Break the Alliance</Text>
  <Text Key="6E701FDF">End the Feud</Text>
  <Text Key="BA5234CD">Mock the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="138D4BBE">Mock the Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="531D1E85">Praise the Moonwood Collective's Commitment to Diplomacy</Text>
  <Text Key="5E45E649">Praise the Moonwood Collective's Commitment to Self-Sufficiency</Text>
  <Text Key="3C521C1E">Praise The Wildfangs' Commitment to Self-Improvement</Text>
  <Text Key="90C7895D">Praise The Wildfangs' Commitment to Exploration</Text>
  <Text Key="5C6BC4F0">Share Concerns about Greg</Text>
  <Text Key="8BA115C5">Growl Seductively</Text>
  <Text Key="6E6EA9B5">Tell about Underground Tunnels</Text>
  <Text Key="45952CD5">Snarl At</Text>
  <Text Key="A6D8ABBC">Ask About Being a Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="DAA7A482">Give the Werewolf Talk</Text>
  <Text Key="D8128486">Tell Joke about Werewolves</Text>
  <Text Key="0163F954">{0.SimFirstName} does not have any food, harvestables, collectables, or books in {F0.her}{M0.his} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="8D42D46E">{1.SimFirstName} is in {0.SimFirstName}'s household.</Text>
  <Text Key="6AD4BD4B">Give {1.SimFirstName} a Packmate Gift</Text>
  <Text Key="C49826CB">Contribute to Pack Resources</Text>
  <Text Key="9919D0DB">{0.SimFirstName} has no acceptable items in {F0.her}{M0.his} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="5251CF98">Give an Uncommon or Rare Collectable</Text>
  <Text Key="D3B25450">Give Excellent Quality Food</Text>
  <Text Key="84BAB7E4">Add Perks</Text>
  <Text Key="01B99434">Add Temperaments</Text>
  <Text Key="E1BD7ABF">Add Fury</Text>
  <Text Key="23B0E768">Give Maximum Fury</Text>
  <Text Key="E3358346">Reduce Fury</Text>
  <Text Key="1A8685AF">Remove Temperaments</Text>
  <Text Key="98E76F62">Turn into Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="CAB20C57">Eat Moonpetal</Text>
  <Text Key="31E0D887">This will reset all of {0.SimFirstName}'s werewolf perks and refund all ability points.</Text>
  <Text Key="5A3AD8AD">Through the power of the Moonpetal, {0.SimFirstName}'s werewolf perks have been reset and all ability points refunded!</Text>
  <Text Key="4413FD60">(From Eating Moonpetal)</Text>
  <Text Key="F7358C5C">Somewhere?</Text>
  <Text Key="906F7EF6">(From Running Off as a Rampaging Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="C0944D7C">Hunting</Text>
  <Text Key="69AC9B1C">(From Being Invited to a Hunting Party)</Text>
  <Text Key="9FC69350">(From Recent Werewolf Rampage)</Text>
  <Text Key="9BAD4D80">Watch Spar</Text>
  <Text Key="D5D28312">Awed</Text>
  <Text Key="0ED3AF00">(From Seeing a Werewolf Attack)</Text>
  <Text Key="53950B7F">Witness Turning</Text>
  <Text Key="D2A97F38">Run Away!</Text>
  <Text Key="DF6A45FA">Try to Cleanse Self of Werebies </Text>
  <Text Key="2B6EC48B">Go to Sparring Area</Text>
  <Text Key="1A67F343">Both members require Transformation Mastery to perform this.  </Text>
  <Text Key="5F49D8D7">Spar With</Text>
  <Text Key="137B7497">No nearby packmates to Spar with. </Text>
  <Text Key="1A58F48D">No willing nearby Sims to go hunting with! </Text>
  <Text Key="57C06979">Lead Hunting Party with {2.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="8603D39C">Lead Hunting Party</Text>
  <Text Key="E74113DA">No packmates are currently available.</Text>
  <Text Key="2905BA89">Call Packmates to the Hangout</Text>
  <Text Key="7EBCEE39">There's no one nearby {0.SimFirstName} can spar with.</Text>
  <Text Key="6BE43280">Spar with</Text>
  <Text Key="3D95D85B">Attempt Simlish Communication</Text>
  <Text Key="95682EEC">Attempt to bridge the gap between Werewolves and society. </Text>
  <Text Key="EDAFD1F8">(From Successful Diplomacy)</Text>
  <Text Key="00D3C139">(From Distrusting a Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="7B7A04FA">(From Lack of Sympathy)</Text>
  <Text Key="34178EB3">{0.SimFirstName} has to experience a transformation first.</Text>
  <Text Key="AFDDFC83">This didn't go over so well last time... Let's give {1.SimFirstName} more time.</Text>
  <Text Key="0FFB84DC">Ask for Werewolf Sympathy</Text>
  <Text Key="2FC19091">Use your diplomacy skills to crown a Sim as a Werewolf Ally!</Text>
  <Text Key="C328257A">{1.SimFirstName} is already a Werewolf Ally!</Text>
  <Text Key="CA070293">Werewolf Diplomacy</Text>
  <Text Key="973C65DE">(From Fighting Greg)</Text>
  <Text Key="2247E9C0">Ferocious Intimidation</Text>
  <Text Key="C2A637CD">Attempt to calm a Werewolf down.</Text>
  <Text Key="391F8176">{1.SimFirstName}'s Fury is still somewhat normal.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CC124C9">It will be some time before {1.SimFirstName} can be pacified again.</Text>
  <Text Key="0AB3F407">Pacify {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="B66F7BEC">Hug Cool Werewolf!</Text>
  <Text Key="0D5DA4EE">Hug Fluffy Puppy!</Text>
  <Text Key="AAC34E78">Spar with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="88AEFC42">(From Sparring)</Text>
  <Text Key="B46D7E6B">Practice Howling</Text>
  <Text Key="BB88FB29">Teach to Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="4C788E1B">Give {1.SimFirstName} the confidence {M1.he}{F1.she} needs to howl anytime, anywhere!</Text>
  <Text Key="D2693F86">Prepare {1.SimFirstName} for when {M1.he}{F1.she} becomes a full-fledged Werewolf.</Text>
  <Text Key="3155D700">(From Learning How to Howl)</Text>
  <Text Key="FAD6C058">If I liked you, I'd tell you to go ask {0.SimFirstName}... \n\nBut I don't. So you can get lost.</Text>
  <Text Key="F1126E3D">Sorry you have to ask our leader, {0.SimName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="4CF92F93">The pack's leadership is in transition right now, so you'll have to wait to ask the new Alpha.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF613ECB">Sorry, {0.SimFirstName}. I don't know you well enough yet. Let's get a chance to know each other a bit better first.</Text>
  <Text Key="C62688BC">Nice try, stinky. Pretty shameless of you to ask me that, don't you think?</Text>
  <Text Key="12F587C4">Allow me to extend a hearty welcome to you, our new Friend of the Moonwood Collective. We're so happy to have you! Don't hesitate to stop by our tree and spend some time with us, or use the facilities. Though not required, we gladly welcome any future contributions to better the pack. Your generosity would be greatly appreciated!</Text>
  <Text Key="DE8FDEE5">{0.SimFirstName} lost the pack's trust too recently. </Text>
  <Text Key="7430C97D">{0.SimFirstName} was kicked out of the pack too recently.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E3B1244">Ask to be Friend of the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="211623F0">Look at you, brand spankin' new Friend of the Wildfangs! Feel free to hang out with us whenever, or pop in and use our trailer. And hey, you don't &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; to do this, but we won't say no if you have any cool stuff to give us in the future. Every bit counts, you know?</Text>
  <Text Key="0C1B4E2F">Ask to be Friend of The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="402B7381">I wish I could let you in, but you'll have to ask our leader, {0.SimName}. </Text>
  <Text Key="EBEBEC4D">Really, &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; want to join MY pack? Are pigs flying right now or something? Even if I could invite you to the pack, I wouldn't. Good luck winning {0.SimFirstName} over.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0BED21C">The pack's going through a leadership change right now. We're not accepting new members until that's settled.</Text>
  <Text Key="F64217A5">{0.SimFirstName} is not old enough to join a Werewolf pack. </Text>
  <Text Key="56BEDB47">Ask to Join the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="FDEABD7C">Ask to Join The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="873F62C3">Honorable Brawl</Text>
  <Text Key="BDB73ABE">{0.SimFirstName} has challenged the Alpha too recently. </Text>
  <Text Key="36EC0E6C">Epic Tug of War</Text>
  <Text Key="D79EA080">Requires a nearby music source.</Text>
  <Text Key="BEF25820">Dance!</Text>
  <Text Key="7FF32B32">{1.SimFirstName} has recently fetched something.</Text>
  <Text Key="ECFB6175">Fetch Something Cool</Text>
  <Text Key="45454BE7">Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="4D44383D">Sit</Text>
  <Text Key="5072B62D">Command To Spar</Text>
  <Text Key="7A4FD964">Workout</Text>
  <Text Key="2B066E96">Demote To Omega</Text>
  <Text Key="71644D06">Demote To Delta</Text>
  <Text Key="97F54C4A">Demote to Lower Pack Rank</Text>
  <Text Key="3DF5C55D">{1.SimFirstName} needs to rest {F1.her}{M1.his} fangs after {F1.her}{M1.his} recent Tug of War.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CA423C9">Challenge to Tug of War</Text>
  <Text Key="7EBEF944">Entrust Leadership of Wildfangs to {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="ECC7E5CB">{1.SimFirstName} recently stepped down from pack leadership.</Text>
  <Text Key="10D87F89">Entrust Moonwood Collective Leadership to {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="E7327208">You know, I appreciate the offer... but I'm going to have to pass. It's just not the right time for me to associate with your pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="F491DDE3">What?! I couldn't hear you! You want me to... send you a snack? I don't have time for that!\n\nOh you said befriend your pack? Yeah, that's also a no. Sorry, buddy!</Text>
  <Text Key="872DA915">Friend? Of YOUR pack? You're joking, right?</Text>
  <Text Key="78B76D62">{1.SimFirstName} is already a Friend of the Pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="FFC494D7">{1.SimFirstName} recently declined that offer.</Text>
  <Text Key="7D54E43A">Invite to Become Friend of Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="705FE8C3">I do appreciate the offer, but unfortunately I can't right now. Maybe sometime in the future!</Text>
  <Text Key="1E03255A">Join your pack? Hmm... no thanks.</Text>
  <Text Key="89060606">Thanks, but I'd rather maroon myself on a deserted island and live the rest of my days in solitude than join a pack led by &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;. </Text>
  <Text Key="3D7EAE77">{1.SimFirstName} is not a Werewolf.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F903A22">{1.SimFirstName} is a member of the Wildfangs.</Text>
  <Text Key="2CE7B927">{1.SimFirstName} recently left the pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="8BDA1E81">Invite to Join Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="9C2B42BD">{1.SimFirstName} is a member of the Moonwood Collective.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E9C006C">Trial: {0.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="DB2A5876">{0.SimFirstName} doesn't have this Werewolf Ability.</Text>
  <Text Key="4C6883A5">Discuss Lunar Epiphany</Text>
  <Text Key="674D7CBA">Demonstrate Pack Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="796A69A1">Demonstrate Scavenging</Text>
  <Text Key="E68DA6C1">(From Alpha-to-Alpha Talk)</Text>
  <Text Key="2AC3E722">{0.SimFirstName} should probably wait before risking another Alpha-to-Alpha Talk.</Text>
  <Text Key="17CA3FD9">Alpha-to-Alpha Talk</Text>
  <Text Key="3067F445">Leave the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="1D8758D6">Leave the Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="85C62C6B">Ha! You really had me going there for a sec.</Text>
  <Text Key="5202FE5C">Well, good! Glad to hear you're sticking around.</Text>
  <Text Key="B99F5A27">Yeah, I get it. That lone wolf lifestyle can be pretty appealing. Don't sweat it!</Text>
  <Text Key="DCF10EEF">I understand. You're our friend, packmate or not. So don't be a stranger!</Text>
  <Text Key="0D42C459">Nice, &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; nice. Why don't you do everyone a favor and scram, runt!</Text>
  <Text Key="E1660F6C">It's not every day you see the trash take itself out. Leave, and take your little attitude with you.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E116A78">.....Okay? This doesn't have to be awkward. We'll see you when we see you, I guess.</Text>
  <Text Key="543C5BB0">Understood, friend. I hope the Moonwood Collective eased your Werewolf journey.</Text>
  <Text Key="159D22C9">Seriously? I mean, really? You're just going to abandon everything? Fine.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBD2821E">Promote To Delta</Text>
  <Text Key="654DE39C">Promote To Beta</Text>
  <Text Key="5DEEE1F4">Promote to Higher Pack Rank</Text>
  <Text Key="52D1A88A">(From Being Kicked out of Pack)</Text>
  <Text Key="8F4D10E6">Kick {1.SimFirstName} Out of the Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="AF447C69">Thanks for checking in, {0.SimFirstName}. Turns out it was just a misunderstanding. You're good to go.</Text>
  <Text Key="8A7675D8">Well, {0.SimFirstName}, you've proved me wrong. I thought you understood what this pack stands for. Thought you wanted to be a part of this community. Guess not.\n\n{0.SimName}, you're officially a &lt;i&gt;former&lt;/i&gt; member of the Moonwood Collective.</Text>
  <Text Key="72EA65C0">{0.SimFirstName}, I see you've gone through a pretty significant lifestyle change. While you can't remain a Moonwood Collective member, you can certainly remain a Friend of the Pack. </Text>
  <Text Key="B4F6E47F">Your blatant disregard of our values makes it seem like you don't care about the pack anymore, {0.SimFirstName}. I'm giving you a penalty to your pack rank, to hopefully motivate you to do better in the future. Now show us you care!</Text>
  <Text Key="5480A199">With the way you've been acting, I have to give you a penalty to your pack rank, {0.SimFirstName}. I know, this isn't a fun conversation for either of us... but when you're part of the pack, you have to act like it.</Text>
  <Text Key="EAD20971">Your recent behavior was... illuminating. {0.SimFirstName}, you're officially no longer a Friend of the Moonwood Collective.</Text>
  <Text Key="B3BD0EBF">Report to Pack Leader</Text>
  <Text Key="18986F78">Listen, the Wildfangs aren't as strict as other packs, but that doesn't mean we're lawless. {0.SimFirstName}, you've crossed the line one too many times. I have to do what's best for our- no, &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; community. I'm kicking you out of the pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F24DF75">Look, you just can't &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; be a Wildfang if you're not a Werewolf. I can't say I'd make the same choices, but who am I to judge. Stick around if you want, as a Friend of the Pack. </Text>
  <Text Key="E46D34B5">This shouldn't be a surprise with how you've been acting, but in case you need to hear it loud and clear: {0.SimFirstName}, you're no longer a Friend of the Wildfangs.</Text>
  <Text Key="16FB18D5">(From Receiving Greg's Gift)</Text>
  <Text Key="52991DB6">Ask for {1.SimFirstName}'s Gift</Text>
  <Text Key="3BA32457">Attempt to Communicate</Text>
  <Text Key="5BCED2CE">Provoke</Text>
  <Text Key="1BB07D7C">Discuss being a Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="5700100F">Share Werewolf Experiences</Text>
  <Text Key="F6964ECF">Say Goodnight to the Moon</Text>
  <Text Key="21B53044">Make Wolf Eyes At</Text>
  <Text Key="376AF9B4">Must be standing on diggable terrain.</Text>
  <Text Key="91F60D9A">Can only tunnel to diggable terrain.</Text>
  <Text Key="A9EC2054">Tunnel Here</Text>
  <Text Key="8BE3A6F1">Mark Territory</Text>
  <Text Key="C426A971">Wolf Nap</Text>
  <Text Key="61894BBF">Go Here &lt;i&gt;Savagely&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="8A81B8A4">Scavenge Ground</Text>
  <Text Key="244243D1">Smell Here</Text>
  <Text Key="9512A6E5">Try to Force Werebies Out</Text>
  <Text Key="A8BA177A">Try to Run Werebies Off</Text>
  <Text Key="122CB8BC">This simple bit of wood looks like it could channel magical powers in the right hands.</Text>
  <Text Key="F1BE9844">Examine</Text>
  <Text Key="8D67716A">Zoomies</Text>
  <Text Key="A1F989D9">This object is already in use.</Text>
  <Text Key="B1ED62CD">Devour</Text>
  <Text Key="AE75E297">{0.SimFirstName} is rampaging and unable to use this right now.</Text>
  <Text Key="A88DFF12">&lt;i&gt;???????&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="50E2EAB4">Groom Self</Text>
  <Text Key="BD14716D">Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="5871C9F5">{0.SimFirstName} has howled too much. {F0.She}{M0.He} needs a little rest!</Text>
  <Text Key="A0533A41">Howl... Somewhere else?</Text>
  <Text Key="67D3900B">{0.SimFirstName} can only perform this once per night.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA1775AC">Can only be done outside and at night. </Text>
  <Text Key="EDE24898">Can only be done outside and at night. </Text>
  <Text Key="839A419F">Lunar Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="9BB0AFDC">Pack Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="B1DFF67E">(From Bellowing Somberly)</Text>
  <Text Key="3BB59604">{0.SimFirstName} needs a little longer before attempting this one again. </Text>
  <Text Key="10E80DA7">Oh {0.SimFirstName} is &lt;i&gt;well&lt;/i&gt; past that. </Text>
  <Text Key="197A5065">Somber Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="EAA3C84D">Vicious Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="4252402F">Hunt for Food</Text>
  <Text Key="E1EB3ABB">Sleep under the Moon</Text>
  <Text Key="15C0EAE8">(From Tapping into Inner Wolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="FB3E1B2B">Activate Primal Instinct</Text>
  <Text Key="767DFD1A">Attempt to regain your senses. The higher your Werewolf rank, the more likely to succeed. </Text>
  <Text Key="29CD04A9">That was mentally taxing, {0.SimFirstName} needs a second before trying that again.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE809AC6">Try to Regain Control</Text>
  <Text Key="2B3BE4BB">Enhance Smell</Text>
  <Text Key="DAEDC853">Deactivate Super Speed</Text>
  <Text Key="74D8CD4B">Activate Super Speed</Text>
  <Text Key="65F4739E">Fainted</Text>
  <Text Key="D40F9201">Feelin' Frisky</Text>
  <Text Key="21BC1311">TEXT WITH WILD DISREGARD FOR ALL THAT IS SACRED</Text>
  <Text Key="4AC20091">(From Being Near a Rampaging Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="EC6F5840">Already a safe distance away! Phew!</Text>
  <Text Key="5F6AE120">Run Away!</Text>
  <Text Key="D0BE2478">Smash</Text>
  <Text Key="3397A496">Scratch</Text>
  <Text Key="A777BF9B">Transform</Text>
  <Text Key="5D89C401">Return to Normal</Text>
  <Text Key="1329CC8D">Watch out! {0.SimFirstName} is transforming!\n\nWerewolf Sims who reach max Fury will erupt with rage and start rampaging. During this time, Werewolves have very little control of themselves and will give in to their beastly instincts.</Text>
  <Text Key="B7400FC8">Be Cured </Text>
  <Text Key="76046F59">{0.SimFirstName} has Werebies </Text>
  <Text Key="9F41D299">{0.SimFirstName} doesn't know {1.SimFirstName} well enough to turn them. Try befriending {0.SimFirstName} first!</Text>
  <Text Key="9CD9E882">Pregnant Sims can't be bitten!</Text>
  <Text Key="E7074234">{1.SimFirstName} does not have the Curse Bearer Ability.</Text>
  <Text Key="538F6705">Ask for Cursed Bite</Text>
  <Text Key="37FD465D">Transform</Text>
  <Text Key="B4E9160B">(From Werewolf Attack)</Text>
  <Text Key="D1937C7F">(From Willingly Accepting a Cursed Bite) </Text>
  <Text Key="0F7AB9B8">Ask if {1.SimFirstName} wants to become Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="17C37B82">It's too late, the curse has begun! </Text>
  <Text Key="A7FA2C6D">Ask for Werebies Remedy</Text>
  <Text Key="1922E72B">Be Asked for Cursed Bite</Text>
  <Text Key="C120C5F4">Be Given Cursed Bite</Text>
  <Text Key="82D173FE">Full Moon Turn</Text>
  <Text Key="A3D6CBDD">Cursed Bite</Text>
  <Text Key="C0FAC44A">Fetching Something Cool</Text>
  <Text Key="502B0233">{0.SimFirstName} must wait before {F0.she}{M0.he} can do this again.</Text>
  <Text Key="A703C26B">Check Pack Resources</Text>
  <Text Key="D78559FD">{0.SimFirstName} cannot do this right now. {F0.She}{M0.He} has to wait to report in to the new leader.</Text>
  <Text Key="F544A4F9">Claim Pack Leadership</Text>
  <Text Key="861BF1C9">Only the Pack Leader can do this.</Text>
  <Text Key="B3600970">Friendly</Text>
  <Text Key="142AC468">Normal</Text>
  <Text Key="69F626FE">Intimidating</Text>
  <Text Key="29928AD9">Hang Out</Text>
  <Text Key="1CC3846C">Use Restroom</Text>
  <Text Key="35C47010">Rest</Text>
  <Text Key="E6CB7D1B">Wash Up</Text>
  <Text Key="42295A0E">View Moonwood Collective Information</Text>
  <Text Key="800D9ADD">View Wildfangs Information</Text>
  <Text Key="BA6DAB69">Various old flyers indicate Moonwood Mill was a bustling logging town back in its heyday. Today, it is home to a much smaller community, made up of two close-knit "groups": the Moonwood Collective and the Wildfangs. \n\nEven without the industry, there's plenty to do... especially during a full moon. Catch the elusive Luna Fish or harvest the rare Moonpetal flower, explore the secret Underground, hang out with the locals, or have a howling good time up the mountain overlooking Lake Lunvik. Just don't go near Greg...</Text>
  <Text Key="CF5AA21D">\nAmongst the flyers are mysterious scribbles, enchanted by lunar magic. Somehow you can understand them... They speak of an enchanted room deep within the underground tunnels, residual overload energy from an untamed spell in the lake, and the original conflict between Werewolves and Vampires. This was where it began.</Text>
  <Text Key="9D31F6E9">Moonwood Mill</Text>
  <Text Key="04BA77C1">View Moonwood Mill Information</Text>
  <Text Key="02B016C6">View Werebies Advisory</Text>
  <Text Key="8D1931A4">Cry Greg</Text>
  <Text Key="E81E3468">Attempt to Distract</Text>
  <Text Key="0C1985FC">Investigate Warning Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="8634698E">Explore Underground Tunnels</Text>
  <Text Key="4C81172E">Travel to {2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="8B9F6C5B">Travel to Peak</Text>
  <Text Key="AE27A59F">Travel to Base</Text>
  <Text Key="8A4E9477">Travel to Sparring Grounds Portal Potties</Text>
  <Text Key="BC819187">Travel to Sewer Grate</Text>
  <Text Key="A406B907">Travel to Ground-Level Bunker</Text>
  <Text Key="3E9B60A4">Travel to Moonwood Mill</Text>
  <Text Key="BD64BF4F">Nighttime Sleep Grants Mood Benefits</Text>
  <Text Key="4D001A0F">Sleeping Grants Mood Benefits</Text>
  <Text Key="29151384">Tonight: Nighttime Sleep Grants Mood Benefits</Text>
  <Text Key="1EAD8ECF">Increased Skill Gain from Fitness Activities</Text>
  <Text Key="72AF61E6">Tonight: Increased Skill Gain from Fitness Activities</Text>
  <Text Key="B31A74D8">Increased Relationship Gain and Loss</Text>
  <Text Key="EB893A05">Increased Relationship Gain</Text>
  <Text Key="0960B714">Tonight: Increased Relationship Gain and Loss</Text>
  <Text Key="1706D939">Tonight: Increased Relationship Gain</Text>
  <Text Key="0828BA91">Heightened Fighting Prowess</Text>
  <Text Key="334F72EC">Tonight: Heightened Fighting Prowess</Text>
  <Text Key="CC0DDD67">Call of the Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="47D27757">Increased Romance Gain</Text>
  <Text Key="0412F3EB">Tonight: Increased Romance Gain</Text>
  <Text Key="7E7E2CD4">(From being a Werewolf during a Full Moon)</Text>
  <Text Key="05ABE7F5">(From Impending Full Moon)</Text>
  <Text Key="4A475969">Tonight: Call of the Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="C82C3095">Increased Handiness</Text>
  <Text Key="31FFA9C9">Tonight: Increased Handiness</Text>
  <Text Key="22039E33">Increased Logic and Reading</Text>
  <Text Key="99F185E9">Tonight: Increased Logic and Reading</Text>
  <Text Key="C57522B8">Werewolf Pack relations are updating. Please wait a moment.</Text>
  <Text Key="3F8A1A9D">The engravings on this relic are encrypted with strange symbols. Only Werewolves who have experienced a Lunar Epiphany can decipher it!</Text>
  <Text Key="4C324EA4">Based on its age, this skull belonged to one of the tamed cowplants used by the &lt;b&gt;Moo&lt;/b&gt;casters, a Spellcaster group that served as a counterpart to the Mooncasters. Both groups formed in response to the vampires' Operation Eternal Flame - a covert operation attempting to turn all remaining spellcasters into vampires. They simply differed in their methods. Rather than harnessing the power of the moon to become Werewolves, the Moocasters instead tamed cowplants to use as (somewhat) loyal companions in battle.

There appears to be a carving leading towards the jawbone, though the writing is hard to deciper. It currently reads "I will..."</Text>
  <Text Key="3953B201">"... avenge you" is carved into the jawbone, originating at the back tip and seeming to come from the skull. The words are carved hastily, using what appeared to have been an unusually sharp Werewolf claw. The final word devolves into a frenzied scratch, cutting deep into the time-brittled bone.\n\nA whiff of Greg's ominous scent lingers upon the bone, concentrated around the carving.</Text>
  <Text Key="22B31D7A">Near the painting of a wolf's tail, this shard is engraved with some vague text describing what appears to be steps of an adapted ritual, likely dating back to ancient Myshupotatmian tradition. The language, however, is consistent with the era of the Mooncasters, suggesting the pot was used to transport the glowing waters of Lake Lunvik to perform certain power-harnessing ceremonies atop the Howling Point cliff in Moonwood Mill. The waters of the lake must have been crucial to their efforts of attuning to the moon...</Text>
  <Text Key="5E5613D4">Etched around the painting of a wolf's head, this shard contains a list. Some adjacent notes reveal that it is based on observations of the children of the Mooncasters, after their parents' transformation into the first Werewolves. It offers solutions to dormant Werewolf genes in a non-Werewolf child born to Werewolves. Some promising ones, such as "full moon- devour ten grilled cheese sandwiches" and "walk around on all fours- no speaking, only howling" are crossed out for some reason.\n\nHowever, one entry on the list is circled: "Lake Lunvik swim - full moon."</Text>
  <Text Key="DC40D70E">Traces of the glowing water of Lake Lunvik are present on this shard. A wolf's body is painted on the outside, the paint faintly shimmering with the unmistakable glimmer of Moonpetal pollen. The Mooncasters must have also used the water transported in this pot to cultivate the legendary Moonpetal bloom atop the Howling Point. Of course, such a magically-infused plant would require such powerful water to sustain it, and likely still benefits from its proximity to the lake to this day.</Text>
  <Text Key="DC413320">This lid is painted with what appears to be four wolf paw prints, with names listed below each. Labeled &lt;i&gt;Kiyah&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Logan&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Mikal&lt;/i&gt;, and &lt;i&gt;Wugbug&lt;/i&gt;, you recall from your studies that these were four of the original Mooncasters' wolf familiars. Even after the transfer of power between the Mooncasters and their familiars, it appears the familiars must have still played an important part in the group as the Mooncaster's trusted lifelong companions.</Text>
  <Text Key="FDCB98B5">In your readings, you learned that many moons ago, the land we now know as Moonwood Mill was actually the home of a small ancient Myshupotamian city. Interestingly enough, Myshupotamians believed that the greatest minds of their society were reborn as wolves that stored their wisdom in the moon via howl. As the cycle progressed towards a full moon, the growing light represented more and more stored wisdom. On full moon nights, Myshupotamians would sport wolf-like masks and ceremonially draw upon the moon's stored wisdom. As the cycle then progressed to a new moon, the light leaving the moon each night represented the stored wisdom slowly dispersing to the Myshupotamian people.\n\nAs the first modern werewolves, Moonwood Mill's Mooncasters likely gleaned much of their information on harnessing the moon's power from studying the Myshupotamians...</Text>
  <Text Key="FCB0BAA1">...Another often forgotten aspect of Myshupotamian culture was taming Cowplants as stationary sentinels of defense, and sometimes cross-breeding them to be mobile attack units (though it was quite difficult to safely reproduce mobile cowplants, for obvious reasons...)\n\nIn modern times, it turns out the Moooncasters were not the only group seeking unorthodox answers to the vampire problem during Operation Eternal Flame. The &lt;b&gt;Moo&lt;/b&gt;casters (who 100% came up with their name first, total coincidence) attempted to adapt Myshupotamian cowplant taming practices to their needs. It was an initial success, and they had a prosperous alliance with the Mooncasters. Needless to say, it didn't last long after one of the "tamed" cowplants feasted upon Yina Kia, an original Mooncaster... and Greggorius and Avelina Lunvik's dearest friend.</Text>
  <Text Key="ABC1071A">The wolf figurine has a name engraved on its base, "Brutus." You recall from your werewolf studies that this was the wolf familiar of Greggorious Lunvik, one of the original Mooncasters.\n\nBrutus was a fearsome Alpha wolf, with fangs and claws sharper than any of his peers or predecessors. After the Mooncasters imbued themselves with the energy of their familiars, they adopted their traits and aptitudes. Thank to Brutus, Greggorious developed an unusually high aptitude for pushing the limits of Fury, and a knack for winning fights.</Text>
  <Text Key="D87125EF">The wolf figurine has a name engraved on its base, "Renga." You recall from your werewolf studies that this was the wolf familiar of Yina Kia, one of the original Mooncasters.\n\nYina was the Lunviks' closest friend in the Mooncasters. She had an insatiable love for going on adventures to unfamiliar places. Renga had a similar wanderlust, and when infused with his energy during the Mooncaster transformation, her energetic will to explore (and get into trouble) was bolstered greatly. This was much to the frustration of her non-Werewolf wife, Emmy, who only wished they could settle once the vampire conflicts were over. One day, during a joint defense mission between the Werewolf Mooncasters and the cowplant-tamer &lt;b&gt;Moo&lt;/b&gt;casters, Yina's mischievous spirit became her downfall as she accidentally became a cowplant's lunch. After Yina's passing, many noted the furrow in Greggorious' brow grew a bit deeper, and it is said that Renga was practically glued to Emmy's side for the rest of his days.</Text>
  <Text Key="162F9B67">The wolf figurine has a name engraved on its base, "Verity." You recall from your werewolf studies that this was the wolf familiar of Maria Volkov, one of the original Mooncasters.\n\nMaria's dedication to community enrichment and diplomacy was no doubt enhanced by Verity's dignified, princely nature upon combining with his energy during the Mooncaster transformation. She and Greggorious often engaged in &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; heated debates over the Mooncasters' new responsibilities as Werewolves. Are all Sims born as good or bad? Or was "good" a title earned? Are Werewolves forever cursed to give into their base instincts? Or do they have a responsibility to exercise caution and discipline?\n\nAs time went on, Maria concluded Greggorious was simply jealous of her ability to control her Fury. For since the night of the transformation, she had never found it difficult to suppress her wild instincts, and he had only grown more and more... beastly.</Text>
  <Text Key="687002CE">The wolf figurine has a name engraved on its base, "Gibby." You recall from your werewolf studies that this was the wolf familiar of Avelina Lunvik, one of the original Mooncasters.\n\nNamed after the Gibbous moon phases, Gibby's powers enhanced Avelina's fascinations with the moon and the workings of space. Upon her transformation into a werewolf, she poured her heart and soul into her studies with an unprecedented fervor. She aimed to do all she could to help her husband Greggorious with his explorations and experimentation with Fury.</Text>
  <Text Key="B713203C">Only werewolves can use this door.</Text>
  <Text Key="E553E278">(From Drinking Power-Sip MIDNIGHT)</Text>
  <Text Key="CEF56030">(From Eating Luna Fish)</Text>
  <Text Key="74F7907D">Gross... meat.</Text>
  <Text Key="DD945EDF">(From Eating Raw Meat)</Text>
  <Text Key="FD9583A2">(From Eating Raw Meat as a Werewolf)</Text>
  <Text Key="3E54761B">Drink the Cure</Text>
  <Text Key="A3F8BC1C">Make sure {0.SimFirstName} is fully prepared to leave {F0.her}{M0.his} werewolf lifestyle behind first!</Text>
  <Text Key="4E7EED44">Harvest Moonpetal</Text>
  <Text Key="FD2CEFE1">Locate the rare Moonpetal bloom in Moonwood Mill and harvest it for the cure recipe.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF53737D">Collect Wolfsbane</Text>
  <Text Key="C094FC52">Harvest Wolfsbane herb for the cure recipe.</Text>
  <Text Key="7D30D2A6">Craft Wolf-B-Gone</Text>
  <Text Key="DABC105F">Once {M0.he}{F0.she}'s learned the recipe for Wolf-B-Gone while exploring Moonwood Mill and obtained all the required ingredients, {0.SimFirstName} should head to a bar to craft a fresh glass of it.</Text>
  <Text Key="92A85E39">Become a Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="EB6EE4DE">No fangs or fur to be found? Try spending some time around werewolves as either friend or foe! Or explore the deep, dark reaches of Moonwood Mill's underground. </Text>
  <Text Key="A870E486">Level up to Runt</Text>
  <Text Key="19DCA3FF">Pup no more! Achieve the second tier of werewolf progression. {0.SimFirstName}'s progress can be tracked via the Werewolf Abilities panel.</Text>
  <Text Key="298514E7">Experience a Full Moon</Text>
  <Text Key="BD2A94C8">In order to understand how the moon affects {F0.her}{M0.his} Fury, {0.SimFirstName} needs to experience the entirety of a full moon night.\nUpcoming lunar phases can be tracked via the Calendar. </Text>
  <Text Key="12BEB3A4">Read Werewolf Books</Text>
  <Text Key="5EE7D501">Try checking out bookshelves around Moonwood Mill, or purchasing werewolf books via the computer. While discovering the secrets of werewolf history, {0.SimFirstName} might even have an epiphany!</Text>
  <Text Key="5467CFBF">Level up to Apex</Text>
  <Text Key="CCC39460">Reach the final tier of Werewolf Progression to truly master the Werewolf lifestyle!</Text>
  <Text Key="BF85DA38">Unleash the Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="0FD5B895">Time for {0.SimFirstName} to bare those fangs and claws, channeling {F0.her}{M0.his} inner beast! To accomplish this, {F0.she}{M0.he} can Smash or Scratch objects around {F0.her}{M0.him}. Or {F0.she}{M0.he} can try Snarling, Ferociously Intimidating, or Viciously Howling at other Sims.</Text>
  <Text Key="3AFADBF1">Spar with Werewolves</Text>
  <Text Key="937E0AD6">Prove to everyone who the strongest Werewolf in town is! Perform Werewolf Spar with 5 different Werewolves to show off {0.SimFirstName}'s fighting prowess.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4EE59E2">Defeat Greg in a Werewolf Brawl</Text>
  <Text Key="DF4691CB">Greg certainly has a reputation... and he is definitely not allowed to be scarier than {0.SimFirstName}! Challenge Greg to a Werewolf Brawl and emerge victorious!</Text>
  <Text Key="8D5F971D">Join the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="CD7DB232">Befriend the Moonwood Collective's leader and pass the trials to join the pack!</Text>
  <Text Key="E67AA6CA">Socialize with Werewolf Friends</Text>
  <Text Key="54221913">{0.SimFirstName} must broaden {F0.her}{M0.his} connections in the Werewolf world, building relationships with different Werewolves until they officially consider {F0.her}{M0.him} a Friend, and continuing to interact with each one of them in a friendly manner!</Text>
  <Text Key="327A66BB">Be a Good Werewolf Ambassador</Text>
  <Text Key="DDCC357C">Live out the Moonwood Collective's pack values by making use of some handy Werewolf Abilities! Try using Werewolf Empathy to Pacify a rampaging Werewolf, regaining control during rampages with The Will to Resist, or spreading the good word outside of the Werewolf community through Werewolf Diplomacy.</Text>
  <Text Key="226CBE40">Become Alpha of the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="9028EF9D">Challenge the current Alpha of the Moonwood Collective and take control as the new pack leader!</Text>
  <Text Key="A934E6F2">Join The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="04B3FD7B">Befriend the Wildfangs' leader and pass the trials to join the pack!</Text>
  <Text Key="771FEB25">Turn Sims into Werewolves</Text>
  <Text Key="CAAF7DFA">Obtain the Curse Bearer ability and use it to create more Werewolves by turning non-Werewolf Sims. </Text>
  <Text Key="DD7B2D0C">Werewolf World Domination!</Text>
  <Text Key="F7D80A69">Time for {0.SimFirstName} to get out there and show the world who's boss! Try obtaining the Territory Marking ability and... making use of it. {F0.She}{M0.He} can also Spar with {F0.her}{M0.his} Werewolf friends, or maybe even try {F0.her}{M0.his} hand at Provoking Greg!</Text>
  <Text Key="9B2BE8CE">Become Alpha of the Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="00DC3927">Challenge the current Alpha of the Wildfangs and take control as the new pack leader!</Text>
  <Text Key="B5129D62">Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="66DE1B3E">Werewolf Cheats</Text>
  <Text Key="3BCCDC9B">Werewolf Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="BB27DE14">Pack Hierarchy</Text>
  <Text Key="4DDD336C">Challenge Leader for Alpha Rank</Text>
  <Text Key="9ABC94E6">Command To</Text>
  <Text Key="ABC1B677">Decorate</Text>
  <Text Key="CC89AE44">Join Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="4AA2643C">Use Facilities</Text>
  <Text Key="779EF20B">This stair railing is sturdy—we think. The metal parts are sturdy. They aren't going anywhere! But how tightly are they fastened to the stairs? Not sure. </Text>
  <Text Key="D3E7A08A">Old Factory Railing</Text>
  <Text Key="70927D27">Moonpetal Punch</Text>
  <Text Key="8B5B76A8">Make Moonpetal Punch</Text>
  <Text Key="FF1DE85E">{0.SimFirstName} doesn't know how to make this. The secrets behind the recipe lie within Moonwood Mill...</Text>
  <Text Key="67C62B54">Wolf-B-Gone</Text>
  <Text Key="75F34E87">Make Wolf-B-Gone</Text>
  <Text Key="D89B9777">Power-Sip MIDNIGHT</Text>
  <Text Key="982FFBAB">Blue Steak</Text>
  <Text Key="814FB584">Make Blue Steak</Text>
  <Text Key="08637C79">Grill Luna Fish</Text>
  <Text Key="94F7EDED">Grilled Luna Fish</Text>
  <Text Key="C638A635">Make Mushroom Steak</Text>
  <Text Key="9AEC5AF1">Mushroom Steak</Text>
  <Text Key="DD9D4AA3">Make Steak Tartare</Text>
  <Text Key="1F0CDC26">Steak Tartare</Text>
  <Text Key="6EAB1E6A">Cold Cuts</Text>
  <Text Key="7944CFCB">Raw Meat</Text>
  <Text Key="66C7EE1B">These Werewolves are tied together for life by the strings of Fate!</Text>
  <Text Key="A7127F3F">Fated Mates</Text>
  <Text Key="253A9F52">{1.SimFirstName} is the worst pack leader EVER for kicking {0.SimFirstName} out of the Moonwood Collective. </Text>
  <Text Key="3A7B0DF8">Grudge Against the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="091AA52F">{1.SimFirstName} is the worst pack leader EVER for kicking {0.SimFirstName} out of the Wildfangs. </Text>
  <Text Key="1D4D2783">Grudge Against the Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="825D405E">Bound by the bite! {0.SimFirstName} has a powerful bond with {1.SimFirstName} for turning {F0.her}{M0.him} into a Werewolf.</Text>
  <Text Key="C1AA6FA4">Lycan Bond </Text>
  <Text Key="C081D44D">{0.SimFirstName} has felt the wolfy warmth of companionship with {F0.her}{M0.his} packmate {1.SimFirstName} and really enjoys {F1.her}{M1.his} company!</Text>
  <Text Key="8FBEF2E5">Wolfy Warmth</Text>
  <Text Key="0D1965B8">Like a storybook, it was meant to be all along!</Text>
  <Text Key="03E826B2">Fated to Wed</Text>
  <Text Key="100FD619">{0.SimFirstName} is enchanted by a romantic First Kiss under the full moon with {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="6FB7EF71">Moonkissed</Text>
  <Text Key="5882E3F4">Do you believe in fated love between Werewolves? Because right now I sure do!</Text>
  <Text Key="7327647E">It's Fate!</Text>
  <Text Key="C6D3ABAE">{0.SimFirstName} is bitter about the hurtful things {1.SimFirstName} did in the name of {F1.her}{M1.his} pack.</Text>
  <Text Key="E5367294">Furious Pack Rivalry</Text>
  <Text Key="30C7957F">Although fate took an unexpected turn, something still feels wrong about all of this.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0CC9F33">Fate Defied</Text>
  <Text Key="94D137A6">{0.SimFirstName} feels a sense of shame for not just leaving the pack, but also for letting {1.SimFirstName} down by taking the cure. </Text>
  <Text Key="1A36F01C">Ashamed of Abandoning Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="0F0ACDF9">{0.SimFirstName} accidently frightened {1.SimFirstName} with {M0.his}{F0.her} werewolfy ways. People close to {0.SimFirstName} deserve better than that. </Text>
  <Text Key="FF017BD1">Big Sad Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="811BE000">{0.SimFirstName} can't believe someone from {M0.his}{F0.her} own pack would treat {M0.him}{F0.her} like that.</Text>
  <Text Key="4B24F02A">Hurt by Packmate</Text>
  <Text Key="F113F266">Sims with a Lunar Link retain the special benefits of the Lunar Cycle they once felt as Werewolves, and can still Howl just like old times!</Text>
  <Text Key="7DDB0BB1">Lunar Link</Text>
  <Text Key="EB6A5D70">Fanged Friends get an additional boost to their relationships with both Werewolves and non-Werewolf Sims.</Text>
  <Text Key="BDF71ED7">Fanged Friend</Text>
  <Text Key="05CC841A">Sims with a Threatening Presence inspire more fear in those around them, sometimes to the point of fainting. And Greg? Well, to them, he might as well be a cute puppy. </Text>
  <Text Key="D1865A55">Threatening Presence</Text>
  <Text Key="24B8DC0C">Refined Lupines turn their noses up at the thought of losing control of their Fury, passively generating less of it over time.</Text>
  <Text Key="F14BF793">Refined Lupine</Text>
  <Text Key="2F81C44B">Sims turned into werewolves by Chomp Champions won't negatively react to being turned, and they'll want to join the Chomp Champion's pack too!</Text>
  <Text Key="C7696C1C">Chomp Champion</Text>
  <Text Key="10D03123">Like the other rusted roof, these patches and wear give the roof a colorful look, and the holes allow light through inside. However, this version comes with a built-in skylight! </Text>
  <Text Key="490C24F2">Hole-Filled Sheet Metal Roof with Accidental Skylight</Text>
  <Text Key="F828D107">This is more like art than a roof, really. The rust, patches, and wear give the roof a colorful look, and the holes allow light through inside. It's beautiful! Perhaps not the best functionally, but doesn't that make it art? </Text>
  <Text Key="AD020EBE">Hole-Filled Sheet Metal Roof</Text>
  <Text Key="6D28C6B7">Turns out the big bad wolf didn't try to blow the wood house down, he SNEEZED on it. Does the pig that lives under this roof at least have a tissue for him? Or, uh, maybe a towel and a mop?</Text>
  <Text Key="2F91920E">Pig #2's "Mossy" Wood Shingles</Text>
  <Text Key="18523827">López</Text>
  <Text Key="8D408E5E">Celene</Text>
  <Text Key="E4A1F9E7">Greg</Text>
  <Text Key="BEBF34F1">Volkov</Text>
  <Text Key="EF0891A4">Jacob</Text>
  <Text Key="687D1FFB">Volkov</Text>
  <Text Key="D120C26A">Kristopher</Text>
  <Text Key="30944CDE">Zhu</Text>
  <Text Key="6301CE79">Lily</Text>
  <Text Key="71F8A046">Howell</Text>
  <Text Key="F8E17411">Lou</Text>
  <Text Key="792CEE1E">Oaklow</Text>
  <Text Key="06047439">Rory</Text>
  <Text Key="BBC151FF">Wilder</Text>
  <Text Key="57E53F06">Wolfgang</Text>
  <Text Key="43B1FA17">Handy Pack Mate</Text>
  <Text Key="ED3D6BD0">Join the Moonwood Collective's dignified, neighborly ranks!</Text>
  <Text Key="3A7594F0">Emissary of the Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="1254A0EE">Seek the cure to continue life as a normal Sim!</Text>
  <Text Key="DCEA3982">Cure Seeker</Text>
  <Text Key="7B81827D">Become the strongest, scariest Werewolf on your own!</Text>
  <Text Key="BD5FFA97">Lone Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="B2E3A165">Join the Wildfangs and show the world who's boss!</Text>
  <Text Key="C223CC6F">Wildfang Renegade</Text>
  <Text Key="A06C19A2">{0.SimFirstName} has completed {F0.her}{M0.his} werewolf initiation!\nIt's time for {F0.her}{M0.him} to embark on the next chapter of {F0.her}{M0.his} werewolf journey. What possibilities does {F0.her}{M0.his} future hold?</Text>
  <Text Key="A3E2EDBC">New Aspiration</Text>
  <Text Key="CD072768">The magic in this stone work hasn't had time to recharge yet. </Text>
  <Text Key="9705D407">Howl with the Moon Music</Text>
  <Text Key="0F3F2F1A">The enchanting music fades as {0.SimFirstName} comes to a large round room with an expansive relief carved into the wall. Embedded, glowing cerulean crystals give off enough light to make out the story within. The artwork depicts a magical conflict between two sides, with some favoring plasma and others who drew power from the moon.</Text>
  <Text Key="6AF25627">An Enchanted Room</Text>
  <Text Key="1EB51F5E">{0.SimFirstName} recalls some scribbled notes {M0.he'd}{F0.she'd} seen in one of the books {M0.he}{F0.she} read, mentioning an underground room filled with the "Moon's Music." Remembering the notes of the magical tune that had been on the air a moment ago, {0.SimFirstName} howls a somber but sweet song to those notes. Further down the wall, a carved wolf's mouth suddenly opens and drops something out onto the ground.</Text>
  <Text Key="84F50838">The Enchanted Room's Secret</Text>
  <Text Key="90A84205">More than once, {0.SimFirstName} nearly trips on some old junk. It's too dark to make out what it is, even after coming across a large pile of old metal. Given how rusty it smells, it's probably safer to leave it alone, since it is too dark to see.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8318B07">The Old Mill</Text>
  <Text Key="D7E58D2C">Attempt to Lift the Wheel</Text>
  <Text Key="2ED7C323">Though hunks of rotted beams and broken metal parts line the tunnel, {0.SimFirstName} is able to move around them with {M0.his}{F0.her} ability to see in the dark. Eventually, {M0.he}{F0.she} comes across a mountain of old logging tools and sawmill blades. This looks like most of the old Moonwood Mill! How did it get down here?\n\n{0.SimFirstName} spies a lockbox, trapped underneath part of an old water wheel. It seems like it'd take supersim strength to get to that thing.</Text>
  <Text Key="7E73D625">It takes all of {0.SimFirstName}'s strength to even budge the broken water wheel. As soon as it starts to move, other pieces of junk fall in on top of the lock box, and {0.SimFirstName} has to quickly set the wheel back down before it crushes an errant limb or appendage! Maybe {0.SimFirstName} can give it another go when {M0.his}{F0.her} arms aren't jelly!</Text>
  <Text Key="9BD29E27">The Old Mill's Lost Treasure</Text>
  <Text Key="5E99A2E3">{0.SimFirstName} manages to lift the heavy water wheel slowly enough, the surrounding junk settles, rather than falling into the opening. Then, just as carefully, {M0.he}{F0.she} manages to secure the lockbox, before giving into the mounting weight. The lockbox is already open and it &lt;i&gt;isn't&lt;/i&gt; empty!</Text>
  <Text Key="9ABE0171">The Old Mill's Treasure</Text>
  <Text Key="025B509B">At the end of one of the tunnels is an old metal door that's been peeled open. The solid metal bends outward like a banana peel, as if something strong and determined forced its way out and ran off into the tunnel {0.SimFirstName} just came from.\n\nPast the broken door is a single room, coated in metal paneling. Judging by the gouges lining the walls, someone - or something - really didn't want to be in here...</Text>
  <Text Key="3C40F2C9">A Busted Chamber</Text>
  <Text Key="F014BEA2">The scent of garlic leads down a twisting tunnel. Eventually, {0.SimFirstName} runs into a large, metal box of some sort, but it's too dark to figure out what purpose it might have...or if there's a way to get inside.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8B09ABC">A Garlic Box</Text>
  <Text Key="EDA8E9E7">Go Inside</Text>
  <Text Key="43897FAC">Old, braided garlic cloves dangle from the walls along the twisting tunnel. Eventually, {0.SimFirstName} comes across a large, metal box with a barred door. {M0.He}{F0.She} tests the bar and finds that it can be lifted with a bit of effort.</Text>
  <Text Key="B2F1850A">A Garlic Room</Text>
  <Text Key="87A5D859">{0.SimFirstName} pulls up on the bar and slips inside the box. It looks like some sort of old refuge chamber. There are beds, supplies, and some broken, carved pieces of wood laying about. Picking through the detritus, {0.SimFirstName} is able to find something of use before heading out.</Text>
  <Text Key="80C7258B">A Garlic Haven</Text>
  <Text Key="2E7E9238">As {0.SimFirstName} pushes through a thin section of tunnel, {M0.his}{F0.her} enhanced vision in the darkness spots a low-hanging pipe. {M0.He}{F0.She} ducks to avoid it and what would surely have been a painful bump on the noggin.</Text>
  <Text Key="811FF8F0">Whoa! Whose idea was it to dig a big old hole smack dab in the middle of the path? Good thing {0.SimFirstName} is able to see in the dark. That could have hurt!</Text>
  <Text Key="F3860E43">{0.SimFirstName} notices a bunch of loose gravel and broken pieces of glass on the floor and scooches along the tunnel wall to avoid it. Good thing {M0.he}{F0.she} can see in the dark!</Text>
  <Text Key="BCB7F5E4">Something furry is scurrying toward {0.SimFirstName}! Looking closer, it's a small rodent with a strange glint in its eyes. It doesn't seem entirely normal and {0.SimFirstName} freezes as it momentarily stops, squeaks, and continues on its way.
{0.SimFirstName} is grateful for {M0.his}{F0.her} ability to see in the dark. Otherwise, {M0.he}{F0.she} may have been charmed by its cute-sounding squeaks!</Text>
  <Text Key="F86F83EE">A Close Call</Text>
  <Text Key="73797370">Continue</Text>
  <Text Key="80266886">The Underground</Text>
  <Text Key="001D6F59">{0.SimFirstName} takes a deep breath and makes {M0.his}{F0.her} way into the underground...</Text>
  <Text Key="0D0A4707">The entrance to the bunker is metal, but as {0.SimFirstName} travels onward, the tunnel twists underground and the pathway becomes dirt on all sides. After a few minutes of walking, {0.SimFirstName} realizes that this seemingly endless tunnel must lead deep beneath Moonwood Mill.</Text>
  <Text Key="E8A1AADE">One of the portal potty stalls has a graffitied arrow pointing down into a dark underground passageway. As {0.SimFirstName} descends, {M0.he}{F0.she} finds {M0.himself}{F0.herself} deep below Moonwood Mill in what appears to be a series of tunnels. Where do they lead?</Text>
  <Text Key="0B08C066">It's evident this sewer grate has been opened recently. There are multiple sets of muddy footprints leading {0.SimFirstName} onward, though they become harder to see as the tunnel gets darker. The pathway leads downward, deep below Moonwood Mill, and it doesn't seem to stop...</Text>
  <Text Key="CE923032">Leaving the Underground</Text>
  <Text Key="1705896D">{0.SimFirstName} can make out some light ahead. It must be an exit!</Text>
  <Text Key="3F36391B">The tunnel starts to snake around before heading upwards at a gradual incline. Eventually, light can be seen in the distance. The dirt walls give way to metal ones, and {0.SimFirstName} exits out of a bunker door.</Text>
  <Text Key="918A43C2">{0.SimFirstName} eventually reaches what seems to be the end of the tunnel. There, {M0.he}{F0.she} finds a ladder leading upward with light spilling into the tunnel from above. As {M0.he}{F0.she} climbs, the echo of {M0.his}{F0.her} feet on the ladder's rungs gets louder and louder until {0.SimFirstName} emerges in a blue plastic box.\n\nOh, wait. It's a portal potty.</Text>
  <Text Key="7AB63F82">The tunnel's earthy scent gets mustier, and {0.SimFirstName} comes to an opening in the dirt passageway that seems to be some sort of large, metal pipe. It angles upwards, eventually leading to an easily removable grate. {0.SimFirstName} pushes past it and out into some sort of industrial culvert above ground.</Text>
  <Text Key="63D8525B">{0.SimFirstName} is making {M0.his}{F0.her} way through a particularly tight corridor when {M0.he}{F0.she} notices something give way underfoot. {M0.He}{F0.She} bends down to check and discovers something!</Text>
  <Text Key="D439C489">Finders Keepers</Text>
  <Text Key="2C3B064F">Follow the Scent</Text>
  <Text Key="1B0DCD62">{0.SimFirstName} is traversing the tunnels when something stops {M0.him}{F0.her}. It starts out faint, but soon there is an undeniably delicious scent wafting through the air. Is it worth checking out?</Text>
  <Text Key="40902F7C">Yummy Scent</Text>
  <Text Key="87CD4F8E">Somewhere ahead, the repetitive creak of metal echoes toward {0.SimFirstName}, followed by a slish-slosh of water. As it repeats, {0.SimFirstName} begins to speculate that it might be a water pump, when {M0.he}{F0.she} stumbles into a room filled with…frogs? It’s almost a proper frog city. They aren't just the common kind either! Someone’s been breeding them. Well, at least the frogs seem happy down here.</Text>
  <Text Key="A3627AE8">Frog City</Text>
  <Text Key="945BBCFC">Turn Back</Text>
  <Text Key="D99C7B6A">Head into the Tunnel System</Text>
  <Text Key="7E88FC30">The tunnel doesn't go too far before it merges with other small offshoots to form a wider path. It's evident that this is part of an extensive tunnel system.</Text>
  <Text Key="9DBBBABE">The Underground</Text>
  <Text Key="455A566E">Run Away!</Text>
  <Text Key="D2F381E3">Investigate the Growling</Text>
  <Text Key="6988C858">As {0.SimFirstName} rounds a corner in the tunnels, {M0.he}{F0.she} hears what sounds like a slight rumble or a murmur. A few steps later, the sound gets clearer...and scarier! Something nearby is growling.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A36C946">Growling</Text>
  <Text Key="BEE84E7A">As {0.SimFirstName} presses on to investigate, the growling grows louder and more vicious by the second. A moment later, {M0.he}{F0.she} comes upon a hunched form, barely visible against the darkness. It doesn't take long for it to notice {0.SimFirstName}. The creature's head turns, and its entire frame rises up, revealing a wild-looking werewolf! It leaps towards {0.SimFirstName} and a scuffle breaks out.\n\n{0.SimFirstName} is able to eventually break loose but not before suffering some bites and scratches.</Text>
  <Text Key="0E10BE74">Furious Growling</Text>
  <Text Key="589D45CE">As {0.SimFirstName} moves towards the sound, the growling ceases. As {M0.he}{F0.she} continues to search for whatever was making the noise, {M0.his}{F0.her} hand lands in something sticky. A quick glance reveals that it's food. It looks like an abandoned snack.</Text>
  <Text Key="788F6328">Searching in Silence</Text>
  <Text Key="075250C8">There's something about this growl that sounds dangerous, that sounds...feral. {0.SimFirstName} turns and runs through the tunnels to escape, but {M0.he's}{F0.she's} unable to get {M0.his}{F0.her} bearings and makes a few wrong turns. The growling gets louder and louder as it gets closer and closer.\n\n{0.SimFirstName} can feel the warm breath on the back of {M0.his}{F0.her} neck just before {M0.he's}{F0.she's} grabbed from behind and drawn into a fight!</Text>
  <Text Key="DCF333B6">The Growling Grows</Text>
  <Text Key="2791502D">{0.SimFirstName} turns around and quickly backtracks through the tunnels, successfully avoiding whatever was making that horrible growling.</Text>
  <Text Key="043812EF">The Growling Fades</Text>
  <Text Key="7B2FCB11">Howl Back</Text>
  <Text Key="830BBE72">Ignore the Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="6C096B55">A lonely howl echoes through the underground, bouncing off the tunnel walls in every direction.</Text>
  <Text Key="8C2AACD7">A Lonely Howl</Text>
  <Text Key="B0BB1277">After hearing the lone howl, {0.SimFirstName} howls back into the void. The silence that follows {M0.his}{F0.her} attempt is deafening...</Text>
  <Text Key="29C878B5">Deafening Silence</Text>
  <Text Key="EE5D1B1A">After hearing the lone howl, {0.SimFirstName} boldly answers in kind. A howl echoes back a moment later and the two howlers - separated by distance but together in spirit - share a beautiful moment.</Text>
  <Text Key="F47D9014">A Moment Shared</Text>
  <Text Key="7FF871D2">{0.SimFirstName} seems to have been walking forward in this tunnel for a long time. Or maybe the tunnel's just been going in circles? It's so very, very dark that {0.SimFirstName} really isn't sure where anything is anymore. {M0.He's}{F0.She's} hopelessly lost!</Text>
  <Text Key="6A5965AC">Lost</Text>
  <Text Key="5800BB69">Even as a werewolf, {0.SimFirstName} is finding it difficult to navigate these tunnels at the moment. There are a lot of different smells and tracks and paths. {M0.He}{F0.She} tries to shake off {M0.his}{F0.her} doubts. These tunnels are well-traveled and the path {M0.he's}{F0.she's} on is sure to lead somewhere.</Text>
  <Text Key="110D4377">What's that? {0.SimFirstName} has discovered something that's warm and fuzzy and making cute little squeaking noises...OUCH! And bitey. That hurt. Note to self: maybe don't pet the animals in the dark Moonwood Mill tunnels.</Text>
  <Text Key="7320444F">On a tunnel straightaway, {0.SimFirstName} breaks into a light run and is making good time when {M0.he}{F0.she} suddenly finds {M0.himself}{F0.herself} tumbling head over heels. Ouch!\n\nIt was impossible to see in the dark, but there must have been a massive hole in the tunnel floor and {0.SimFirstName} ends up on a path some distance below where {M0.he}{F0.she} started.</Text>
  <Text Key="57FBC47D">It's kind of tight, but {0.SimFirstName} just needs to squeeze through...OUCH! {0.SimFirstName} just took a face full of metal from a jutting pipe that was impossible to see in the dark.</Text>
  <Text Key="0D3A650E">As {0.SimFirstName} enters a wider section of tunnel, {M0.he}{F0.she} is surprised by a bunch of loose gravel on the floor. Before {M0.he}{F0.she} can catch {M0.himself}{F0.herself}, {M0.he's}{F0.she's} fallen flat on {M0.his}{F0.her} back. Ouch!</Text>
  <Text Key="B629BB5A">Ouch!</Text>
  <Text Key="A4870C6B">Unexplainably, {0.SimFirstName} feels a twinge of fear. {M0.He}{F0.She} looks around in the dark tunnel but can't see anything that may have caused the sensation. Still, it feels like someone is watching...what a creepy feeling!</Text>
  <Text Key="795EFC59">A Presence</Text>
  <Text Key="3E5E0B9B">Follow the Magical Melody</Text>
  <Text Key="A9B6E0AB">Find the Fresh Air</Text>
  <Text Key="865CBA86">Head Towards the Garlic</Text>
  <Text Key="A4D18D4E">Navigate the Debris</Text>
  <Text Key="8B023EAC">Diverging Paths</Text>
  <Text Key="7E98035C">As {0.SimFirstName} crawls under a particularly low stretch, {M0.he}{F0.she} notices that the tunnel splits into three paths up ahead. From one path comes a faint but magical-sounding melody, down another the lingering scent of garlic, and down the third a welcoming bit of fresh air on the breeze.</Text>
  <Text Key="5B401B9D">{0.SimFirstName} encounters a tiny chasm and hops across it. On the other side, the tunnel splits in three. A faint melody, strange yet almost magical, seems to emanate from one path. The next is littered with old, rusted debris. And the final path carries the scent of fresh air.</Text>
  <Text Key="F9B7102A">{0.SimFirstName} seems to come to a dead end, before noticing a small ledge off to the side. It's a bit of a tight squeeze, but {0.SimFirstName} manages to clamber up and finds a set of three different tunnels. The one that heads left seems littered with debris and gives off a rusty scent. The one in the middle smells a lot like garlic. Only the tunnel to the right has a pleasant odor: the smell of fresh air.</Text>
  <Text Key="57B51573">As {0.SimFirstName} is making {M0.his}{F0.her} way through the tunnel, {M0.he}{F0.she} starts making up a song in {M0.his}{F0.her} head. "Secret Tun-nel... Secret Tun-NEL!" It's a catchy song. {M0.He'll}{F0.She'll} have to remember it.</Text>
  <Text Key="5ED0BD0C">These tunnels seem to go on forever, and {0.SimFirstName} gets lost in {M0.his}{F0.her} thoughts. How long did it take to dig all of this, and who covers the maintenance costs? They do maintenance down here, right?</Text>
  <Text Key="CBD9B37E">{0.SimFirstName} gets lost in thought as {M0.he}{F0.she} travels the seemingly endless tunnels. "{0.SimFirstName}" really was an interesting name. Who decided to name {M0.him}{F0.her}? Was it {M0.his}{F0.her} family? And what does {0.SimFirstName} mean anyways? {M0.He}{F0.She} repeats {M0.his}{F0.her} name over and over until it starts to sound funny in {M0.his}{F0.her} head.</Text>
  <Text Key="F35174F3">Tunnel Thoughts</Text>
  <Text Key="C3F1FFFB">{0.SimFirstName} spies something on the ground just ahead. It seems to be...moving? As {M0.he}{F0.she} gets closer it scatters, and {M0.he}{F0.she} realizes it was a small hoard of rats. What could cause them to swarm like that? Ah. It’s garbage.</Text>
  <Text Key="535852A9">The Swarm</Text>
  <Text Key="045ED546">There's suddenly a strange scent coming from somewhere in these tunnels. At first, it smells like decay...then iron maybe? The longer {0.SimFirstName} sniffs the more confusing and invigorating the smell becomes, like the air of a bygone age...</Text>
  <Text Key="8C3F0FA0">A Dark Scent</Text>
  <Text Key="8DF3E467">Contemplate the Dripping</Text>
  <Text Key="744365A1">Drip. Drip. Drip. In the back of {M0.his}{F0.her} mind, {0.SimFirstName} can hear a faint but steady dripping sound. It must be coming from one of the tunnel's many leaking pipes. </Text>
  <Text Key="F4020213">Water Leak</Text>
  <Text Key="3C912523">Drip. Drip... Drip. After listening to the dripping for a bit, {0.SimFirstName} now can't stop hearing the dripping sound, try as {M0.he}{F0.she} might. Drip. It's annoyingly (drip) stuck at the (drip) forefront of {M0.his}{F0.her} (drip) mind. Drip. Plus it's really making {M0.his}{F0.her} bladder feel (drip) full.</Text>
  <Text Key="ABDD38B1">Annoying Drip</Text>
  <Text Key="3237C3A5">Upon contemplation, {0.SimFirstName} finds the dripping to be rather rhythmic. Within its patterns, {M0.he}{F0.she} finds calmness in these dark tunnels, that the drip offers a real sense of reassurance and familiarity.</Text>
  <Text Key="915E07A7">Calming Drip</Text>
  <Text Key="23901E3D">The tunnels are damp, and {0.SimFirstName} can't seem to escape the smell of wet dog that's everywhere.</Text>
  <Text Key="9AB8C37F">A Wet Dog?</Text>
  <Text Key="001DBB89">Only werewolves can join packs.</Text>
  <Text Key="F94DA49E">{0.SimFirstName} still needs to complete one more trial.</Text>
  <Text Key="F3F2ABA4">{0.SimFirstName} still needs to complete two more trials.</Text>
  <Text Key="EDBAF675">{0.SimFirstName} still needs to complete three trials.</Text>
  <Text Key="C094126A">{0.SimFirstName} already completed this trial recently.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CB5344B">{0.SimFirstName} cannot do this while on Pack Probation.</Text>
  <Text Key="0DD1E942">{0.SimFirstName} cannot do this while {F0.her}{M0.his} Leadership is Under Scrutiny.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E089F6B">{0.SimFirstName} must report to the Moonwood Collective's leader first.</Text>
  <Text Key="69CD6C6C">{0.SimFirstName} must report to the Wildfangs' leader first.</Text>
  <Text Key="8C7A9CED">{0.SimFirstName} isn't familiar enough with the underground tunnels.</Text>
  <Text Key="145B2A95">I always want to know just how safe my stairs are. Let's consider these: sure, you could cut yourself on them and get an infected wound, but you're way less likely to slip because of the textured surface. Then again, the open stair design does mean you can miss the step with both legs and fall completely through. We'll give them a 5/10 safety. </Text>
  <Text Key="9B3256B0">Old Factory Stairs</Text>
  <Text Key="D2CE7828">Fury envelops Werewolves like a beautiful flaming blanket. As Fury grows, their animalistic instincts begin to manifest, and will eventually take over.\n\nFury gain is constant and is hastened by:\n• Temperaments\n• Preferences\n• Werewolf Abilities\n• The Full Moon\n\nBe careful out there.</Text>
  <Text Key="76D59135">(From a Dangerous Amount of Fury)</Text>
  <Text Key="31F167AA">Fury</Text>
  <Text Key="2EF2D761">(From Howling Too Much)</Text>
  <Text Key="A028DFEC">(From a Werewolf Bite) </Text>
  <Text Key="B8437B34">(From Tussling with Werewolves) </Text>
  <Text Key="B46A801B">Next Reward: \n1 Ability Point</Text>
  <Text Key="A3C8AE0A">Next Reward: \n1 Ability Point</Text>
  <Text Key="6D756CD6">Next Reward: \n1 Ability Point</Text>
  <Text Key="15DAE041">Overmax!\n\nNext Reward: \n1 Ability Point</Text>
  <Text Key="C6C34A91">Next Reward: \n1 Ability Point</Text>
  <Text Key="83585B3F">Next Reward: \n1 Ability Point</Text>
  <Text Key="8D56F35F">Next Reward: \n1 Ability Point</Text>
  <Text Key="68B1D2DD">Next Reward: \n1 Ability Point</Text>
  <Text Key="9AD85F48">Next Reward: \n1 Ability Point</Text>
  <Text Key="DBA73CA4">Prime</Text>
  <Text Key="391C1C13">Pup</Text>
  <Text Key="4A8BFC38">Veteran</Text>
  <Text Key="4AACC26F">Runt</Text>
  <Text Key="262E323C">Apex</Text>
  <Text Key="46314E78">Tier 4: Veteran!</Text>
  <Text Key="121B22FD">{0.SimFirstName} is now a Veteran Werewolf!\n\n{F0.She}{M0.He} has experienced most of what Werewolf life has to offer, but there's always room to learn!\n\nThis Sim has a new Temperament that affects how {F0.she}{M0.he} navigates the world and what causes Fury to bubble over. Be sure to check out the new Abilities too.</Text>
  <Text Key="0E7BCA4E">Tier 3: Prime!</Text>
  <Text Key="CA6DA677">{0.SimFirstName} is now a Prime Werewolf!\n\nBeing a Werewolf gets easier by the day!\n\nThis Sim has a new Temperament that affects how {F0.she}{M0.he} navigates the world and what causes Fury to bubble over. Be sure to check out the new Abilities too.</Text>
  <Text Key="1D1F51D0">{0.SimFirstName} is now &lt;i&gt;the&lt;/i&gt; Apex Werewolf!\n\n{F0.She}{M0.He}'s the best of the best, the cream of the crop, top of the food chain!\n\nThe final tier of Abilities are now available for purchase. </Text>
  <Text Key="4FDAF725">Tier 5: Apex!</Text>
  <Text Key="8ED419C4">{0.SimFirstName} is now a Werewolf Runt!\n\n{F0.She}{M0.He} is starting to get the hang of this Werewolf thing!\n\nThis Sim has a new Temperament that affects how {F0.she}{M0.he} navigates the world and what causes Fury to bubble over. Be sure to check out the new Abilities too.</Text>
  <Text Key="C56F2F24">Tier 2: Runt!</Text>
  <Text Key="62E17D08">As the sole Alpha of {F0.her}{M0.his} pack, {0.SimFirstName} is the official pack leader! {F0.She}{M0.He} has the power to Promote/Demote packmates, kick packmates from the pack, and even choose how the hangout is decorated!\n\nBut it's not all fun and games now. Alphas are still expected to uphold all pack values. To avoid losing the faith of {F0.her}{M0.his} pack members, make sure {0.SimFirstName} continues to set a good example.</Text>
  <Text Key="B5FD3EEB">{0.SimFirstName} is currently an Omega, the lowest pack rank. They need to prove themselves before enjoying additional pack benefits! In addition to getting to know {F0.her}{M0.his} packmates more, {0.SimFirstName} should pay close attention to {F0.her}{M0.his} pack's values. Upholding them is the key to ranking up!</Text>
  <Text Key="DD42B0C5">{0.SimFirstName} is a Delta, which means {F0.she}{M0.he} is able to Pack Mentor and Discipline {F0.her}{M0.his} Omega rank packmates. Keep living by the pack values and {F0.she}{M0.he} will move up the hierarchy in no time!</Text>
  <Text Key="98E8CF1E">{0.SimFirstName} is a Beta, the highest rank under the pack’s Alpha. {F0.She}{M0.He} can now Pack Mentor and Discipline packmates in both the Omega and Delta ranks.\n\nIf {0.SimFirstName} wants to be the Alpha, {F0.she}{M0.he} has to do more than just adhere to pack values. Leadership must be won by challenging the current Alpha. Is {0.SimFirstName} willing to take that risk for the sweet taste of power?</Text>
  <Text Key="7D244627">Oh no! {0.SimFirstName} has been demoted to Delta rank!</Text>
  <Text Key="BCF2B8C4">Check the data, {F0.she's}{M0.he's} a Beta!\n{0.SimFirstName} is now no longer the Alpha of the pack, which means {F0.she}{M0.he} is also no longer the pack leader. </Text>
  <Text Key="A8F96BCC">Oh no! {0.SimFirstName} has been demoted to Omega rank! {F0.She}{M0.He} can no longer perform the Mentor and Discipline interactions allowed at Delta rank. </Text>
  <Text Key="8B8614C7">Omega</Text>
  <Text Key="C5E94826">Beta</Text>
  <Text Key="892B0BD6">Delta</Text>
  <Text Key="1BCE873A">Alpha</Text>
  <Text Key="90FD7F2E">Splendid! {0.SimFirstName} has been promoted to the rank of &lt;b&gt;Delta&lt;/b&gt; in the Moonwood Collective.\n\nNew Unlocks!\n- Pack Mentor and Discipline interactions can be performed on lower-ranked packmates\n- The &lt;i&gt;Mooncaster Memento&lt;/i&gt; has been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory and is also available for purchase!</Text>
  <Text Key="8C1746A5">Glorious! {0.SimFirstName} has been promoted to the rank of &lt;b&gt;Beta&lt;/b&gt; in the Moonwood Collective.\n\nNew Unlocks!\n- The &lt;i&gt;Surreptitiously Studious Stationery Pile&lt;/i&gt; has been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory and is also available for purchase!</Text>
  <Text Key="41C3424B">Absolutely magnificent! {0.SimFirstName} is now the Moonwood Collective's &lt;b&gt;Alpha&lt;/b&gt; and official pack leader.\n\nNew Unlocks!\n- Unique power over pack membership and ranks\n- Exclusive interactions with members of both packs (and with the hangout tree!)\n- The &lt;i&gt;Moonlit Fable Wall Clock&lt;/i&gt; has been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory and is also available for purchase!</Text>
  <Text Key="B0FDAC08">Welcome to the pack! {0.SimFirstName} has joined the Moonwood Collective at rank &lt;b&gt;Omega&lt;/b&gt;.\n\nNew Unlocks:\n- One bag of Wolfitos delivered weekly\n- One copy of &lt;i&gt;The Good Boy&lt;/i&gt;\n- New pack-exclusive interactions!</Text>
  <Text Key="752835C3">Rock on! {0.SimFirstName} has been promoted to the rank of &lt;b&gt;Delta&lt;/b&gt; in the Wildfangs.\n\nNew Unlocks!\n- Pack Mentor and Discipline interactions can be performed on lower-ranked packmates\n- The &lt;i&gt;Fury-Fueled Nonconformity Poster&lt;/i&gt; has been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory and is also available for purchase!</Text>
  <Text Key="E40A27E4">Radical! {0.SimFirstName} has been promoted to the rank of &lt;b&gt;Beta&lt;/b&gt; in the Wildfangs.\n\nNew Unlocks!\n- The &lt;i&gt;World's Most (In)Accurate Sundial&lt;/i&gt; has been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory and is also available for purchase!</Text>
  <Text Key="6C2660E5">Welcome to the pack! {0.SimFirstName} has joined the Wildfangs at rank &lt;b&gt;Omega&lt;/b&gt;.\n\nNew Unlocks:\n- One bag of Jerky Bites delivered weekly\n- One issue of &lt;i&gt;BARK Magazine&lt;/i&gt;\n- New pack-exclusive interactions!</Text>
  <Text Key="02CA896E">Leader leader pumpkin eater! {0.SimFirstName} is now the Wildfangs' &lt;b&gt;Alpha&lt;/b&gt; and official pack leader.\n\nNew Unlocks!\n- Unique power over pack membership and ranks\n- Exclusive interactions with members of both packs (and with the trailer hangout spot!)\n- The &lt;i&gt;Rockmeister Syzygy 7000 Guitar&lt;/i&gt; has been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory and is also available for purchase!</Text>
  <Text Key="EA417DB2">Abandoned Werewolf Study</Text>
  <Text Key="716C6326">Lunar Boho Den</Text>
  <Text Key="DD4048EF">Moongazer's Garden</Text>
  <Text Key="80A5C6C3">Rebel Wolf's Hangout</Text>
  <Text Key="E92FC675">Lunar Confidant</Text>
  <Text Key="F06EF5D4">These Sims get an initial relationship boost when introducing themselves to werewolves (positive &lt;i&gt;or&lt;/i&gt; negative, depending on how they act!)</Text>
  <Text Key="912402BF">(From Choosing a Werewolf Aspiration) </Text>
  <Text Key="C641ECD5">Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="52A3F0FB">Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="53392689">Refined Lupine</Text>
  <Text Key="1813DD27">Refined Lupine</Text>
  <Text Key="5CED3910">Refined Lupines turn their noses up at the thought of losing control of their Fury, passively generating less of it over time. </Text>
  <Text Key="7B9D55B3">(From Completing the Emissary of the Collective Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="4AF784B5">Chomp Champion</Text>
  <Text Key="C7118E5B">Chomp Champion</Text>
  <Text Key="C24F5A14">Sims turned into werewolves by Chomp Champions won't negatively react to being turned, and they'll want to join the Chomp Champion's pack too!</Text>
  <Text Key="06793EFF">(From Completing the Wildfang Renegade Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="659F3A04">Lunar Link</Text>
  <Text Key="B3E04814">Lunar Link</Text>
  <Text Key="1B2FA02B">Sims with a Lunar Link retain the special benefits of the Lunar Cycle they once felt as Werewolves, and can still Howl just like old times!</Text>
  <Text Key="95E0BDB6">(For Completing the Cure Seeker Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="E8D1F28F">Fanged Friend</Text>
  <Text Key="4A4A180D">Fanged Friend</Text>
  <Text Key="043E6F92">Fanged Friends get an additional boost to their relationships with both Werewolves and non-Werewolf Sims.</Text>
  <Text Key="183E6F85">(From Completing the Werewolf Initiate Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="FAB3A37F">Threatening Presence</Text>
  <Text Key="2E11B1DD">Threatening Presence</Text>
  <Text Key="8EF05722">Sims with a Threatening Presence inspire more fear in those around them, sometimes to the point of fainting. And Greg? Well, to them, he might as well be a cute puppy. </Text>
  <Text Key="F2BFC175">(From Completing the Lone Wolf Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="F75A0B03">Dormant Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="98CF4159">Dormant Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="6F8D0E9E">The wolf sleeps soundly within {0.SimFirstName}. What would it take to awaken? </Text>
  <Text Key="0766D579">(From Having Werewolf Lineage)</Text>
  <Text Key="13B402E4">Greater Wolf Blood</Text>
  <Text Key="4A4CE374">Greater Wolf Blood</Text>
  <Text Key="08BD428B">The moon has blessed {0.SimFirstName} with a Greater Wolf Blood, enhancing their Werewolf growth. Talk about high expectations!</Text>
  <Text Key="3A939E56">(From Having Werewolf Parents, and a Bit of Luck)</Text>
  <Text Key="E5DF8DD9">Lunar Confidant</Text>
  <Text Key="A5D6C12A">(From Werewolf Temperaments)</Text>
  <Text Key="2383FEFA">Anti-Capitalist Canine</Text>
  <Text Key="E3FF87AA">Anti-Capitalist Canine</Text>
  <Text Key="3B3A7255">Ever since the beast awakened, doubts about societal norms have begun to stir. This Sim now rejects the daily grind, and will gain extra Fury if forced to partake in this endless, crushing, rat-race.  </Text>
  <Text Key="6F0EA135">Big Bad Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="10752FDB">Big Bad Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="40518F94">The inner demon within is unleashed. Not only will this Sim gain additional Fury while angry, but will also need to fight other Sims in order to keep aggression down. If this wolf asks to come inside, best to say "Not by the hairs on my chinny chin chin!"</Text>
  <Text Key="B3F34B17">Carnivore</Text>
  <Text Key="928B6BF5">Carnivore</Text>
  <Text Key="E3A2FFEA">This Sim has always had an appreciation for food, unfortunately this has a different meaning for Werewolves. This Sim must adhere to a very strict diet of fresh meat, &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; fresh meat. </Text>
  <Text Key="5F2C247F">Easily Excitable </Text>
  <Text Key="8A888CDD">Easily Excitable</Text>
  <Text Key="A9819A22">Oh! What's that? Is there fun happening over there?! This Sim now gains Fury while feeling playful, and while watching TV or playing videogames too! Like a hypersonic puppy about to hit critical mass.</Text>
  <Text Key="69B3C111">Feels Outcasted</Text>
  <Text Key="4744CF0F">Feels Outcasted</Text>
  <Text Key="4EBFE7E8">This Sim gains Fury when feeling ignored or otherwise low on Social. You just like... wouldn't understand. </Text>
  <Text Key="C1F83832">Frisky</Text>
  <Text Key="DEDAB0E2">Frisky</Text>
  <Text Key="204B391D">Something has awoken within this Sim! Frisky Werewolves can sometimes get a little hot under the collar when their beast within is looking for some company. Fury gains increase while feeling Flirty. </Text>
  <Text Key="714F33DA">Grumpy Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="73ABC58A">Grumpy Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="3158B3B5">This Sim might need a little extra rest in order to stay... balanced. Just don't poke a sleeping wolf. </Text>
  <Text Key="02A61548">Hates Being Wet</Text>
  <Text Key="154CB550">Hates Being Wet</Text>
  <Text Key="3A7D8467">Shower? Just don't. Rain? Just don't. This Sim loathes water and will gain extra Fury when wet.</Text>
  <Text Key="0553EC1F">Hungry Like The Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="28BE22FD">Hungry Like The Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="AAC95442">These Sims are more ravenous than they’ve ever been and gain Fury while hungry. This Sim might also be subject to sometimes extreme and sudden cravings.</Text>
  <Text Key="63D23F29">Mark of the Forest</Text>
  <Text Key="FFD53DC7">Mark of the Forest</Text>
  <Text Key="C13ACAB0">Symbols depicting a forest, engraved on the Werewolf's heart by the light of the moon. With this mark, both natural Fury gains and Fun decays are reduced. </Text>
  <Text Key="470D4589">Mark of the Hunt</Text>
  <Text Key="1F79E227">Mark of the Hunt</Text>
  <Text Key="2519D610">Symbols depicting the hunt, engraved on the Werewolf's heart by the light of the moon. With this mark, both natural Fury gains and Hunger decays are reduced. </Text>
  <Text Key="E6448BD4">Mark of the Night</Text>
  <Text Key="F80E5044">Mark of the Night</Text>
  <Text Key="C705369B">Symbols depicting a night sky, engraved on the Werewolf's heart by the light of the moon. With this mark, both natural Fury gains and Energy decays are reduced. </Text>
  <Text Key="0BCD99F6">Mark of the Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="4332DDDE">Mark of the Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="50F18549">Symbols depicting a wolf, engraved on the Werewolf's heart by the light of the moon. With this mark, both natural Fury gains and Social decays are reduced. </Text>
  <Text Key="3912091F">Must Be Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="D80F71FD">Must Be Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="B9A46B42">This Sim gains Fury with poor Hygiene, and has a newfound appreciation for tongue-baths. Being a Werewolf is weird like that. </Text>
  <Text Key="A74085CA">Night Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="A9F76C5A">Night Wolf</Text>
  <Text Key="50535845">Night Wolves prefer sleeping during the day, and gain Fury when deviating from a nocturnal sleep cycle. </Text>
  <Text Key="3FC40FE9">Prideful</Text>
  <Text Key="09B74687">Prideful</Text>
  <Text Key="CEAE3A70">This Sim feels a special pride about being a Werewolf, and doesn't appreciate being made to feel otherwise. Aside from gaining Fury while embarrassed or uncomfortable, they also might take things a little too personally. </Text>
  <Text Key="368E2D6B">Restless Animal</Text>
  <Text Key="D70D6101">Restless Animal</Text>
  <Text Key="D9F05D16">Restless Animals feel too constrained while indoors, and gain extra Fury without anything fun to do.</Text>
  <Text Key="FCDE499E">Sensitive Hearing</Text>
  <Text Key="2B19A386">Sensitive Hearing</Text>
  <Text Key="C650A541">These Werewolf enhanced ears means the world can be a terrible cacophony sometimes... Things like the TV, loud radio, instruments, and other noise cause Fury to rise in this Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="5F6AFD4D">Survival Instincts</Text>
  <Text Key="10315FB3">Survival Instincts</Text>
  <Text Key="7F7343DC">These Sims seem to have an extra sense for danger, gaining additional Fury while Scared or Tense, and try extra hard to keep themselves physically safe.</Text>
  <Text Key="491F3211">Territorial</Text>
  <Text Key="D906FA0F">Territorial</Text>
  <Text Key="00EDFAE8">These Sims have an unusually high desire to "claim what's theirs," so to speak. This Sim will gain Fury if around another Werewolf's "boundaries." You see where this is going, right? &lt;i&gt;right?&lt;/i&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="882D30D0">Wolf Brain</Text>
  <Text Key="8C402CB8">Wolf Brain</Text>
  <Text Key="4A040E9F">These Sims have trouble with intellectual or logical pursuits when their wolf brain is constantly calling. </Text>
  <Text Key="0BC1DCCC">Wracked With Guilt</Text>
  <Text Key="05E9229C">Wracked With Guilt</Text>
  <Text Key="C5BC4BE3">Sometimes the weight of this Werewolf curse is too much to bear. Not only do these Sims gain extra Fury while sad, they also might feel a sliver of remorse for their actions. </Text>
  <Text Key="BBD99CBA">(From Hanging Out in Beast Form)</Text>
  <Text Key="3B82D6DB">Werewolf Ally</Text>
  <Text Key="A8B8E791">Werewolf Ally</Text>
  <Text Key="45803B26">These Sims have a special kinship with Werewolves, and aren't &lt;i&gt;as&lt;/i&gt; alarmed by their Werewolfy antics. </Text>
  <Text Key="8D9AF721">(From Werewolf Diplomacy)</Text>
  <Text Key="C74BC559">(From Not Upholding Pack Values)</Text>
  <Text Key="F0D4441B">(From Werewolf Pack)</Text>
  <Text Key="C5965EA4">Friend of the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="5302A734">Friend of the Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="5C58BA4B">Sims who are the Friend of a Pack have limited access to that pack's hangout and can socialize with that pack's members in special ways.</Text>
  <Text Key="EBB33F16">(From Becoming the Friend of a Pack)</Text>
  <Text Key="479BAD8F">Friend of The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="AC1A910D">Friend of The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="80446A43">The Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="4B854B99">The Moonwood Collective</Text>
  <Text Key="9FDFA9B8">The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="FA3A0860">The Wildfangs</Text>
  <Text Key="8BC02831">Werewolves</Text>
  <Text Key="82A4A197">Sims can also ask the local Werewolves to give them the Cursed Bite.\n\nIf the Sim already has Werebies, most werewolves will take pity and turn them right away. Otherwise, they need to be on friendly terms. The biting Werewolf must also have the Cursed Bite Ability available to them.</Text>
  <Text Key="1C053966">Sims who get into a fight with Werewolves are at risk for contracting Werebies. They may also get it while exploring the secret underground tunnels. This infection will eventually progress into full blown lycanthropy. \n\nRumor has it, the bartender at Grimtooth knows of a remedy if your Sim is not quite ready for this life change! There are also &lt;i&gt;less conventional&lt;/i&gt; ways to try to get rid of it, like trying to sweat it out as well as a few other things to try. Be warned though, the window to do this is limited. </Text>
  <Text Key="8DD3304F">There is a cure for the Werewolf affliction that is waiting to be discovered. Read Lore and find the ingredients needed to craft Wolf-B-Gone!</Text>
  <Text Key="425AEAC8">Similar to asking, Sims who are Werewolves may turn other sims with Cursed Bite. \n\nThey can use social interactions to learn whether other Sims would like to become Werewolves in the first place, or they may choose to bite them anyway. Only Werewolves within your household may bite Sims without being asked. </Text>
  <Text Key="BF7A10EA">Becoming a Werewolf</Text>
  <Text Key="66FA370F">Fury is the driving force behind Werewolves. More and more beastly behaviors come out as the orb fills. \n\nUnlike other Sim needs, Fury is constantly ticking up with few ways to lower it. Sims gain extra Fury based on their likes, dislikes, and the Temperaments they gain as they grow. Abilities and Fighting will also increase this, so use them wisely! The Moon phases have a variety of effects, and on a Full Moon the call of the beast is too much to resist.  </Text>
  <Text Key="C3F25568">When a Sim reaches max Fury, watch out! They will Rampage!\n\nRampaging Werewolves have limited control of themselves and will engage in destructive activities.</Text>
  <Text Key="A444CB42">Managing Fury</Text>
  <Text Key="C35C3A7D">The first step to getting involved with Werewolf packs is to befriend them by getting to know their leader! You can earn Friend of the Pack status for one or both packs, as either a Werewolf or non-Werewolf. \n\nKeep in mind that you can also lose your status as Friend of the Pack by acting in a way that betrays the pack's trust.</Text>
  <Text Key="13271434">Once you're a Friend of the Pack, you can choose to undertake three different pack trials to officially join. These trials may involve certain Werewolf Abilities and Skills, or impressing the leader with a great gift. </Text>
  <Text Key="067D945C">Joining a Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="4B568394">Werewolves are particularly susceptible to Lunar Cycles. They have access to unique interactions at night and different phases of the moon will affect their moods, skill gains, or social success rates.  \n\nYou can view how a Lunar Phase will affect your Sim by hovering over the moon icon at the bottom center of the screen in Live Mode. </Text>
  <Text Key="053E1EE4">Lunar Cycle &amp; Werewolves</Text>
  <Text Key="C45B314D">Upon joining, you'll be assigned the lowest rank of Omega. Adhering to Pack Values will net you Pack XP and allow you to rank up and earn unique benefits. To become the sole Alpha and leader of the pack, you must challenge the current Alpha. This can be done at any rank, but make sure you're ready to duke it out!\n\nYou can find more information on current pack rank and XP by checking the Werewolf Packs Panel.</Text>
  <Text Key="02C8A3E1">Both packs have unique Pack Values that dictate the behavior of the members. Each pack member is expected to live by the Pack Values, performing actions that go along with them and avoiding actions that go against them. \n\nYou can find more information on each value, and ways to fulfill them, on the Werewolf Packs Panel.</Text>
  <Text Key="899A66FF">Pack Values &amp; Hierarchy</Text>
  <Text Key="199E3232">You can switch between editing your Beast Form and Sim Form while in CAS by clicking each of the preview images at the bottom left. </Text>
  <Text Key="133E2D0B">A Werewolf's Sim and Beast Forms are initially linked. Clicking on the link button will disable or enable this link. \n\nWhen linked, any changes made in either form will automatically be copied to the other. Individual parts can be included and excluded from this linkage in the Link Filters menu above. \n\nWhen unlinked, you can copy the parts and settings of the other form onto the current form by clicking on the Copy button. This action can include or exclude individual parts via the Copy Filters.</Text>
  <Text Key="F5B134CE">To create a Werewolf in CAS, first click the "Add a Sim" button on the bottom left of the screen. Then choose "Add an Occult Sim" followed by "Add Werewolf."</Text>
  <Text Key="4437424C">Creating a Werewolf in CAS</Text>
  <Text Key="C9092B9E">When you're done painting, go ahead and click the Back button in the upper left of the paint panel. Or click the Clear All button to start from scratch. </Text>
  <Text Key="A76EE7B2">If you want to cover your entire Werewolf with a certain color, use the Fill Color tool. </Text>
  <Text Key="3CDC9101">Choose from a variety of paintbrush shapes and use the Size and Rotation sliders for the exact look you want. Or go a little crazy and play with the Stamps from the Stamps tab. Who said Werewolves can't be covered in jellyfish? </Text>
  <Text Key="E3EBC15D">While customizing a Sim's Beast Form, Paint Mode can be accessed from a few places: click on the bottom arc menu button from the body arc menu, or click on the Paint Mode button at the top of the Coat Color/Pattern catalog.</Text>
  <Text Key="2A3F95DD">Use the Stencils tab to paint within artist-crafted marking patterns with precision. Play around with the Fill Color tool or paint over the stencil area with multiple colors to get some wild combinations!</Text>
  <Text Key="7EE0AB78">Start painting! Just like you can directly push and pull to change the shape of your Werewolf, you can use your mouse cursor as a paint brush to create a hairy masterpiece. Choose from the available color swatches or fine-tune your own color with the color wheel. Click the square to the left of the color wheel to adjust the hue/saturation/brightness values manually. </Text>
  <Text Key="55DD1517">Painting Werewolves</Text>
  <Text Key="F88AB294">Experience points are gained by using what comes naturally to a Werewolf. Using new wolfy social interactions, transforming into beast form, and using Abilities.</Text>
  <Text Key="D147D4DF">Werewolf Sims become stronger as they learn more about what it's like to live as a beast. They gain cool new Abilities, and new Temperaments that affect how and why they gain Fury.  \n\nThere are 5 tiers total and Sims will continue to gain points even after hitting Apex.</Text>
  <Text Key="FB109C2C">As your Werewolf grows in power, they also learn more about themselves and what makes them reach the rampage point sooner.\n\nAt each tier, Werewolves acquire Temperaments that impact fury gain. Some Sims hate being wet and will get angry if they are, others feel like nobody understands them and gain Fury as relationships fluctuate, and many more!</Text>
  <Text Key="AE295CEF">As Sims gain experience, they also get Ability Points. The points are awarded when reaching the halfway and final marks of a tier, and can be spent on various things, unlocking even more Werewolf behaviors and powers. </Text>
  <Text Key="6C90C005">Werewolf Gameplay</Text>
  <Text Key="20E0BE1C">There are two Werewolf Packs that live in this world: The Moonwood Collective and the Wildfangs. You can find the Moonwood Collective at the large hollowed tree near the mountain, and you can find the Wildfangs on the other side of the river, around the trailer by the old factory ruins.</Text>
  <Text Key="CAD15F8B">If you're looking to learn more about the town or the local packs, check out the Moonwood Mill bulletin board in the middle of town. </Text>
  <Text Key="38186A27">There's always something to do in Moonwood Mill. This former lumber mill town has a rich history with plenty of secrets to discover. It's also full of Werewolves.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E7D3683">If you want to know more about Moonwood Mill's history or it's citizens, try using the "Ask about Moonwood Mill" interaction. </Text>
  <Text Key="08128332">There's an old network of tunnels that runs beneath Moonwood Mill. While there are plenty of adventures to be had and secrets to be found in the Underground, Sims can also uses these tunnels to navigate the world more quickly. Once you've discovered a new tunnel path, click on any of the connected tunnel entrance objects to navigate between them. \n\nEntrances are located in the Bunker, the Sparring Grounds Portal Potties, and in the Sewer Grate. There is also a Moonwood Mill Tunnel Entrance object that can be placed on any lot in Build/Buy mode that can connect you to the main network.</Text>
  <Text Key="B87C0242">Exploring Moonwood Mill</Text>
  <Text Key="5CC70F3F">Deselect current Ability and return {0.OccultPoints} to wallet.</Text>
  <Text Key="CE555FF7">Ability Points</Text>
  <Text Key="2C1E8F26">Ability Points: &lt;span class="balance"&gt;{0.OccultPoints}&lt;/span&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="946FC376">Level up to earn more Ability Points!\n\nSims can level up to the next tier by doing werewolf-specific socials and abilities, as well as by spending time in beast form.</Text>
  <Text Key="7C01E0F3">This button is disabled until changes are made.</Text>
  <Text Key="BCF6E34C">Revert Changes</Text>
  <Text Key="201D05D6">Purchase new Abilities or check the actions needed to unlock Dormant Abilities.</Text>
  <Text Key="E5A3E686">Werewolf Abilities</Text>
  <Text Key="D4FDE198">Thrice-Rebuilt Cabin Walls</Text>
  <Text Key="05E56D44">No Caution Brick Wall</Text>
  <Text Key="F189E691">Caution Brick Wall</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>