<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="6D60FF76">What's the use of a bar if it doesn't add style to your space? After all, a bar is more than just a place to make drinks; it's a chance to bring your friends and family together. Our Chic &amp; Chill Home Bar cabinet blends in with your decor to accent and complement your space. It will surely become a permanent fixture in your home for years to come.</Text>
  <Text Key="B56563A9">Chic &amp; Chill Home Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="953868DB">This minimalist, invisible dance floor may not be the flashiest of party tricks, but it will certainly impress. It's 100% invisible and as close to nothingness as a dance floor can get. The upside is that it will blend seamlessly with your home decor and emit the perfect amount of dance floor fog! How is this done, you may ask? A good magician never reveals their secrets...</Text>
  <Text Key="11371BBA">The Minimalist's Dance Floor</Text>
  <Text Key="2842AB0A">It’s time to celebrate! Whether it's your birthday or another special occasion, help celebrate with this decorative poster. The colorful designs are a fun way to bring the party vibe, and it looks great just about anywhere!</Text>
  <Text Key="181CF215">Party On! Poster</Text>
  <Text Key="7088C90F">Light up the dance floor like no one else! This Colorful Gobo Light is made from lightweight materials and equipped with a tripod base, so it’s easy to transport and store. Spend less time setting up and more time partying! Let's dance!</Text>
  <Text Key="AF681CD6">Party Starters' Colorific Gobo</Text>
  <Text Key="662ECE84">Whimsical, spherical pendants cast a gentle glow from above to make your home feel cozy, inviting, and dreamy... perfect for creating a fun, festive atmosphere in any space!</Text>
  <Text Key="A721C04B">Luminous Lighticles</Text>
  <Text Key="65AA6CAB">The Party Starters' Disco Ball helps set the stage for a night of crazy dancing, fun music, and good times. Hang from the ceiling, swing from the chandeliers, and let the party begin!</Text>
  <Text Key="1B151DAA">Party Starters' Disco Ball</Text>
  <Text Key="ADDE6506">If you're throwing a party, add some elegant lighting effects! With The Partylite, you can create an atmospheric ray of light up any wall or display for a dramatic and eye-catching result. Suitable for outdoor or indoor events, this light is something you'll return to time after time!</Text>
  <Text Key="EC61F099">The Partylite</Text>
  <Text Key="80E7F5B1">The best part about parties is the chance to meet new Sims and for new Sims to meet you! But they can't learn everything about you right off the bat... so there needs to be some added mystery. For that, there is the Party Starters' Fog Machine. Envelope the room in a mysterious fog to ensure no one knows precisely who you are.</Text>
  <Text Key="17DE4584">Party Starters' Fog Machine</Text>
  <Text Key="8EFA9803">Don't be afraid to get a little glowy because this Fiber Optic Garland is the perfect party accessory! This string of glowing, fiber optic garland will add a touch of color to your next celebration and is a must-have for creating a luminous display on any wall.</Text>
  <Text Key="526BBB52">Fiber Optic Garland</Text>
  <Text Key="D72FB38A">Create a bold, stylish, and on-point presentation with this food pedestal. Introducing the centerpiece of the party snack line-up! "The Centerpiece" Food Pedestal is a striking way to display your cake, desserts, or other tasty snacks you may want to show off. </Text>
  <Text Key="08ECA395">"The Centerpiece" Food Pedestal</Text>
  <Text Key="0CE4452F">It's noon the next day; the house is a mess with colorful confetti. It makes you remember how fun last night was, and suddenly, you don't care much about all the cleanup you have ahead of you.</Text>
  <Text Key="0325C476">"About Last Night..." Confetti</Text>
  <Text Key="50D11BEA">"Where troubles melt like cowplant berry drops,\nAway above the Sim's thought props,\nThat's where you'll find me."</Text>
  <Text Key="0EF67F75">Under The Streamers</Text>
  <Text Key="D4064B1F">The Party Starters' Balloon Pile is the perfect way to get your party started. This bundle of balloons comes wrapped with string lights to add an extra glow and ambiance to the party. You'll love how easy these are to set up and how great they'll look no matter where they are in your space.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6DF51C6">Party Starters' Balloon Pile</Text>
  <Text Key="91A743D1">Are you looking for a quick and easy party starter? The Party Starters' Balloon Bundle is the perfect addition to any celebration. Made of string lights and ribbons, this string of balloons is sure to impress guests.</Text>
  <Text Key="5BD87924">Party Starters' Balloon Bundle</Text>
  <Text Key="61A4C9C0">So many snacks! Where to begin? This assortment of snack clutter can be placed all over your kitchen and dining surfaces to prove to your guests that you are truly the host with the most. Remember your mini napkin!</Text>
  <Text Key="03A5768F">Snack Clutter for Party People </Text>
  <Text Key="FA0C6F98">Keeping cups, straws, and napkins together makes for a tidier party. That's why you need this Cups 'n Straws Station! This station keeps cups, straws, napkins, and your favorite party drink at the ready for all your party guests.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B692A17">Cups 'n Straws Station</Text>
  <Text Key="B66A204A">The perfect way to get a party started or keep it going longer! Add some fun to your party with this colorful and vibrant LED PARTYstrip. Use it as a decorative accessory to make any room look cooler or add ambiance to your day-to-day. </Text>
  <Text Key="B68DA655">LED PARTYstrip</Text>
  <Text Key="EFF6688C">A Balloon Bouquet is always a crowd-pleaser. Add some extra special pizazz to your walls with this unique Balloon Bouquet, accented with vibrant ribbons and fun pops of color.</Text>
  <Text Key="68EB7943">Balloon Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="293AF1FA">Recently, pixel-eye imagery has sought to gain ground. Sadly, their desire to find new ground has been their downfall. Stepping away from both the concave and convex autostereogram approaches has resulted in less-than-ideal outcomes. Though the pixels are still quite enticing, they fail to produce any hidden image.</Text>
  <Text Key="3CA642A5">"Simstagram-Worthy" Stereoscopic Drape</Text>
  <Text Key="D56DC86A">Transform the mood at your next party with rows of hanging, glowing light strip ribbons. These ribbons glow to life and are perfect for creating a fun and vibrant party atmosphere.</Text>
  <Text Key="4DBBDCF5">Luminescent Ribbons</Text>
  <Text Key="9C35E415">Get your party started by decorating the room in our Festive Party Streamers. Hanging these streamers is a great way to add color, depth, and texture to any dull space. There’s just something about a colorful party that makes you want to smile and dance. The possibilities are endless when it comes to decorations for celebrating, whether you’re having a baby shower, birthday party, or holiday get-together!</Text>
  <Text Key="AD4A4B30">Festive Party Streamers</Text>
  <Text Key="C7D89F4D">Make your guest's entrance a memorable one with The Partyboard! This fun and festive sign features a wooden stand and an upbeat welcome message that is sure to draw in the crowd and set the tone for an unforgettable event! </Text>
  <Text Key="476F9A98">The Partyboard</Text>
  <Text Key="C420A045">Add a pop of color and instant ambiance to your party space with this "Simstagram-Worthy" Neon Sign. Perfect for parties, this neon sign will provide the perfect photo-ready backdrop for selfies and Simstagram posts. Your photos are guaranteed to be the envy of all your friends and followers!</Text>
  <Text Key="6C437E40">"Simstagram-Worthy" Neon Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="9238D829">You hear that? That crackle. That hiss. That is the sound of a genuine article—New Faithful produces only the highest fidelity, original quality, and lossless analog music for your listening pleasure. It even has space to show off your painstakingly assembled record collection! Just so everyone in the room knows how important music is to you... good music, that is.</Text>
  <Text Key="3126E50C">"New Faithful" Turntable</Text>
  <Text Key="60010917">This surround sound speaker delivers big, bold, beautiful sound to your home. Thanks to its wall-mounted design, you can place it out of the way, leaving more space for even more partygoers!</Text>
  <Text Key="9FEAAEEE">Good Vibes Wall Speaker</Text>
  <Text Key="D31ED57F">It’s easy to get carried away with all the excitement of having a party, but don’t forget about your tables! The Partyscape Dining Table is perfect for displaying your favorite snacks, drinks, and decor for any occasion. It features a bright and festive tablecloth that will make a statement at dinner parties and casual gatherings. You can even use it as a snack table to display all your impressive party snacks!</Text>
  <Text Key="D6DB31A6">Partyscape Dining Table</Text>
  <Text Key="3EFF1D99">Show your friends that you have the latest and greatest! The Curve TV by Screensure is a high-tech curved TV featuring a state-of-the-art wall mounting system. Choose from a variety of vibrant backlighting options for an added touch of ambiance suited for any occasion. Great for entertaining or everyday use!</Text>
  <Text Key="2E88F61C">The Curve TV by Screensure</Text>
  <Text Key="0A81B039">Turn Off Fog</Text>
  <Text Key="80312848">Turn On Fog</Text>
  <Text Key="4E8F5F0F">The Party Room</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>