<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="3FECBCC7">(From Globe Bar)</Text>
  <Text Key="E8AE828B">(From Reprimanding Butler)</Text>
  <Text Key="65F3C10D">(From Vanity Table)</Text>
  <Text Key="6C2C95EB">What to do tonight, what to do... The same thing {0.SimFirstName} does every night. Try to take over the world.</Text>
  <Text Key="ED2D9BEA">Contemplated World Domination</Text>
  <Text Key="F9DABBC2">Hey! That's where {0.SimFirstName} lives!</Text>
  <Text Key="FD16BDBD">Found My City</Text>
  <Text Key="4268DCE4">Oh, to hold the entire world in the palm of one's hand... what can't {0.SimFirstName} accomplish?</Text>
  <Text Key="CF8BB22B">Striving For Greatness</Text>
  <Text Key="9FE9BADC">So many exciting places, so little time. Where will {0.SimFirstName} travel next?</Text>
  <Text Key="7CE26CB3">The Vast World</Text>
  <Text Key="DF43E638">{0.SimFirstName} added a few layers of makeup... just to be sure! {M0.He}{F0.She} even mostly got it in the right spots!</Text>
  <Text Key="7BE5A237">Glamorous!</Text>
  <Text Key="8221DD29">Huh... {0.SimFirstName} is pretty sure that's not what makeup looks like when adults wear it.</Text>
  <Text Key="5218E40C">Oops</Text>
  <Text Key="8D470F78">Sometimes you have to remind the help that they're supposed to be... well... helpful.</Text>
  <Text Key="A8A4C577">Reprimanded Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="E004E2EA">Windenburg Butlering Academy</Text>
  <Text Key="B5C70DD6">Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="9B14F90C">Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="5788F6DC">Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="3945EC05">Star Quality</Text>
  <Text Key="12C84A9D">Well Turned Out</Text>
  <Text Key="00D5338D">Glittering Heights</Text>
  <Text Key="9D6ED495">Bewitching Sophistication</Text>
  <Text Key="8702EADF">Dazzling Vestment</Text>
  <Text Key="C4DBDC17">Ritzy Frock</Text>
  <Text Key="22A1624A">You'll want to journey to the center of the planet in this elegant piece by famed artisan J. Marano. A walnut hardwood inlaid with gold forms the base upon which the globe sits. Bridge the old world and the new, with natural dyes painted over a pearlescent surface. Of course this planet's treasure lies in its liquid core...</Text>
  <Text Key="57ABCC55">16th Century Monte Vista Globe Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="805C3C7B">Surprisingly, the gilded bed frame of this elegant sleeper is not its defining feature. As you're undoubtedly aware, locally sourced textiles are all the rage in furniture fashion as of late. It just so happens that the headboards are inset with restored wall padding that was reappropriated from the old Windenburg asylum - long since abandoned due to advances in medical education.</Text>
  <Text Key="800E5CDA">Tufted &amp; Tucked</Text>
  <Text Key="57F99452">You'll find no better sleep than the Maleficent Bedstead. Its understated elegance is second only to the comfort it provides. The padded leather head and footboards are guaranteed to have a timeless appeal... so much so that the manufacturer has issued a lifetime "style warranty", the first of its kind in the furniture industry.</Text>
  <Text Key="8733606D">Maleficent Bedstead</Text>
  <Text Key="11FBA71F">Genre: Self-Help\nAuthor: Alfred the Butler\n\nA who's who of butlers with a how to guide to butlering. Discover the origins of butlering in Windenburg, and how the role has adapted to modern butlering in the 21st century. Inspirational quotes from famous butlers will keep you motivated and moving!</Text>
  <Text Key="98C8A5C6">How to Serve and Not Be Served
</Text>
  <Text Key="22F211AA">A triumvirate of The Coalition's finest horologists collaborated to bring you this exquisite timepiece. The spindles around the edge represent the original measurements of time by Neanderthal Sims, in stark contrast to the standard 12 hour intervals we use to track time in the modern day.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0B49B35">Burst, a clock by The Coalition</Text>
  <Text Key="B9E48DB8">We may never know which came first between the chicken and the egg, but doilies definitely came from these intricate curtains. As the legend goes, far back in the 17th century Mara S. Doily invited the region's wealthiest socialites to a gala at her mansion in Windenburg in the hope of finding a husband for her daughter. While the event did not unearth a suitable suitor, one fashionable duke offered a princely sum for Mara's exquisite sitting room curtains, as he found himself entranced by their frilly pattern. Passed down through subsequent generations, the pattern eventually made its way to the common folk, who now enjoy it as a fanciful way to dress their plates.</Text>
  <Text Key="BDF000B7">Doily Drapes - Left</Text>
  <Text Key="BEFA223C">A simpler curtain for simpler times. If it's refined elegance you seek, these curtains deliver it aplenty. Leave the frills for those who need to make a statement; you've already ascended.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F9AF293">Some Like It Plain - Left</Text>
  <Text Key="535F5581">A simpler curtain for simpler times. If it's refined elegance you seek, these curtains deliver it aplenty. Leave the frills for those who need to make a statement; you've already ascended.</Text>
  <Text Key="46116DB4">Some Like It Plain - Right</Text>
  <Text Key="4EEB28D7">We may never know which came first between the chicken and the egg, but doilies definitely came from these intricate curtains. As the legend goes, far back in the 17th century Mara S. Doily invited the region's wealthiest socialites to a gala at her mansion in Windenburg in the hope of finding a husband for her daughter. While the event did not unearth a suitable suitor, one fashionable duke offered a princely sum for Mara's exquisite sitting room curtains, as he found himself entranced by their frilly pattern. Passed down through subsequent generations, the pattern eventually made its way to the common folk, who now enjoy it as a fanciful way to dress their plates.</Text>
  <Text Key="17847EAE">Doily Drapes - Right</Text>
  <Text Key="A9545C85">Famous entertainers who called Starlight Shores their home are now preserved in timeless pop art to adorn your walls.</Text>
  <Text Key="314FF680">Starlet Shores</Text>
  <Text Key="6F1394A1">The pen is mightier than the sword, and you will wield all the power when seated behind this stately desk.</Text>
  <Text Key="CEA39154">Mauman's Working Desk</Text>
  <Text Key="B67439CA">Definitely not a door for dorks; the Art Doorco flaunts its playful art deco style to add elegance to any ingress.</Text>
  <Text Key="6955BAD5">Art Doorco Double Door
</Text>
  <Text Key="1BE35DBD">An elegant dresser with a low profile. You'll have to fold your clothes as there's no room for hangers, but if you can afford this dresser, then surely you can afford a butler to do the folding for you.</Text>
  <Text Key="483FB728">The Short Of It</Text>
  <Text Key="51C40C8A">Feel large and in charge with this stand up dresser. With no need to fold, you'll never have any unwanted creases or wrinkles!</Text>
  <Text Key="D5985E95">The Tall Of It</Text>
  <Text Key="03CCFF7C">A crystal decanter for juice.</Text>
  <Text Key="D142A5D3">Decanter</Text>
  <Text Key="A29CED8A">A serving tray with room for four drinks.</Text>
  <Text Key="235B3195">Drink Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="57CB2918">A short glass, appropriate for juice.</Text>
  <Text Key="91ED1E97">Tumbler</Text>
  <Text Key="3733BF0A">The mantel of this fireplace is actually a piece of the decorative facade taken from the city hall building in Roaring Heights. Originally commissioned as a gift to the city's mayor, it disappeared from his estate following his untimely death. It has since passed through the lucrative architectural black market in search for the right buyer... will it be you?</Text>
  <Text Key="DE3BEE15">Fiery Facade</Text>
  <Text Key="C125731A">The Punchinello family is renown in theatrics, and this chandelier is representative of the height of their heyday. Only ten of its kind were made, custom designed to illuminate the foyer of the old Punchinello Theater in downtown San Myshuno. Whereas Patrick Punchinello once dreamed of passing the business to his son, the family ultimately went bankrupt when little Peter failed to live up to his legacy. While the assets of their once expansive properties were liquidated, their memory lives on by giving this regal chandelier a place in your own home.</Text>
  <Text Key="733EDA45">Punchinello Theater Chandelier</Text>
  <Text Key="1867ECF2">This evocative lamp invokes the form of a box jellyfish, each leg dangling from the top-heavy mass. Unlike the bioluminescence found in certain species, this particular piece is lit with a standard 60 watt incandescent bulb.</Text>
  <Text Key="69B0E88D">Jellyfish Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="B3EB957F">Add some kitsch to your home with Geoff the giraffe; he's the light of the party! It's the greatest lamp base since the nylon stocking clad leg.</Text>
  <Text Key="822571A6">Gentle Geoff</Text>
  <Text Key="0BF8F9BF">When lit, the aroma from this scented candle intermingles with the fragrance of the fresh flowers to create a nasal bouquet for the ages. All you have to do is relax... relax... relax.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B6496E6">Aglow Aromatics</Text>
  <Text Key="6B33FC43">The perfectly round base of this lamp is quite perilous, leaving it with a predilection for predicaments. It took seven painstaking hours to simply balance it upright, and another three hours to rebalance it after realizing the bulb hadn't been screwed in. Do not bump the table that this lamp is set upon. Don't you even dare breathe... Just slowly back up, turn around, and exit the room.</Text>
  <Text Key="568F5792">Newton's Provocative Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="9C01D176">Inspired by the designs of classical astrolabes, this mirror will guide you to a beautiful appearance, the same way astrolabes guided astronomers to celestial bodies.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B6B39A9">Astrolabe Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="F59F44EB">When you look this good you want to show off. Nothing accommodates your self-absorption better than a floor to ceiling mirror. Don't worry - we know about your sharp knees problem and added a low bar to help mask it. Your secret is safe with us!\n\nThis mirror is best suited for short wall heights.</Text>
  <Text Key="025878EA">Narcissus's Folly - Short</Text>
  <Text Key="82B1B82E">When you look this good you want to show off. Nothing accommodates your self-absorption better than a floor to ceiling mirror. Don't worry - we know about your sharp knees problem and added a low bar to help mask it. Your secret is safe with us!\n\nThis mirror is best suited for medium wall heights.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF0592D1">Narcissus's Folly - Medium</Text>
  <Text Key="70C2B7A9">When you look this good you want to show off. Nothing accommodates your self-absorption better than a floor to ceiling mirror. Don't worry - we know about your sharp knees problem and added a low bar to help mask it. Your secret is safe with us!\n\nThis mirror is best suited for tall wall heights.</Text>
  <Text Key="D9B76B8C">Narcissus's Folly - Tall</Text>
  <Text Key="825EC91F">Reflect on the beauty of these vibrant star-shaped flowers which are nearly in full bloom... just one bud remains.</Text>
  <Text Key="ACE46BC6">Growing Home</Text>
  <Text Key="A1939032">A partnership between the senior ranking sewer and weaver within The Coalition bore fruit with the release of this striking rug. Each interlocking cog can be positioned in lockstep to create intricate mechanical patterns sweeping across your floor.</Text>
  <Text Key="09DDABCD">Gears; a rug by The Coalition</Text>
  <Text Key="4EFF700C">Fur so soft you'd swear it was real...</Text>
  <Text Key="1900F7C3">Faux Fur Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="00CEE619">What do you get when dividing by zero? Nothing. And that's just about as much privacy as this metallic divider offers. Thankfully what it lacks in secrecy it makes up for in style.</Text>
  <Text Key="7904E79C">Arithmetically Challenged Divider</Text>
  <Text Key="5F047AD0">La Luz is fiercely protective of anything in its possession. Some swear up and down that its eyes shift their gaze when nobody is looking.</Text>
  <Text Key="2C5EE4FF">La Luz the Lion</Text>
  <Text Key="5327F72A">Why would anyone create a collection of fragrances that smells like the bathroom? I guess it'll remain one of life's little mysteries.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C5E53B5">Eww the Toilet</Text>
  <Text Key="11B571A2">No longer do you have to suffer through the awkward chair showroom experience.  Lisa's Resplendent Receptacle is ordered completely online! The chair's padding is crafted from three unique foam layers. You'll sink into two inches of memory foam, two inches of a latex like foam called Simvena, and two inches of... well, we just don't talk about the third layer.</Text>
  <Text Key="49D6121D">Lisa's Resplendent Receptacle</Text>
  <Text Key="1F0E7F15">Aches and pains? How droll! After all, lumbar support is for those who can't afford back surgery. Instead, you'll be pleased to discover that every thought that went into designing this chair culminated in a singular achievement - the most comfortable plush padding for your posterior.</Text>
  <Text Key="27AB2C30">Tush-tastic</Text>
  <Text Key="8423D159">An ottoman conceived for the masses, but ultimately relegated to the elite. Each one made represents over 1000 man hours of work, as the metal frame is hammered into shape on an anvil until the surface is perfectly smooth.</Text>
  <Text Key="682DF6DC">Mauman's Ottoman</Text>
  <Text Key="11471764">The name of this sofa says it all. So refined, so elegant, so dignified... this luxurious lounger is only intended for the most delicate of derrieres. Absolutely positively no animals allowed.</Text>
  <Text Key="F6A459AB">Mauman's Sofa For People</Text>
  <Text Key="B72F8E54">This coffee table serves as proof that two heads are better than one, as the city's two top metallurgists came together to design the base of this grand coffee table. The marble slab topper is scientifically proven to be the best surface for serving tasty treats!</Text>
  <Text Key="48E7843B">Cold Stone Coffee Table
</Text>
  <Text Key="3D6AE565">The mirrored surface of this beverage cart will appear to double the amount of drinks available for tasting, but this is no simple trick of the eye. We guarantee this cart holds more glasses per square inch than any other cart you'll find, hands down.</Text>
  <Text Key="A6DCFFE0">MoBev Cart
</Text>
  <Text Key="6B50B351">When placed outside, the true incandescent brilliance of this orrery-cum-table gleams for all to see.</Text>
  <Text Key="8992AFA4">Rory's Orrery
</Text>
  <Text Key="0BF8088C">Merry-Simster's Dictionary defines "vainglory" as a display of pride that's excessive or ostentatious. How then did it come to describe this very vanity? Such a name must be in jest; the owner of this piece has no need for other's plaudits.</Text>
  <Text Key="3BFE5943">Vainglorious Vanity</Text>
  <Text Key="9E1552F6">Trust the French for your vanity table needs. This French Contemporary styled vanity table works well in the common household. It blends seamlessly into the style of any residence from an abode to a villa!</Text>
  <Text Key="43C30629">Coiffeuse de Champs Les Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="3066B192">A bell that emanates high frequency sound waves. Butlers are trained to be particularly perceptive to this exact sound.</Text>
  <Text Key="893CB1AD">Butler Bell</Text>
  <Text Key="80017528">Rich Sims aspire to have style like you. Poor Sims aspire to have money to have style to be like you. With these windows on your home, you'll represent the pinnacle of the architectural glitterati of wherever you choose to call home.</Text>
  <Text Key="A72B4D47">#winning #fabulous #vogue</Text>
  <Text Key="64DAF82E">Pour Drink</Text>
  <Text Key="880C0B14">Pour Drink Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="200BF90B">Assign Bed to Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="A116C36D">{0.SimFirstName} has already claimed this bed.</Text>
  <Text Key="290676C1">Start Attending to Minors</Text>
  <Text Key="2729800E">Start Cleaning</Text>
  <Text Key="069D392E">Start Gardening</Text>
  <Text Key="B53C7948">Start Repairing Objects</Text>
  <Text Key="6A13CC0D">Stop Attending to Minors</Text>
  <Text Key="1D65E11A">Stop Cleaning</Text>
  <Text Key="8420A26A">Stop Gardening</Text>
  <Text Key="56F45B5C">Stop Repairing Objects</Text>
  <Text Key="8F3D9C22">Force Quit</Text>
  <Text Key="21F276D6">Research Butler Techniques on Ask Alfred</Text>
  <Text Key="8C864CBA">Everyone But Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="F0AAD7DD">Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="3BEFD01A">Grab a Drink</Text>
  <Text Key="8CF396EC">Make Drink</Text>
  <Text Key="84402701">Pour Drink</Text>
  <Text Key="3634352C">Study Globe</Text>
  <Text Key="9FFAF053">Contemplate the Big Picture</Text>
  <Text Key="BE6305F0">Ponder World Domination</Text>
  <Text Key="66C2276C">Search for My Name</Text>
  <Text Key="1DEB6254">Ponder Exotic Locals</Text>
  <Text Key="7C1274B1">Apply Makeup</Text>
  <Text Key="0546BF09">Beige Eyes / Dark Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="07C9CAA8">Beige Eyes / Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="572AD7FB">Black Eyeliner / Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="27710D67">Black Eyes / Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="154A0543">Blue Eyes / Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="57BADB3A">Blue Eyes / Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="0F263919">Blue Eyes / Rose Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="34E544B8">Blue Eyes / Satin Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="F0A497EF">Bronze Eyes / Glossy Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="8DC02156">Brown Eyes</Text>
  <Text Key="A0A0BCC5">Brown Eyes / Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="418BBC04">Brown Eyes / Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="5165C8CB">Brown Eyes / Rose Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="82263FC2">Brown Eyes / Satin Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="82CFD1EA">Gold Eyes / Glossy Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="70355D08">Black Eyes / Satin Black Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="8DC701E9">Black Eyes / Satin Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="84F4C7CA">Brown &amp; Gray / Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="1A096B53">Gray Eyes / Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="31EC9B54">Gray Eyes / Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="A70D3015">Green Eyes / Bronze Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="784D83A6">Green Eyes / Glossy Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="199F2A3F">Green Eyes / Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="09B2B950">Green Eyes / Satin Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="8DB53191">Green Eyes / Satin Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="6B15BCC9">Magenta Eyes / Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="8898B268">Mauve Eyes / Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="B2D22433">Mauve Eyes / Glossy Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="B6F16CAA">Pink Eyes / Glossy Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="C95A3EF5">Plum Eyes / Satin Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="D4A1E4B4">Purple Eyes / Satin Violet Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="15FCE41F">Red Eyes</Text>
  <Text Key="4350F286">Silver &amp; Blue / Rose Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="0FEEE2F1">Silver &amp; Blue / Satin Blue Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="DFCC0E30">Silver &amp; Blue / Satin Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="8B0B8BF4">Silver &amp; Brown / Satin Beige Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="70296456">Silver &amp; Brown / Satin Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="D30DDAEF">Silver &amp; Green / Satin Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="23F4FF04">Silver &amp; Pink / Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="8309FFC5">Silver &amp; Black / Satin Bronze Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="A88A495F">Turquoise Eyes / Coral Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="E09DF4C6">Turquoise Eyes / Rose Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="4C02F031">Turquoise Eyes / Satin Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="0E651370">Violet Eyes / Red Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="27748BB8">Black Cat Eyes</Text>
  <Text Key="55C7A7A2">Black Eyeliner / Satin Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="F6695E8A">Black Eyes</Text>
  <Text Key="01C4CAB5">Black Eyes / Glossy Orange Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="8D921606">Black Eyes / Satin Black Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="13C79B59">Light Blue Eyes / Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="FA3BC286">Blue Eyes / Glossy Blue Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="3F3A566F">Blue Eyes / Glossy Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="0F9F2F91">Blue Eyes / Satin Bronze Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="73E00992">Gray Eyes / Glossy Pink Lips</Text>
  <Text Key="92DD4B50">Black Eyeliner</Text>
  <Text Key="EA07D21E">Play With Makeup</Text>
  <Text Key="1ABDC1B6">The household's butler has been released from their position. We at the Windenburg Butlering Academy hope their service met your undoubtedly high standards.\n\nShould you require a butler in the future, please do not hesitate to use your phone and inform us of your intent to employ a new one.</Text>
  <Text Key="F480DEC8">Dismiss Butler Service</Text>
  <Text Key="EF362BD5">The Windenburg Butlering Academy has an excellent candidate to join your residence as a live-in butler. They will report for work within the day.\n\nUpon your butler's arrival, please assign them a bed to sleep in. Should you be providing private quarters for your butler, you may set door locks for their section of the home.</Text>
  <Text Key="91D66C24">A butler has already been hired. You may fire your current butler if you desire to hire a different one.</Text>
  <Text Key="E3701A6B">The Windenburg Butlering Academy has an excellent candidate to join your residence as a live-in butler. They will report for work within the day.\n\nUpon your butler's arrival, please assign them a bed to sleep in. Should you be providing private quarters for your butler, you may set door locks for their section of the home.</Text>
  <Text Key="0941EF3B">Hire Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="1DA0DDA7">Caught Slacking Off</Text>
  <Text Key="DADAEA81">Caught Not Working</Text>
  <Text Key="0FD9020A">{1.SimFirstName} seems pleased with {0.SimFirstName}'s evaluation and vows to continue working hard. {1.SimFirstName} will be even faster at performing {M1.his}{F1.her} responsibilities for a period of time.</Text>
  <Text Key="132C0392">Praise</Text>
  <Text Key="0336B7DF">I can't take it anymore! I QUIT! Never have I been in the service of such a boorish and downright hostile employer. If you care to hire another butler you may call the Windenburg Butlering Academy, but I'd suggest you work on your demeanor first.\n\nOh and by the way, I'm helping myself to a severance package on my way out. Read our contract; it's included in the fine print.</Text>
  <Text Key="28B7CADB">Quit</Text>
  <Text Key="74DE39F2">{1.SimFirstName} is slightly irritated but seems to be looking to improve {M1.his}{F1.her} performance in the future to match {0.SimFirstName}'s expectations.</Text>
  <Text Key="D99490FA">Reprimand</Text>
  <Text Key="8F785A68">Find Book</Text>
  <Text Key="0C2B717F">Check Cleanliness</Text>
  <Text Key="B37F5F8A">Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="1F1817F2">Sabotage Object</Text>
  <Text Key="38E84DFC">Butler Cheat Actions</Text>
  <Text Key="D3818F5E">Force Idle - Butler Pose</Text>
  <Text Key="89261930">Force Idle - Butler Fidgeting</Text>
  <Text Key="13344965">The residence's butler could not carry out the requested task. Please allow time for {M0.him}{F0.her} to complete {M0.his}{F0.her} current task, or provide sufficient facilities for completing the task.</Text>
  <Text Key="FEF2D3D4">Attend to a Minor</Text>
  <Text Key="248888A5">Clean a Dirty Object</Text>
  <Text Key="2794C6A5">Cook Family Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="A65ED8E1">Cook Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="27CB3DBB">Cook Party Meal</Text>
  <Text Key="30E83D52">The butler is carrying out this order.</Text>
  <Text Key="A86916BE">Invite All Visitors Inside</Text>
  <Text Key="47760FC8">Ignore Front Door</Text>
  <Text Key="73EA2991">Dismiss All Visitors</Text>
  <Text Key="CBB66409">Prepare Bar Drink</Text>
  <Text Key="8BED1D1F">Repair an Object</Text>
  <Text Key="7A4EF5A4">If you must demand that I "get jiggy with it", I will require music playing near a dance floor with enough space for me to "bust a move."</Text>
  <Text Key="41870DAC">Burn Up the Dance Floor</Text>
  <Text Key="CEA268E8">Perform Comedy Routine</Text>
  <Text Key="8D326252">Play Guitar</Text>
  <Text Key="D65A9B0D">Play Piano</Text>
  <Text Key="719EBDA7">Play Violin</Text>
  <Text Key="704CDC7B">Use DJ Booth</Text>
  <Text Key="3DAD93DD">Water Plants</Text>
  <Text Key="F667FA7A">Watch TV Classics</Text>
  <Text Key="AFC02499">Change Appearance</Text>
  <Text Key="4D408E80">Quarters of Luster</Text>
  <Text Key="A2D26997">Enchanting Chamber</Text>
  <Text Key="64BFEEBE">Lavish Ruminations</Text>
  <Text Key="4A58D16E">Evening At The Parlour</Text>
  <Text Key="C6230B8F">{0.ObjectDescription}</Text>
  <Text Key="0F41CCA1">Black &amp; white shows from the golden age of TV.</Text>
  <Text Key="976FDB32">TV Classics</Text>
  <Text Key="0944C2F2">Assign Task</Text>
  <Text Key="D41128DE">Responsibilities</Text>
  <Text Key="1413DA35">Visitors</Text>
  <Text Key="C46259DF">Management</Text>
  <Text Key="A088F404">Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="BC9F7AAA">Browns</Text>
  <Text Key="972FDFB7">Silvers</Text>
  <Text Key="F0D25078">Goth</Text>
  <Text Key="81B31B65">Pinks / Purples / Golds</Text>
  <Text Key="D589A155">Blacks / Grays</Text>
  <Text Key="263F764F">Blues</Text>
  <Text Key="FDA127FA">Greens / Turquoises</Text>
  <Text Key="E8576DBD">Bacciform Firkin</Text>
  <Text Key="87BF910E">Pour Bacciform Firkin</Text>
  <Text Key="2C813EF7">Black Fern</Text>
  <Text Key="6AA24D98">Pour Black Fern</Text>
  <Text Key="889CCD2A">McDillian's Single Nect</Text>
  <Text Key="842F01D5">Pour McDillian's Single Nect</Text>
  <Text Key="09CDF279">Old Yorkfield Classic 16</Text>
  <Text Key="60FB8242">Pour Old Yorkfield Classic 16</Text>
  <Text Key="9C5A9BC1">Bacciform Firkin Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="DF9726AA">Pour Bacciform Firkin Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="7F7B9883">Black Fern Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="E61B077C">Pour Black Fern Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="9ADD397E">McDillian's Single Nect Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="2B55AF31">Pour McDillian's Single Nect Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="2F1EF39D">Old Yorkfield Classic 16 Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="90B145EE">Pour Old Yorkfield Classic 16 Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="C451267C">Simadder Cherry Sap Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="DFA69DAF">Pour Simmadder Cherry Sap Platter</Text>
  <Text Key="95C427E8">Simadder Cherry Sap</Text>
  <Text Key="FF1698F3">Pour Simadder Cherry Sap</Text>
  <Text Key="35A50DB8">The Windenburg Butlering Academy taught me one thing well... "No occupation without compensation." As you've let your household bills lapse, I'll now be taking my leave.\n\nShould you get your finances in order, you may use your phone to inquire about entering into a new butler service arrangement.</Text>
  <Text Key="EECF6B74">I regret to inform you that my customary daily remuneration has not been paid in full. As a courtesy I've added {1.Money} to this week's household bills. Failure to deliver on owed wages via remittance will be regarded as an unspoken termination of the butler service agreement.</Text>
  <Text Key="BEAC41D1">Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="D3593A66">Give Butler An Order</Text>
  <Text Key="1E43C6F6">Click on the household's butler, select the Butler category, and then choose any interaction from within the Assign Task category.</Text>
  <Text Key="077974CF">Praise Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="FEB32DC1">Click on the household's butler, select the Butler category, and then choose Praise from within the Management category.</Text>
  <Text Key="7A792F7F">Reprimand Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="BCDDC0F1">Click on the household's butler, select the Butler category, and then choose Reprimand from within the Management category.</Text>
  <Text Key="B9683915">Play With Makeup</Text>
  <Text Key="E545FF3F">Click on a Vanity Table and select Play With Makeup.</Text>
  <Text Key="9F2B921C">Ponder World Domination</Text>
  <Text Key="A06CDDBC">Click on a Globe Bar and select Ponder World Domination.</Text>
  <Text Key="F5A967D2">Pour a Drink from the Globe Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="E3AC9BAA">Click on a Globe Bar and select Pour Drink.</Text>
  <Text Key="600E973A">Study Globe</Text>
  <Text Key="77CA7662">Click on a Globe Bar and select Study Globe.</Text>
  <Text Key="C56935B9">Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="A5B81A98">Butler</Text>
  <Text Key="B52BC771">Crushed Metallic Paneling</Text>
  <Text Key="0BE662B5">Shine Bright Like a Diamond</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>