<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="7F52035B">Fancy Craze A-Maze</Text>
  <Text Key="EF5105A5">Triangulate</Text>
  <Text Key="1251B2A4">Let the lush colors of this fireplace imbue your home with warmth.</Text>
  <Text Key="491379EB">Warmly Chromatic Fireplace</Text>
  <Text Key="A6BC219B">The creator of this lamp had a dream about exploding stars that led them to design this fixture.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F556D7A">Explosion of Light Fixture</Text>
  <Text Key="30B44296">A lamp as elegant, fun, and flirty as this one can be a bit much for some, but it’s absolutely perfect for any maximalist’s gorgeously over the top abode.</Text>
  <Text Key="93CC2E49">Fringe of Elegance Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="B61A3A95">There are enough panels in this mirror for you to examine every facet of your gregarious personality.</Text>
  <Text Key="EB2286B0">Panels of Self Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="C3CD1BCB">A gallery wall is like a journal of your likes, interests, and wishes... but for your wall! Gather all your best thoughts and put them up there!</Text>
  <Text Key="8C5D4A4A">Collage of Personality</Text>
  <Text Key="02726B7B">If your walls are bold, your furniture is fierce, and even the lighting hanging from your ceiling is daring, you’re going to need a floor to match. Lucky for you, this rug has come to the rescue.</Text>
  <Text Key="EECBB9DA">Plushly Bold Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="6F2B3568">Have you ever spent so many simoleons on furniture that you forgot to add in a wall or two? Well, thank goodness for this wall divider! It'll solve your problems and still look fancy!</Text>
  <Text Key="5DF57287">The Luxurious Divide</Text>
  <Text Key="5B54B697">This deliciously bold art piece will be a touch of regal whimsy to any space.</Text>
  <Text Key="25733F6E">Stately Plumage Sculpt</Text>
  <Text Key="D8D8E19E">A lovely 3D printed piece of a giraffe mother and her babe.</Text>
  <Text Key="5FD5FBA1">Geometric Giraffes</Text>
  <Text Key="1A8E215F">Don’t get lost staring into the circle of infinity. Don’t get lost staring into the circle of infinity. Don’t get lost…</Text>
  <Text Key="1FEDCB06">Circle of Infinity</Text>
  <Text Key="CF3121FE">This wainscoting trim is so bold and fearless you could pair it with anything!</Text>
  <Text Key="47328C81">Truly Fearless Wainscoting</Text>
  <Text Key="91CECBFB">This wainscoting trim is so bold and fearless you could pair it with anything!</Text>
  <Text Key="D299F35A">More Truly Fearless Wainscoting</Text>
  <Text Key="6F436D90">This wainscoting trim is so bold and fearless you could pair it with anything!</Text>
  <Text Key="835F4BBF">Way More Truly Fearless Wainscoting</Text>
  <Text Key="761E6193">Mixing textures in a room is a great way to play with maximalism. Mixing textures in one piece is next level for sure. Level up with the soft plush upholstery and the sleek polished metal base of this living room chair.</Text>
  <Text Key="89629142">Sumptuous Throne for Everyday Living</Text>
  <Text Key="1431D24F">All the patterns are meant to go together. And all the colors or meant to go together. Live life boldly, don’t let anyone tell you differently.</Text>
  <Text Key="31FA1716">Maximalist’s Dream Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="7C783DC1">This coffee table is exactly what it was named: A Balanced Place for Coffee.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8EF67F4">A Balanced Place for Coffee</Text>
  <Text Key="DFA46E9D">Add a touch of regal elegance to any room with this accent table.</Text>
  <Text Key="3F1C5688">A Regal Stand</Text>
  <Text Key="AC005752">Refined, dynamic, and fun. This hallway table playfully elevates any setting.</Text>
  <Text Key="6DF6396D">Bold Indulgence Hallway Table</Text>
  <Text Key="674CAFC7">Max Luxe</Text>
  <Text Key="7F0D472A">Birds and Flower in Hand</Text>
  <Text Key="74182B2C">Geo and Logic</Text>
  <Text Key="DADC1365">The Tiger Stalks Tonight</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>