<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="62468B4B">(From Wearing Filthy Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="213E839C">(From Wearing Clean Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="931470DE">(From Wearing Damp Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="117E1230">(From Wearing Dry Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="00A20AAF">(From Wearing Fragrant Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="A50DCEAB">(From Wearing Dirty Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="F182E2AF">(From Wearing Pristine Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="B64F2348">(From Wearing Foul Smelling Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="24AC14DC">(From Wearing Soaked Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="3817FD77">(From Wearing Used Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="8A600A07">(From Wearing Warm Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="2A2050F1">(From Splashing in a Wash Tub)</Text>
  <Text Key="1F0BF0C6">(From Washing Laundry in the Wash Tub)</Text>
  <Text Key="FBA1FDF8">(From Watching Laundry Spin)</Text>
  <Text Key="565A06D9">(From Hamper)</Text>
  <Text Key="EC810B04">(From Laundry)</Text>
  <Text Key="76326968">(From Having No Laundry Appliances)</Text>
  <Text Key="14CEE230">(From Washing Machine Failure)</Text>
  <Text Key="B5A817CB">{0.SimFirstName}'s dressed so fresh and so clean!</Text>
  <Text Key="FBC57E4A">Clean Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="BFD26EC3">Bleh, this laundry didn't dry thoroughly.</Text>
  <Text Key="44032712">Damp Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="C893BA4F">{0.SimFirstName}'s so dizzy, {M0.his}{F0.her} head is spinning... like a whirlpool, it never ends.</Text>
  <Text Key="262B4F16">Spin Cycle</Text>
  <Text Key="6907C5E2">The household's laundry load dried sufficiently... Sometimes it's the little things in life that mean the most.</Text>
  <Text Key="F7CB935D">Dry Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="3AFCC003">{0.SimFirstName}'s clothing is disgusting. It's well passed time to do a load of laundry. Don't walk... RUN to the nearest Washing Machine.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF09B352">Filthy Clothing!</Text>
  <Text Key="37F79120">Mmm... {0.SimFirstName}'s clothing smells like a flowery meadow thanks to that laundry additive.</Text>
  <Text Key="D6C2966F">Floral Scented Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="5CB78BDB">{0.SimFirstName}'s clothing is pretty dirty. Stop slacking and clean some laundry.</Text>
  <Text Key="E63514BA">Dirty Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="65C1F4A5">The clothes from this load of laundry turned out exceptionally clean. Nice!</Text>
  <Text Key="B2B9EF20">Pristine Clothing!</Text>
  <Text Key="FBDC908B">Oh gross, who slipped the rotting food into the laundry load? {0.SimFirstName}'s clothing smells truly foul.</Text>
  <Text Key="E579340A">Foul Smelling Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="664873D4">Did someone forget to dry the laundry after it was washed? {0.SimFirstName}'s clothing is absolutely drenched. </Text>
  <Text Key="45CA3CBB">Soaked Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="C7E31982">Icky wet water...</Text>
  <Text Key="75C1247D">Yucky Splash</Text>
  <Text Key="C203E132">{0.SimFirstName}'s outfit isn't exactly fresh from the washer, but nobody will call {M0.him}{F0.her} out for wearing it either. Set aside time to do laundry in the next few days though...</Text>
  <Text Key="F6EBCECD">Used Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="F2CC4CDE">Wearing clothing that was recently dried is like a big warm hug that goes on and on!</Text>
  <Text Key="1A5078E1">Warm Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="9547C861">Keeping scrubbing through the pain!</Text>
  <Text Key="161E9314">Washed-Out Arms</Text>
  <Text Key="1619AB70">Ladylike Bug</Text>
  <Text Key="C5E93B4B">Woven Threads</Text>
  <Text Key="39634070">Sun-Day Best</Text>
  <Text Key="BAC2C26E">Fresh Boho Chic</Text>
  <Text Key="70FC479D">Topped With Knots</Text>
  <Text Key="1D4AD44E">Country Vibes</Text>
  <Text Key="CA5A2B34">Comfortably Torn</Text>
  <Text Key="6AAB39C5">Relaxed Fit</Text>
  <Text Key="F2E54845">Fresh from Crockery Kitchen comes a "reclaimed" lumber door. Artificially aged and stressed, it's the perfect addition to your home, without the risk of termites!</Text>
  <Text Key="58A0F640">Crockery Kitchen Door</Text>
  <Text Key="27FC7EDA">Sometimes you want a hint of the outdoors, without all the nuisance of bright sunlight streaming in. Crockery Kitchen has just what you need! For a modest fee, this optional curtain upgrade on their popular "reclaimed" lumber line lets you enjoy the best of both worlds.</Text>
  <Text Key="5E448C05">Shaded Crockery Kitchen Door</Text>
  <Text Key="CCA52FD9">Approximately 15 million Model T clotheslines were produced, and were so prolific that they dotted the backyard of every home in suburbia. Time marched on, and while most Sims rely on the modern convenience of a dryer, the old Model T remains as reliable as ever for your laundry drying needs.\n\n*Owning this object will cause your Sims' clothes to become dirty over time. Wet laundry can be hung on the Clothesline to be dried.</Text>
  <Text Key="B7BECA5C">Model T Clothesline</Text>
  <Text Key="86A05AAB">A stack of clothes, folded after being washed and dried.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE9787AA">Folded Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="72620DE6">This dryer is hot, hot, HOT! A controlled fire fueled by natural gas quickly raises the temperature, while the drum rapidly spins to ensure your clothes never stay in one place long enough to get singed. In the unfortunate event that you get burnt, your purchase legally equates to implicit consent to our liability waiver... After all, regular maintenance is the responsibility of the owner!\n\n*Owning this object will cause your Sims' clothes to become dirty over time. Wet laundry can be dried inside the Dryer.</Text>
  <Text Key="1C894BF9">Fyre Dryer</Text>
  <Text Key="04450F46">A trail of clothing leading to the bedroom is so cliché. Don't act like a slob; place your clothing in this hamper from Wicker Whims.\n\n*Owning this object will cause your Sims' clothes to become dirty over time. When your Sim changes outfits, discarded clothing will automatically be placed in the nearest hamper that has available space.</Text>
  <Text Key="DBFD04D9">Wicker Whims Hamper</Text>
  <Text Key="53AAFDDF">With the Feelin' Fabric Hamper, you'll feel compelled to stop and run your hand across the exterior to appreciate the sumptuous feel of this fine fabric. Double canvas layers make a valiant effort to block any unpleasant odors wafting off your soiled clothing.\n\n*Owning this object will cause your Sims' clothes to become dirty over time. When your Sim changes outfits, discarded clothing will automatically be placed in the nearest hamper that has available space.</Text>
  <Text Key="02DCB886">Feelin' Fabric Hamper</Text>
  <Text Key="9F927BD0">New from LaundryMaid, it's our most reliable hamper yet! The soft plastic frame offers superior durability, while the chic open hole design allows air to freely circulate.\n\n*Owning this object will cause your Sims' clothes to become dirty over time. When your Sim changes outfits, discarded clothing will automatically be placed in the nearest hamper that has available space.</Text>
  <Text Key="2AF717FF">LaundryMaid Clothing Hamper</Text>
  <Text Key="AB79DB97">A pile of laundry.</Text>
  <Text Key="841F9E6E">Clothing Pile</Text>
  <Text Key="C8FA541E">Guilt free washing is just a click away with the Green Clean Washing Machine. An on-board microchip analyzes your laundry load and automatically adjusts the machine's settings to select the most efficient wash cycle possible. Save time. Save money. Save the planet! Go Green Clean!\n\n*Owning this object will cause your Sims' clothes to become dirty over time. Dirty laundry can be collected from a Hamper, or from clothes piles on the floor, and cleaned inside the Washing Machine.</Text>
  <Text Key="3262CB21">Green Clean Washing Machine</Text>
  <Text Key="361DA1C1">Rub-a-dub-dub,\nFoul clothes in this tub,\nWhat are you waiting for?\nOn hand and knee,\nYou'll scrub this tee,\nUntil you complete this chore!\n\n*Owning this object will cause your Sims' clothes to become dirty over time. Dirty laundry can be collected from a Hamper, or from clothes piles on the floor, and cleaned in the Wash Tub.</Text>
  <Text Key="115A53F4">Ole Timmy's Wash Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="7C2EA3BE">This light bulb is 100% eco-friendly. You ask how this can be possible, considering light bulbs are quite old-fashioned and usually less healthy for the environment? Well, we at MorcuCorp spend all the Simoleons we earn by selling this light bulb in exploration of green energy. Big MorcuCorp promise! We won't lie to you!</Text>
  <Text Key="2B86D041">Eco-Friendly Light Bulb by MorcuCorp</Text>
  <Text Key="167D205D">In a worry that the "Wicker Whims" moniker was limiting the company's product lineup to wicker furniture, management decided to blaze new trails in the candle industry!</Text>
  <Text Key="21F0FB48">Wick-er Whims Candle Bowl</Text>
  <Text Key="31A18888">A simple farmhouse pitcher.</Text>
  <Text Key="9F36DA27">Galvanized Pitcher</Text>
  <Text Key="482F389E">Come on down to Barry Potter's Plant Emporium! Today we've got a special deal on indoor shrubbery... and while supplies last, they're available in authentic aged barrels from the Bacciform Firkin Compound. When you reach the register, be sure to say the magic phrase that pays: "Hocus Ficus!"</Text>
  <Text Key="4E8B50A1">Barry Potter's Potted Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="7881BB2C">Succulents so tender, juicy, and tasty... it'd be a shame to keep them around purely as decor.</Text>
  <Text Key="28CA7263">Succulent Succulents</Text>
  <Text Key="535FF1E1">They say that the right fragrance can trigger endorphins that result in feeling flirtatious. This potpourri arrangement from Wicker Whims provides a custom blend of floral and pine, guaranteed to get the special Sim in your life in the mood.</Text>
  <Text Key="CE93D794">Wicker Whims Potpourri</Text>
  <Text Key="A6CF42D7">The rings and circles on this mat are actually markers of the ancient Simolonean calendar. The date they point to is August 16th, 2032. What grim future did our ancestors predict? What calamity awaits us? Only time will tell...</Text>
  <Text Key="A5E1ACAE">Simolonean Mat</Text>
  <Text Key="E2CCAF3C">This rug's unique pattern is derived from a nautical knot that was pioneered by the fishermen of Brindleton Bay.</Text>
  <Text Key="DF830993">Escalloped Escape</Text>
  <Text Key="5A9A5009">It's no bear skin rug... but if you absolutely need a place to roll around for a romantic romp, you could do worse than this rug from Wicker Whims.</Text>
  <Text Key="A4C8196C">Wicker Whims Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="5C02FC5C">Southwestern stylings and plant patterns? It's madness to try and understand the various variants this rug offers, but hopefully you'll discover one to be the perfect fit in your own abode.</Text>
  <Text Key="F4DF7933">Fruit of the Loon Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="B0E251E9">In today's world of plain Jane rugs, you want to add something to your room to give it that extra oomph. Introducing the Fringe Benefits Rug; bringing fringe back into style one home at a time.</Text>
  <Text Key="E0299BCC">Fringe Benefits Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="D920C73E">Many companies make utility mats, but only one company has the complete confidence to brand themselves after this important accessory. Buy the Utilitarian Utility Mat; every home needs one!</Text>
  <Text Key="BF94E2C1">Utilitarian Utility Mat</Text>
  <Text Key="BAA232B2">Do you need a rug? How about three? You're in luck! Here at Bigby's Rug Emporium Outlet Store we take rugs with "quirks", and stitch them together to hide the manufacturing defects. One company's trash is YOUR bargain! Save now!</Text>
  <Text Key="E84B0B4D">Eclectic Rug Trio</Text>
  <Text Key="304482DF">This carefully arranged selection of fruits, flowers, and branches really puts the "still" in "still life". As in... this is still the same scene that you painted yesterday, and it'll still be unchanged tomorrow.</Text>
  <Text Key="11F83786">Still Country Life</Text>
  <Text Key="696AE853">Three laundry baskets should be more than enough for any household. </Text>
  <Text Key="CE1A4C02">Panier à Trois by Wicker Whims</Text>
  <Text Key="AD12D580">Need quick storage for your laundry supplies? No worries, they're a mere drop in the bucket for the ample space provided by this galvanized bucket from the trusted household name of LaundryMaid!</Text>
  <Text Key="638D134F">LaundryMaid Galvanized Bucket</Text>
  <Text Key="9EF0F4D4">Say the magic word, "ABRACADABRA!" and your laundry will be as soft as a bear cub's fur. That's the Dabra Detergent guarantee!</Text>
  <Text Key="C4A9EFBB">Dabra Laundry Detergent</Text>
  <Text Key="E269A71A">Old fashioned cleaning devices such as brooms and dustpans have been phased out of Sim society. Nowadays, mops are the only tool you need for messes big and small. Hang these on your wall to reminisce about simpler times.</Text>
  <Text Key="F3AD3645">Clean Sweep</Text>
  <Text Key="AA321F7B">While these plastic herbs look as fresh as ever, a number of lawsuits and increasingly expensive settlements have caused the warning label on this decorative herb rack to undergo some changes over the years.</Text>
  <Text Key="DAD495DA">Crockery Kitchen Herb Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="253BF0D2">Ah the ironing board... a vestige of a time gone by. Now that Sims have discovered the technique of dipping their clothes in formaldehyde, there's simply no need to iron one's laundry anymore.</Text>
  <Text Key="5A9ACDED">Pressed To Impress</Text>
  <Text Key="303885E7">If you ever find yourself in a pinch with dirty laundry, you'll be glad you had the foresight to purchase this emergency laundry kit. A wash board, drying rack, and ironing board provide everything you need to make yourself presentable. Best of all, it folds up and mounts on the wall for easy storage. Can you really put a price on peace of mind? Buy today!</Text>
  <Text Key="DD88531E">Emergency Laundry Kit</Text>
  <Text Key="CFED62F8">A towel is the most important item a Sim can carry, so don't limit yourself to just one. With this particular towel rack, you'll have redundancy upon redundancy to allow you to make liberal use of your towels to your heart's content.</Text>
  <Text Key="863867F7">Redundant Towel Rack</Text>
  <Text Key="C9A2D873">From Appaloosa Plains to Twinbrook, Sims have been practicing zydeco music for generations. This musical skill was once held in high regard alongside instruments such as the piano, violin, and guitar, but it unfortunately fell out of vogue in recent times. Perhaps future generations will rediscover this lost art, but for now we pay tribute by hanging these old instruments on our walls.</Text>
  <Text Key="16FE1FA2">Zydeco Rub-Board</Text>
  <Text Key="B592CD40">MAGIC ITEM LORE ITEM NO DROP\nSlot: WALL\nSkill: GARDENING\nEffect: Nature's Blight\nFocus Effect: Silence of the Snake\nCotton R: +0 G: +0 B: +10 A: +10\nWicker R: +0 G: +0 B: +80 A: +60\nFlowers R: +0 G: +10 B: +30 A: +80\nSize: 1x1x1\nOccult: DRU\nRace: SIM\n\nNature's Blight\nEffect: Diffuses mystic protection, allowing spells to do more damage.\n\nSilence of the Snake\nEffect: Causes Sims to be less hateful of any heal or damage spell that is cast.</Text>
  <Text Key="CA21290F">Wreath of Living Brambles</Text>
  <Text Key="A47FDC14">This farmhouse furniture will make any space a little cozier. With plenty of shelving for knick-knacks and doodads, it's the perfect piece to personalize and add personality to any home!</Text>
  <Text Key="D2B85CFB">Dutch Hutch</Text>
  <Text Key="B1A2B0DE">Don't muck up your clean home! Place the Muck Down Cabinet in your mudroom to provide an organized spot to hang up your coat or slip off your shoes.</Text>
  <Text Key="297E64E1">Muck Down Cabinet</Text>
  <Text Key="C1E59EB2">Most shelving is just so... utilitarian. How droll. Spice up your shelf life with these decorative baskets from Wicker Whims.</Text>
  <Text Key="8DA18F4D">Wicker Whims Shelving</Text>
  <Text Key="50293909">LaundryMaid Essentials comes with everything the home needs for an efficient laundry room configuration.\n\nCleaning pads? Check. \nHand towels? Check. \nHangers? Check. \nStorage baskets? Check.\nAdorable plant? Check.\n\nBuy one and you're done!</Text>
  <Text Key="293E846C">LaundryMaid Essentials Shelving</Text>
  <Text Key="37374740">Step up to LaundryMaid Deluxe Shelving when you're ready to take your laundry to the next level. Three separate compartments provide ample room for storage, and a doublewide clothing rack lets you get a head start on hanging and folding.</Text>
  <Text Key="8711770F">LaundryMaid Deluxe Shelving</Text>
  <Text Key="96B1D736">This one of a kind antique sink developed a unique patina after decades of use in the back bayous of Twinbrook.</Text>
  <Text Key="0B33CD69">Bai l'Est Galvanized Sink</Text>
  <Text Key="D15FD6F8">Sick of spending top dollar for a simple sink? This one simple life hack will save your hard-earned money! It's easy... simply purchase a 2x4, cut it into three even sections, and then cut a hole in the middle for the sink's basin. You're done!</Text>
  <Text Key="475D83F7">DIY Sink</Text>
  <Text Key="70C48772">Are you dining out or eating in? Either way, this affordable dining chair from Wicker Whims is the safe bet for your bottom dollar.</Text>
  <Text Key="B636B00D">Wicker Whims Dining Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="D5E96312">Feeling lonely? Don't have that special someone to snuggle up to? Don't worry; grab a big bowl of ice cream, plop down in the Wicker Whims Living Chair, and watch Simder for the 9th time. You'll be feeling better real soon.</Text>
  <Text Key="C15B0E2D">Wicker Whims Living Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="90DF058F">Whicker Whims is putting the love back into loveseats. Cuddle up with your favorite companion on this seat built for two.</Text>
  <Text Key="5E052A56">Wicker Whims Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="A9089EA6">Designed for the ultimate in comfort, the thick padding on The Bottoman ensures you'll always have a cushy surface to sink into.</Text>
  <Text Key="9E5CADB9">The Bottoman</Text>
  <Text Key="23A22A34">There's only one word that describes the thought process that goes into thinking outside the rectangle: "courage." Introducing the latest innovation that's sweeping through coffee houses across the land. It's a coffee table... squared.</Text>
  <Text Key="24A4019B">Coffee²</Text>
  <Text Key="EC2B2F6A">Gather 'round this large dining table from Crockery Kitchen. With seating for six, every generation in the household has ample room to pull up for a bite to eat.</Text>
  <Text Key="DCD961F5">Dinner's On! by Crockery Kitchen</Text>
  <Text Key="B9B219C2">Not exactly an end table, this little unit just ends up being a bit odd. Still, it's perfect for storing odds and ends in out of the way locations.</Text>
  <Text Key="57A277BD">Odd Ends Table</Text>
  <Text Key="8B8AEEC3">Sometimes you just need a practical place to store your linens without dedicating an entire closet to it. For those times when life gives you linens... buy this handy storage unit!</Text>
  <Text Key="10C4A712">When Life Gives You Linens</Text>
  <Text Key="98A0BF2F">A trusty rag for scrubbing in the Wash Tub.</Text>
  <Text Key="12DE1276">Cloth Rag</Text>
  <Text Key="C0CD37B2">When you tell your boo about the countryside cottage you'll settle down in to grow old together, she's envisioning a home with these beautiful bay windows.</Text>
  <Text Key="94630A4D">Bae Window</Text>
  <Text Key="7B1F27B3">A Hamper with available space is required to clean this up.</Text>
  <Text Key="86435196">Take to Hamper</Text>
  <Text Key="5B78AD12">No available Clothesline.</Text>
  <Text Key="13F10A1E">These clothes are already dry.</Text>
  <Text Key="5F2EBAFC">Hang on Clothesline</Text>
  <Text Key="A5804D42">No available Dryer.</Text>
  <Text Key="3303F18C">Add to Dryer</Text>
  <Text Key="BD746611">These clothes are already clean.</Text>
  <Text Key="85633C80">No available Washing Machine.</Text>
  <Text Key="7847758A">No available Wash Tub.</Text>
  <Text Key="2EB37754">Wash in Wash Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="9B0924D8">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Clean\n• Dryness: Dry &amp; Warm</Text>
  <Text Key="0CF8F700">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Dirty\n• Dryness: Dry &amp; Warm</Text>
  <Text Key="F6D10F2E">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Filthy\n• Dryness: Dry &amp; Warm</Text>
  <Text Key="DF52E061">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Used\n• Dryness: Dry &amp; Warm</Text>
  <Text Key="0BB0144C">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Pristine\n• Dryness: Dry &amp; Warm</Text>
  <Text Key="CBF64667">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Dirty\n• Dryness: Soaked</Text>
  <Text Key="E616B776">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Clean\n• Dryness: Dry</Text>
  <Text Key="4C3BE56D">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Clean\n• Dryness: Soaked</Text>
  <Text Key="E1DC1D6A">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Filthy\n• Dryness: Soaked</Text>
  <Text Key="A1D55354">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Dirty\n• Dryness: Damp</Text>
  <Text Key="A6564B9D">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Pristine\n• Dryness: Soaked</Text>
  <Text Key="F97D453B">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Used\n• Dryness: Soaked</Text>
  <Text Key="71F409D2">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Pristine\n• Dryness: Dry</Text>
  <Text Key="C82321AD">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Dirty\n• Dryness: Dry</Text>
  <Text Key="6F09ED98">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Filthy\n• Dryness: Dry</Text>
  <Text Key="C8ED0145">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Filthy\n• Dryness: Damp</Text>
  <Text Key="6AEC80B9">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Used\n• Dryness: Damp</Text>
  <Text Key="CE4E8B53">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Pristine\n• Dryness: Damp</Text>
  <Text Key="117F0D5F">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Clean\n• Dryness: Damp</Text>
  <Text Key="0B592B8A">No available Clothesline.</Text>
  <Text Key="A05B79A7">Hang on Clothesline</Text>
  <Text Key="D9DBE2CF">Add to Dryer</Text>
  <Text Key="9CDE5887">No available Dryer.</Text>
  <Text Key="1E699FF7">{0.SimFirstName} has no laundry additives available to add.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB3C6B02">Add Flowers</Text>
  <Text Key="1C8EB5E3">Add Food</Text>
  <Text Key="BD89FA9E">Cheat Cleanliness: 4 - Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="2A60EF7F">Cheat Dryness: 2- Damp</Text>
  <Text Key="3A31D35A">Cheat Dryness: 3 - Dry</Text>
  <Text Key="883C6E77">Cheat Cleanliness: 1 - Filthy</Text>
  <Text Key="2EC63500">Cheat Scent: Fragrant</Text>
  <Text Key="9BDE7687">Cheat Cleanliness: 2 - Dirty</Text>
  <Text Key="BE1EBD99">Cheat Cleanliness: 5 - Pristine</Text>
  <Text Key="9C4CB48F">Cheat Scent: Foul</Text>
  <Text Key="0034FA64">Cheat Dryness: 1 - Soaked</Text>
  <Text Key="5325E8F2">Cheat Cleanliness: 3 - Used</Text>
  <Text Key="CB3BAA6E">Cheat Dryness: 4 - Warm</Text>
  <Text Key="75947D73">Children are too short to interact with this.</Text>
  <Text Key="78E24BE7">There are no wet clothes that need drying.</Text>
  <Text Key="ED3120BE">This clothesline is already in use.</Text>
  <Text Key="EB20B5A1">The clothesline is broken.</Text>
  <Text Key="D85C7ACB">Hang Clothes to Dry</Text>
  <Text Key="23C9AF9B">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished installing the Clothesline upgrade.</Text>
  <Text Key="178EF74D">Iron Line</Text>
  <Text Key="068CBA54">Clothesline will never break or catch on fire.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="34272227">Resume Iron Line</Text>
  <Text Key="20FCFF40">A full lint tray is a fire hazard.</Text>
  <Text Key="7013ED68">Clean Lint Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="3826135D">Dry Laundry</Text>
  <Text Key="5D76D50A">Unload &amp; Put Laundry Away</Text>
  <Text Key="0E2956BF">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished installing the Clothes Dryer upgrade.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CD7A4B5">Lint-Less</Text>
  <Text Key="A59BDA2C">Using the Dryer will not create lint. This helps laundry dry faster, and prevents the chance of starting a fire.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="D0D9D05F">Resume Lint-Less</Text>
  <Text Key="50BB03EA">The Dryer will not break down over time.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="C32D953D">Whisper Quiet</Text>
  <Text Key="FDBD8224">Decreases the noise when the Dryer is turned on.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="E797EC77">Resume Whisper Quiet</Text>
  <Text Key="CFA2DF47">The Dryer will take less time to dry laundry.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="0496A70B">Drop Clothing in Hamper</Text>
  <Text Key="9BA7149F">Add to Washing Machine</Text>
  <Text Key="9396B807">Wash in Wash Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="F383794B">Pick Up Clothing Piles</Text>
  <Text Key="97CA479B">There's nothing left to find.</Text>
  <Text Key="0BD0C522">Add to Washing Machine</Text>
  <Text Key="02204671">Put Laundry Away</Text>
  <Text Key="354558F6">Search Pockets</Text>
  <Text Key="5D1C9CCB">Add Extra Soap</Text>
  <Text Key="3153C5ED">Break Plumbing (DEBUG)</Text>
  <Text Key="D3E35B7A">Clean Out Additives</Text>
  <Text Key="A72D8D11">Load Laundry</Text>
  <Text Key="2928C58F">Repair Plumbing</Text>
  <Text Key="BB36DC30">Unload &amp; Set Laundry Down</Text>
  <Text Key="7336EAB4">Can't upgrade while laundry is inside.</Text>
  <Text Key="88604D24">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished installing the Washing Machine upgrade.</Text>
  <Text Key="0DFBE302">Laundry Additive Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="7B7E1C09">Unlocks a laundry additive tray that can be used to add pleasant or foul scents to loads of laundry.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="E1198AF6">Resume Laundry Additive Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="9B5431E1">Tungsten Drum</Text>
  <Text Key="AD11E8C0">The Washing Machine will not break down over time.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="DB0FD05B">Resume Tungsten Drum</Text>
  <Text Key="69C5FA0A">Whisper Quiet</Text>
  <Text Key="983E2221">Decreases the noise when the Washing Machine is turned on.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="611F48EE">Resume Whisper Quiet</Text>
  <Text Key="8708AB86">Presoak</Text>
  <Text Key="427DCA75">The presoak cycle will take slightly longer, but increases the chance that the Washing Machine will make your clothing pristine.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="530324CA">Resume Presoak</Text>
  <Text Key="FED47D02">Speed Cycle</Text>
  <Text Key="2526FA09">The Washing Machine will take less time to clean laundry.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="FED088F6">Resume Speed Cycle</Text>
  <Text Key="79D2E0B9">Wash Laundry</Text>
  <Text Key="984D07EF">Replace Water</Text>
  <Text Key="C277613A">You need the strength of an older Sim to properly scrub clothing.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA713F70">Wash Laundry</Text>
  <Text Key="F91C1EF4">Wash Laundry</Text>
  <Text Key="FCA1BA41">Watch Laundry</Text>
  <Text Key="B9BFA23E">Sniff Foul Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="05A7BDF7">Sniff Fresh Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="52CC3449">Insta-Repair Plumbing!</Text>
  <Text Key="9307140B">Repair Electronics</Text>
  <Text Key="00CE1D5E">What's That Spot?</Text>
  <Text Key="5E9A07D8">Pieced Together</Text>
  <Text Key="01C77FAA">Hangout to Dry</Text>
  <Text Key="C1FE5227">So Neat and So Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="AAC76434">Wickered and Honeycombed</Text>
  <Text Key="E16F2142">Cleanliness: Dirty</Text>
  <Text Key="0CFBA3F6">Dryness: Soaked</Text>
  <Text Key="3DD7C9F9">Cleanliness: Filthy</Text>
  <Text Key="0CF54FCF">Cleanliness: Used</Text>
  <Text Key="AFCE6BD1">Dryness: Dry &amp; Warm</Text>
  <Text Key="B9D80B68">Dryness: Damp</Text>
  <Text Key="DB970D80">Cleanliness: Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="CA34630C">Dryness: Dry</Text>
  <Text Key="89079E41">Cleanliness: Pristine</Text>
  <Text Key="EDADC818">Scent: Foul</Text>
  <Text Key="39F09EC6">Scent: Fragrant</Text>
  <Text Key="E77DFB93">For the city living, latte sipping, avocado toast munching, environmentally conscious millennial comes this particularly helpful stacked washer / dryer combo unit from Urbanite Appliances. Sure, you could purchase each machine individually and stack them yourself, but who has the time when you've got a planet to save (and a protest to attend). Not only will this stacked unit save space in your microapartment, you'll be pleased to know that it's a sustainable water resource; the moisture literally evaporates in the dryer and drains back into the washer for your next load. While you're out there busy being a leader of tomorrow, you can rest assured your laundry is in good hands here.\n\n*Owning these objects will cause your Sims' clothes to become dirty over time. Dirty laundry can be collected from a Hamper, or from clothes piles on the floor, and cleaned inside the Washing Machine. Wet laundry can be dried inside the Dryer.</Text>
  <Text Key="CC5A3F42">Urbanite Appliances Stacked Washer / Dryer Unit</Text>
  <Text Key="6C70206C">Set Laundry State</Text>
  <Text Key="F29AA00C">Do Laundry</Text>
  <Text Key="F150399D">Add Laundry Additive</Text>
  <Text Key="B664A870">Do Laundry</Text>
  <Text Key="30087B48">Unload &amp; Move Laundry To</Text>
  <Text Key="A44CC603">Upgrade a Dryer</Text>
  <Text Key="E842020D">Click on a Dryer and select an Upgrade to apply.</Text>
  <Text Key="73C62A25">Upgrade a Washing Machine</Text>
  <Text Key="64AE468F">Click on a Washing Machine and select an Upgrade to apply.</Text>
  <Text Key="DFD1DF1C">Buy a Dryer</Text>
  <Text Key="06FC6CBC">Purchase a Dryer for laundry from Build Mode.</Text>
  <Text Key="C29C464C">Buy a Washing Machine</Text>
  <Text Key="2D95CA6C">Purchase a Washing Machine from Build Mode.</Text>
  <Text Key="F7B8C124">Buy a Wash Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="562C9734">Purchase a Wash Tub from Build Mode.</Text>
  <Text Key="B35591DD">Hang Laundry on the Clothesline</Text>
  <Text Key="5A4690F7">Click on wet laundry that's on the ground or in a Washing Machine and select Hang on Clothesline.</Text>
  <Text Key="CB459BF6">Pick Up Clothing Piles</Text>
  <Text Key="FF9117C6">Select Pick Up Clothing Piles on the Hamper to clean up any clothes left laying around on the floor.</Text>
  <Text Key="2C084B0C">Take Clothing Pile to Hamper</Text>
  <Text Key="25C5052C">Click on a Clothing Pile on the floor and select Take to Hamper.</Text>
  <Text Key="7133CCD3">Dry Laundry in the Dryer</Text>
  <Text Key="B24C8CDD">Click on a washing machine when finished, select Unload &amp; Move Laundry To, and then Add to Dryer. You can also click on a wet pile of laundry, select Do Laundry, and then Add to Dryer.</Text>
  <Text Key="273B7127">Take Clothing to Hamper</Text>
  <Text Key="131D7209">Click on a pile of clothing on the ground and select Take to Hamper.</Text>
  <Text Key="9972BA9C">Wash Laundry in the Washing Machine</Text>
  <Text Key="17973B3C">Click on a pile of dirty laundry on the floor or click on a hamper, select Do Laundry, and then select Wash Laundry.</Text>
  <Text Key="D4C51019">Wash Laundry in a Wash Tub</Text>
  <Text Key="39E2C84B">Click on dirty laundry and select Wash in Wash Tub.</Text>
  <Text Key="7FBC3416">This load of laundry is...\n• Cleanliness: Used\n• Dryness: Dry</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>