<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="71EB9780">Are you running out of space? Do you need to extend your Sleeqframe Cabinet system? We guarantee that this cabinet piece is exactly what you need.</Text>
  <Text Key="E1D7B94F">Sleeqframe Cabinet (Left)</Text>
  <Text Key="AB215FDF">Not sure where to start with your first ever Sleeqframe Cabinet system? Maybe this piece is the &lt;i&gt;right&lt;/i&gt; one.</Text>
  <Text Key="7D4E3E86">Sleeqframe Cabinet (Right)</Text>
  <Text Key="397DCC61">We at Sleeqframe Co. know the drill. You don't always need a giant bookshelf to display your questionable book selection. Be as discreet or as loud as you want to be with our compact Sleeqframe Cabinet.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA195F14">Sleeqframe Cabinet (Center)</Text>
  <Text Key="D55F03EC">Some of these books are written in a language that is so hard to comprehend. So what?! You can &lt;i&gt;feel&lt;/i&gt; the knowledge of the world enter your brain just by reading those ridiculously long titles alone.</Text>
  <Text Key="02322A23">Best of Nonfiction</Text>
  <Text Key="F34A120A">Looking for a simple way to brighten up your home? This bold pendant light by Myshuno Studios not only provides a stable source of light, but does it in a stylish way.</Text>
  <Text Key="1DF87715">Pendant Light by Myshuno Studios (Short)</Text>
  <Text Key="3945EC5F">Looking for a simple way to brighten up your home? This bold pendant light by Myshuno Studios not only provides a stable source of light, but does it in a stylish way. Now available for taller ceiling heights!</Text>
  <Text Key="48653C06">Pendant Light by Myshuno Studios (Medium)</Text>
  <Text Key="AF285D44">Looking for a simple way to brighten up your home? This bold pendant light by Myshuno Studios not only provides a stable source of light, but does it in a stylish way. Now available for extra tall ceiling heights!</Text>
  <Text Key="84846F0B">Pendant Light by Myshuno Studios (Tall)</Text>
  <Text Key="BAC50EE0">When you feel like something is missing from your interior, we at Myshuno Studios know the answer. It's The Signature.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D9F832F">The Signature by Myshuno Studios</Text>
  <Text Key="5532154C">A perfectly balanced triplet of candles that adds harmony to any living space.</Text>
  <Text Key="D9F76303">Cozy Candles</Text>
  <Text Key="30E45510">A wall-mounted neon sign for those who want to make a bold statement. Literally.</Text>
  <Text Key="5DF66A3F">Nuff Said Neon Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="DF83576D">Do you like visual clutter? We &lt;i&gt;love it&lt;/i&gt;, so we decided to express it in our artwork. What does it mean? We don't know. You don't know! Who knows? Nobody!</Text>
  <Text Key="12A65638">Mixed Signals Poster</Text>
  <Text Key="C72D9B32">Some might call this selection of colors and patterns a "visual cacophony", and to them we say, "And what about it?" Express yourself!</Text>
  <Text Key="00E7DCCD">Dream Pop Frames</Text>
  <Text Key="4CAB275A">Simple in presentation, yet bold in color; this vase duo adds a sweet touch of gentle beauty to any room.</Text>
  <Text Key="83671D85">Succint Vase Duo</Text>
  <Text Key="FB091AEF">The rumors are true—after a series of meticulous calculations, we came to the conclusion that these squares pass the vibe check. We arranged them in a neat, symmetrical pattern that will surely satisfy the most demanding geometry nerds.</Text>
  <Text Key="18938D36">Vibe Checked Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="B0151C4E">Someone carefully arranged this fruit on a set of color-matched plates. It's almost impossible to resist the urge to bite into one of these juicy apples... But wait! Think about the aesthetics!</Text>
  <Text Key="30C08371">Charli's Apples</Text>
  <Text Key="8730694E">This light switch proves that even the smallest things in life can be a source of delight.</Text>
  <Text Key="22A6DA71">The Delightful Light Switch</Text>
  <Text Key="E5442FDC">Long ago, this fireplace emitted constant heat. Now, it emits pure joy and unapologetically grabs everyone's attention the moment anyone enters the room. Oh, and it displays your favorite trinkets!</Text>
  <Text Key="538DBBB3">Ex-Fireplace</Text>
  <Text Key="1A098C91">Sleeqframe Co. guarantees supreme quality and full satisfaction with every piece we manufacture. Nothing beats a reliable wall shelf that does exactly what it's supposed to do.</Text>
  <Text Key="D76CC0E4">Sleeqframe Wall Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="71E8FAE4">This chair's paint job might not be the smoothest, but don't let this fact distract you from the joy of giving your basement antiques a second chance.</Text>
  <Text Key="5335AC2B">Grandma's Painted Dining Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="E9E4BC94">No seating set is complete without a matching pouf. This is it, the missing Comfy Groove piece!</Text>
  <Text Key="9138167B">Comfy Groove Pouf</Text>
  <Text Key="552E8CF1">The shape of this living chair provides comfort and support when you need it the most.</Text>
  <Text Key="20C093C4">Comfy Groove Living Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="183F8202">Don't reject modernity—simply embrace it with this Comfy Groove loveseat! The extra soft corduroy fabric ensures both comfort and style—the two things that we all expect our loveseats to provide.</Text>
  <Text Key="BF00F5FD">Comfy Groove Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="4016A47D">Sure, this sofa is great on its own, but we just couldn't resist throwing a few funky cushions in the mix. Stay comfortable, stay cute.</Text>
  <Text Key="74BFC8E8">Comfy Groove Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="B491D8AD">This vintage radio is a cherished heirloom. Despite being well-loved throughout its lifetime, it barely has any visible scratches.</Text>
  <Text Key="3F565578">Good Chunes Vintage Radio</Text>
  <Text Key="1508042B">The timeless design of this coffee table will complement every interior. Could you ever go wrong with a natural wood look? Absolutely not.</Text>
  <Text Key="6FE34C2A">AINA Coffee Table</Text>
  <Text Key="81F09212">Gather your friends and family by this spacious dining table. We are &lt;i&gt;cutting corners&lt;/i&gt; and letting you take care of the important stuff—the food, the laughs, and the chats.</Text>
  <Text Key="F91B6B2D">AINA Dining Table</Text>
  <Text Key="14DD4DDA">We don't recommend standing on this step stool... It makes a nice end table though.</Text>
  <Text Key="901FC905">Grandma's Painted Step Stool</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>