<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="F86C82D9">Compressed Earth Flooring</Text>
  <Text Key="C2687E77">This minimalist wooden awning, inspired by the beauty of the desert landscape, provides shelter from the elements while still allowing natural breezes to flow through.</Text>
  <Text Key="5E395FCE">Deserted Awning</Text>
  <Text Key="DD405369">The Sand Bar is perfect for serving drinks or snacks while entertaining guests at your next get-together. This unique design will add an elegant touch to any setting.</Text>
  <Text Key="2858E84C">The Sand Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="8895D986">This ceiling fan has a minimalist design that makes it perfect for any room. The wooden blades are strong enough to cause a sandstorm but can also give a gentle breeze.</Text>
  <Text Key="EB6D2619">Sandstorm Ceiling Fan</Text>
  <Text Key="4F51C633">Are these curtains actually short? Are they average? What does average even mean anyway? In comparison to what? Taller curtains?</Text>
  <Text Key="66792B62">Decidedly Neutral Short Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="06EC2AD6">In a world filled with bright and boldly patterned curtains, the truly audacious choice is to go neutral.</Text>
  <Text Key="5D7E0289">Decidedly Neutral Tall Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="8DA34251">Giant rooms require giant curtains. There's nothing neutral about that opinion, but these gorgeous textiles have plenty of neutral beauty.</Text>
  <Text Key="89972CA4">Decidedly Neutral Giant Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="F3BC793D">Do you have a giant window problem? This curtain mount pairs with any size of Decidedly Neutral Curtain to cover any sized window and keep the sun out.</Text>
  <Text Key="C7E131A8">Decidedly Neutral Curtain Mount</Text>
  <Text Key="24FCB53F">We build homes to keep the elements out, but the most luxurious homes let the beauty of nature in. Add some luxury to your home and enjoy the wonders of indoor-outdoor living with this transformative archway.</Text>
  <Text Key="A343F166">Transformative Open Space Arch</Text>
  <Text Key="06E3C61E">Earth and Fire. Hark back to the essential elements invoking the security and warmth of the hearth and home with a fireplace made from the abundant natural resources in Oasis Springs.</Text>
  <Text Key="84A08121">Earthen Fireplace</Text>
  <Text Key="4204A86F">Meet SunBlaze, GrillMania's modern take on the classic propane grill that combines sleek design with high performance. </Text>
  <Text Key="16CDBDB6">SunBlaze by GrillMania</Text>
  <Text Key="61C53015">The artist who created this lamp had a vision of three suns competing for dominance in the sky after getting lost one day in Oasis Springs. The fantastic image disappeared upon rehydration, but this wicker light set remains a reminder of the sight.</Text>
  <Text Key="99FE6F30">Three Suns in Wicker</Text>
  <Text Key="5AA85584">The artist who created this lamp had a vision of three suns competing for dominance in the sky after getting lost one day in Oasis Springs. The fantastic image disappeared upon rehydration, but this wicker light set remains a reminder of the sight.</Text>
  <Text Key="7479A54B">Three Suns in Wicker from Orbit</Text>
  <Text Key="FA34079F">The artist who created this lamp had a vision of three suns competing for dominance in the sky after getting lost one day in Oasis Springs. The fantastic image disappeared upon rehydration, but this wicker light set remains a reminder of the sight.</Text>
  <Text Key="386ADF46">Three Suns in Wicker from Space</Text>
  <Text Key="712E8DAE">The desert can be a dark place at night, but sometimes all we need is a tiny spot of light to see us through until sunrise.</Text>
  <Text Key="DFF11B51">Tiny Spot of Light</Text>
  <Text Key="8B39E094">This shelf contains sand from around Oasis Springs, bringing the beauty of the majestic desert into any home.</Text>
  <Text Key="DE26427B">Of the Earth Floor Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="0C0EC51B">The Nested Bliss Bar Stool brings a sense of elegance and sophistication to your bar or kitchen space. The sleek design will complement any decor, while its contoured seat offers a plush seating experience.</Text>
  <Text Key="159CFFFA">Nested Bliss Bar Stool</Text>
  <Text Key="2B0D6BA6">This chair has a simple shape and clean lines, which allows it to be placed anywhere, whether in the living room or bedroom.</Text>
  <Text Key="C1C784B9">Simply Luxe Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="D79D9797">This lounge chair was built for relaxation. Designed with a low profile, it has a sleek, modern design that will blend into any space. Its metal frame provides support, while its cushioned seat provides maximum comfort.</Text>
  <Text Key="3A86126E">The Minimalist's Lounge Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="3A8A1F42">Do you ever look at a bug on a rock and think, "Hmm, I wonder how comfortable that is?" Well, look no further than the Soft as Stone Loveseat. While this loveseat is made of stone, the thick cushioning system provides maximum comfort and support.</Text>
  <Text Key="1958903D">Soft as Stone Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="809A80F7">Lush. Soft. Marshmallow-y. Those were the keywords that inspired the designer of this sofa. Sitting on it should feel like floating away on a fluffy, sugary cloud.</Text>
  <Text Key="29F2DF4E">Prime Luxe Plush Sofa</Text>
  <Text Key="CBC341E2">This beautifully simple end table has been handcrafted using natural stones found in Oasis Springs. The unique design creates an inviting space where you can place your favorite items. This piece will add an element of serenity to any room.</Text>
  <Text Key="4AED475D">Calming Stone End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="95487501">This unique wooden end table is made from natural wood and has an elegant minimalist design. The table top is flat and comes with a low-profile storage compartment underneath. </Text>
  <Text Key="401BB434">Balanced Wood End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="EFE0D18B">The Desert's End Table is a minimalist stone end table made from natural sandstone. The simple design makes it perfect as an accent piece or centerpiece.</Text>
  <Text Key="2C20270A">Desert's End Table</Text>
  <Text Key="509FC89F">Made of 100% locally sourced Oasis Springs reclaimed wood, this privacy window lets in the light of the desert sun, while keeping the extreme heat out.</Text>
  <Text Key="A2B05246">Reclaimed Style Privacy Window</Text>
  <Text Key="1FA0A7E1">Made of 100% locally sourced Oasis Springs reclaimed wood, this privacy window lets in the light of the desert sun, while keeping the extreme heat out.</Text>
  <Text Key="0AEC1994">Reclaimed Style More Privacy Window</Text>
  <Text Key="127C3245">Desert Oasis</Text>
  <Text Key="49B1E76C">Sand Mixed Concrete Wall</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>