<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="1B722BA8">(From the Ball Pit)</Text>
  <Text Key="490E1143">(From Playing Pretend)</Text>
  <Text Key="746D6F42">(From Playing Make Believe)</Text>
  <Text Key="0D8595A9">(From Playing Make Believe)</Text>
  <Text Key="179002E1">(From a Toddler Slide)</Text>
  <Text Key="F30E8E73">(From the Toddler Tunnels)</Text>
  <Text Key="8FF24A50">Here fishy fishy fishy...</Text>
  <Text Key="D1F83B7F">Underwater Adventure</Text>
  <Text Key="A017A267">The stars at night, are big and bright!</Text>
  <Text Key="58AA009E">Spaceport Captain</Text>
  <Text Key="ADA70816">The world through the eyes of a toddler is shining, shimmering splendor!</Text>
  <Text Key="355686C9">A Whole New World</Text>
  <Text Key="5553A062">Wheeeee! Sliding down super fast!</Text>
  <Text Key="227B1ADD">Fun Slide!</Text>
  <Text Key="7BE000C4">Too fast, TOO FAST! That slide is scary!</Text>
  <Text Key="89EB018B">Scary Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="ED1BA19A">Get out! It's Mine! Mine, Mine.... MINE!</Text>
  <Text Key="0A751DC5">No, My Tunnel!</Text>
  <Text Key="BD46038C">The tunnel, go through the tunnel!</Text>
  <Text Key="FB015A43">Tunnel Fun</Text>
  <Text Key="ADBCAC2F">Twisty tubes!</Text>
  <Text Key="4FA44976">Tunnel Adventure</Text>
  <Text Key="DB82BCF7">Owie! Waaaahhh!!</Text>
  <Text Key="107ED34E">Scraped Knee</Text>
  <Text Key="ECE65280">A fun explosion of colorful balls!</Text>
  <Text Key="F0C4FA4F">Kaboom!</Text>
  <Text Key="58D2C394">Proper For Play</Text>
  <Text Key="9E010F93">Frippery Frock</Text>
  <Text Key="6760DF3D">Ruffle Puff</Text>
  <Text Key="3FC01CE0">Print Perfect</Text>
  <Text Key="5852D0C2">Pixie Princess</Text>
  <Text Key="8873B606">Sunday Best</Text>
  <Text Key="952366DB">Fun With Ribbons</Text>
  <Text Key="4CB1EA88">Mix Match Chic</Text>
  <Text Key="4B433C91">Effortless In The Sun</Text>
  <Text Key="1A9793B1">Superhero In Training</Text>
  <Text Key="6B78C3FA">Overall Fun</Text>
  <Text Key="7FDFFF7D">Animals In The Wild</Text>
  <Text Key="148C1BBB">Just about any old fence can keep a toddler out, but when you want to keep a toddler safely in, you need Trapped Tots Fencing. Parents can rest easy, knowing their tyke won't be wandering out of sight from their watchful eyes.</Text>
  <Text Key="4FD5E01A">Trapped Tots Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="6807B3BC">Parents, don't do the heavy lifting for your next family picnic. Pack a meal into the Cool Kids Cooler, and watch your little ones fight over the privilege of dragging the food along!</Text>
  <Text Key="CCA3EF13">Cool Kids Cooler</Text>
  <Text Key="B0F6710B">For the rough and tumble outdoors lovin' youngin' in your life comes the Tiny Tot Treehouse. Nymphs, dryads, fairies, and sprites come out and play to your kid's delight!</Text>
  <Text Key="0B07ED8A">Tiny Tot Treehouse</Text>
  <Text Key="B2C2B715">Trapped Tots Fencing, keeping your tykes safe. The safety latch has an easy to remember unlocking mechanism to allow adults easy traversal. Just pull up twice, push down twice, then left, right, left, right, push in, pull out... and you're through!</Text>
  <Text Key="0DA25430">Trapped Tots Gate</Text>
  <Text Key="9275CE6B">A high-tech heat ray in the hood of the Quadpod ensures an even cook every single time. That's not to say that you won't burn your hot dogs... just rest assured that the problem lies with you.</Text>
  <Text Key="5BFADD6A">Quadpod Grill</Text>
  <Text Key="3218105E">If you love your toddler, you'll make room for a Bam BAM BamCo Ball Pit in your home... at least that's what the marketing department at BamCo would argue. Filled to the brim with colorful balls, toddlers will dive right in and have a blast!</Text>
  <Text Key="D4F96B61">Bam BAM BamCo Toddler Ball Pit</Text>
  <Text Key="55213299">Hot metal playground slides are a thing of the past... introducing the BamCo Safety Slide, a plastic slide for 21st century sensibilities. Tested to last in both indoor and outdoor usage, it'll quickly become a favorite of your little tyke! Not only is it fun to use, the climber will help teach valuable movement skills. You'll marvel at how swiftly they start scampering up the side to slide!</Text>
  <Text Key="2FB9251C">BamCo's Toddler Safety Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="76C33BF5">While traditionally sold to commercial venues, the fine folks at BamCo recognized that their All-Inclusive Jungle Gym spoke to a growing market niche - helicopter parents. Instead of going to the playground, why not bring the playground to you? With BamCo's Jungle Gym monopolizing your backyard, your toddler will never leave your sights.</Text>
  <Text Key="F6AFEF90">BamCo's All-Inclusive Toddler Jungle Gym</Text>
  <Text Key="BBFB8BAF">What's the best way to occupy an inquisitive toddler's time? Send them into BamCo's Twisty Tunnels - a series of tubes that toddlers will crawl through and explore for hours on end. While this impressive structure is more commonly found in restaurants and parks, there's no quicker way to show off just how much you love your little tot! At the end of the day, isn't one-upping other neighborhood parents what child rearing is all about?</Text>
  <Text Key="9F43CFF6">BamCo's Twisty Toddler Tunnels</Text>
  <Text Key="F5FDF9D1">A string of outdoor lights, appropriate for any fun occasion that you don't want to cut short when the sun goes down.\n\nTip: Place multiple Lightropes in a row, then use the "Lightrope Pole" to hold up the other end of the string.</Text>
  <Text Key="9892BB24">High-Wire Lightrope</Text>
  <Text Key="FEF4E750">Troublesome toddlers throwing tantrums? Place them on The Brat Mat to work out their aggression! This rubber surface comes in a number of fun patterns to grab a tot's attention and jump start their imagination. It's the perfect surface to inspire play!</Text>
  <Text Key="E153827F">The Brat Mat</Text>
  <Text Key="FD9B0609">The Packanack Blanket inspires thoughts of the simple pleasures in life. Spread them outdoors to set the scene for a tasty picnic, or lay back and gaze up at the clouds. Rest assured that its durable woven material is resistant to the toughest stains and splatters.</Text>
  <Text Key="29605B6C">Packanack Blanket</Text>
  <Text Key="89694E2B">Don't pop these balloons too soon, or they'll turn from Party Poppers to party poopers.</Text>
  <Text Key="6FD10A2A">Party Poppers</Text>
  <Text Key="43D071C5">Some say the lightrope pole is used by nimble Sims to help balance themselves when navigating a tightrope. Those people are wrong.\n\nIt's a pole. It holds up the other end of the "High-Wire Lightrope" string lights. That's it.</Text>
  <Text Key="9B1F3AC0">Lightrope Pole</Text>
  <Text Key="EE3EA6EA">Vita means life - and using these sail shades to protect your skin from harsh UV rays is a sure fire way to stay looking younger, longer.</Text>
  <Text Key="56233075">Vita Sail Shades</Text>
  <Text Key="6AE39A00">Whatcha gonna do with all these stumps... all these stumps you saved from the dump.  My stump, my stump, my stump, my lovely little stumps.</Text>
  <Text Key="B70338CF">My Stumps - Part One</Text>
  <Text Key="AEC649CD">Whatcha gonna do with all these stumps... all these stumps you saved from the dump.  My stump, my stump, my stump, my lovely little stumps.</Text>
  <Text Key="0DBB9218">My Stumps - Part Three</Text>
  <Text Key="DA02E722">Whatcha gonna do with all these stumps... all these stumps you saved from the dump.  My stump, my stump, my stump, my lovely little stumps.</Text>
  <Text Key="30117A9D">My Stumps - Part Two</Text>
  <Text Key="FD1B704F">Whatcha gonna do with all these stumps... all these stumps you saved from the dump.  My stump, my stump, my stump, my lovely little stumps.</Text>
  <Text Key="CAA89116">My Stumps - Part Four</Text>
  <Text Key="9B99C7BC">You're ready to party at a moment's notice... and now, so is your food! Disposable plates, cups, silverware, and napkins are at your disposal for any occasion. Party on!</Text>
  <Text Key="ECD5EB13">Party Pak</Text>
  <Text Key="494B58E1">Straight from the back lot in Bridgeport comes surplus director's chairs. Used in the production of films such as "Diamonds Are For Sims", "Simder", "Sims of the Dead", and many more!</Text>
  <Text Key="D7DB5C94">D-lister's Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="C811BD1B">Take a load off on the Plump Pillow Pad! A dense memory foam packing will provide the support you need to comfortably relax.\n\n...just be sure to give it a thorough shake first to remove that pesky purple packing powder,</Text>
  <Text Key="81C467FA">Plump Pillow Pad</Text>
  <Text Key="8AFE6CB2">The government says that HDPE stands for high-density polyethylene, and we're required to inform you that this table is 100% built from it. We prefer to think of HDPE as Hungry Diners Picnic Extravaganza - the perfect surface for an outdoor feast!</Text>
  <Text Key="D056994D">HDPE Picnic Table</Text>
  <Text Key="8C345701">Eight renowned artists collaborated on designs for this joyous toybox! You can feel good knowing that no matter which one you choose, all proceeds are being donated directly to the Toys For Tykes charity.</Text>
  <Text Key="4BF5BA34">Toys For Tykes Toybox</Text>
  <Text Key="EC594C42">The chipmunk says, "chirp chirp chirp".</Text>
  <Text Key="AB54873D">Chipmunk Doll</Text>
  <Text Key="32A06E04">Part of Mr. Chip, not to worry, Mr. Chip is safe and sound.</Text>
  <Text Key="D15D86CB">Mr. Chip</Text>
  <Text Key="F81B364C">Help {2.SimFirstName} Climb</Text>
  <Text Key="8AECA883">Help {1.SimFirstName} Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="BA972DFA">Help Toddler Climb</Text>
  <Text Key="4D145D61">Play In Ball Pit</Text>
  <Text Key="4EA62154">Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="0EE6514E">Climb</Text>
  <Text Key="2367A83A">Wait</Text>
  <Text Key="7FEDA4A8">Crawl Through</Text>
  <Text Key="2910226A">Play as Monster With {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="309BDEB5">Play Pretend</Text>
  <Text Key="217096D5">Make Believe Pirate Shipwreck</Text>
  <Text Key="11604BE2">Make Believe Spaceport</Text>
  <Text Key="B5C19539">Must know a toddler with level 2 Imagination Skill.</Text>
  <Text Key="47E00F80">Play Pirates With</Text>
  <Text Key="93EB3FAD">Play Spaceport With</Text>
  <Text Key="AD89328D">Party In The Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="EF74CF7D">Family Picnic Spot</Text>
  <Text Key="119140C8">Playpen Of Tiny Terrors</Text>
  <Text Key="F47CDBFB">Make Believe</Text>
  <Text Key="9FDC1870">Everyone seems to have had a decent time at the play date... There's one easy way to take your next play date to the next level though. Adorable animal plates. That's right, and you'll find that a set of them have been placed in your household inventory for free! The cute little lion face printed on them is sure to be a hit the next time the tots get together.</Text>
  <Text Key="7F2DD048">\nBronze Level rewards the household with a set of cute lion plates.</Text>
  <Text Key="62BEF7C2">Word of this legendary play date has started to spread... In fact, the fine folks in the marketing department at BamCo (esteemed maker of toddler toys) has reached out with a special "influencer" opportunity! They've provided their All-Inclusive Jungle Gym set, completely free of charge! You'll find that it's already been delivered to your household's inventory. All they ask is a small, tiny, little favor... Won't you please place it in your front yard and invite all the neighbor's tots over to play, to help spread the good BamCo name?</Text>
  <Text Key="5F9EDB4E">\nGold Level rewards the household with an all inclusive Toddler Jungle Gym.</Text>
  <Text Key="EE4CC603">The play date was a great success! The little tots were bouncing all over as they played, frolicked, and strengthened friendships that will last for years to come. You know what really ramps up a toddler's excitement though? Balloons! Lots and lots of balloons! You'll find a whole cluster of them in your household's inventory... be sure to decorate with them for the next play date!</Text>
  <Text Key="08157967">\nSilver Level rewards the household with a colorful cluster of balloons.</Text>
  <Text Key="8FC50CC8">Toddler Play Date</Text>
  <Text Key="8BD302B4">Host a big party for tiny tots! Invite all the toddlers your little one knows for fun, play, and general merriment. While the tykes run to and fro, grill up some food and exchange parenting tips with fellow caregivers.</Text>
  <Text Key="76AD5F04">Read a Book to a Toddler</Text>
  <Text Key="FE748096">Bake Chocolate Chip Cookies</Text>
  <Text Key="11A725BB">Cook Mac and Cheese</Text>
  <Text Key="1663D8C0">Have a Toddler Climb up the Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="93623A35">Help a Toddler Climb</Text>
  <Text Key="59A0266C">Have a Toddler go Sliding</Text>
  <Text Key="6270FC13">Help a Toddler Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="A2F51523">Play With a Toddler</Text>
  <Text Key="734A11F8">Talk to a Toddler</Text>
  <Text Key="F6B69507">Help a Toddler Climb</Text>
  <Text Key="30D1F6E9">Click on a Slide and select Help Toddler Climb</Text>
  <Text Key="EFF5574D">Help a Toddler Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="ECE906E7">Click on a Slide while a toddler is sitting on top and select Help Slide.</Text>
  <Text Key="429494F6">Buy a Toddler Jungle Gym</Text>
  <Text Key="E1CF0AC6">Purchase the Toddler Jungle Gym in Build Mode.</Text>
  <Text Key="98E06C98">Buy a Toddler Slide</Text>
  <Text Key="058DBAF0">Purchase a Toddler Slide in Build Mode.</Text>
  <Text Key="3ADA80AF">Buy a Toddler Tunnel</Text>
  <Text Key="119F91A1">Purchase the Toddler Tunnels in Build Mode.</Text>
  <Text Key="F219A65E">Buy a Ball Pit</Text>
  <Text Key="025A2C1E">Go to Build Mode and purchase a Toddler Ball Pit.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA0A8860">Guest Caregiver</Text>
  <Text Key="DEF36DE2">Your toddler has been invited to a play date. Get ready for lots of fun, love, and chaos!</Text>
  <Text Key="81ED9DE2">Guest Toddler</Text>
  <Text Key="08447430">You've been invited to a play date. Get ready for lots of fun, love, and chaos!</Text>
  <Text Key="29983122">Host Caregiver</Text>
  <Text Key="D5246870">It's your play date... Go forth and have fun!</Text>
  <Text Key="5636B620">Host Toddler</Text>
  <Text Key="F7023FA2">Be a fun host to the toddlers and their caregivers that are attending the play date.</Text>
  <Text Key="33B6B621">Must be a toddler aged household member.</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>